Chapter 191

Attack Land (4)

◆

Meanwhile.

When Sinclaire, the head of the Hot Class, is carried out on a stretcher with a dismal score, the mood of the entire class is somber.

The usually cheerful Sinclaire had become something of an idol to the first-year students.

But not everyone was saddened by Sinclaire’s tragedy.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, that commoner bitch, finally got her nose flattened.”

“She doesn’t know what she’s talking about, and she’s just gotten the head of the Hot Class.”

“Exactly. The head of the Hot Clas should be from our noble family.”

“She’ll get extra points for being pretty and flattering the professors, anyway.”

Some of the group sneers darkly.

“Now it’s time for someone who’s truly worthy of the title: our Granola.”

It was Granola who was the leader of this group, composed entirely of the scions of the Empire’s most prestigious families.

But why does he have such an expression on his face?

He was completely unresponsive to the words of his subordinates and friends.

“….”

His gaze is fixed on Sinclaire in the distance.

She is in pain as she is carried out on a stretcher.

Sinclaire had always been a hardworking and determined student at school.

Despite her commoner origins, she was never intimidated by the nobles and achieved more than anyone else in her studies.

But Sinclaire is in pain. She even shows tears that have never been seen before.

Grrrr!

Granola’s teeth gritted.

“Be quiet.”

The boys and girls of the noble faction fell silent at her words.

Granola spoke in a low, bass voice.

“It was not a fair fight.”

“Huh?”

“Maybe the other professors will make up for her marks, whether it’s extra credit or attitude points.”

At that, the noble boys and girls nodded.

“It’s Granola after all.”

“He’s so strong, he deserves to be the leader of the Noble Faction.”

“You can’t let your guard down yet, can you, A battle for head position?”

“Let’s show this lowly commoner girl a lesson!”

But Granola still looks bitter.

Then. Granola’s expression softened slightly.

“…Professor Sadi. I thought I told you to do it in moderation?”

It was Professor Banshee Morgue.

He spoke as if he could take no more.

“There is a limit to what I can do to save the face of a Principal, and I cannot tolerate your behavior any longer.”

“Huh? What are you going to do?”

Professor Sadi puffed out his chest, showing his guts.

The other professors behind Professor Banshee began to walk out and protest.

“Professor Sadi, don’t you think this is too much? Some of the students you’ve hurt are under my guidance!”

“Prof. Sadi. This isn’t right, isn’t it? You’ve been turning a blind eye to the Magic Wall B-key incident the other day, and you’ve been turning a blind eye to people using their annual or semi-annual leave on the same day without reporting it, and leaving the workplace without authorization.”

“Are you a psychopath? Are you crazy? What are you thinking, bullying students? What kind of grading system do you have? Do you think other professors are so weak that they give students grades?”

However, Professor Sadi was not deterred in the slightest, and even bared his sharp teeth and snarled.

“These mongrels, where are they really… barking about building a pack? Barking.”

The professors’ faces lit up in shock and embarrassment.

A few of them leapt to their feet, but Professor Banshee stopped them.

“There are many eyes watching.”

Suddenly, the professors realize that there are a lot of students around.

Professor Sadi’s demeanor was brash and arrogant.

“If only … weren’t a descendant of the Marquis de Sade.”

It’s been a long time since Professor Banshee, whose facial expression never changes, so much so that he is nicknamed a wax doll by his students, folds his eyebrows like cooking foil.

“Anyway. This is really your last chance, Sadi.”

“Ew-don’t call me by my first name, old man. If you’re going to call me by my full name, call me by my title.”

“I’m not kidding, Professor Donatien Alphonse Fran?ois Sadi de Sade. If you show any more harshness than necessary with your students, I will personally exclude you from the midterms. And I will severely discipline you for stealing the principal’s seal.”

Professor Banshee’s tone was so vicious that it was almost murderous.

Professor Sadi, on the other hand, only smiled meaningfully and did not return the Banshee’s anger.

By this time, the next examinee had arrived.

It was Pigi from Class B, Cold Warriors.

Pigi was holding the sword with trembling hands.

Professor Sadi immediately snorted.

“You don’t even know how to grip a sword. Are you a scumbag?”

Professor Sadi is verbally abusive when it comes to violence.

But Pigi trembles and doesn’t back down.

‘I’m not a coward, and I’m supposed to be Vikir’s proud friend, and I can’t back down from that!’

Pigi was smart, and he knew what was coming.

If even the great Sancho or Sinclaire had fallen to the ground, how could he be sure he was okay?

But even so, Pigi didn’t back down.

Nor did he declare a quit, as Dolores had advised Sinclaire to do.

‘This trial is my chance to break through my glazed shell and bring out the strong courage inside me….’

Pfft!

But Pigi’s thoughts were cut off mid-sentence.

[Hogwash].

Professor Sadi’s avatar, Mudgolem, suddenly approached and kicked Pigi’s body.

Quack, quack, quack!

Pigi bounced three times on the stone floor.

In no time, Pigi is covered in blood.

Suddenly, there are groans of pity from the crowd.

Even those who usually despised Pigi for her weakness were sympathizing with Pigi as the victim of Professor Sadi.

And his friends, Tudor and Sancho, were becoming even more furious.

“Damn it! I want out! I want revenge!”

“I’ve already been beaten down once. But to have a friend get screwed like that is really….”

Neither Tudor nor Sancho could do anything but clench their fists and turn red in the face.

Just then.

[Okay, next examinee up… Huh?]

Professor Sadi starts to turn her head, but stops.

Pigi. He’s staggering out of his seat.

“…I’m not going to lose like this.”

Pigi is covered in blood. But he still hadn’t let go of the sword.

“I got in trouble with the other kids at the defense test, and I don’t want to do that again.”

With that, Pigi thrust his sword forward with a cheer.

Professor Sadi laughed in disbelief.

[Hohohoho. I’ll have to make him a pork skewer].

The mud golem moved. The mud golem, wearing pointy kill heels like Professor Sadi’s, charged toward Pigi.

Tudor and Sancho gasped.

“Pigi! You should just lie down! You can’t get into a close combat with that crazy professor!”

“There’s a difference between courage and bravery, Pigi! In a situation like this, it’s better to just give up!”

Sinclaire, next to him, disagreed.

“ …I don’t think so.”

“What?”

Tudor and Sancho turned their heads, and Sinclaire jerked at the ground in front of Professor Sadi.

“…Ah!”

They let out a collective gasp.

That’s right.

Pigi was now luring Professor Sadi away.

To where?

To the mud hole he had just fallen into!

In the previous match, Sinclaire’s fire and ice magic had caused the ground to freeze, melt, and form a muddy pit over and over again.

The arena with Professor Sadi still had a solid stone floor, but the arena with the golem on top was filled with mud pits, and the direction Pigi was standing was in the dead center of Professor Sadi’s back, hidden by the golem’s back.

In other words, if the golem mimicked Professor Sadi’s movements on the flat ground, it would soon fall into a mud pit, and that would be the perfect opportunity for a counterattack!

“As expected, Pigi’s brain is the best!”

“This will do it!”

“Guy. That’s pretty good, isn’t it?”

“Go, Pigi! Show her what you’re made of!”

Tudor, Sancho, Bianca, and Sinclaire began cheering for Pigi.

Pigi drew Professor Sadi in with an exquisite square and landed a terrain conversion blow.

But.

[What? There’s mud?]

Professor Sadi’s genius chews through all of these variables.

Bam!

The golem’s high heels didn’t stick in the mud.

…More accurately, they were stuck, but they came off as quickly as if they were stepping on flat ground.

“!?”

Pigi’s eyes widened. His eyes are wide with horror.

In front of him, Professor Sadi’s golem leaned in close.

A sweet voice spoke dangerously and giddily.

[You think you’re a genius at installing things?]

Pigi’s attention was suddenly drawn to Professor Sadi’s high heels.

To his surprise, the heel had fallen off her shoe and was lodged in the mud behind her.

That’s right.

Professor Sadi was used to walking on the tips of his toes with his magpie feet pushed to the limit.

Without putting any weight on her back heel. Just the strength of his toes.

And those trained toes are the perfect finishing touch to a kick that packs a tremendous amount of power.

It was a glimpse of how much she had been training herself.

“Iiiigh!?”

Pigi finally swung his sword, but it was about two seconds later than he had planned.

And against Professor Sadi, two seconds was the difference between heaven and earth.

Pfft!

Another horrible gurgling sound erupted.

Pigi fell to the ground outside the arena, not just bloody, but completely covered in blood.

[That’s a lot of bullshit for a second time].

Prof. Sadi turned around, unleashing an unrelenting barrage of abuse.

At that moment.

There was a sound that stopped her in her tracks.

-Ting!

Pigi’s score popped up.

.

-Valid hits: 1 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 0 (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 0 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total score: 1 point

1 point. Only one effective hit.

But Professor Sadi never allowed Pigi to attack.

[What? There’s no way I’d give that scumbag a point].

But Pigi’s score is definitely one.

Then.

[…!]

Professor Sadi’s eyes widened.

A broken blade was deeply embedded in the lower belly of the golem she was controlling.

◆

“Pigi! Are you okay!?”

Tudor and Sancho frantically rushed to Pigi’s aid.

Covered in blood, Pigi could barely stand up on his own.

One of his eyes was swollen shut and completely closed.

“Hehe… guys, I still got a point.”

Tudor and Sancho were silent for a moment as Pigi spoke.

Pigi had clutched the broken sword in his hand the moment Sadi’s kick had hit, and he had driven it into the golem’s body.

It was only worth one point, though the shards of the clenched blade made a mess of his hand.

Pigi did it, and he did it.

“Well done, asshole…, you did it.”

“You didn’t blink until the moment you got hit, which is something I couldn’t do either. I admire you.”

Tudor and Sancho said, supporting Pigi.

Pigi didn’t even have the strength to speak anymore, only the faintest movement of his dried lips.

Just then, a medic rushed over and began tending to his wounds.

Dolores looked at him with concern.

“Your left head is badly cracked. You could have been blinded if the Holy Power had been applied a moment later. You’ll be blind for a while, so be sure to wear the medical one-eye glasses.”

“…That’s a good thing, my mother would have cried a lot if I had gone blind.”

The sigh of relief that followed Pigi’s words was met with clenched teeth by neither Tudor nor Sancho, nor Bianca and Sinclaire, who had just arrived.

Meanwhile.

In the ballroom, Professor Banshee was issuing an ultimatum to Sadi.

“Step out of the training grounds, Sadi. From now on, I will revoke your test administrator qualifications. You are a human being unworthy of testing a warrior’s honor. Because you yourself are not a warrior right now.”

Sadi smirked at Professor Banshee’s rebuke of his dishonorable behavior.

“A warrior? There are no warriors in the academy, they’re all idiots.”

At the same time, she muttered in a low voice.

“Only ‘He’, the one who stirs the night of the Empire, is a true warrior.”

Professor Banshee did not hear Sadi’s words.

“Come down here now. You are not worthy of a professor, and from this point forward, I will strip you of all rights and privileges as an examiner….”

But Professor Banshee was cut off mid-sentence.

“Next.”

A voice interrupted the conversation between Professor Sadi and Professor Banshee.

Extremely cold, but with something calming rising from it.

“I’m next.”

Vikir.

The expressionless face of Vikir finally stood in front of the examination board.

“Personally, I’d like to be tested by that professor.”

If you didn’t know Vikir, you’d think he had nothing on his mind.

But for those who know Vikir, it’s easy to see how he’s feeling right now.

On top of the white skin, one faintly exposed vein can be seen with a blue edge.

Vikir was angry.

Chapter 192

Attack Land (5)

◆

The unleashed hound took to the field.

Vikir had a special meeting with Professor Banshee before he was put to the test.

“Vikir-gun.”

Professor Banshee’s gaze and voice were cold, and as usual, he didn’t like Vikir.

But.

“As a professor, I have a duty to see that my students are not put in harm’s way. That’s why I don’t want you to take Professor Sadi’s exam.”

“I’d like to take the test as scheduled, on principle, if possible, but I also think I might get something out of it.”

“…What? Something to gain?”

Professor Banshee tilted his head as if he couldn’t figure out what Vikir was thinking.

Then he spoke firmly.

“There is nothing to be gained from a person like Sadi. Except for the experiential realization that there are many absurdities in the world.”

Professor Banshee was still cold.

He took a few steps in front of Vikir, then moved his hand and held a piece of paper in front of him.

“If you want to test Professor Sadi, sign this memorandum, and only then will I allow you to do so.”

“….”

A normal student would have given in right there.

No, there wasn’t a single big lunatic here at Colosseo Academy who had the nerve to go against Professor Sadi and Professor Banshee in the first place.

…None. Except for Vikir.

Shhhhh.

Vikir signed the memorandum and handed it back to Professor Banshee.

Everyone around him was stunned by his nonchalance.

Professor Banshee also showed a change in expression that was worthy of being called a wax doll due to Vikir’s unexpected behavior.

“You’re really going to take on Sadi? You’re still so arrogant.”

“….”

“Hahahaha, those greenhouse plants that have been fed nothing but sweet fertilizer need to taste the bitterness of the world, so they can learn to recognize what’s good for them and what’s not.”

Professor Banshee’s face crumpled into a grimace and he snorted.

And then.

It was Vikir’s turn.

[That’s it, you scumbag pigs].

The shadow of Sadi’s golem looming eerily in front of Vikir as he steps up to the test.

Professor Sadi looks at Vikir curiously.

[I’m not interested in weak pigs… but you’re kinda interesting, how dare you pick me, a scum from a talentless commoner].

“….”

[Are you friends with the short pig that came up earlier, hohoho- his left eye is probably going to be blind, how about I match you with the right eye, asshole and douchebag duo. What do you think?]

Vikir didn’t bother to answer.

Just.

Karak.

I just fed the arrows to the archery show.

Ping.

The arrow flies at high speed.

But Professor Sadi’s golem reacted surprisingly quickly.

[Hmph- An archer closing the distance like this? That’s a good strategy for the early game. You sure can think on your feet, can’t you?]

Archers typically fight from a distance.

However, when you need to score points in such a short amount of time, it can be a good idea to move forward while shooting arrows.

It would dramatically reduce the time it takes for the arrow to fly to the target.

However, Prof. Sadi’s physicality was a monster.

With incredible flexibility, she swung her waist like a bow and dodged all the flying arrows.

Even the mighty Vikir had to hold his tongue at the instantaneous reaction.

The phrase ‘crooked genius’ seemed like it was created just for her.

Even the professors who criticized her character and behavior were speechless at her skill.

‘It’s a shame, because if she hadn’t lost her personality, she would have been a great warrior and a great contributor to the Allied Forces of Humanity.’

But Professor Sadi doesn’t seem like the type to fight for anyone.

The kind of person no one would follow, no one would respect, and no one would love. That’s Professor Sadi.

‘If that’s the case. There is no need to look after it.’

And Vikir was now flashing a cold glare at Professor Sadi.

Paan-!

Arrows fly with a crash.

Vikir had a bunch of arrows attached to the string and was firing them at an incredible speed.

Admiration began to erupt from those around them.

“My God, who is he, following Professor Sadi’s movements!?”

“That short distance isn’t getting any shorter, how is he dodging those?”

“Plus, look at the speed of the firing, it’s insane!”

The students and professors alike marveled at Vikir’s movements.

Of course, Professor Sadi’s synchronization with the golem had limited his mana and slowed his movements, but it was still encouraging to see a first-year student keeping up.

However.

[Hohohoho- You’re only a archer after all].

Professor Sadi was right.

Vikir’s arrows hadn’t scored a single hit on Professor Sadi since the beginning.

Ting-ting-ting-ting-ting-pa-pa!

The arrows were shattered by fists, feet, and whips before they even reached the golem’s body, or bounced off into the distance.

Some of the arrows were shot in the wrong direction, as if I had miscalculated the wind.

Every once in a while, like beans in a drought, the golem would get a hit, but it would mostly hit the lower part of a limb and bounce off, so it wouldn’t count as a hit.

Even Bianca, watching it from outside the testing area, shook her head.

“Archers have no chance in a real attack test, and while I did well with my gentle professor, you’ll be hard pressed to get a single point against Professor … Sadi.”

She was right.

Tudor, Sancho, Sinclaire, and even Pigi, who had a bandage on his face, looked worried.

Dodging the golem’s punches and kicks, Vikir picked up the arrows that had fallen to the ground and fired them again.

But still, most of the arrows bounced off the backs of the golem’s hands or fists, or were broken beyond use, and the number of usable arrows continued to decrease.

[Hohoho- are you going to continue? It was a rat, not a pig].

Professor Sadi seemed to be in high spirits.

After all, she hadn’t managed to land a single whip on Vikir either.

She looks restless, as if she wants to abandon the golem and go out on her own.

[Come here, you wimpy child, you need corporal punishment].

Professor Sadi wants to corner Vikir, but the circular shape of the examination hall makes that impossible.

Vikir cleverly realizes this and continues to run in circles, stalling for time.

There are points for evasion.

But Professor Sadi had no intention of going along with Vikir’s plan.

[Hohoho- Trying to collect points through effective evasion? It’s a rat-like idea. But that cannot be allowed!]

And with that, her whip began to strike even more fiercely.

Bam! Crack!

Professor Sadi did not attack Vikir. She wasn’t going to give him a dodge point.

Instead, she struck the floor of the examination room.

The round, circular surface of the test is gradually cracked by the whip.

In the end, one corner of the test field changed into a sharp shape, and angled corners naturally appeared.

What Professor Sadi did next was to drive Vikir into this corner.

The whip is cracked and the floor bursts open everywhere but the corner.

Vikir, who had been stalling for time by running clockwise and counterclockwise around the circular testing area, was forced into the corner.

[Die, scumbag].

Prof. Sadi shouted at Vikir with a verbal assault unlike anything you’d expect from a test examiner.

The whip flew and the arrows were falling apart.

Vikir rolled and crawled across the mud and stone-covered floor, dodging Professor Sadi’s attacks and picking up and firing the few arrows that were still intact.

When he does manage to escape a corner, a whip comes flying at him, leaving a faint cut.

Vikir was like a cornered mouse.

Everyone watching could only sigh.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, Dolores, and even Professor Banshee, who has always disliked Vikir, are getting nervous.

And Professor Sadi, who has finally gotten a hold of Vikir’s leash, declares cheerfully.

[The pain, disability, and death you are about to suffer will be worth nothing].

At the same time, her hand holding the whip is raised high.

If you are hit by this whip that is imbued with aura, you may suffer at least serious injury or even death.

Professor Banshee growled.

“Have the medics stand by.”

At that, the professors scramble to their feet.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and Dolores had all moved closer to the examination area.

So that if Vikir goes out and fails, they’ll be there to pick him up.

…But.

[Huh?]

Professor Sadi tilted her head.

A subtle foreign sensation on her arm for a moment.

It made her whip-wielding arm pause for a moment.

…Thwack!

Near the joint where the arrow had been hitting earlier. I hadn’t paid much attention to it because it wasn’t considered a valid hit.

The spot felt strangely stiff.

Chapter 193

Attack Land (6)

◆

Ziggy Geek…

A momentary phenomenon, surely a temporary event.

But it was a shock to Professor Sadi nevertheless.

The golem stopped.

The whip attack that had threatened to crush Vikir at any moment had been interrupted.

[…?]

Professor Sadi jerked back in surprise.

This time, the golem listened and followed.

…?

All the spectators were dumbfounded.

“What’s going on? What’s going on? Why are you stopping?”

“Is it a bad mood? The golem seemed to stop for a moment.”

“Anyway, this is your chance! Run, kid!”

“Abstain! You’ll get yourself killed!”

Everyone who saw Professor Sadi’s golem moving again exclaimed in unison.

[This is ridiculous, what was that just now?]

Mud Golems and Stone Golems often malfunction like this.

But most of the time, it was just a minor glitch that would go away with a test drive.

Professor Sadi raised the whip again and aimed it at Vikir.

Down, then up, then down, then up again.

But.

…Pinch!

Once again, the movement was stopped.

Zap!

The whip that was falling towards Vikir stopped midway, destroying the wrong place.

[No, really! What the hell!?]

Prof. Sadi threw up her hands in annoyance and stepped back.

Just then.

Ta-ang!

Vikir, who had escaped from the corner, fired another arrow into the golem’s lower abdomen.

Crunch!

The golem made another short stop.

Finally, a gasp escapes from the professors.

“That’s it! I get it!”

“It’s because he kept hitting the same spot!”

“You’re constantly putting fatigue on the joints that weaken with every movement!”

“Oooh, that’s a pretty good hit rate!”

And then there’s the reaction from the students.

“Wow, he keeps hitting the same spot with the arrow, is that possible?”

“It’s possible! He’s a really good archer!”

“Yeah, I saw him shoot right up there with Bianca on the range the other day!”

“And from what I saw during the defense test, it looks like he’s almost an advanced Sword Expert, too!”

“Who the hell are you?”

The public opinion took a sharp turn.

The crowd booed at the villainous Professor Sadi and cheered at the unexpected appearance of the dark horse, Vikir.

“Great!”

Tudor, who was cheering outside the arena, exclaimed.

“Vikir, you’ve been targeting the joints of the most mobile golem’s limbs and the joints of its underbelly, I’ve got to give you credit for some real archery skills!”

But Sancho, beside him, shook his head.

“It’s certainly a feat to keep shooting at the same spot without missing a beat, but… can you really make Professor Sadi’s golem stutter like that?”

Tudor scratches his head at the question.

It was Sinclaire, the young girl next to him, who answered their questions.

“Partly because of my hyung’s arrow, but also because of Professor Sadi’s habits.”

“Habits?”

“Uh-huh. Professor Sadi uses a whip, so where do you think it takes the most effort to use a whip?”

“Yeah…… Is it the lower abdomen? Due to the structure of the golem, both arms and legs move while applying force to the lower abdomen. Moreover, the characteristics of the weapon called a whip are the same.”

“Exactly. That’s why he’s been targeting the lower abdomen. If he can loosen the joints there, he can seal the arms and legs as well, which will weaken the whip’s power and accuracy.”

“Is that even possible? Those areas are much smaller than normal joints…… It’s supposed to be super-precise sniping.”

Bianca cut in on Tudor, Sancho, and Sinclaire’s conversation.

“He can.”

Bianca chewed on her bottom lip as everyone turned to look at her.

“The other day, we were practicing archery together at the training grounds… and he shot and killed a flying mosquito from a hundred meters away, and he didn’t even use any mana.”

“Hey, does that make sense?”

“It’s real!?”

Sinclaire ran a hand through his hair as Tudor and Bianca bickered.

“Alas, the joint in the lower abdomen is a weak point. You’re always one step ahead of me. Why didn’t I think of that?”

Then. A voice answered everyone’s questions.

It was Dolores, the student council president.

“That’s because it’s a weakness you didn’t have against Professor Sadi.”

At this, everyone’s eyes widened.

Dolores turned her head as if to answer, and there was Pigi, looking awkward.

“Do you remember the last piece of sword that Pigi put in?”

Dolores asks, and everyone gasps.

Even Pigi himself.

The piece of sword that Pigi had stuck into the golem at the last moment had been countered, embedded deeply, and created a tiny weakness.

Vikir, a veteran warrior, sees that weakness and grabs hold of it.

He was so confident that he would never lose that he willingly signed Professor Banshee’s waiver.

Sensing this, Professor Banshee could not help but make another face in front of the stadium.

“…What an annoying little thing.”

Professor Sadi’s golem visibly creaked, and she twisted her mouth in disbelief.

Even though she’d dealt with a lot of examinees in her time, she’d never had a student dare to play mind games with a professor.

Even more so, it had never worked, let alone against the mighty Professor Sadi!

As time passed, public opinion was turning in Vikir’s favor.

“Good job, kid, keep it up!”

“This is your chance to score big!”

“Go, Vikir, go!”

“Show me what you can do from a commoner!”

“Brother- you’re awesome!”

Cheers and responses erupt from the audience. It’s pushing Vikir’s back.

But.

[You’re funny].

Prof. Sadi has turned all these flows upside down once again.

She straightened her posture.

Her posture, which had been so fragile that she could have fallen at any moment, was quickly regained.

It was a wonder how she could balance on those unstable-looking heels.

At the same time, her whip swept around like a fierce snake.

Kwa-kwa-kwa-kwak! Pop! Ttuduk! Crash!

Broken shafts and broken arrowheads scattered in all directions.

All the arrows lying on the ground were shattered and scattered.

Rather than attacking Vikir, Professor Sadi is trying to disable the arrows around him.

All the arrows that were still in good condition were now gone.

The battle was effectively over.

[Hohoho-what can an archer do without arrows?]

Professor Sadi gritted her teeth, a wry smile tugging at one corner of her mouth.

It was true.

Vikir didn’t have any arrows left.

All of the supplied arrows had already been used up, and even when he tried to use those that were stuck on the ground or off, most of them had already broken after being shot several times.

The wind had carried them off in strange directions, making them impossible to retrieve.

And now, with all of the remaining arrows broken by the blows of Professor Sadi’s whip, there was nothing the archer could do.

In the end, Vikir was left with no means of offense.

“….”

“….”

“….”

The crowd’s cheering dies down rapidly as the harsh reality sinks in.

[Hohohoho- do you get it now, pigs?]

Prof. Sadi said, smacking the whip a few times on the floor.

[Did I say get out of the way? There’s still quite a bit of time left in the test. What are you going to do, quit or play with your sister some more?]

But.

“….”

Vikir just stood there, expressionless.

It didn’t mean he was going to quit, but it also didn’t mean he was going to continue.

[…?]

Professor Sadi frowned.

Vikir’s eyes were obscured by his bangs, but it was clear that his gaze was directed in this direction.

An unpleasant gaze.

It did not belong to a cornered prey.

Absolute confidence without a single doubt.

The eyes of a predator who is clearly looking at this as prey.

A moment.

…Creepy!

Professor Sadi shuddered once.

Where does this chill running down my spine come from?

The opponent was a first-year academy student, a commoner with nothing to show for it, an archer with a broken arrow.

But for a moment, Professor Sadi was overwhelmed by the unseen energy, neither mana nor aura, emanating from the boy.

It was an instinctive reaction, similar to that of a frog in the presence of a snake, or a dog recognizing a dog dealer.

But reason overcame emotion.

Professor Sadi came to her senses and quickly recognized the obvious: there was no reason for her to be intimidated by the boy in front of her.

And being pushed off the momentum even just for a moment left a nasty scratch on her stubborn pride.

…Is that why?

Professor Sadi was furious.

The genius, who normally would have trusted and respected his own instincts, ended up making the mistake of looking down on the prey in front of her.

[How dare you arrogant pig, you don’t even know the subject, and where do you get your eyes like that, just close your eyes…!]

She growled, her eyes widening.

At that moment, Professor Sadi, who had been focusing all his attention on Vikir, saw his lips curl into a small smile.

So small that no one else could have possibly seen it.

A message that could only be understood by reading the shape of the lips.

‘Blinded by anger, where are you looking?’

Suddenly, Sadi’s eyes widened.

At the same time.

…Puck!

A strange sound came from somewhere.

It sounded like the popping of something soft, and it must have been very close.

[…?]

Professor Sadi blinked a few times through her wide eyes.

Her left eye felt strangely hot, and then her vision went black.

At the same time.

[…! …! …! …!]

A searing pain began to engulf the entire left side of her face.

Chapter 197

The Corpse Queen (2)

◆

Wearing a bone helmet and armor, and a cloak that seems to reflect only the darkest parts of the night sky.

It stood at the center of the ruins, the master of the nine thousand dead who roamed the land.

And Vikir saw right through its ominous identity.

Danger Rating : S

Size: ?

Found in: ‘Serpent’s Womb’, deep within the Gate of Destruction.

-Nicknamed ‘Eighth Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Herds of cattle and beasts shall perish.”

– The Ten Commandments 10: Top.

The eighth demon, Seere.

The highest ranking demon who crossed over to wipe out mankind.

Vikir swallowed hard, a groan boiling in the depths of his throat.

‘…I never thought I’d meet you so soon.’

Seth, the ‘Inferior Second Son’, Dantalian, the ‘Face of a Thousand’, and Seere, the ‘King of Corpses’, appeared rather abruptly.

Vikir recalled a memory from before the regression.

The black mage was called the King of Corpses. Seere was a master of bringing the dead back to life.

When the army of the dead, a marionette circus of corpses, came to town, all living things held their breath and feared him.

Vikir also knew the identity of the one who had contracted with the Eighth Corpse Seere.

Unlike the other contractors of the Ten Corpses, Seere’s contractor was relatively well known.

It was Marquis Snake Morgue.

He was the highest ranking member of the Dark Hall of the Mage Family Morgue.

Snake Morgue had always secretly practiced black magic, so he would have been a perfect match for Seere.

‘He was a rival of the mad Adolf, and a formidable force to be reckoned with, even in his lifetime.’

Snake Morgue is a high council member of the Dark Hall, and Adolf Morgue is a high council member of the Light Hall.

For some reason, the two had not been on good terms for a long time, and the head of the family, Raspane Morgue, was barely able to control it.

Before his regression, Vikir hadn’t known for what purpose Snake had contracted with Seere, but he remembered clearly enough that the results had been disastrous.

‘This is the time when Adolf Morgue is still a Class 6 Mage. If that’s the case, then Snake Morgue might not be at a very high level of mage yet either….’

But. Vikir’s thoughts were interrupted.

The King of Corpses had sensed Vikir’s intentions.

[…Who is there?]

A booming voice called out.

Surprisingly, the voice, somewhat muffled with demonic energy, clearly belonged to a woman.

“…?”

Only then did Vikir take a closer look at the woman.

It was different.

Something was different from his memory before the regression.

Snake Morgue, the man who should have been the King of Corpses, was tall and unnervingly thin.

So much so that when he walked, he looked like a clown on a pole.

Once a target for assassination, his appearance and strength was something Vikir knew best.

But the King of Corpses in front of him was about the same height as Vikir, ….

What’s more, it had a well-trained body and balanced proportions, quite unlike the Snake Morgue.

Moreover.

‘…Woman?’

Vikir’s mouth was half open in disbelief.

Judging by the height, chest, and hips, the Corpse King’s body was definitely female.

Something is amiss.

Seere’s contractor has changed.

According to the original history, Snake Morgue should have been the contractor for Seere.

But that was long after the fact.

But now, Seere’s contractor is already here, and she’s nothing like Snake Morgue.

The Corpse Queen.

A human, clearly a woman, though it was impossible to make out her face as she wore a helm made of skulls.

She turned around, her long hair flaming red beneath the skull helm that covered her entire face, and her black cloak fluttering at the same time.

“….”

Vikir frowned slightly behind his mask.

I don’t know what’s going on here, but it’s good.

Snake Morgue was a high-ranking mage who even Vikir couldn’t guarantee victory against, and if such a being had made a pact with a demon, it would have been even stronger.

But it was not him, but someone else entirely, who became Seere’s contractor.

The aura emanating from her is peculiarly half-human, half-demon.

Perhaps that makes her a little easier to deal with.

‘Luck of the draw, the heavens have helped. If I do well, I may be able to kill Eight Corpse today.’

Debating whether or not to retreat in the face of Eight Corpse, Vikir turned toward the battle.

At the crossroads of death or death.

The demon and the demon hunter faced off.

◆

The devastation minutes before Vikir’s arrival.

[….]

The Corpse Queen.

She stared at the ruins of what was left of the building.

I don’t know what happened, but there must have been some sort of massive explosion.

[Dantalian, you lowly thief, how dare you steal from me…..]

At the same time, she stretched out her hand and emitted an aura that was like the darkness of the abyss.

Crackle- crackle- crackle- crackle-.

Suddenly, the pieces scattered throughout the remains moved and gathered into thin air.

Bitterness, sadness, anger, hatred, longing….

Drops of congealed blood, torn flesh, shattered bones, missing hair….

Traces of the dead that have not yet been sorted out remain tangled here and there, without distinction between those of the soul and those of the body.

They have gathered in one place at the call of the Queen.

Crackle, crackle, crackle!

A black magic circle appeared from nothing, and a woman’s body began to regenerate on top of it.

Geronto. The red-haired undead reappeared.

The Corpse Queen looked at the resurrected Geronto and stroked her hair.

[…So Seere’s power is working to some extent, the ability to ‘find the person you want to find’].

The Corpse Queen stroked Geronto’s hair as if she were handling something very precious.

[‘Rosie’, I managed to find this child, but I still couldn’t find… who I really wanted to find. Perhaps I shouldn’t have believed everything the demon said].

A Demon Contractor. But I have yet to make that power fully mine.

So, The Corpse Queen was working hard on her closed training without missing a single day.

She had closed herself off from the world.

[After all, … the only way to fully master this power is to cross the gates of death once and for all, for now I am only halfway there].

I have not yet made the power completely my own.

So when I brought Geronto back to life, I wasted mana unnecessarily, raising up a bunch of random corpses as plague.

I still need to train more to be able to use my power where it’s needed.

And then.

[…!]

The Corpse Queen sensed an unwelcome visitor.

A monstrous figure in black robes and a plague doctor’s mask.

An ominous aura radiated from him.

“Eight Corpse Seere. ‘King of Corpses’. You are my copycat.”

An eerie voice modulation came from his mouth.

The Night Hound. The worst villain to terrorize the Imperial City, and indeed the entire Empire, in recent times.

The Corpse Queen, however, shook her head at the sight of the Night Hound.

[Who are you?]

“Do you not know me?”

[I don’t know you.]

“You don’t seem interested in what’s going on in the world. Don’t you even read the newspaper?”

The Corpse Queen snorted lightly at the Night Hound’s question.

[…Newspaper? Why would I read such a thing. I have no more interest in this world].

Yes, I do. Newspapers are a tool to inform us of worldly events.

Those who have no interest in the affairs of this world have no need for newspapers.

The Night Hound and The Corpse Queen. Two masked men and women face each other.

Neither revealed their identities to the other, but the enemy they harbored was clear.

“The demon slays.”

[Do it if you can].

The Night Hound drew his black bow, Anubis.

The Corpse Queen also summoned her dead soldiers, including Geronto.

Cuddle-Up.

Deep underground in the Orphanage. Unexcavated bones, flesh, and ghosts rose to their feet.

Danger Rating: C

Size: 1.7 meters

Found in: All continents

-Name: ‘The Bone Man’.

A common wraith that can be found in graveyards, battlefields, abandoned houses, and sewers.

In rural areas and run-down cities, they are almost as common as rats.

Danger Rating : C

Size: ?

Found in: All continents

-Name: ‘The ghostly remnant’.

A ubiquitous wraith that can be found in graveyards, battlefields, abandoned houses, and sewers.

In rural areas and run-down cities, they are almost as common as rats.

Danger Rating: C+.

Size: 1 meter

Found on: All continents

-Name ‘corpse eater’. Ghoul.

A low-level demon that can be found in graveyards, battlefields, abandoned buildings, sewers, and other places where corpses are found.

They are not a resurrected form of the dead, but an entirely different species of undead that twists to feed on corpses.

Unusually, ghouls are not known to be an undead creature born from the dead, and it is said that once a ghoul has died, it cannot be reborn as an undead again.

In other words, it’s not known where they come from or where they go.

Skeletons, zombies, ghosts, and ghouls. The most basic forms that make up the Black Mage’s army of the dead.

As place is place, many of the resurrected undead were once children of the orphanage or were twisted to feast on its corpses.

Tsk.

The Corpse Queen clicked her tongue at the gathering undead.

As if she didn’t want them around.

Then the Night Hound’s attention was drawn to a skeleton in the forefront of the group.

Rattle.

A golden necklace glowed brightly around the small skeleton’s neck.

‘Nymphet’

The moment he saw the words.

“….”

The Night Hound bared his teeth.

“You will not die a pretty death.”

Fierce. Even more fiercely.

Chapter 199

The Corpse Queen (4)

◆

“…Ahhhhhh?”

Vikir expressed his disbelief through his mask.

The undead in front of him was skeletal, but clearly had brown skin and flowing hair that was a mixture of silver and black hair.

Moreover, the tattoos on its body were unmistakably Ballak’s.

Ah’Heman, the Shaman of Ballak.

A black mage of considerable distinction, born of the shamanic tribe Rokoko.

Yes, he was definitely dead.

He was crushed and shattered by Iliad’s battle with Vikir, and eventually burned to death at the hands of his own people.

But his gritty life force.

And the tenacity, inferiority complex, grief, anger, jealousy, despair, greed, frustration, and hatred that he harbored to the very end have brought him to this place as an undead.

Now there is no native shaman who was once so ancient and honored.

[Ttagag- ttagagag- ttag!]

However, only the undead, whose only way to express themselves is by clashing their teeth, remain ugly.

Meanwhile.

The Corpse Queen looked at the lich she had created from the corpse of Ah’Heman and said.

[The corpse of a black mage, picked up relatively recently, a good thing from the depth of the Black&Red Mountain].

Ah’Heman was an ugly twisted creature on the inside, but otherwise a formidable force to be reckoned with in terms of qualities and talents, comparable to Adolf Morgue.

He would have been a formidable foe, even for a Vikir, if he had focused on the ways of the Mage from an early age instead of trying to impersonate a warrior.

But he was eventually consumed by the Abyss, unable to overcome the inferiority complex and sense of victimization that consumed his soul.

The classic case of a talented, perverse mage being consumed by the Abyss of Magic. That is the Lich.

[Ttagag- ttag- ttattag-]

A skeleton whose lips had rotted away, leaving his teeth and rotten gums exposed, Ah’Heman could only grind his teeth together to make a sound, unable to speak, as if he had lost all sense of self.

He was a faithful puppet, doing the Corpse Queen’s will.

“Why is Ah’Heman’s body here when it should be in the Black&Red Mountain?”

Vikir pondered for a moment.

After all, hadn’t a knight from Donquixote’s Family been a puppet of Dantalian’s not too long ago?

Furthermore, Staffordshire of the Baskervilles, Mozgus of the Quovadis, and Rosie Morgue had all fallen prey to the demon as living corpse puppets.

This should come as no surprise, as collecting corpses and turning them into puppets is the demon’s specialty.

Vikir didn’t have time to ponder this.

[Ttag- ttagag- ttagagag-]

The sound of teeth and jawbone colliding is loud.

Ah’Heman’s lich shifted, and an unpleasant aura began to fill the air.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The bones began to move again.

Vikir narrowed his eyes.

Ah’Heman’s specialty in life had been playing with the dead.

And now that he was a Lich, the stench was even more vile, threatening the entire battlefield.

Whoosh! Whoosh!

A black air currents rushed around Ah’Heman, and the dead around him came back to life.

Surprisingly, even Ephebo, Pedo, and Hebe, who had been killed by Vikir earlier against the Dantalians, came back to life.

[Grrr…]

[Giggle- giggle-]

[Swoosh! Swoosh!]

Unlike Geronto, who was brought back to life with a clean look, Ephebo, Pedo, and Hebe were in a state of disrepair.

But Vikir soon realized that they didn’t need to be restored to good looks.

Pow! Woodchuck!

He waved his hand, and the three undead began to merge into one.

The bodies of Hebe, Ephebo, and Pedo merged into one, each compensating for a missing body part.

Danger rating: A+.

Size: 8 meters

Found in: Nine Heaven’s Tomb

-Nicknamed the ‘Giant of the Flesh Wall’.

A golem made from the flesh of once living things. Miscellaneous meat is made by lumping meat together like clay and roughly imitating the shape of a human being, with almost no trace of the original material remaining.

They are filthy, unclean, and unholy, but their power is said to be real.

Another higher undead has arisen.

Powerful limbs sprouted from its sturdy flesh, and its gnarled, distorted face lifted its head to glare at Vikir.

[Ttagag- ttag!]

[Gurgle… gurgle-]

The lich and the ragged golem surround Vikir.

At the same time, the dark spear summoned by the lich and the fist of the raggedy golem flew at the same time.

“…Hmm.”

Two A+ Danger Classes would be a difficult opponent for even Vikir to deal with.

Moreover, the Lich and the Rags Golem were both high-level creatures that were difficult to figure out how to defeat at this point, so Vikir had no choice but to keep retreating.

By this time, the Corpse Queen’s infernal fire had begun to burn.

Quack, quack, quack!

A spear of fire flew out and caught Vikir off guard.

The ground that the spear sliced through was immediately transformed into a long lava tube that began to bubble and boil.

[Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!]

The raggedy golem began to press down on Vikir with its massive bulk.

The Lich of Ah’Heman also summoned black flames, grinding his teeth and jawbone together.

Vikir fires back with arrows, but is unable to land a critical hit on the Corpse Queen due to the meat shield the Rags Golem creates as it throws its entire body at him.

Then, the Corpse Queen and the two high-ranking undead under her command began to prepare for the final blow.

The dark clouds in the sky swirled and ominous mana pulsed.

And Vikir had a hunch.

‘Fighting with only a bow has its limits.’

The Corpse Queen can create fire spears and deadpools to intercept enemies at a distance.

The Lich, too, can use the roots of plants pulled from the depths of hell to attack enemies from a distance, while the Ragged Golem can use its large, tough body to block attacks from the opposite direction.

In the end, the power of the Black Bow Anubis alone can only do so much.

Vikir is just about to draw his sword.

[Hmph-]

The wrist of his left hand suddenly feels empty.

Turning his head, he sees the hatchling on the ground, running wildly into the distance.

Didn’t they say that animals sense danger in advance?

Like a rat running away from a shipwreck or a catfish swimming to another river to escape an earthquake, the cub had left Vikir’s body.

A pet leaving its owner in a life-or-death situation?

It was a deeply ominous sign, but Vikir turned his head unconcerned.

“…Yes. You should live.”

No need to get caught up in someone else’s fight.

This cub has just hatched from an egg, so it will still have a long life ahead of it.

‘It’ll be a long time before it grows up to be as big as its mother.’

One concern was that there would be space in this Imperial City for him to forage and stay warm.

‘Please, stay out of sight of humans and survive to the end.’

Vikir tore his gaze away from the retreating cub and turned back to the corpse queen.

Yet.

[…Die, barbarian].

The corpse queen raised a black sun above her head.

The infernal flames bubbled and boiled like oil.

A black aerola stretched out like a coiled snake.

“….”

Vikir crouched low to the ground where the pillar of frightening flames fell.

Kiriririk-quack!

The black vines of the Infernal Tree that Lich had summoned and the giant hands of the Ragged Golem had sealed off Vikir’s escape route.

Vikir gritted his teeth.

‘Truly rotten. King of Corpses.’

Even though it was only half a human, its power was immense.

However, Vikir did not back down either.

Go-o-o-o-o…

Having already killed Andromalius and Dantalian, the experience imprinted on his body and soul accelerated the mana coursing through his veins, harder and faster.

Baskerville Seventh Formula.

A small but distinct seventh tooth in the aura of a Peak Graduator.

Purr-.

Vikir drew the magic sword Beelzebub from his wrist and swung it lightly once.

The seemingly insignificant movement, like the flapping of a butterfly’s wings, instantly created a tremendous ripple.

Kurrrrrr!

Spinning in a circle at high speed, the aura storm soon formed a sphere, emitting a blinding red light.

A black aura sun rested on the tip of a tall sword, preparing to descend.

At the same time.

Quack, quack, quack!

The Infernal Tree summoned by the lich, the body of the rag golem, and the aura emitted by Vikir clashed head-on.

The shredded roots of the Infernal Tree and the body of the Ragged Golem.

The seven teeth of the Night Hound gathered together in the shape of a sphere and soon viciously attacked everything that stood in their way.

And the final battle is the Black Sun summoned by the Corpse Queen.

Uh-oh!

Vikir’s crimson sun and the corpse queen’s black sun clashed together to form a penumbra.

The half-destroyed buildings were completely destroyed.

Stone shattered into sand, and sand boiled.

Steel rebar melted like cheese in the hot winds blowing from the center of the collision.

Everything was falling to pieces on the battlefield.

“…!”

Vikir suddenly saw something strange.

It was the eyes of the Corpse Queen.

The corpse queen’s red eyes shining through her skull helmet.

Snake Morgue, who was supposed to be the Corpse King. Those eyes that were so different, yet somehow so familiar.

[…!?]

Her eyes glowed with the reflection of the magic sword that was emanating from Vikir’s hand and the aura it carried.

And at the same time.

[… Now, wait a minute!]

The Corpse Queen cried out when she saw Vikir’s aura.

Her tone was both urgent and desperate.

Chapter 200

The Corpse Queen (5)

◆

…Boom!

The world crumbled into blackness.

Vikir stepped back, feeling his entire body turning into mud.

Thick blood and bits of guts leak from his mouth. His vision blurred and his body refused to respond.

Vikir drew upon the power of his magic sword, Beelzebub, to restore himself.

Tsutsutsutsuts-

Though it took a great deal of stamina and mana, Vikir was able to reattach broken bones and repair torn muscles.

However, he was unable to regenerate the numerous wounds across his body, as most of his strength was spent repairing his core skeleton, guts, muscles, and severed organs.

Vikir thought as he touched his bloodied body, the mask barely covering his face.

‘I’ll never make it back to the Academy in this condition.’

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi would be horrified if they saw him now.

Then.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

There was a presence clinging to his left wrist.

Madame cub. The little guy had returned.

“ …Thank you. You saved my life.”

Vikir stroked the cub’s head.

Just before the clash with the Corpse Queen, there was a thread that grabbed the back of Vikir’s neck as he was caught in the explosion.

A thread that the cub had secretly attached to the back of Vikir’s head. A sturdy lifeline that had survived the maelstrom of mana without breaking.

It was connected to a rock behind it.

The cub tugged Vikir onto that rock, and it was only because of it that Vikir narrowly escaped the explosion.

If not for the thread, he would have been mortally wounded, unable to regenerate even with the power of Beelzebub.

Meanwhile.

Passtssss…

The Lich of Ah’Heman and the Ragged Golem crumbled to dust and vanished.

And behind them, the Corpse Queen stood tall.

…But then.

Thump!

The corpse queen dropped to one knee.

She was motionless, probably stunned by the shock of the mana backflowing into her body.

“ …Since you’re half-demon, half-human, the effects of the mana backflow must be even greater.”

Vikir stared at the corpse queen.

He remembered her last, fleeting words, just before the confrontation.

‘…Now, wait a minute!’

Why did the Corpse Queen lose focus at such a crucial moment?

Thanks to her distraction, Vikir was able to shatter the Black Sun, a mana concentration in the negative dimension, with his seven teeth.

Although it was only half, the power of the Eight Corpse was strong. As time passes, it will become stronger.

“…Must be killed here and now.”

I don’t know why the Corpse Queen takes her power at the end, but that’s not what matters now.

The Corpse Queen lay defenseless, the eighth corpse, Seere. I had to kill her now.

Jeopuk- Jeopuk- Jeopuk-

Vikir walked forward with the magic sword Beelzebub hanging down.

Blood oozed from his ragged body, making long snail-like tracks on the floor.

Then.

[… Don’t.]

The corpse queen’s mouth opened.

Her head drooped like a condemned man about to be hanged, her skull mask already shattered, her face invisible.

But her lips were definitely moist.

[…Don’t leave me].

A muffled, disheveled tone. Then a faint noise. It was a sob.

Apparently, the Corpse Queen had a story.

But.

“There is no grave in the world without a story.”

Vikir’s grip on his sword tightened.

Who among the undead didn’t have some sort of excuse, or story to tell.

Vikir didn’t care what kind of life the woman in front of him had lived before becoming the Corpse Queen, or what kind of story she had to tell.

For he had a greater mission than all of that.

To avenge his own fleeting death, that of his comrades-in-arms, and that of humanity as a whole.

To stop the age of destruction.

That’s what brought the Night Hound back to his feet after his fall.

And with that, Vikir stood before the Corpse Queen.

“….”

The corpse queen shook her head, unmoving. She fainted and let out an unconscious sob.

Then Vikir lifted Beelzebub high into the air.

The sword, sharp as a guillotine preparing to fall, will soon separate the Eight Corpse from her neck and body.

This is the moment when the third demon is hunted.

And now.

Pow!

The sword fell.

Thus, a total of three of the Ten Demons are killed. The age of destruction is pushed back. A fitting tribute to the many comrades who died in the blink of an eye.

But. Things don’t always go according to plan.

Clang!

There was a presence blocking the magic sword Beelzebub.

“…Geronto!”

Vikir’s brow furrowed.

A metal skewer blocking a dark red sword.

The mage who had gone by the name of Rosie Morgue in the past had become a lich and was blocking Vikir.

Clang!

The skewer broke, but it managed to deflect Beelzebub.

Vikir staggered backward.

Now, Geronto’s dark mana began to spew out flames and metal skewers everywhere.

Vikir adjusted his mask, thinking.

“Dantalian’s minions… are a pain in the ass.”

At this point, he was stuck.

He’d seen Geronto’s power before. He was no match for her, especially in his current state of exhaustion from fighting the Corpse Queen.

Vikir took a few steps back, creating distance. Every inch was good, and he needed to give his body time to recover.

What?

Surprisingly, Geronto didn’t pursue Vikir.

Instead, she politely picked up the corpse queen who had fallen behind her.

“…?”

Vikir shook his head.

By nature, the undead, the dead, are jealous of what they don’t have.

That’s why they blindly bite and rob the living.

The same is true for the raised undead

Their first priority is to attack the nearest living being rather than defend their master, which is fine as long as the master is strong-willed, but once the master is unconscious, the undead are out of control.

But what about now?

Geronto holds the Corpse Queen close to his heart.

It hasn’t even bothered to attack Vikir, who is now in a state of exhaustion.

‘What? No way….’

It’s one of two things. Either Geronto is not a normal undead, or the Corpse Queen’s spirit remains strong on this battlefield.

‘Maybe both.’

Geronto is undead, so it’s safe to assume that the Corpse Queen’s mind is still roaming the battlefield, controlling Geronto.

The idea is.

‘Do not attack the author.’

It’s a will to avoid fighting Vikir.

In the final confrontation, and now in Geronto’s case, the Corpse Queen seemed to have no intention of fighting Vikir.

‘What the hell, how could you….’

Vikir frowned.

The mysterious woman who had become the Corpse Queen in place of Snake Morgue. As a Demon Contractor, why was she acting so strangely?

His vision blurring, his breath quickening, Vikir tried to gather his thoughts, but he couldn’t focus.

And then, taking advantage of the gap, Geronto drew a circle of magic.

Pow!

It was a teleportation magic circle.

A blue light burst forth, teleporting Geronto and the sleeping Corpse Queen in her arms.

“Chet-”

Vikir drew his black bow, Anubis, and fired an arrow, but Geronto’s teleportation was half as fast.

Flash!

In the blink of an eye, the two women disappeared in front of Vikir.

“Did I miss …?”

Vikir sighed and leaned back against the molten steel.

It was the usual: a surprise when you weren’t ready. The future unexpectedly changed. These variables had caused me to lose sight of my goal.

For the first time, I failed in my assassination.

“Afterthought. Still, I knew I had a chance against the Eighth Demon. He’s still a weak demon.”

Vikir muttered to himself as he patted the hatchling that was spewing threads into his arm to form a cast.

Suddenly, there was a commotion around him.

…Flash!

Torches and mana lights were lighting up the area.

As you turn your head toward the low ground below, you see guards approaching at full alert, having heard the commotion.

I also hear a familiar voice.

“Hohoho- this way! It must be the Night Hound! Come on, pigs, follow me!”

One eye, high heels, and a thorn whip wrapped around a slim waist.

The Imperial Guard, led by Professor Sadi, was rushing toward them.

“…You’ve become a nuisance.”

Vikir melted into the darkness, his body covered in tattered black cloth.

With Mushu Hushu’s ability to glide through the darkness without making a sound, it wasn’t hard for Vikir to escape the encirclement.

Taking the cub’s thread, Vikir ascended to the heights of the ruins, crossing the void in an instant to reach the skyscrapers outside of the encirclement.

…Tuck!

Reaching the ground below the building, Vikir looked back at the ruins in the distance and smiled bitterly.

“I don’t know what I’m going to tell the kids about this.”

Just like back in Dantalian, his body would be wracked with the after-effects and fatigue for some time.

Midterms are over and the festival season is upon us, so I could use a break.

It’s also a good idea to check yourself into the nurse’s office with the excuse of overwork.

‘Three days, in which to recover, and then we’ll go in search of the Eight Corpse.’

Vikir adjusted his Picaresque mask as he thought.

And then.

Vikir’s body transformed.

Hack-hack-hack

An exhausted-looking black puppy with severe wounds all over its body trotted toward the Academy.

Chapter 202

Mixed Bath (2)

◆

“…What do you guys think you’re doing?”

Student Council President Dolores. The Academy’s youngest early entrant and current third-year senior.

The most prominent member of the Faithful Quovadis, one of the seven great Houses of the Empire, and the most influential among the Empire’s young nobles.

In her presence, the second-year tremblers froze in their tracks.

Senior students, inferior in skill, in grades, and in family connections.

As long as they weren’t idiots, they should be able to read the atmosphere.

The food and water bowls in Dolores’ hands, obviously prepared for the stray dogs and cats in the vicinity.

They put one of the abandoned puppies in the center of the space and kicked, spit on, stabbed with broken liquor bottles, and burned with cigarettes.

“…Uh, how long have you been watching?”

The one in the front asked in a shaky voice.

Dolores replied with a grim look and a voice he hadn’t seen or heard from in the nearly two years they’d been in school.

“I haven’t seen it since the beginning.”

The second-year students were slightly relieved.

But.

“But I have seen enough to despise you.”

Their faces began to turn white again at Dolores’ next words.

The word “saint” could not be more fitting, for Dolores had always had an angelic heart.

Her warm smile, kind demeanor, and gentle voice had always been liked and followed by everyone in the school, whether they liked it or not.

…But what about now?

Dolores’s expression was as cold as the wind in the North Sea.

It’s always more frightening when someone who doesn’t usually get angry gets angry.

No one had ever seen Dolores so angry before.

Then, Dolores pushed her way through the crowd and picked up Vikir from the ground.

Vikir, a small black puppy, squirmed and was picked up by Dolores.

Ko-ok.

Dolores reached out, careful not to touch Vikir in case he felt any pain, and pulled him close to her chest.

“That hurt, didn’t it?”

The warm voice in his ear was imbued with a faint holy power.

Just hearing it made the wounds on his body hurt a little less.

Meanwhile, the six second-year students were slowly backing away, looking away.

‘Oh dear, we’re going to get tarred and feathered for messing with the wrong bastard.’

“I thought President Dolores really hated this kind of thing.”

‘Instead of wasting time by harassing it, I should just kill it.’

Then, Dolores looked at the second-year students in front of her and said.

“…That most serial killers begin their crimes by abusing animals. Do you guys know that?”

Everyone craned their necks between their shoulders at the piercing stare.

But even they had arguments.

“That’s too much of an analogy. Aren’t we the elite who will lead this country?”

“Yes, and you’re accusing us of being a little rough with an ownerless dog because of academic stress.”

“We apologize that we were drunk and made a few mistakes, but aren’t those dogs just dirty dogs that carry diseases anyway?”

The men’s defenses only made Dolores’ expression grow even more icy.

“Leading the country, you guys?”

The second-year students’ faces drained of all color.

Dolores continued.

“The Academy is where we train people to lead the country. And to graduate from this academy and serve the state, you must have a spirit that is weak to the weak and strong to the strong.”

There was a conviction in her words that was harder than steel.

And it was forged and honed by passion, sharpened to a razor-sharp edge.

“But you are the opposite. Strong for the weak and weak for the strong. Such men are everywhere, even outside the Academy. Why should we entrust the affairs of state to such common folk?”

Disqualification from nobility. Yellow sprout. Those who do not deserve to be called elite. A pest that harms more people the more high-ranking people become successful.

To them, Dolores showed no mercy.

“By the authority of the president, I’m giving each of you demerits. I’m giving all six of you all the demerits I can give in a year.”

The power of the student council president is enormous because the professors have granted the student council some authority.

This means that the student council president can kick a few students out of school a year if he/she feels the need.

Of course, if this were done to the children of powerful families, it might raise a few eyebrows, but the six bullies here don’t have any powerful backers.

There’s no way that a small noble family from the countryside would be able to protest against Quovadis, the Faithful.

The six people in front of him realized what was happening.

“Ms. President, this, this, this is not right, is it? How can you expel a junior….”

“Expulsion for harassing a dog, we’re from the aristocracy too!”

“I, I belong to the aristocratic faction as well. Please have mercy!”

The second-year students crouched down on the ground, their sobriety gone.

They had every reason to be, admitting a child to the academy was an enormous expense.

It’s unimaginable for an ordinary family, and quite a burden even for a well-to-do noble family.

However, the wealth and power that comes with graduating from this academy is so great that it is quite an honor just to be admitted.

…But what if you were to be expelled?

Great honor can only lead to great dishonor.

Moreover, the influence of the Quovadis on the entire nation was immense, and once you were disrespected by them, your path was blocked.

Rune is the state religion of the Empire, and the family that represents the Order of Rune is the Quovadis.

Once you’ve been stampeded by Saintess Dolores here in Quovadis, your life as a noble within the Empire is effectively over.

You will never be able to take a new name.

What’s more, the plight of a young, junior member of the family means that even the family itself is in decline.

The stock price will plummet and the market capitalization will evaporate.

There was a strong possibility that all trade routes and jobs within the family would be cut off.

“I’m sorry, President!”

“Please cut me some slack! Please! Please!”

“Help me, my father is going to beat me to death, please have mercy!”

The second year students, who finally understood exactly what was happening, fell to their knees in unison and begged.

“Did you have mercy on this poor puppy?”

Dolores was still firm.

Not even a needle could get in.

◆

Bathroom.

Puddle-

Vikir stepped into the warm water.

Splashing.

Who doesn’t like warm water? His tail wags against his will.

Night Hound. Wounded and exhausted. Still a black pup.

Vikir closed his eyes and recalled the events of earlier.

‘Did you have mercy on this poor puppy?’

Dolores was unusually firm.

It was as if there was a glimpse, however slight, of the woman who had been known as the ‘Iron Saint’ on the battlefield before the regression.

‘Surprisingly. Until the war of destruction with the demons began, she was often evaluated as indecisive.’

Apparently, the fight with Dantalian had changed her a lot.

Boggle.

Vikir thought to himself as he submerged his nose in the tub.

He could feel his body slowly recovering.

It was no wonder, then, that the waters of Dolores’s favored baths had a slight but holy power, to the point of being considered holy water.

Vikir soaked in it, lost in thought.

The Eighth Corpse. The Corpse Queen.

He hadn’t been able to kill her in the end.

‘If only my cultivation had been higher.’

Peak Graduator. A power powerful enough to represent an entire country, but still, it would be a struggle to face her in single combat.

Moreover, the fact that he had struggled so much against a corpse queen who could only use about half of her power, no matter how unexpected the encounter, was something to reflect on.

‘Well, during Andromalius, I borrowed the knights of the House of Baskerville, and during Dantalian, I had Saintess Dolores with me.’

After all, it takes strength to hunt demons one-on-one.

Vikir began to explore the path to Swordmaster while also perfecting his still-imperfect mastery of the Baskerville Seven.

The incisors, central incisors, lateral incisors, and molars of the upper jaw.

The upper incisors, central incisors, lateral incisors, and molars.

The sixth and seventh teeth must be in proper harmony to form a true seven, but the seventh tooth that Vikir can produce is still small and unstable.

‘The sixth and seventh teeth of the 10th ambush tooth as the ‘ambush horizontal bicuspids’. This is the ultimate killing technique that can only be mastered by understanding the subtleties between the sixth and seventh teeth….’

The 6th Form manual clearly states the following.

-In order to cross the barrier of the Sixth Form, one must abandon all human emotions of happiness, joy, and pleasure.

And in the 7th Form manual, the twin swordsmanship manual, which is an exquisite combination of the 6th Form, the following was described.

-To reach the seventh level, one must regain the human emotions of joy and happiness.

Only by abandoning the emotion of happiness can one cross the barrier to the highest level of the Graduator.

But in order to become a Swordmaster, he would have to reclaim his feelings of happiness and joy.

‘I don’t understand what this means. Are you telling me that I have to revive an emotion that I’ve already killed?’

In his previous life, Vikir had also become a Graduator.

As he crossed countless lines and lost countless companions, Vikir became an increasingly precise and cold-blooded killing machine, and was even able to step onto the level of a Graduator with ease.

But that was all.

Vikir could never become a Swordmaster. He didn’t know the theory, and he didn’t know how to become one.

But now is different. The path to mastery and beyond was paved.

Vikir was lost in thought, recalling Hugo’s inaction in slaughtering Andromalius.

‘To become an Iron Man, I killed all my emotions. But to become a superhuman, I need emotions? What is this….’

Vikir had been trained by Hugo to kill his emotions.

It was the way hounds are bred, not to be good, but to be used and discarded.

‘Now that I think about it, it’s a way to quickly raise a character to a certain level of power. It’s a method of training to create an entry-level Graduator army, so it doesn’t really suit me now.’

I realized that I needed to change the way I was training, which was based on hands-on experience.

How could I bring back the emotions that were already dried up and worn out?

“….”

When Vikir was really thinking about it.

Kkiiig-

A small noise made Vikir’s ears perk up.

And then.

“…!”

All of Vikir’s thoughts were interrupted in an instant.

Something so startling that even the veteran Vikir lost his composure for a moment.

“Choco, your sister is here, let’s wash together!”

Saintess Dolores, she came into the bathroom.

Chapter 213

Festival Night (10)

◆

A black curtain falls.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Vikir rubbed his ring to create a barrier.

Creating the barrier took a lot of mana, but it was definitely worth it.

Two spaces are overlapping in one coordinate, but they are distinctly different concepts and cannot interfere with each other.

This would be very useful if you needed to store a lot of stuff, or if you needed to get into a big fight with a lot of people watching.

Vikir stared into the space between the barrier.

An empty abyss. A barren, vast wasteland.

Countless swords stuck into the ground, old and weathered by the winds of time.

Only broken and destroyed stone statues roll around.

“….”

Beyond the countless swords, Vikir gazed at the two statues that stood tall in the center of the abyssal hollow.

One was that of Hugo Le Baskerville, and beside him was that of Osiris Le Baskerville.

They were enormous compared to the size of the other miscellaneous statues, and though they were chipped here and there, they were still solid.

And beneath them were a number of smaller, shattered statues, all of them with familiar faces.

The Baskerville family’s servants, nannies, butlers, guardian knights…… Occasionally, I saw stone statues that seemed quite large, and they were the Seven Counts.

Vikir had an instinctive hunch.

‘This is the mind of Seth Le Baskerville.’

If he was right, what was Seth’s state of mind before he was possessed by the demon?

What had he seen, what had he heard, what had he thought, what had he lived in?

The statues of his father and brother still loomed large in the space that had been left empty after their deaths.

Vikir recalled the battle with Andromalius.

‘…, Son, what are you doing there?’

‘Ah, father, I came here on business…!?’

Andromalius froze at the mere sight of Hugo because of the residual thoughts of Seth, the original owner of the body.

His inability to live up to his father’s expectations, the inferiority complex he had with his brother, and his intense self-hatred.

It must have destroyed his relationships with everyone around him.

And it would have driven him to the depths of his mind, where there was nothing but empty darkness.

Seth must have heard Andromalius’ voice in the deepest reaches of this barren space.

When he was at his most bitter and most desperate.

‘Well, those who make contracts with the demon are usually like that. They come when a person’s heart is completely broken.’

A broken heart means you’ve given up on life.

Unlike the lesser demons, who pact through emotions such as momentary pleasure or greed, the higher demons of the Demon King class only visit such people.

The moment when a man, once the most virtuous of all, falls from the top to the bottom in the greatest of falls.

A terrible temptation, an irresistible offer.

Such is probably the case with the Corpse Queen, who now stands before Vikir’s eyes.

[…Is this within the barrier of the Ten Corpse?

The Eighth, the Corpse Queen, raised her head and looked at the Vikir before her.

Vikir looked at the corpse queen through the eyeholes of his mask.

The skull-masked woman must have a story, too.

Perhaps she’d struggled through unimaginable pain, sorrow, and screams before accepting the demon’s offer.

‘…But no grave without an excuse.’

What the Corpse Queen’s story was that led her to take Snake Morgue’s place in the position of Eight Corpse.

As far as Vikir is concerned, she is simply an absolute evil that killed countless allies before she was turned.

“Let’s end this, demon.”

The battle would have been much more difficult if it had been the Eight Corpse who had taken over Snake Morgue’s body.

But the current Corpse Queen is not yet up to par.

Her talent and potential for magic was on par with Snake Morgue’s, even exceeding his, but time had not yet allowed the Eight Corpse Seere itself to develop much strength.

Furthermore, the Corpse Queen, for some reason, had not yet fully surrendered herself to the demon.

“This is good news in many ways.”

Vikir immediately fed Anubis an arrow.

Puff-puff-puff!

The deadly snipe he had learned from Aiyen shot towards the Corpse Queen and flew away.

But.

POP!

A rock wall rising ninety degrees from the ground deflected all the arrows.

Geronto stood firmly in front of the Corpse Queen.

Hoodeducs-

The bone seeds sown by the Corpse Queen began to produce countless skeleton soldiers once again.

With her undead army at her side, the Corpse Queen once again regained her monarchial dignity.

[Show me your face].

She was determined to tear off the mask of the Night Hound and leave him naked.

Vikir frowned at her persistence.

Soon, a large number of dead soldiers began to press in around him.

Archery was at a disadvantage against such a large number.

The Corpse Queen was well aware of this, and was pressuring Vikir from all sides.

However.

…A flash!

Vikir unleashed his true power only now that all the eyes were gone.

[Hack-]

Vikir, who had attached the threads from the cub to Hugo’s statue, rose up from his seat.

The ground where Vikir stood a moment ago was covered in skeleton soldiers.

Quack, quack, quack!

A blood-red aura swirls around like a six-and-a-half-headed snake, tearing the ground apart.

Baskerville Form Sword Technique!

A crimson aura rises up and engulfs the dead soldiers.

Passtsss…

An exorcism ritual using physical force. The undead return to where they belong.

Crackle, crackle, crackle! Pow!

The power of the highest level of the Graduator burst forth unchecked.

Vikir pushed forward, slaughtering his enemies relentlessly.

Six and a half gigantic wheels made of aura were moving forward, breaking, crushing, crushing, and tearing the bone wall without hesitation.

Lich Geronto cast a few spells to try and stop Vikir’s attack, but it was no use.

Source.

[….]

The Corpse Queen does nothing as she watches Geronto get pushed back.

Vikir was able to easily break through the encirclement and stand in front of the Corpse Queen.

Soon, he’ll be able to kill the demon and its host in front of him.

‘First, we’ll separate the neck and head, then remove the skull mask to see what’s inside.’

“You will remove the mask.”

With that, the tip of the blade extending from Vikir’s wrist is aimed at the Corpse Queen’s throat.

You will now know the identity of the one who has taken the place of the Eighth Corpse, the Snake Morgue who rules the dark faction of Morgue the Mage.

Then.

[… No].

The Corpse Queen’s mouth opened.

[I can’t take off my mask].

At the same time.

Pow!

The tip of Vikir’s blade deflected.

It wasn’t because the Corpse Queen had done something tricky, and it wasn’t because of a lapse in concentration or stamina.

Instinct. The instincts of a veteran hound who has seen countless battles, and at the last second, the tip of the sword slightly twisted its trajectory.

In the end, Vikir struck the corpse queen near her forehead, and it ricocheted off the hard part of her skull mask.

Crack!

It was as if he had struck a chestnut.

…Crack!

The ears of the skull mask were incontinent.

“…?”

Vikir landed on the ground and shook his head.

He didn’t understand why he’d just twisted the tip of his sword, even to himself.

‘What is this? Has this ever happened before?’

No, I assure you. Not once. In all my life, before and after my regression, in all the many, many slopes I’ve crossed, I’ve never made that mistake.

Only.

Parr…

The right hand holding the magic sword Beelzebub trembled faintly.

This was not a matter of the flesh but of the spirit. A movement of the mind.

The emotions he had killed, or thought he had killed, as he rose to the highest levels of the Graduator, were still alive and stirring, albeit faintly.

‘What the hell….’

The Night Hound’s brow furrowed slightly at a situation he had never experienced before.

The Corpse Queen, in contrast, remained nonchalant.

Her voice was steadfast, as if she had some sort of conviction.

[I can’t take off the mask].

“….”

[This was put on by contract. I can neither show my face nor reveal my name of my own volition].

“…?”

[That’s why I need you to reveal your identity].

“…!”

The Corpse Queen’s voice trembles slightly.

A voice so hoarse from crying so much, from shouting so much, from being so overwhelmed.

But the watery voice at the end resembles the voice of the past, if only for a moment.

“…No way.”

Vikir froze for a moment.

And when the Corpse Queen saw him hesitate, she shouted again.

[So show me your face! Tell me your name!]

At the same time, hot flames erupted from the Corpse Queen’s hands.

Black infernal flames, and iron skewers poking out of the center of the flames.

In the heat of the fire and the skewers, Deadpool stepped in front of Vikir and quickly raised his sword.

Baskerville’s fangs burst forth, shredding both the flames and the skewers.

And it plunged straight into the defenseless corpse queen.

…Woodduck, snap!

Another crack in her skull mask.

Soon, the bone fragments slowly scattered.

Time passed slowly.

The pieces of the mask fall apart, and the pieces of the memory fit together.

In a distant memory amidst the shards and bones, the face of a child, a young girl, rises to the surface of my subconscious.

‘No! Vikir! Please come back!’

The same voice I last heard.

A face from so long ago was here.

Chapter 214

My Neck Will Be Your Sheath (1)

◆

The Corpse Queen.

The skull mask that covered her face was pulled off.

Inside was a very familiar face, one that hadn’t changed much since she was eight years old.

Eyes as big as deer’s, always moist whenever she looked this way, dark eyebrows, a sharp nose, and plump lips.

The only thing that has changed a little is that most of the fat on the cheeks has disappeared, all the freckles on the face have disappeared, and the color combination of the black and white eyes has changed.

Camus Morgue.

She was looking at him, her expression exactly the same as the last time he had seen her in Vikir’s memory.

The face streaked with tears and snot, the expression that now refused to speak, the hoarse throat.

It was as if time had stood still since that moment when she had fought to the death against the ‘Madam Eight-Legs’ in the depth of the Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

“….”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

Why hadn’t he known before?

The original culprit. The main enemy. The Black Curtain.

He’d been running tirelessly, thinking he had to kill the demon and stop the age of destruction.

The appearance of the Ten Corpses in front of him completely excluded all thoughts and feelings.

He was only concerned with killing his enemies.

Was that why? Vikir could think of all the things he’d been missing, all the things he’d deliberately avoided thinking about.

Camus hadn’t missed a day in the years since Vikir’s disappearance.

After leaving the Light Faction of her uncle ‘Adolf Morgue’, with whom she had such a good relationship, she joined the Dark Faction of his maternal uncle ‘Snake Morgue’, with whom she had a bad relationship.

Afterward, she declared herself in a closed training and cut off all ties with the world.

Coincidentally, there was an event that occurred at this point.

A ghostly woman took the place of Snake Morgue, who was supposed to be the Corpse King. The Corpse Queen, whose identity in life was unclear.

She raised the undead Rosie Morgue, who was killed in a war between her enemies and the natives of the Black Mountains, to pamper her.

She was also in possession of the remains of Ah’Heman, who was supposed to be abandoned in the depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

In hindsight, there were many strange things about her, even when we first met her.

The Corpse Queen was strangely enraged by Ballak’s archery skills, perhaps due to the memory of losing Vikir and Rosie in quick succession.

Her flinching at the Baskerville-style sword technique at the end, and the way she grabbed Rosie from behind when she fell unconscious, were both signs.

Vikir asked, trying to remain as calm as possible.

“Why did you become the Eight Corpse, and why does your voice sound like that?”

[…It’s either because I’ve been crying for years, ever since you disappeared, or it’s completely locked up].

The Corpse Queen’s voice was even more husky than before.

How many times had she wailed, screamed, struggled, collapsed in exhaustion, passed out, woke up, and wailed again.

Her neck was already tattered.

Camus said, tears dripping from his black-and-white eyes.

[Fool… I thought you were… dead… and I was going to find your body or something…]

So you’re saying that you’ve been searching Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain depths for all these years, not missing a single day?

…That’s understandable up to a point.

However, Camus next words caused Vikir to press a hand to his forehead.

[So… I tried to bring you back to life].

Black magic. The art of bringing the dead back to life, the resuscitation of the dead.

Was that why she left the Light Faction and joined the Dark Faction?

Certainly, Snake Morgue, the leader of the Dark Faction, is a master of black magic.

Before his regression, he, too, signed a contract with the Eight Corpse Seere to reach the ultimate in black magic.

Then I remembered the testimony I had heard from Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis in Red Fang Castle.

‘If it’s Camus, she’s in closed training right now.’

‘…Closed?’

‘She split up with her Uncle Adolf.’

I was told that Camus had changed a bit since the search was stopped.

She’d lost a lot of her bubbly personality and spoke less.

Then, out of the blue, Adolf Morgue announced his withdrawal from the Light Faction, of which he was a member.

Since Camus had always followed Adolf, who was his uncle and the leader of a Light Faction, like a parent, Morgue was shocked even internally, but Adolf said that he did not express any official opinion on this.

He watched in silence as Camus defected and joined the dark facction, which stood in opposition to the light faction.

Knowing how sad Camus had been since “that night” in depth, and how much she had been beating herself up over it, he hadn’t dared to dissuade her.

“….”

Vikir frowned.

Camus, who had forsaken everything and chosen the path of the Black Mage to bring himself back from the dead and make him undead.

What had happened to the woman who, if fate had its way, would one day become the Ironblood Empress, the Invincible, and rule the world beyond Morgue?

Vikir asked in a low voice.

“So you’re saying that you made a contract with the demon because of me? Why?”

[Do you ask because you don’t know?]

“I’m asking because I don’t know. It’s said that you became the Eight Corpse to find my body and turn it into a undead.”

[… It kind of sounds like that when you say it like that].

Camus thought for a moment, then nodded in agreement. She then stated her position simply.

[If death would separate us, I wanted to be there behind it].

There was a moment of silence between them.

“….”

[….]

The Night Hound and the Corpse Queen removed their masks and faced each other’s bare faces.

It was Vikir who broke the awkward silence between them.

“…But in the end, demons must die.”

A man is a man. Life is life.

No matter how heavy an individual’s personal feelings may be, they cannot be weighed against the fate of humanity as a whole.

Eventually, the picture became clear.

A man must kill a woman to prevent the destruction of the world.

A woman who doesn’t care if the world ends as long as she can be with her man.

[….]

Camus has no answer.

Then, her lips parted.

[Okay].

Vikir’s eyes widened a little. It was a completely unexpected answer.

But to his surprise, Camus didn’t seem to mind.

[Ever since I joined forces with the demon, I knew my life wasn’t going to end well].

Camus and Vikir’s gazes locked together.

Camus took a step in front of Vikir.

Her shoulders and chest straightened.

[Now, kill me].

“….”

Vikir hesitated for a moment.

One of the Ten Corpses says she’s going to give her head, so why is he hesitating?

The faces of so many comrades-in-arms flashed through his mind.

But despite his guilt and sense of debt, Beelzebub, the magic sword at his wrist, does not move.

Finally, Camus speaks again.

[What are you doing, kill me?]

“….”

[Kill me! Kill me!]

Suddenly, her voice rises.

Kwakwang! Hududug- hududug- hududug-

Emotions and mana surged, and showers of fire and iron skewers began to rain down around them.

Tears well up in Camus’s eyes and trickle down her cheeks.

[Yeah! You obviously don’t like blackened witches like me, so you can kill me now and get it out of your life or not! Your meddlesome ex-girlfriend will die right here and now, and you can live happily ever after with your innocent bagel current girlfriend, Saintess!]

“????”

Vikir’s reaction was incomprehensible.

What was an ex-girlfriend and what was a current girlfriend? And why the name of St. Dolores?

Vikir knew there was a fatal misunderstanding, but it was hard to explain.

To add insult to injury, the demonic energy emanating from Camus seemed to be growing stronger.

The closer it got to midnight.

Camus unleashed a barrage of magic that seemed to use up every ounce of mana in her body, and then she slumped back in her spot and began to sob.

[You bastard! It’s been a while since we met, so the demon must die? Who doesn’t come from the Baskervilles? … pup! You bastard!]

“….”

Vikir stood still, unable to speak.

This was the third time he had seen tears in Camus’s eyes.

The first time when they met at age eight, then again when they were older and reunited at Red Fang Castle, and now.

All three times, Vikir has been unable to offer any comfort in response to Camus’s tears.

And as if Camus was used to it, after a while, she stopped crying on her own.

[…I know, you’re not good at comforting people].

I suspect a similar conversation took place when she lost her cousin to the Rokoko tribe.

Rosie, who was next to Camus, who still had red eyes, hugged her and comforted her.

Then.

…With a pop!

Camus pulled a tattered booklet out of her arms and threw it in Vikir’s direction.

[It’s my diary].

“….”

[Even if I disappear, read it at least once, there’s a lot of stuff I can’t say to your face].

Of course, even if Vikir answered, there would be no Camus in this world this time.

“….”

Vikir picks up the diary from the floor.

It is quite heavy for a book made entirely of paper.

It was the weight of all the time a woman had written to a man, inscribing feelings that would never be answered, that would forever remain questions.

With , Camus loosened his front cloth.

The bony armor cracked to the left and right, revealing a white neck in the middle.

[Now do it].

“….”

[You’re good. No, you’re the only one who deserves it].

“….”

[I gave up on the prize when I made my contract with the demon anyway, I might as well go to your hands].

Camus stepped in front of Vikir and knelt down silently.

She took Vikir’s right hand and brought it to the hilt of her own throat.

[My throat will be your sheath].

Camus’ lips touch Vikir’s right arm. Vikir feels a small trembling breath.

“….”

Vikir was still unable to move.

Ten demons who crossed over from the demon world to the human world. The giant gates they would later open. The age of destruction they will bring.

Before those gates open, I must kill all ten demons.

…Boom!

Vikir clenched his hands together.

Camus looked up at Vikir as if he was determined.

But why? Vikir’s hand didn’t move.

It was due to an emotion that lurked in the depths of his heart, unknown even to him.

Suddenly, Vikir’s mind was reeling with the details of Baskerville’s seventh form.

-To reach the pinnacle of the sixth level, you must let go of your emotions.

-But to open the door to the seventh, you must embrace it.

To reach the highest level of the Graduator, you must become a being of steel, with no emotions.

But to reach the next level, the highest level, Swordmaster, you must bring your emotions back to life.

Vikir has lived a life of hardened steel.

A killing machine, stripped of all emotion and driven strictly by command. A hound of death.

Throughout his life, he has loved no one and been loved by no one.

That was also proven in the Dantalian match. Aside from comradeship, there was no bond that connected Vikir to the world.

But.

But Vikir was agitated now.

The girl kneeling before him, opening her arms and chest to receive his sword.

As he looked down into the demon’s face, he could feel a faint emotion he hadn’t realized existed stirring within him.

No matter how heavy an individual’s feelings may be, they cannot be weighed against the fate of the entire human race.

…But in the face of such a heavy sense of duty, an iron heart becomes a superhuman heart.

A wall began to appear in Vikir’s vision.

The wall of the Swordmaster, the ultimate in swordsmanship – the ability to cut through anything, even a formless spirit or abstract concept – loomed large in front of him.

And at that moment.

…Pow!

Pain shot through his lower abdomen.

This sensation of something hot piercing through.

[…What?]

Camus looked dazed for a moment.

A metal skewer extended from her hand and pierced Vikir’s stomach.

At the same time.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

A black mist began to rise from Camus’s back. It was forcibly controlling her body.

[It’s midnight, little lady].

An eerie voice flows from a crack in the fog that is torn like a mouth.

.

Danger Rating : S

Size: ?

Found in: ‘Serpent’s Womb’, Deep inside the Gate of Destruction

-Nicknamed ‘Eighth Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Herds of cattle and animals shall perish.”

– The Ten Commandments 10: Top.

It was a demonic voice, tangled up in half of Camus’s consciousness.

Chapter 216

My Neck Will Be Your Sheath (3)

◆

Seere’s expression becomes wet and distorted in the dark red glow emitted by the Aura Sword.

[If you kill me, this girl will die too!]

But Vikir replies with veiled determination.

“No. Only you will die.”

At the same time, a red crescent moon rose and lodged itself in Seere’s neck.

…Blood!

Red blood dripped down.

In an instant, Seere jerked her neck back to avoid the blow.

Vikir twisted his sword at the last second, deflecting the blow.

‘…Failure.’

Vikir clicked his tongue.

He’d verbally assured himself of success, but it was a bluff.

At the last moment, Vikir hesitated to slit Camus’s neck, which saved Seere’s life.

…Boom!

Vikir gritted his teeth as he rolled across the skewered field.

Since reaching the top of the Graduator, there was little matter he couldn’t slice through.

But he still couldn’t cut through abstract things, things like souls and emotions.

Vikir’s mind flashed back to a Hugo sword strike he had once witnessed.

A blow so casually swung at the fleeing Andromalius that it split the sky into seven pieces and sliced through Andromalius’ mind, which was located somewhere on the border between matter and antimatter.

‘If I can’t reach that level, I won’t be able to separate Camus and Seere.’

For now, Camus and Seere are bound together by a contract, a bond of bad blood.

The unyielding knot is abstract and conceptual, and even the Graduator’s aura, which can cut through steel, cannot break it.

…But not so with the aura of the Swordmaster, the highest realm.

A superhuman power that surpasses even ironman. Only it can completely slice and sever the relationship between Camus and Seere.

‘With my current strength, I can only kill them both.’

It was a difficult task indeed.

Pfft.

Magic and sword intersected again.

Puff-puff-puck!

Twenty-four halberds stabbed into Vikir’s left forearm.

Seere was also struck by a sword, but this time, t was only a blow that avoided a vital area.

[Hohoho- once again, your actions don’t match your words, try being a little more impudent].

The more poisonous the words that come out of her mouth, the thicker the magic in the air.

Grrrr…

As you touch the life force exuded by Seere, you can feel the underlying emotions of Camus.

Sadness, affection, longing, resentment, anger, and fond longing.

The emotions she’s been harboring since she was eight years old, the ones she’s tried to erase and hide, the ones that keep sprouting and taking root.

It’s what she felt after Vikir disappeared, what she felt when she searched the depth day and night for him, what she felt when she thought he was dead and gave up the search, what she felt when she immersed herself in the research to bring him back, what she felt when she turned her back on her mother and uncle and became part of the Dark Hall, and what she felt when she was involved in a horrific accident that cost her half of her body and soul and made a pact with the demon….

“….”

Vikir gritted his teeth.

No matter how hard I try, I can’t do anything about it with the Graduator’s skills.

Dignity. Even if it means crying, you must be truthful.

Emotions that I thought had died out in my heart a long time ago were creeping up again.

‘Did Hugo feel this way too?’

I had heard that he, too, had lost his wife and daughter before becoming a Swordmaster, a superhuman.

It was hard to imagine what kind of emotions Hugo must have felt then, and to what extent.

Vikir first took a deep breath.

Puff, puff, puff!

Even now, the iron skewers piercing his body, burning hot as hell.

Seere burned away all of the spider traps that Madame cub had set.

She frowned at Vikir’s silent suffering.

[There’s no chance for you to win anyway. You cannot kill this girl.]

“….”

Turning to the silent Vikir, Seere made a deal.

[Alright, then we’ll make a deal.]

“…?”

Vikir’s eyes narrowed.

Seere smirked, thinking that Vikir’s demeanor had changed.

[Let’s make a deal].

Her demands were simple.

[If you release this barrier, I will leave this place, without killing anyone].

“….”

[But if you refuse this offer, you know that, right?]

Seere smiled broadly with Camus face.

[The moment all of your mana is used up, I will break this barrier and go out and kill every single child in this academy].

Seere didn’t seem to be too pleased with the current situation either.

In other words, no matter how hard you fight here, there is nothing to gain for Seere.

You have to survive to get your money’s worth, and the demon never makes a losing deal.

[If you back off, we can all live. You, me, this girl, and all the civilians at the Academy.]

Seere demanded, as if it were a given.

But.

Vikir shook his head again.

“I don’t make deals with demons.”

[What? You’re going to kill her?]

“No. I will only kill you.”

[No, this kind of wall window…… By what means?]

At Seere’s words, Vikir narrowed her eyes.

The liquid aura of the Graduator. Surely, something this fluffy can’t cut the cord of Camus’s contract with Seere.

The Swordmaster’s solid aura. Only something solid like that could cut through that invisible, formless knot.

At the same time, the thoughts that had been floating around in my head from earlier are organized.

-To reach the pinnacle of the Sixth Form, you must abandon your emotions.

-But to open the door to the seventh, you must retain your emotions.

Vikir didn’t know exactly what feelings he had for Camus now.

Before the regression, respect for a hero of the Age of Destruction.

And after returning, I became attached to my childhood friend of the same age.

‘I wonder if I would have felt the same way if I had a younger sister?’

There’s a similar, yet subtly different, feeling with his nephew, Pomeranian.

The feelings that Vikir thought he’d killed were alive and well, rooted and sprouting deep within him.

And. Vikir is just discovering that feeling.

[…Now!]

Seere’s expression suddenly changed.

The whites and blacks of Camus’s eyes instantly regained their original colors.

She cries out with tears in her eyes.

Her strength instantly pushed back Seere’s spirit and regained control of her body.

…It was only a small amount, though.

Seere protested as she was pushed backwards.

[Crazy bitch! How dare you take over my body after 12 hours! This is a breach of contract! Your soul will be destroyed!]

But Camus was still in control of her body. Despite the pain of her soul being shredded.

Focusing only on her mouth and hands, she shouted.

[Do it!]

Camus’s hands grabbed at the hard bony armor and tore it apart, exposing her neck and chest.

Soul and spirit clashing within a single body.

It was only natural that a mana surge would occur.

Seere, floating like a mist behind Camus’s body, cried out in alarm.

[The mana surge is coming again! Are you going to suffer through that again? This time you’re going to die!]

[Vikir! Come on!]

Camus cried out with her eyes tightly closed.

Now, indeed, she and her neck and chest are ready to become Vikir’s sheath.

And.

“….”

The moment he swung the red trajectory towards Camus’s neck. Vikir thought.

‘Make no mistake.’

Only one chance.

Even a veteran who had crossed so many lines of fire could not help but be drenched in sweat this time.

A split second, a terrifyingly short moment.

Vikir swung his sword with so much thought, anguish, and conflict.

During that time, the emotions he thought he had killed took root, sprouted, and eventually bore fruit.

A whirlwind of emotions that burst forth like a flood.

It violently swept away all the dryness and cracked lack that had existed.

A wall in front of me.

The wall that was so big and high that nothing seemed to be able to overcome or break down, crumbling away like a sand castle soaked in waves.

It’s almost comical how easy it was.

At the same time, unprecedented forces that had been blocked behind the wall began to surge in explosively.

“…! …! …! …!”

Power surges through my veins. A sense of exaltation, as if he had transcended humanity and become something else, something higher.

Vikir had only felt this once before.

Only once before had he felt this way, when he’d beheaded Dantalian under the blessing of Saintess Dolores.

But there was one difference: there was no saintess here now ….

There’s just a scarred hound who bared his teeth to save the girl in front of him!

Next.

The trajectory of Vikir’s sword’s tip splintered into many different paths.

The most prominent of them was the seventh tooth, larger and sharper than any of the others, a blood-red trajectory that stretched toward the Camus’s neck in front of him.

And.

The sword that cut what could be cut became a knife that could cut what could not be cut.

Sprout-

It was a supreme realm.

Chapter 217

My Neck Will Be Your Sheath (4)

◆

All humans live in the world wearing colored glasses that do not match the prescription.

Swordmasters are those who take them off.

‘Decapitation (脫鏡)’.

They are beyond the ironman and have attained the status of superhuman, able to see things that ordinary people cannot.

‘Heart Sword’.

Capable of cutting through them.

Snip-

The sword, which had reached the realm of the Supreme, sliced through the air once.

The seventh tooth cut space in half in a massive trajectory.

“…!”

Vikir felt his entire body’s mana increase like an explosion.

This wasn’t a mana surge. There was a tremendous sense of power and exaltation that washed over him.

The realization that he’d been living on the edge for so long.

A sense of liberation that made his former self feel like a worm.

Only then did Vikir understand the old Hugo.

The self he’d only discovered after losing what he held dear, and the heights he’d reached in that moment.

The Swordmaster’s overwhelming power, vision, and mindset, a realm that had long since transcended humanity.

It’s no wonder all others are considered insects or expendable.

…But Vikir was not like Hugo; he could understand him, but not empathize with him.

Hugo lost the object of his affection the moment he crossed the last wall, and Vikir regained it.

Quack, quack, quack, quack!

The sword went through first, followed by the sound about a second later.

A terrifying shockwave erupted, clearing away the surrounding black mist in an instant.

But.

…Boom!

Surprisingly, Camus, standing in the center of the storm, was unharmed.

She just fell to the ground like a marionette with a broken thread.

At the same time.

[Huh!? Shut up!?]

The scattered black mist gathered again, forming a sphere.

Seere. The one who was bound by a contract with Camus.

But just a moment ago, Vikir’s attack severed her bond with the demon.

The moment the knot of their souls was severed, Seere broke free from Camus’s body.

[No, no, no! You can broke the contract with the demon? How could you do that….]

Seere squeezed the last of her life force together and fell out of Camus’s body.

But.

Seven hound’s teeth loomed over it.

[No! I, I have a great mission to open the gate…!]

Seere argued why she should live, but it only made Vikir’s reasons for killing her all the more clear.

…Flash!

The space within the barrier split into seven pieces.

A boom like an explosion. A strike faster than a thunderbolt.

The seven black thunderbolts that accompanied the storm completely dissolved Seere’s remaining thoughts in the air.

Pagic-

Seere was gone, not a scrap of meat, not a soul.

Vikir stood and thought.

‘If only time had made Seere a little stronger, it would have been harder to deal with.’

Demons grow stronger the longer they remain.

The Eighth Corpse Seere, in particular, with its vast army of dead soldiers, was a foe that only grew more terrifying with time, and it was a tremendous blessing to have found and slain it so early.

Meanwhile.

Vikir recovered the mask and the Black Bow Anubis.

The body that has reached the level of master is noticeably different from before.

His stature had increased dramatically, and his body had become more muscular.

“….”

The flower of joy and happiness that he had dried up in order to become an Ironblooded Graduator had blossomed once again after becoming a Swordmaster.

Then.

Boom!

A bolt of black lightning streaked through the air.

“…!?”

Vikir turned his head to see Camus’s body fading away.

A magic circle glowed on the floor, centered on her unconscious body.

…Pow!

Teleportation. A technique for moving a short distance.

It was Geronto who was moving Camus’s body.

The moment the teleportation spell was activated, Vikir was troubled.

Should he reach for his sword and slit Geronto’s throat in front of him?

“….”

[….]

For a brief moment, Vikir and Geronto’s gazes locked.

“….”

But in the end, Vikir doesn’t raise his hand.

In fact, it was decided to let Camus go, whom he had reunited with after a long time.

Geronto stood still and looked up at Vikir. As if to say thank you.

Vikir released some of the barrier, and Geronto disappeared, taking Camus with her.

Pfft.

And with that, Vikir was alone in the empty barrier.

…No, he was not alone.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

The hatchling landed on Vikir’s shoulder and nuzzled his cheek.

Its eyes seemed to ask him why he would let an enemy go.

Vikir answered briefly.

“This is my younger sister who cares deeply for my older sister. There must be something going on.”

Geronto hadn’t attacked Vikir when Camus was unconscious before, only acted to protect her.

Vikir figured that this time she must have her own reasons for wanting to take her away.

“A black mage’s healing methods are different from those of a normal person. Potions and healing spells are at odds with the black mana that flows through a black mage’s body, so there must be a different treatment….”

Since the streets of the Academy appeared immediately after walking through the barrier, I had no choice but to hope that Geronto would treat Camus properly.

◆

Meanwhile.

“…The barrier is gone!”

Professor Banshee, who was reading the flow of mana around him with his eyes closed, shouted.

All of the professors and members of the Imperial Guard who had rushed over after receiving the call could not help but panic.

“Then the Night Hound!”

“And the unregistered black mages!”

“Where did they just disappear to!”

But even Professor Banshee, the most advanced mage of them all, was unable to discover where this barrier had been established or where it had disappeared to.

He could only faintly sense that it was there, but missed it.

A bead of cold sweat rolled down Professor Banshee’s face as he realized he had missed it.

“A sneaky move, indeed. A level of barrier beyond the grasp of mere humans.”

When Professor Banshee, the Academy’s newest candidate for Vice Principal, says something like that, it’s enough.

While everyone was stunned, one of them let out a high-pitched laugh.

“Ho ho ho – indeed, this is the work of the demon. So artistic, Night Hound.”

Professor Sadi. She was giggling, one eye covered by an eye patch.

Gazes around her sharpen. Professor Banshee spoke up on their behalf.

“As an imperial professor and advisor to the Imperial Guard, please refrain from saying or doing anything that seems to praise criminals. Professor Sadi.”

“Don’t say my name with that mouth, old man.”

Professor Banshee and Professor Sadi began to argue again.

Meanwhile.

The students look on in bewilderment.

As the night drew to a close and the festival cooled down, everyone sobered up from the alcohol and the atmosphere.

“What happened? Why were all the performances canceled? Why was the music turned off?”

“Didn’t they say some villains attacked?”

“Oh, no. What’s going on at the academy~”

“It’s true. That’s why all the professors have just gathered and the Imperial Guard has arrived.”

“Holy shit! The villains that attacked are the Night Hounds!”

“Crazy! Really! What’s the damage?”

“…Says there’s no damage.”

Everyone is busy shouting.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire were all chattering amongst themselves.

“Did you see that? Did you see that? That woman in the skull mask was really scary.”

“I’m ashamed to say, but I was too scared to fight her. What the hell was that?”

“Wow- I thought I was going to pass out from all the heart pounding.”

“The Night Hound was really scary too. Of all the things I’ve ever seen, that was the deadliest.”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah, I almost peed myself just hearing the voices….”

Then.

“Seriously. I was so scared I couldn’t breathe.”

A voice creeped into their conversation.

It was Vikir.

His friends hadn’t noticed his absence because they hadn’t been in a panic, so they naturally resumed their conversation.

“Vikir! Where have you been, you man! I was worried about you!”

“I was in the kitchen at the bar earlier, I’m glad you’re okay.”

“Awww, Vikir, I was so worried! I brought the professors here and looked for you first, but you weren’t there!”

“Come to think of it, where were you?”

“You went to fetch the professors too!”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire each said something as they greeted Vikir.

Then.

“…Vikir?”

There was one being who questioned Vikir.

Saint Dolores turned to Vikir with a questioning look on her face.

“I didn’t see you while I was searching these streets, where have you been all this time? With a character of your nature, you couldn’t have hidden or run away, leaving your friends behind.”

Pure curiosity in her eyes.

There was no way Vikir, who had sacrificed himself for his friends during the midterms, would have run away from this disaster alone.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire’s gazes turn to Vikir once again as Dolores raises a reasonable question.

“…That.”

Vikir hesitates a moment, about to offer an excuse.

“You commoner, you can’t just drop out of the line of defense by yourself, you almost got yourself killed!”

“You did!”

“You did!”

There were three voices that proved Vikir’s alibi.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro. They stood in front of Vikir.

“He’s a good bowman, but what are we if he gets ahead of us? Don’t go out on the fence first.”

“Don’t show off.”

“Don’t show off.”

A distraction?

The Baskervilles’ triplets squirmed as if they were trying to grab Vikir by the hair, or maybe by the scruff of the neck.

Suddenly, Vikir glared at them from an angle no one else could see.

‘Don’t overdo it’

‘….Yes.’

The triplets gave Vikir a little less attention.

After that, well, it was the same as before.

Tudor jumped in to tell them not to bother Vikir, and the Baskerville triplets jumped in at just the right time.

The professors were busy analyzing the situation.

It seemed like they wanted to find good material to write a research paper on.

“Perhaps the Night Hound can only use its powers at night, which is why it fled at first light.”

“Then it could be a vampire type of demon.”

“But who suppressed this situation in the end?”

“From the witnesses’ statements, it seems that Professor Banshee and Professor Sadi had a lot to do with it.”

“Before that… the student council president of the previous batch, Mr. Osiris Le Baskerville, who graduated from the Academy a long time ago, was here! I’m guessing he had something to do with it.”

A rush to judgment. A tacked-on conclusion. Everything was the same as before.

“….”

Vikir stood near the intersection of the end of the great event and the beginning of daily life and raised his head.

The end of dusk. Dawn is breaking in the distance.

Night passes and morning comes.

Even the darkest darkness is pushed back by the weakest light.

Vikir had proven it today, and he stood here, alive.

Standing at the end of the battlefield where he had fought for his life before he was turned back, the thrill of seeing the dawn safely upon him pounded in his heart.

…But only one thing.

‘Will she be okay.’

I was worried about the missing Camus.

Chapter 218

That Day, Him and Me (1)

◆

-About three years ago

In the great mansion of the Morgue family, whenever three or more people gathered, they told the story of the day.

Stories told through the mouths of the maids.

“Did you hear that?”

“I heard it.”

“Does anyone else know the rumor?”

“That you went into the depths of the Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain not long ago.”

“Yes, with a party of mages from Morgue and swordsmen from Baskerville.”

“And you said it was to rescue Lady Camus?”

“Well, she made it back safe and sound.”

“But why didn’t Ms. Camus come out of her room?”

“She must have been scared, after the horrors of that day.”

However, one of the maids who had gone out to do the expedition’s errands that day has a new testimony.

“…I heard it was for a different reason.”

Why Camus, after returning from the depths, locked herself in her room and didn’t come out for days.

“It’s because of love.”

“Love?”

“Yes. On that expedition, a man she’s had a crush on for a long time went missing.”

“What? You mean the one from Baskerville?”

“That’s right.”

“In the depths of the Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain… if he too had gone missing at night….”

“Yeah, he’s probably dead. What else could it be? Besides, they say there was a huge monster there.”

“It’s definitely dead.”

“I feel sorry for Ms. Camus.”

The maids were worried about her in their own way.

“Ms. Camus was always so blunt, but she was always so good to us servants.”

“She needs to eat something. She hasn’t eaten in days.”

“I don’t think she’s been sleeping, I keep hearing her crying.”

“Well, she didn’t seem to be crying today. Is she asleep?”

“No. I put my ear to the door and listened, and I could faintly hear her crying. She’s probably too hoarse to cry out loud.”

“Oh no. That’s going to change her voice forever.”

“I’m really, really worried.”

“Is this all because of the man from Baskerville?”

“I don’t know. Ms. Camus was so sweet, I wonder what she’ll do later if she’s already like this at her age.”

“That’s right, if I had Ms. Camus’s face, body, and status, I wouldn’t be tied down to a single man.”

“Really, what kind of man was he for you to fall this hard for?”

“Whatever man he was, he’s no match for our lady, eh, she’d better shake it off and get up, what’s a man to… huck!?”

The three maids gathered in the corner of the corridor and chattered.

Just then.

The last maid to open her mouth, her face turned blue.

The maids turn their heads to see what’s going on, and then they all turn the same color and shut up.

The maids’ jaws dropped, because all of a sudden, a man was standing in front of them.

A man with a long red mustache.

He was Marquis Adolf Morgue, exuding an air of authority over the maids.

The maids quickly bowed their heads.

“Im, sorry, Marquis, we were just worried about the young lady….”

“You’re right, I didn’t have any ulterior motives!”

“We were just upset….”

Normally, Adolf would have paid little attention to the maids.

But this time was different.

“Are these the same tongues that go around gossiping about the private lives of those they serve?”

Adolf snapped his fingers, and the tongues of the three maids darted out of their mouths in unison.

Aaah!

Their tongues were soon joined together at the tips.

“Uh-uh-uh-uh!”

“Ugh! Ugh!”

“Eeeeeee….”

As the tips of their tongues came together, the three maids were forced to stand in a circle, cheek to cheek.

Adolf clicked his tongue.

“The virtue of employees is to have a heavy mouth. You guys are busy using your worries as an excuse to spread gossip about your master. Its tongue is as light as a bluebird, so I tried giving it some of my weight.”

The tips of the tongues, once stuck together, would remain so for about a month.

To survive, you’ll have to lean on someone for water and mashed food.

Or have the tip of their tongues amputated.

Adolf then made his way through the corridors to Camus’s room, deep within the manor.

Before knocking on the door, Adolf listened for a moment to hear what was going on inside.

Beyond the door, it was eerily silent.

But a man of Adolf’s strength could hear.

…………….

A sob, a faint, almost muffled sob.

It was like a wail of remorse from the grave, the wail of the dead, not yet dead, but buried alive.

“…Haaaa.”

Adolf sighed heavily as he stood.

He hesitated a moment longer before knocking on the door.

Ding-ding-ding.

A light knock, in contrast to the heavy hand.

Adolf tried to keep his voice as soft as possible and opened it.

“Camus, it’s your uncle.”

He waited, but there was no answer.

With little choice, Adolf opened his mouth once more.

“I’m coming in.”

This time there was no answer.

Understanding this as permission, Adolf slowly and very carefully opened the door.

…

Adolf stepped into the room and saw a bed in the center of the dimly lit room.

The blanket was sticking out like a tomb.

Adolf sat down at the head of the bed.

A small voice came out of the blankets.

“There is nothing wrong with the maids, please break the spell.”

The words startled Adolf.

“You, your voice!”

Adolf carefully pulled back the blanket.

In the lightened darkness, he could see a grim-faced Camus lying there.

Adolf pulled back the blanket a little more.

It was as if he were removing the cloth covering a corpse.

“What’s wrong with your voice! Huh?”

Adolf demanded, and Camus closed her eyes helplessly.

Then, in a fading voice, she answered.

“It happened to Rosie, and then to Vikir, and it’s all because of me.”

Adolf was silent for a moment.

He was the type of person who couldn’t say something that wasn’t there, but that didn’t stop him from saying, ‘You’re right.’ Because you can’t say, ‘It’s because of you.’

And knowing the nature of his uncle’s character, Camus closes her eyes with a faint smile.

Anyone could see that the spark of life was dying.

Adolf was not a consoler, but his love for his nephew was great, so he tried to comfort her in this situation.

“You shouldn’t do that, Camus. Rosie and Vikir wouldn’t want that, and you shouldn’t give up like this. Don’t you realize that the weight of your life is even heavier with their share added to it?”

It is the duty of the living to live up to the dead.

Adolf spoke sincerely at this common consolation.

…But?

“!”

Camus’s closed eyes suddenly flashed open.

As if a spring had sprung, Camus sprang to her feet and looked at Adolf.

“Uncle, what did you say to me?”

“Eh, eh, It shouldn’t be like that.”

“Then!”

Camus scolds Adolf in a louder voice.

Adolf couldn’t remember what he’d just said, so after a moment’s thought, he said something similar.

“…Do we have to live up to the share of the dead?”

“Exactly!”

Camus’s cloudy eyes sparkle with light once again.

Firewood was thrown on the dying embers once more.

Camus jumped out of bed.

Her body, which hadn’t eaten or slept in a while, swayed once.

Adolf jumped to his feet and helped her up.

“Camus, what the hell is going on? What happened to you?”

In response to her uncle’s concern, Camus smiled.

It was the same smile, full of energy, curiosity, and hope.

“The living have to live with the dead, don’t they?”

“Huh?”

“That’s what your uncle just told you, that you have to live up to the dead man’s share, and that’s why you shouldn’t give up!”

“Uh-huh, that’s right.”

Adolf nodded quickly, hoping that his consolation had worked.

But Camus seemed to have come to a different conclusion than Adolf had expected.

“So if the living give back their share, the dead will come back to life, too, because they’ve gotten theirs!”

“Huh? Is that how it works?”

“Yes, because the total amount of the share is the same anyway!”

The heat radiating from Camus’s eyes was now beginning to take on a slightly strange glow.

“That’s right. The thermodynamic state function of life is the same. Magic is all about how we calculate them, and I suppose we could reverse the calculations and order a bit to get a different result, if we could access the negative dimension and pull the entropy from there… and replace the quotient from the positive dimension with the remainder in an equivalent exchange form…”

Hearing his nephew mutter, Adolf knew something was wrong.

“Camus, wait. What are you thinking…?”

But before Adolf could stop her, Camus slammed the door open and ran out.

“Food. Feed me!”

It took less than a minute for the maids, who had been keeping a close eye on Camus’s behavior, to set the table.

The Morgue’s little lord began to eat.

It was such a surprise that head of the family Raspane, who was in the middle of an important meeting dealing with the Red Fang Castle and the ruby mines, ran over to see the vassals.

Wah, wah, wah.

Camus ate her food like a madman.

Spoon and fork abandoned, she shoved food into her mouth until both cheeks were bursting.

Suddenly, something caught her eye.

It was a potato. It was a Morgue-bred variety.

‘You don’t have anything like this at home, do you?’

Suddenly, Camus’s eyes moistened.

The moisture in her body, now dried up and seemingly unable to come out, was once again escaping through her eyes.

She shoved the potatoes into her cheeks until they burst.

“…Smells like dirt. It’s not working.”

And she swallowed it whole.

Having consumed all the food on the table in one fell swoop, Camus called out to the maids.

“Give me more!”

More, please.

Raspane, pleased that her daughter had begun to eat, brought out more food.

And Camus devoured them, too.

“More!”

As much as you want.

Raspane instructed her maids again.

This time, bring enough food for Camus to eat.

…And. Camus devoured all the food that was brought to her.

“More!”

…Any amount.

Raspane set the food down, looking a little stern.

And Camus ate them.

She threw up, but she ate again.

She threw up, but she kept shoving them in her mouth.

“More!”

…Now it wasn’t enough.

Raspane tried to stop the gluttonous Camus, but she wouldn’t listen.

“More! Give me more! I have to eat more, I have to reserve my strength… yuck!”

Camus ate and vomited, ate and vomited, ate and vomited, ate and vomited, over and over again.

With tears and madness in her young eyes, neither Raspane nor Adolf could say anything.

Everyone was frozen in front of the table.

After several rounds of vomiting, when all the food on the table was in her stomach, Camus jumped to her feet.

She turned to her lord, Raspane, her eyes shining.

“Give me Morgue’s military authority. Let me search the forest.”

Chapter 222

That Day, Him and Me (5)

◆

The one who knocks on the door is just a visitor, nothing more.

It was December. On the floor where dying embers burned shadows.

I desperately wanted tomorrow to come and tried to forget his death and the sadness that came from it by reading books.

The man who would forever be nameless in this place.

I left the door wide open for any visitors who might be standing outside.

There was nothing there but darkness, nothing.

I stared into that darkness for a long time. Puzzling, fearing, doubting, and dreaming dreams no one had ever dared to dream.

I whispered, “Vikir!” and only the words came back as an echo, “Vikir!”

Only these words, nothing else.

As I closed the door, every soul in me on fire, I heard a knock, loud and clear.

Just the wind, nothing.

I opened the door, and a raven, flapping its wings in a loud flutter, puddleduck! I stepped inside.

Up, perched, and that was it.

I smiled sadly and spoke to the solemn bird.

Its head is shorn and naked, but it is not a coward. Tell me your old and noble name, dreadful raven that wanders the dark shores.

And the crow said, “Nevermore.”

I spoke again.

Prophet, wicked one! Tell me, whether in life or in death I shall ever meet again that noble and radiant man whom the gods have named Vikir!

And the crow said, “Nevermore.”

I was enraged.

That fiend must go back. To the netherworld of night. Without leaving behind a single black feather, the mark of a liar.

And the crow said, “Nevermore.”

So the crow never flew, but sat still, still, still.

Its eyes are like the eyes of a demon dreaming fiendishly, and the light of the lantern beneath it casts evil shadows.

There is no escape for my soul from those shadows cast upon the floor…

…For ever.

-Camus Morgue from 『The Raven, Diary of a December』-

*Quote from Edgar Allan Poe’s “The Jackdaw”

◆

Camus closed the diary.

Tucking the journal that contained all her memories under her arm, she set out for the city.

Her destination was the most famous place in the entire Imperial Capital, the Colosseo Academy.

The Academy’s gates were wide open for the Halloween festival, which allowed outsiders to enter.

The gates of the Colosseo are so high that you have to raise your chin as high as you can to see through them.

The enormous crowd inside, the lights.

For a moment, Camus followed their movements with wistful eyes.

‘If I had lived a normal life, would I be here now?’

Good men and women her own age, or perhaps slightly older, bustled about.

Men and women, arm in arm, holding hands, or on the verge of holding hands, were building or decorating booths, doing business, or just enjoying themselves as guests.

If Camus had grown up normally, she would have been the prodigy of her family by now, growing up to be beautiful, and gaining early admission to the Academy.

She would have cried and laughed with her classmates, created a festival bar, peddled her wares in the streets, and cooked in the kitchen.

And her cousin Rosie, who probably entered the academy with her or a year or two later, would be smiling shyly next to her.

Also next to her, ….

“‘He’ is a good at cooking, so he probably cooked in the kitchen, and then I would take it and serve it to the guests. …No, he’s handsome, so I’d have to ask him out, and I’d have a hard time because there would be a lot of girls clinging to him. But then again, I wasn’t the kind of girl who could get away with anything.”

Camus smiled bitterly.

Beside her, Rosie, who had become Lich, nodded.

Then.

Turning an alley, Camus stopped short at a large mirror in the street.

She wore a raggedy cloak and a ghoulish skull mask.

Her reflection was a ghastly sight, no match for the pretty schoolgirls crying, laughing, and enjoying themselves at the festival.

“….”

Camus looked away from the mirror for a moment.

Boom.

The moment she looked away, the mirror shattered into hundreds of pieces.

A life of normal birth, normal growth, normal entrance into a good school, normal rise to a high position, normal relationship with a good man, normal marriage, normal children, normal growing old, normal closing her eyes in the love and respect of everyone.

You can’t expect that kind of life anymore.

The life of the gossipy girls at the academy is now a completely different story. A life that would never apply to her.

Camus thought so.

And then.

Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow.

At the night market that night, amidst the fireworks and cherry blossoms. Camus met the love of her life.

The one she’d been hoping for. The face she’d never seen, not even in her dreams.

Vikir. Vikir Van Baskerville.

He was at the school festival bar.

“…! …! …!”

Camus doubted her eyes.

But no matter how hard she squinted, that face definitely belonged to Vikir.

“…He, did he have a sister?”

No way.

I had researched my potential husband’s family history.

There are no women in his family. No daughters are born.

Daughters have been scarce in this family ever since the disappearance of their only daughter, Penelope, a long time ago, as if a curse had been placed on them.

Camus walked forward as if mesmerized.

She was about to meet the girl. Or at least get a clue.

Her faint hopes were becoming concrete certainties, pointing the way forward.

Just then, she approached a festival bar with a sign that read, “Newspaper Department Ryukeion.”

[…Who are you, hanging out at someone else’s place of business?]

A familiar outfit. The Night Hound stops me in my tracks. Only this time, it was someone else.

You again.

Camus was furious.

The clues she’d barely gotten, the hopes she’d barely gotten, kept getting in the way.

She had come here to see the man she had loved for so long, and she was prepared to stop at nothing.

“Get out of the way.”

There would be no second mercy.

◆

And now time has passed again.

…Paat!

Geronto brought the crippled Camus back to the lair and healed her using the Life Vessel.

Despite the massive amount of Highly Concentrated Mana Potion flowing into her body, she barely recovered.

However.

“…Puha! I almost missed it for real this time.”

She barely managed to cling to her consciousness after being sent to death’s door and back.

As soon as she woke up, she checked her body.

“My body has become a rag. But whatever, it doesn’t matter. As long as you have time, you can treat anything.”

More importantly, Vikir was alive.

“…Yes. He was alive. That’s why I couldn’t meet him. Stupid, why did I think he was dead?”

I can’t stop laughing, even through my bloodied, battered body. I can’t stop the corners of my mouth from turning up.

“And then I checked his heart at the end, and he couldn’t kill me after all, because he has a heart!”

Camus can’t fully fathom Vikir’s mind, but Camus can intuit that Vikir crossed a threshold when he was torn between killing her and not killing her.

It was at that point that Camus took another look at her body.

Most of the wounds on her body were the result of Seere’s rampage, and none of Vikir’s wounds were on her limbs.

None of them were fatal, and even those were healing quickly.

Camus looked at Rosie beside her.

“Didn’t Vikir try to kill me at the end, when I was running away?”

Nodded.

Suddenly, Rosie’s memory came back to Camus.

“…It worked.”

Camus smiles wryly.

When she had first met Vikir as a Night Hound, she could have killed him, but a strange intuition had kept her from doing so.

It was the same with Vikir.

He let the unconscious Camus go, which meant he trusted her and Rosie.

The possibility that Camus could not only come back to life on her own, but that she could eventually break free of the demon’s grip.

“…So then, how should we live up to my husband’s expectations?”

Camus’s eyes suddenly calmed down.

With her eyes closed, she could see into the depths of her mind, into the abyss.

There was a high, steep cliff.

A peak jutted out from the edge of the cliff, and there was someone clinging to the edge.

[Ouch! Help! Somebody help me!].

It was Seere.

Her connection to Camus had been severed by Vikir, and she was pushed to the very bottom of her consciousness.

She was reduced to the size of an infant.

Camus had regained nearly 99.99% control of her body, and the parts of her body that had been rendered half-dead were fully restored thanks to Seere’s efforts to repair the damage.

Most of Seere’s consciousness had been extinguished by Vikir, so very little of Seere’s consciousness remained in Camus’s mind.

In terms of juice, it was about the amount of juice that would remain on the surface of a glass after it had been poured into it and drained.

It would be an exaggeration to say there was none.

Camus asked.

“Why aren’t you completely annihilated?”

[That’s because… you broke the 12 hour contract, and that penalty kept me alive a little bit].

During the fight with Vikir, Camus had violated Seere’s privileges.

As a result, Seere is currently acting with a little bit of life in her body.

“Hmph~”

Camus stood on the cliff and stroked her chin.

Then the sulking Seere grabbed onto Camus’s toes and begged.

[Please, please don’t let me go, after all we’ve been through together!]

She did. Camus spoke in a cold tone.

“A fearless brat who relied on her talent and her will.”

[…E?]

“Hohoho-there’s a guy you really want to meet again? What kind of fool risks her life for that?”

[Uh, uhhh……]

“If I had a face like this and a body like this, I would never have lived like that, I’d have gotten stronger by beating young males and draining his blood. Ah, life is really difficult in this world.”

[Hic!]

The things Camus was saying now were the same lines she had said to Vikir when Seere was in 100% control of her body.

Seere swallowed hard.

Camus spoke to her in a cold voice.

“Listen, don’t judge people by your standards. He’s not one of those fishy males, he’s the real deal. Do you understand?”

[Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!]

“Yeah. He’s a man worth risking your life for.”

Camus regained full control of her body.

Seere’s insignificant share, at best, would be enough to make her itch like a mosquito bite for about a second, once a day.

Camus. She was once again the master of her own life.

A master who has complete control over her body and soul. The queen of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

“Get down.”

In her consciousness, her command is absolute.

Seere cried out in her diminished form.

[…Hiing].

And just like that, Seere had surrendered all of her power and strength to Camus.

It was the moment when a bilateral contract turned into a one-sided master-servant relationship.

The black mage gained demonic powers.

Camus smirked as she held the ever-smaller Seere on her fingertips.

“Your prophecy was correct, for you did lead me to him after all.”

Vikir had come to Camus in the course of a demon hunter’s search for a demon, but the prophecy had been fulfilled anyway.

Climbing gingerly onto Camus’s finger, Seere looked up and asked.

[Hey, what are we going to do now?]

“Well. Should we open the gate?”

[Zee, seriously!? Are you really going to do that?]

“You’re kidding. Am I crazy?”

Seere visibly frowns at Camus’s words.

Camus smiles brightly.

“The world can’t end now. As long as he’s alive and I am alive.”

[…So what are you going to do now?]

“I’m going to heal my broken body for a while. Someone’s been messing with it.”

[Meh, sorry, I didn’t mean to do that….]

Under Camus’s gaze, Seere completely shrank.

She was sweating so profusely that it was like looking at a piece of butter thrown onto a hot pan.

Camus was really starting to think about what to do next.

“There are many things I need to prepare to be a good bride, and I’ll start one by one as I recover.”

[Bri, bride? Get married?]

“Then I have to do it. After all this trouble, what if I meet him again and he’s already gone?”

[You love him that much?]

Seere asked in disbelief, and Camus nodded emphatically.

“Yes. I love him so much.”

So much so that I want to be next to him, even if he’s dead.

Or that she wanted to be next to him even if she was dead.

A man who has to kill a woman to prevent the end of the world. And a woman who doesn’t care if the world ends as long as she can be with him.

In the end, they come to a dramatic conclusion. One where no one has to be unhappy, and everyone can be happy.

“For now, I must return to Morgue. Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, those thundering sisters, must be thrilled that I’m gone. I must go get them back in line.”

I can already see how happy my sisters will be to see me.

Only then was Camus able to smile with a playful smile appropriate for his age.

“I’ll say hi to my mom, and visit my uncle… and again.”

Suddenly, her expression grew heavy.

Snake Morgue.

She had to announce his death to the world.

What a noble and holy sacrifice he had made, and he needed to be given a funeral worthy of it.

“First and foremost, it is imperative that I carry on my master’s work.”

It was necessary to take full control of the Dark Hall, which had fallen into disarray during Snake’s long absence.

Representative. Camus had formed the idea in her mind that she would succeed her master as head of the Dark Hall.

The death of Snake, who had ruled the Dark Hall for decades, would trigger another election of Representative and a nasty power struggle.

Into the mix would come Camus, who has been in hiding for the past few years due to her training.

Once again, she is a black mage with demonic powers.

A being who has fully absorbed the power of Seere, the Great Demon King of Bones and Corpses, who can kill livestock and bring them back to life.

“Once I’ve completely conquered the Dark Hall, I’ll become a Representative and rise to the same rank as Uncle Adolf.”

It would be quite a task, but Camus was confident.

In fact, no matter what I do, it will be much easier than bringing the dead back to life.

And then again….

Camus looked up.

In the distance, far, far away, she could see the night sky of the Imperial Capital.

The place with the sharp spire and high walls is the ‘Colosseo Academy.’

Finally, Camus’s mouth opened.

“When I get in, I’ll be in class 21.”

A junior one grade lower.

But she was confident nonetheless.

“The day I come back, I’ll be….”

Camus’s eyes glowed black.

She looked to Vikir in the distance, her voice full of confidence.

“You are mine.”

It was a possessive desire so strong that even the Demon King Seere shivered for a moment.

Chapter 223

Tuition (1)

◆

The Festival is over.

But even after the festival was over, the excitement remained like a residual fire, making the students feel strangely excited.

The students were still talking about the events of the festival whenever they got together in groups of three or more.

“Did you hear, he’s dating that girl in Hot Class A and she’s dating that girl in Cold Class B.”

“Wow, I was wondering when they were going to get together. I guess it’s finally happening.”

“They confessed during the fireworks at night during the festival. Wow.”

“Huh? That new couple in Hot Class B broke up that day?”

“Huh! The chicken CC broke up? That’s a bit of a shock.”

“The moment someone gets together, someone breaks up… Youth is a strange thing.”

Everyone is talking about who confessed to whom, who flirted with whom, who fell in love with whom, who fought with whom, who broke up with whom, and… love play is the hottest topic because it is a place where teenagers and 20s gather.

In addition, rumors of who got drunk, fought, threw up, lied, or took a leave of absence were slowly spreading.

…But the hottest topic was this.

“By the way, is it true that the Night Hound came to the Academy during the festival?”

“Uh-huh. They said he tried to come back and terrorize us again. Creepy.”

“But the professors stopped him!”

“That’s really scary. What’s with the Imperial Guard? They don’t take down villains like that fast enough.”

“That’s right. He should be in the ‘Nouvelle Vague’ prison, for a villain like that.”

“But from what I’ve seen, the Night Hound is really, really strong.”

“And I hear there’s a new villain on the scene this time, an unregistered black mage?”

“But I heard they fought two of them, which is why the professors were easily dispatched.”

“Too bad. It would have been better if we could have arrested them.”

Students who don’t know anything about it just talk about it in a cheerful tone.

The “Night Hound Incident,” which could have turned into a horrific disaster in the wrong hands, seems to have faded into nothing more than spooky gossip.

….

…But here’s one student who can’t let it pass as urban legend.

“Guys.”

Dolores, the student council president, shouted, throwing open the door to the newspaper department.

“Who wrote this article!”

She asked, sounding more than a little annoyed.

In Dolores’s hand was a copy of an article that had not yet been published.

[Exclusive] The Night Hound, on its viciousness…

-The Night Hound’s misdeeds have crossed the line. On the 0th of last month, the Night Hound attacked the Academy, which could be said to be the future of the Empire…… The young sprouts who will be responsible for the future of the empire must be protected…… The actions aimed at this are inhumane and anti-national…… He is a villain who must be punished…… Meanwhile, the number of major facilities in the Imperial Capital destroyed by the Night Hounds during the festival was the Imperial Imperial Bank, the Imperial Clock Tower, Indulgentia Orphanage, Imperial Cemetery, etc…

A scathing article condemning the Night Hounds.

Dolores swallowed hard at her anger.

“The Night Hound didn’t come to the festival and cause any disturbances, the disturbances were caused by that mysterious black mage. This article makes it sound as if the Night Hound came to the festival and massacred the students. He’s a criminal as defined by the Empire, but at least he didn’t do anything at the festival that day, so you should take the emotion out of your article and just list the facts… After that, never mind. So who wrote this article?”

The entire newspaper staff, including Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and others, were silent.

But they were all honest about their eye contact.

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

All eyes were on the same place.

That was where Vikir was.

Dolores sighed.

“Vikir. It’s you again.”

A child who consistently writes articles criticizing the Night Hounds as to why anyone would hold a grudge against it.

There’s nothing wrong with criticizing a criminal the Empire has declared evil.

Vikir simply replies in his characteristically emotionless tone.

“The article was written under the direction of my club advisor, Professor Banshee.”

“Then why did you write it when I wasn’t around…”

“Ms. Dolores, weren’t you busy with student council affairs throughout the festival season, and I just happened to have the time during that period to write an article in the direction of my advisor, Professor Banshee.”

In a way, he had a point.

Dolores sighed softly.

“It’s official from the Imperial Guard this morning: it’s not the Night Hound who’s been responsible for the recent raids on the festivals and the destruction of the city’s major facilities.”

Eyes widened at the words.

Dolores continued.

“According to the captain of the guard, the Night Hound’s primary weapon is a knife. However, there are very few stab wounds at recent terrorist sites, but….”

Dolores showed me some mana screenshots.

Ruined clock towers, banks, and mansions.

All that remained were marks, as if a giant snake had crawled across them.

“…These are not marks that can be made with a knife, so the culprit is a different villain altogether.”

The Imperial Guard had identified a villain other than the Night Hound.

It was named “Ms. Ouroboros,” a vicious terrorist of unknown purpose.

“Female, presumed gender, unknown purpose of attack, unknown motive, but generally believed to be Graduator class. We don’t even know what weapon she’s using, because all the witnesses are dead.”

The entire class shuddered slightly at the introduction of a new villain.

If you were a Graduator, you could expect to be favored wherever you traveled in the Empire. They were the pinnacle of martial arts.

If such an existence had an evil heart and committed an act of terrorism against an unspecified number of people, how great would the repercussions be?

I can’t even imagine the amount of blood that would be shed.

The Night Hound, an unregistered black mage, and now Ms. Ouroboros.

With three fearsome villains on the loose, the people of the Imperial Capital must not be able to sleep at night.

Dolores was adamant about this fact.

“So, in the future, don’t blame all evil deeds on the Night Hounds alone. I’m not taking sides, I’m just presenting the facts. There are three villains, shouldn’t there be a clear distinction between the crimes committed by each?”

Everyone nodded at her words. There was nothing wrong with that.

Vikir nodded as well.

‘…It doesn’t really matter.’

Vikir’s criticism of the Night Hound was based on the fact that he might one day find himself in a situation where he was suspected of being a Night Hound.

And if he did, it would be easier to avoid suspicion if he maintained his long-standing criticism of the Night Hound.

Meanwhile.

While Vikir was distracted, the conversation among the newspaper staff took a different turn.

“What is this ‘Ms. Ouroboros’ villain, anyway?”

“We don’t know what she looks like, what her primary weapon is, or what her purpose is.”

“The only thing we do know is that it leaves tracks that look like a giant snake crawled across it.”

“The other thing is that it seems to follow the places where the Night Hound has been spotted.”

“Certainly, judging by the route it took, it seems to want to meet the Night Hound. Is there a grudge?”

“But she’s not coming to the Academy? That’s where the Night Hound was last seen.”

“Ugh, I hope not. If nothing else, it’s made the professors more vigilant, so I’m sure she won’t come now.”

“…How did they know it was a woman?”

“They found high-heeled boot prints around the area. There were also lipstick marks on an abandoned vodka bottle.”

“Is it possible that it’s just a guy who enjoys high heels and lipstick?”

“Of course it’s possible. It’s not uncommon these days.”

Ms. Ouroboros. A mysterious terrorist bent on sabotaging the Empire’s major infrastructure.

Vikir was already aware of her existence, thanks to the information Cindywendy had given him.

‘She’s after me.’

Why would she be chasing the Night Hound?

Whether it was out of admiration, resentment, or curiosity, Vikir didn’t care.

As long as she didn’t get in the way of the demon hunt.

It could be said that I am more interested in the fingers and knitting needles that are currently moving diligently.

Meanwhile.

Sinclaire, next to him, admired Vikir’s knitting.

“Wow, you’re really good at knitting, aren’t you?”

No wonder. After all, no one wants to keep a torn combat uniform from a war.

Vikir felt the need to make the masks even stronger after this incident, so he was in the process of re-crafting the masks, cloaks, and robes from the Cerberus pelts he had captured so long ago.

I’m using only the toughest, strongest parts of Cerberus’ hide, so they won’t tear again.

Of course, what he was sewing now were the useless scraps of Cerberus’ hides.

Vikir was gathering these pieces and making a scarf.

“I’ve made a scarf as a test, but I don’t need it. Do you want it?”

Vikir held out a scarf made of Cerberus’ hide to his friends.

It was highly resistant to fire and poison.

But Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire don’t recognize the wonders of the hide, and they all shake their heads.

“Ugh. What is that. It’s crusty and smelly.”

“I don’t like the smell.”

“It’s also really heavy.”

“No one should be wearing that!”

“Brother, … this is not cool.”

Then Vikir nodded.

“I know. It’s kind of hard to eat.”

????

Question marks appeared over the heads of the friends, one for each of them.

Sinclaire stammered.

“Brother, did you eat this?”

Vikir remained silent, only nodding slightly.

An age of destruction, a desperate fight for survival, when you had to eat anything to stay alive.

‘…The battle to the death at Tochka Fortress back then was so desperate.’

During the Battle of Tochka, when we were surrounded in deep trenches and had to survive for days on end.

There was nothing to eat, so I had to boil and chew my leather army boots, and that’s when I first got to know the taste of Cerberus’ hide.

“It tasted like rotten fish dried in the strong sunlight and dipped in spoiled milk.”

Hearing Vikir’s statement, all of his friends silently covered their mouths with their hands.

Just then.

“Hey, Vikir, there’s a letter for you!”

One of the seniors waves at Vikir from the window.

A letter was placed in an envelope and handed to Vikir.

It was not only for Vikir, but also for Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire.

“Is this …?”

Vikir tore open the envelope and pulled out what was inside.

The writing read

<First semester tuition payment notice

-Name: Vikir

-University: Colosseo

-Faculty: Cold Warrior

-Department: Archery Department

-Class: Class B

-School number: 20

-Year: 1

-Semester: 1

-Classification: Tuition (A)

-Tuition fee: … G

.

.

It was something that some students would pass over without thinking about, but for others, it would be a terrifying reminder.

Chapter 224

Tuition (2)

◆

It’s tuition season at Colosseo Academy.

“Hey. Did you pay your tuition?”

“Tuition? Is there such a thing at our school?”

“I think I paid it yesterday when the butler came by.”

“I seem to remember paying for four years at once when I got in.”

“How am I supposed to study when I have to worry about that?”

Most of the time, this season passes without even knowing if it’s coming or going, but….

“What can I do. My father couldn’t find money for tuition this semester.”

“ …Should I take a break from school?”

“Haa, this isn’t a part-time job.”

“Am I going to have to worry about this for all four years?”

For some students, anxiety was written all over their faces.

The academy’s tuition is so significant that it can be a burden not only for commoners but also for nobles if their families are small.

Even at Colosseo Academy, where admission is as difficult as picking a star in the sky, it’s a bitter reality that there are always a few students who take a break or drop out at this time of year.

That’s why Vikir is now thinking.

‘I guess I didn’t get a full scholarship after all.’

His attitude score was so bad that he didn’t get a full scholarship.

However, about 80% of the scholarships were merit-based, so the amount of money wasn’t too much to ask for.

This was made possible by an unexpected and unasked-for letter of recommendation from Professor Banshee.

‘…Hung. I don’t know.’

When Vikir went to thank him, Professor Banshee didn’t even look up from his book, just snorted.

Whatever.

‘But even so, since I decided not to get help from the Baskervilles or Cindywendy, I’m still going to have to find the money for tuition.’

The reason Vikir hadn’t insisted on bringing in outside money was simple.

The demons would track it back. It is to prevent that.

In order to raise military funds, you must decide on a method of money transaction, the most popular being a borrowed-name account or cash hiding.

Vikir has seen too many hunting dogs lose their lives due to being traced back by the enemy or betrayed by intermediary contacts in the process of raising military funds.

“Unless it’s absolutely necessary, it’s best to keep your contacts to a minimum, especially those funding streams that can be stepped on first.”

The best way to hide something is to make sure it doesn’t exist in the first place.

So Vikir had no financial contact with either Baskerville or Cindywendy.

In case one day he really needed the “big bucks”.

“Professor Banshee wrote me a letter of recommendation for a scholarship, so I’ll just have to make up the rest.”

Vikir muttered as he fiddled with his tuition bill.

Essentially, the most optimal way to raise military funds is to raise military funds directly in the field.

“I need to look for a high-paying, short-term part-time job.”

Vikir stepped into the central lobby of the lecture hall.

On the walls of the plaza on the first floor, there were numerous posters, some of which were obviously looking for part-time jobs.

High school students were already gathered in front of the bulletin board looking for part-time jobs.

Then.

Vikir spotted a familiar face.

Sinclaire, a white-haired girl.

She was staring at the advertisements on the board.

“Hmm. There’s a month and a half until tuition is due…… Should I increase my part-time job? What I’m doing right now is tutoring, part-time work at a cafe, and librarianship…… Should I take another tutoring class when I have some free time on the weekend? No, that doesn’t mean I can reduce my volunteer work hours.”

Sinclaire is one of the highest-performing first-year students in the Hot Class. She works a part-time job to make time for her studies.

…And she’s also taking a few classes!

She’s even volunteering, which makes other students think she’s a freak.

But Vikir was also going above and beyond, even if it wasn’t visible.

Every night, he goes out and assassinates people who will be enemies of the Human Coalition in the future.

But assassinations cost money, and it doesn’t make money.

Furthermore, Vikir has a nasty habit of collecting all of his targets’ ill-gotten gains and secretly dropping them off at orphanages and other institutions.

He had been doing this ever since he met and separated from Nymphet before Dantalian.

As such, there was very little wealth in Vikir’s possession at the moment. At best, enough to buy supplies for next week’s class?

He would have to find a part-time job anyway.

“….”

Vikir stood a little distance away so as not to disturb Sinclaire.

He read through the numerous flyers that covered the bulletin board, one by one.

“What a bunch of crap.”

Ignoring most of the advertisements, Vikir continued to scan the board until he found a short-term job that seemed perfect for him.

It was a part-time job that involved killing monsters with bounties on them and selling their byproducts.

This type of part-time work is usually done through hunting guilds or mercenary guilds, and you can go to the guilds and give or receive requests, or even ask them to dispatch workers if you want.

Depending on the nature, type, and power of the guild, you could hire warriors, mages, and other mercenaries, as well as hunters, alchemists, cooks, blacksmiths, and other supportive professions, and even guides and porters.

A structure in which you can become a client, carry out someone else’s request, hire a separate mercenary, or become a mercenary yourself.

In other words, a guild is basically a large form of labor.

Of course, it is a bit unusual that the price is clearly defined in the form of ‘money’.

The students of the Colosseo Academy are generally skilled enough to be employed by various mercenaries. The hunting guilds welcomed them, but the academy students didn’t have to work with them.

Unless, like Vikir, they needed a quick paycheck.

◆

When Vikir returned to his dormitory after all his errands, he found Tudor and Sancho in his room.

They were tutoring Pigi in a subject he was lacking in.

“So, here’s a reminder of the administrative definition of settlement: a fiscal year’s income and expenditures are summarized in definitive coefficients… and the imperial family must submit an Imperial Settlement Report to the Senate, which is inspected by the Auditor General… and the head of each of the Seven Great Houses prepares a settlement report of their funds for each fiscal year, which is consolidated into the Central Office Settlement Report….”

“Hmmm. I’ll never get used to administration.”

“I think information science is more difficult. I guess I’m not cut out for a desk job.”

Tudor and Sancho were impressed with Pigi’s administrative, clerical, and information analysis and synthesis skills.

What’s more, Pigi is a good teacher, able to explain the professor’s words in a way that would have been incomprehensible to a cancer patient.

So Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi put their heads together and focused on their studies.

It was a win-win situation, with each of them helping the other in practical and written work.

Vikir walked into the room.

“Sorry to interrupt your study, guys. I’ll just grab my coat and head out.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi turned their heads in delight.

“Oh, Vikir, you’re just in time! You’re a good student too, aren’t you? Help us out! This time, please, we need to beat Bianca and that little bastard…!”

“Come on Vikir, I need to avoid failing next week’s written exam right now! I want to break the stereotype that I’m just a big guy and not smart…!”

“I have a lot of issues I’d like to discuss with you, Vikir! Just last week’s note test alone, we had a multiple choice controversy on the last multiple choice question…!”

But Vikir shook his head firmly.

Right now, he was more concerned about paying his tuition than next week’s quiz.

“I have to go out to earn money.”

Vikir briefly explained his situation, and his friends looked stunned.

Tudor stroked his chin.

“I thought you were so good at school and so skilled that you must be the scion of a noble family with a hidden identity, or that your parents were commoners but with great wealth. If you’re so desperate for tuition, I’ll pay it for you, my friend! What’s wrong with being a friend? We have plenty of money!”

Of course, Vikir declined. It was a matter of money.

The last thing he needed was to get his tail stepped on by the demon, only to have Tudor spark a firestorm.

Vikir shook his head, and Tudor gave him a disapproving look.

“What? Why? If you can’t afford it, you can pay it back slowly! Maybe they’ll ask you to join our family after graduation? If that’s the case, you don’t have to worry about it. You know I’m not a formal person like that! Well, my sister’s been begging me to bring you home for a visit during vacation so she can introduce you, but it’s not about that!”

Sancho and Pigi explained Vikir’s situation to Tudor.

“We’ve been taught that it’s not good for money to go directly between friends, no matter how close, because it’s a matter of pride.”

“That’s true, Tudor. I’m sure Vikir would really appreciate your thoughtfulness.”

The normally reticent Vikir nodded once in Tudor’s direction, and suddenly Tudor’s expression brightened again.

“So. How are you going to come up with the money? We can mock it up together, is that okay?”

“Uhm. I have an idea.”

Tudor’s ears perked up at Vikir’s answer, as did Sancho and Pigi.

To his grateful friends, Vikir asked briefly.

“Do you know of a hunting guild that is good for short runs?”

Chapter 229

Tuition (7)

◆

“Vi, Mr. Vikir. That woman… is probably ‘the one’.”

MiniPin, a skilled Graduator, was trembling slightly. This indicates that his senses are just as sensitive and sharp.

Skilled people recognize skilled people. The higher the level of skill, the greater the understanding.

“….”

Vikir’s brow furrowed as he looked at the woman in front of him.

‘Ms. Ouroboros.’

A villain who, despite the onslaught of the Imperial Guard, a group that includes some of the most powerful people in the world, has never been able to reveal her identity.

The number of major facilities she has destroyed within the Imperial Capital is nearly triple digits.

But despite this, no one knows who she is. Not even her powers, skills, or primary weapon.

That’s because all the witnesses are either dead or insane.

“…Well, at least one guess was right: it’s a woman.”

Vikir’s spirits lifted as he realized he had a formidable opponent.

Ms. Ouroboros had a rather unique appearance.

A helmet with two large snake scales sprouting from it like horns, and a mask with eyes twisted and torn like a lightning bolt.

She was covered in glossy black tights and wrapped in a long cloak and scarf.

Her unusually high heels made her already tall figure appear even taller.

In her hand, she held a long whip, which might explain the snake-like marks on her skin.

[Hohohoho- rats crawled into my piggy bank?]

A modulated, high-pitched voice came through the wind holes in the mask’s mouth.

Landing on the ground, Ms. Ouroboros lifted her masked face to look at Vikir.

Moment.

[…!]

Miss Urovoros flinched slightly at the sight of Vikir’s face.

“…?”

Vikir squinted.

Because Ms. Ouroboros had changed the momentum she was exuding from the moment their eyes met.

Koo-koo-koo-koo…

The frightening force began to crush the nearby dozen meters.

[Children who touch other people’s piggy banks should be punished, right?]

At the same time, a whip flew out.

Jaag- peog!

The whip, which sprouted thorns like a rose vine, crushed the hard rock floor with ease.

It was like hitting soft tofu with a club.

‘The aura is dense. At least a Graduator, maybe more.’

Vikir marveled at Ms. Ouroboros’ unexpected helplessness.

Her aura is like boiling asphalt, and if she were to join the Imperial Army, she’d be a high-ranking officer in no time.

If he had not reached Master level due to his match with Camus recently, Vikir might have also reached a tight tie.

‘I’ve never pushed my power to its limits since becoming a Swordmaster, so maybe this is a good opportunity.’

But now that he’s shown his face, he’s Vikir, a first-year academy student.

Even if he was in Night Hound mode, he couldn’t fight with his face exposed like this, let alone against one of the most dangerous people in the Empire.

Just then, I heard MiniPin call out in a small voice.

“Boss. There’s a government office just down the road from here, and it’s Imperial Guard patrol time.”

It’s refreshing to see a man who doesn’t just run off on his own, but sticks by his client to the end.

Vikir nodded at MiniPin’s advice and stepped back.

Right then.

[Where are you going to get out?]

Ms. Ouroboros’s whip flashed again.

“…!”

Vikir quickly twisted his head outward.

Snap!

A sharp gust of wind hits Vikir’s left cheek. A vicious snake had once again sliced through the trees beside them.

Ms. Ouroboros’s whip had an awl-like tip that could pierce like a spear or slash like a sword.

Even if you dodged the pointed end, the slashing sides curved long and hard, making it very annoying.

Even the thorns that sprouted from the whip seemed to be coated with a strong poison.

“Hmph. I guess it won’t be easy to run away.”

Vikir grimaced and continued to back away.

Ms. Ouroboros’s momentum grew more and more vicious as Vikir dodged her whip’s tightening points by flying up and down a few times.

[Ho, look at that, you had me believing, you’ve been hiding your skills, you devious thing].

Ms. Ouroboros’ whip aura grew larger and larger.

Clap-clap-kwakwakwauk!

Ms. Ouroboros’s power was like a one-man army, shattering everything in its path.

The aura-loaded whip spun in an infinite trajectory, like a serpent, and soon formed a sphere around Ms. Ouroboros’ body.

Trapped!

Everything that touches the aura sphere is torn apart and shattered.

…Terrible!

Except for one.

[…!?]

Ms. Ouroboros was puzzled to see her whip suddenly snap in midair and bounce away.

A whip is basically an unstable weapon, a terrifying device that can harm even its owner if it loses control.

Poof!

Ms. Ouroboros’s whip crashed into nothingness and spun in circles.

Ms. Ouroboros was nearly struck by her own whip.

[What is this?]

She shook her head in confusion.

But Vikir quietly brushes his left cuff.

“You did well. But next time, don’t do it. It’s dangerous.”

[Hack-hack-hiss-]

On top of Vikir’s wrist, the cub was snorting with an angry expression.

The area around Ms. Ouroboros was now dotted with transparent wires that the cub had put up.

At the same time, the cub began to emit a dark poisonous aura, blocking Ms. Ouroboros’ vision.

[What the hell! Why is there such an unpleasant fog all of a sudden…]

Ms. Ouroboros waved her hand in front of her eyes in annoyance.

“Boss, now!”

To his surprise, MiniPin raised his sword.

He summoned all his strength, imbued the sword with aura, and slashed with all his might.

Even so, the blow was so powerful that Ms. Ouroboros had no choice but to raise her whip to block it.

And then.

Into the gap, Vikir drew his bow.

Black Bow Anubis.

The five-piece tip bowstring and five quivers were drawn taut in unison.

It shot out in a black trajectory toward the enemy in front of him.

[…!]

Ms. Ouroboros quickly retrieved her whip, but was slowed by the web of the Madam cub that hung over every inch of the forest.

Puff-puff-puck!

Four arrows were deflected by the whip, but only one flew off on a proper trajectory.

“…Hmm?”

As Vikir put the next arrow to the quiver, he noticed something odd.

One of the arrows he had just fired had grazed Ms. Ouroboros on the left side of her face.

A person as skilled as Ms. Ouroboros could definitely see and dodge the attack, but for some reason, she was a little slow to react to attacks coming from the left.

The same thing happened when I alternately shot right and left again.

A subtle difference that would have gone unnoticed by anyone less skilled.

‘Is there a blind spot over there?’

Vikir raised his Anubis and fired a grain toward Ms. Ouroboros’s left side.

The arrows curved in a parabola, aiming relentlessly for Ms. Ouroboros’ left facial area.

[Oh no, not this guy again…, He even brought a strange bow!]

And with that, the unexplained rage in Ms. Ouroboros’ eyes grew and grew.

Just then.

Ping-ping!

The night sky was suddenly bright.

Red firecrackers were being set off, creating a bright pillar of light.

MiniPin. He ran to the wagon and fired the signal flare that hunters used to set off in times of danger.

[….]

Ms. Ouroboros gritted her teeth and turned her head.

The black fog from earlier, the unidentifiable wires, and Vikir’s skill with the strange bow were beyond that of a first-year Academy student.

Ms. Ouroboros was furious at Vikir’s skill, as he ducked and weaved like a hunter who had spent decades in the forest.

But then.

“What is this noise?”

“I thought a hunter was in trouble… It doesn’t seem like something out of the ordinary.”

“The ground is shaking hundreds of meters away, call for backup now!”

“Halt the march, we’re in combat formation!”

The rumblings at the base of the mountain were clearly coming from the direction of the flares.

Coincidentally, a unit of Imperial Army troops happened to be marching in the vicinity.

[Ho-ho-ho- bad luck].

Ms. Ouroboros retrieved her whip in an annoyed manner.

Then she sent a fierce glare at Vikir, who had now closed the distance between them.

[…Well, okay, I guess I’ll have ‘another’ connection to you].

She brushed a hand across the left side of her face, near her mask.

Then, in the blink of an eye, she stomped off the ground and flew up, crashing through the branches and disappearing.

Her departure was as swift as her arrival.

“Sir, sir, are you all right?”

MiniPin, who had whistled to alert the Imperial troops to their location, came running toward Vikir, breathless.

Vikir only nodded, still in a nonchalant mood.

“The signal flare. Good timing.”

“You’re welcome. It’s a good thing I had one in the wagon as a backup.”

After MiniPin’s embarrassed laugh, Vikir turned his attention back to the forest.

The forest at night, silent as if it had never been noisy. The sound of branches and leaves swaying in the wind.

Ms. Ouroboros had melted into the thick darkness and was no longer visible.

The only thing left at the scene were the marks on the ground, as if a large snake had slithered across them.

Chapter 232

Suspicion (1)

◆

Student Council President Dolores L. Quovadis.

She had a strange feeling when she heard that the Aristocratic and Noble factions, which had been the eyesores of the student council, had gotten into a lot of trouble due to the recent incident at the bazaar.

Unlike the student council, which is an official organization and wields power on the positive side of campus, the aristocrats and nobles mainly form their power on the negative side of campus.

Whereas the student council operated according to legitimate rules and procedures, the aristocrats and nobles were using connections, favors, and insider information to gain power.

So, student autonomy on campus was divided between the student council, the aristocracy, and the nobility, and Dolores didn’t like them because they were always enjoying extrajudicial power, avoiding the responsibilities of official organizations and reaping the benefits of unofficial organizations.

However, since it was the student council that had to collect public opinion and establish policies accordingly, the aristocratic faction and noble faction that led the flow of public opinion were always annoying opponents that had to be watched closely.

…And that’s when they drank the water. To one individual, a first-year student named Vikir.

The aristocrats and nobility, who had been secretly growing in power to rival the student council, had lost a lot of face in this one incident, and it had caused a lot of defections.

The weakening of the enemy is the same as the strengthening of the enemy.

Many of the people who were disappointed with the aristocrats and nobility turned around, and some of them even joined the student council.

So the executives in the student council were smiling all day.

“Vikir, why don’t you recommend him to our student council?”

“Sure. Who can resist the golden badge of student council?”

“Kya, he’s a rising star. I can’t believe he’s a candidate for student council since freshman year.”

“Maybe he could make a run for the youngest student council president?”

“Uh, that’s a little too much. I mean, not student council president, but still.”

“Anyway. We’ll have to move fast, because the aristocracy and the nobility will be trying to bully him and recruit him at the same time.”

In the worst case scenario, Vikir would have been a candidate for an executive position as early as second year.

But Dolores didn’t think Vikir would accept the invitation to join student council, let alone an executive position.

‘A normal freshman would jump at the opportunity to be a student council member, but… he’s different.’

No, actually, it was more than different.

Not only did he go out and collect a huge amount of gnoll skins, but he also donated all the proceeds to a scholarship foundation for students in academy.

What’s more, he has the nerve to offend the aristocracy and nobility in the process.

‘Gnoll skins may not be incredibly valuable, but they’re still quite valuable, and to burn them in front of your enemies and then haggle over the price? That’s not the boldness of a first year, no matter how you look at it.’

Dolores was intrigued by Vikir’s character.

A junior who had received an unusually high number of detentions since the beginning of the semester.

And because of the sincerity shown at orphanage and the kindness shown in resolving the disaster(?) that occurred during a drinking game, I was paying a lot of attention to it now.

‘And as it turns out, he was the top student in both written and practical exams.’

A student who is good at studying and has good skills, and moreover, a very conscientious student.

It was a pity that we would have become closer friends if the newspaper club I belonged to had not written a harsh article criticizing The Night Hound.

And now. Dolores found herself feeling more than a little fond and curious at Vikir’s behavior, which gave a blow to the aristocracy and the nobility.

Those feelings had only grown stronger after watching the conversation between Vikir and Professor Banshee last evening.

‘Let’s call the prize ‘Nymphet’.’

Professor Banshee didn’t understand the meaning of Vikir’s words, but Dolores recognized them immediately.

Nymphet. The poor child who had been sacrificed in the fight against Dantalian.

Vikir still remembered Nymphet.

‘Don’t you think you were too hard on her? Did she get a kiss?’

‘No.’

‘It’s not ‘no’, it’s ‘can’t’! She wants to give you a kiss like that!’

‘It’s embarrassing.’

Dolores recalled a conversation she had with Vikir during her last volunteer assignment at the orphanage.

Vikir had rejected Nymphet’s kisses because he was embarrassed.

‘Maybe it’s because of the memories of that day that he can’t forget the Nymphet even more?’

If so, Vikir must be hiding a warm heart beneath his blunt outer shell.

No, Dolores was sure of that.

…Jump up!

Dolores jumped to her feet.

For some reason, she felt a rush of urgency now that her thoughts had gone this far.

It seemed like something needed to be said to Vikir right now.

It was probably out of a sense of responsibility and debt as the one who had watched Nymphet’s last moments with the Night Hound in the fight against Dantalian, and some other unexplained emotion she didn’t recognize.

“Uh, Ms. President, where are you going?”

“Is there anything urgent?”

“What’s the agenda for today’s meeting…?”

The student council executives look over with puzzled expressions.

“Sorry, everyone! I will handle the agenda even if it means staying up all night!”

Dolores ducked her head and apologized, then hurried out the door.

She left the lecture hall and headed for the dormitories.

Most students would be there by this time.

…But Vikir was not so easy to find.

“Vikir? He’s the last one to get into the dorms.”

“Shouldn’t he be in the library by now? He’s a study bug.”

“Not in the library? Hmm, then maybe he’s in the gym. He looks like he’s working out hard… if you look at his body.”

“What? He’s not in the library or in the gym? Then maybe….”

I asked Tudor, Sancho, Sinclaire, and others who were familiar with Vikir, but I had no idea where he was.

The sign-in sheets at the front and back gates didn’t say he’d left, so he must be somewhere at the Academy.

“…Where the hell are you?”

Dolores stood, catching her breath.

I’ve noticed this before at the orphanage, but Vikir is really good at getting around.

‘Come to think of it, he was also missing when the mysterious black mage appeared at the festival.’

A student who is shrouded in mystery and doubt about everything.

Dolores felt her questions about Vikir grow more and more intense.

Even when I happened to be nearby and tried to smell the soul, I couldn’t find anything.

There was no way to tell, as Vikir usually kept his heart far more closed than most people his age.

Suddenly, Dolores remembered Vikir’s record of demerits.

‘I can’t believe he’s accumulated so many demerits for taking a wrong turn. For such a smart kid.’

I didn’t realize it at the time, but it’s strange to think about now.

I can’t help but think that Vikir must have accumulated those demerits with some sort of intent.

Dolores opened the chart recorded on the mana stone and took a closer look at Vikir’s penalty points record.

<Vikir’s Life Attitude Score (Points deduction factors)

-1 point for using the emergency exit on the third floor of the dormitory building.

-1 point for entering the 4th grade private area of the Performance Hall

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 1st floor of the Deadly Poison Experiment Building building

-1 point for entering the smoking area of the Experimental Monster Breeding Center

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 6th floor of the Faculty Research Center

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 3rd floor of dedicated training room Hot Class.

-1 point for entering the physical training room outside of normal business hours

-1 point for entering the restricted area next to the food warehouse in the cafeteria.

.

.

“…These places. I see they’re categorized by date. Given the location, what will be the route of movement?”

Dolores decided that it wouldn’t be a good idea to find Vikir today anyway, so she decided to follow Vikir’s movements so far.

Why on earth. The purpose was to understand whether an ordinary first-year student would have received penalty points for going to a place where he would never set foot.

…And.

After visiting each of the places listed in the demerit book, Dolores noticed an odd similarity.

“A dark, high place?”

They all faced the Academy’s high walls.

Dolores looked around.

“…What? Were you planning on crossing the walls of the Academy?”

Why else would he have picked these places? It was a series of increasingly incomprehensible situations.

Just then.

-TING!

A chime sounded from the mana stone.

Dolores quickly turned it on.

<Vikir-Life Attitude Score ( Deduction Points Factor )

-1 point for using the rooftop emergency exit on the first floor of the dormitory building.

A notification popped up that Vikir’s demerit had been updated. It was only a few seconds ago.

This meant that Vikir had climbed onto the roof of the dormitory building and had been caught by the supervisor.

“There you are!”

Dolores remembered that the rooftop of the dormitory building was also a very high place.

Wondering why anyone would want to go to such a high place, Dolores started running with all her might.

She soon reached the roof of the first-year dormitory building.

But there was no one there.

Neither Vikir nor the supervisor who had penalized him was there.

“If you were in the dormitory, that means you went to your room, right?”

Dolores hurriedly climbed down from the fire escape and, after getting permission from the supervisor, went in search of Vikir’s room.

…But even there, he couldn’t find Vikir.

Instead, he met Pigi, who was studying in his room.

“Vikir, did he just come in and then leave again?”

“Well, do you know where he is now?”

“He said he was going to the shower, but why…?”

As soon as Dolores heard Pigi’s answer, she was about to leave the door, but stopped for a moment.

This is because I realized too late that if the place was a shower room, I wouldn’t be able to meet him even if I went there.

“He’ll come back to the room when he’s done showering, right?”

“I don’t know, Vikir wanders around a lot in the evening.”

“…Is there ever a time when he doesn’t come in?”

“Not really, he always comes in, even if it’s late.”

Dolores nodded at Pigi’s words.

Suddenly, her gaze traveled to where Vikir was staying.

A worn wooden desk. Thin blankets and a frayed pillowcase. A cheap matrix that looked like it had a few springs out.

It’s hard to tell that anyone was living here.

Pigi’s plain bedding above looks as luxurious as the emperor’s.

Feeling Dolores’s gaze, Pigi smirked.

“Vikir never keeps much stuff in his room, like someone who will always leave.”

“…Leave?”

“No, no. It’s just a feeling I have, and it’s kind of a roommate thing.”

Dolores’ expression grew serious as she listened to Pigi.

Around that time, the supervisor in charge of the men’s dormitory warned Dolores.

He warned her not to spend too much time on the men’s floor with underclassmen.

Dolores had no choice but to turn and walk away without seeing Vikir.

“Yeah. Anyway, thanks, Pigi. I’ll see you later.”

“Yeah. When Vikir gets back, I’ll let him know you paid a visit.”

Dolores left the room with a polite bow from Pigi.

As I looked back several times.

….

…And.

Alone in the room, Peggy muttered to himself after witnessing this incredible turn of events.

“No way, the student council president… Vikir?”

It was an understandable misunderstanding.

Chapter 234

National University League (1)

◆

There was a strange feeling in the air at the Colosseo Academy, the Empire’s best university.

The reason for this was the approaching date of a tournament for the Empire’s top universities.

The National University League.

An annual event where the four leading universities of the Empire come together to determine their supremacy.

Colosseo Academy had always been the top-ranked institution in the annual evaluations, but the other three were formidable opponents.

(Colosseo Academy).

(Boot Camp Varangian).

(Magic Tower).

(Themiscyra Women’s University).

Hot on the heels of the Colosseo Academy are three other prominent universities, Varangian, Magic Tower, and Themiscyra.

Varangian is a northern university known for its “Warrior Training Center,” a specialized college that specializes in cold weapons such as swords, spears, axes, and bows.

Magic Tower is another eastern university known for its “law vocational school,” where those who follow the path of the Mage gather to study.

They specialize in hot weapons, of course.

Themiscyra is a southern university with an educational system that most closely resembles the Colosseo Academy.

Students can choose to specialize in either cold or hot weapons, depending on their talents, aptitudes, and tastes, and can pursue other disciplines as minors, majors, or liberal arts.

The difference with Colosseo Academy is that enrollment is limited to girls only.

(Except in very rare cases).

With a showdown between these two great rivals on the horizon, there is a sense of tension in the air at Colosseo Academy.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, all first-graders at Colosseo, were among the first to admit it.

“It’s my first time meeting people from other schools.”

“It’s hard to be first, because if you do well, you win, and if you don’t, you lose.”

“I’m a little nervous. Do you think I’ll do well?”

“What’s the point? You’re doing so well in Colosseo.”

“That’s right, we’re all the same age after all!”

As new students, they were curious about the culture and academic style of other schools.

Meanwhile, Sinclaire and Sancho had taken entrance exams for other schools, so they were getting a lot of stares from other students.

“By the way, didn’t Sancho get first place in the Varangian entrance exam?”

“If those kids see Sancho, they’ll grind their teeth.”

“Why would they grind their teeth?”

“Of course they will. They ditched their school and went somewhere else. Doesn’t that look good?”

“Then Sinclaire’s in even more trouble, because she was first in her entrance exams at Magic Tower and first in her entrance exams at Themiscyra.”

“I don’t know, but I’m sure there are a lot of kids at other schools who are studying with her.”

Sinclaire was a monster, topping the entrance exams for all the universities with magical faculties, including Magic Tower, Themiscyra, and Colosseo.

I don’t know, but it seemed certain that she’d get a lot of jealous glances.

Then. A boy in a black cloak appeared with an arrogant air.

“Don’t worry, foolish friends. I will personally attend the tournament and educate you lesser beings.”

It was Granola Leviathan.

He had recently been recruited into the Noble Faction and had become quite a contributor.

Tudor, who usually thought nothing of Granola, sneered.

“Hey, Pansy, are you going to the tournament too?”

“What kind of rude thing to say! Don’t you know that there are no grade restrictions in this competition? Anyone who hasn’t taken the same course more than once, whether they’re a paid student, a deferred graduate, or a repeat student, is eligible to compete!”

“Who doesn’t know?”

Tudor quickly lost interest and turned his head away, but Granola’s admonishing and explanatory temperament seemed to remain.

“Allow me to explain the nature and rules of the competition to you idiots.”

1. The official name of the competition between the four university leagues is the Olympiad Survival Contest, otherwise known as Battle Royale Ground Zero.

A total of 400 students are dropped into a large, randomized area called the Warp, where they are challenged to survive for a limited amount of time.

3. Everyone will compete in an HP suit, and the moment this HP reaches zero, they will be automatically eliminated.

4. The top 10 people who achieved good results in the survival competition will be awarded a world-class artifact stored in a treasure trove jointly managed by the four universities.

“Now that I’ve explained it to you in such detail, please refrain from holding me back at the competition site~”

Granola concluded his explanation with a pouting posture.

Then.

…Puck

Granola’s shoulder was hit by something.

“What the hell, what kind of person dares to touch this jade body….”

Granola turned his head with an annoyed expression.

Standing there was a tall male student with black hair and red eyes.

“What.”

Highbro Le Baskerville.

He stared down at Granola, the real head of Class B of the Cold Warriors.

“….”

Granola stared up at Highbro’s face, which was at least two feet taller than his own, for a moment.

The normally arrogant Granola knew. Highbro, a member of Class B of the Cold Warriors, could have a hell of a temper.

“Oh, no.”

“You’re an asshole.”

The Highbro glanced Granola up and down once, and then walked away.

“….”

“….”

To make matters worse, he was followed by the stares of Middlebro and Lowbro.

Alone, Granola began to shake.

“Those crazy dogs! If there weren’t three of them, I would’ve kicked their asses! You thugs, you thugs!”

Everyone was looking at Granola with salty eyes.

Then.

One more boy came walking down the street from where Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro had passed.

When Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire saw the face, they shouted in delight.

“Vikir, over here!”

“Good morning again, my friend.”

“Good to see you’re so excited, Vikir~”

“Is that real or not? I mean, with the real student council president?”

“Ugh! Of course not, he said he wasn’t interested in a relationship!”

The friends soon surrounded Vikir and started talking about the competition.

“But what about the real love story…?”

“No, Vikir, it’s not, but this time, there are no grade restrictions. If there are 100 students from each school, there should be about 20 freshmen.”

“Right, because the real aces are the juniors, and it’s customary for the seniors not to participate.”

“Maybe 50 juniors, 30 sophomores, and 20 freshmen?”

“We had good midterms, so of course we’re in.”

The conversation then turns to Vikir.

Tudor asks.

“So, Vikir. What about you? I read that the scores are evaluated individually, but you have to participate in groups. I think it’s groups of five.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and Vikir.

With a group size of six, it’s a little difficult to get everyone in a group.

They’d rather split into three groups of three.

“Yeah. Let’s make it three-on-three and put two other kids in each group. Okay, Vikir, you’ll be in our group.”

“What’s wrong, why are you taking Vikir?”

“That’s right, it’s a fair swallow!”

“I’ll go with Vikir’s group~”

“That’s cheating! I want to be in the same group as him this time!”

Everyone wants to be in the same group as Vikir because they’ve been divided into two groups.

But Vikir has a different answer.

“Umm. I’m already in the other group.”

“What? Again? You said that during the midterms!”

“That’s a pre-arrangement. I’m sorry.”

Vikir’s friends were openly frustrated by his answer.

Sinclaire was the most obviously upset.

“I really wanted to be in the same group as you this time.”

“Well. I’m sorry again. This time, I have a very clear sense of purpose.”

Everyone’s eyes widened at Vikir’s words.

“…Purpose?”

This was the first time Vikir had ever revealed his true intentions, so everyone forgot about their embarrassment and expressed their curiosity.

And for some reason, Vikir was happy to answer.

“I heard that if I place in the top 10 in this competition, I’ll get one of the treasures stored in a treasure trove jointly managed by the four universities.”

Vikir said with a rare twinkle in his eye.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire all shook their heads in surprise.

It was the first time they had ever seen Vikir so blatantly want something.

“Is there some kind of treasure you’re after?”

“Yes.”

“What is it?”

“It’s a secret.”

“Oh, come on, I thought you were going to tell me!”

The impatient Tudor is the first to speak up.

Sinclaire, who is usually secretive, also has a glint in her eyes.

“I’m guessing you’ve got your own artifact you’re after, and so do I. But you know what?”

“?”

“It seems that just because you enter the treasure room doesn’t mean you can get the treasure. You have to be chosen by the treasure.”

Artifacts that can be considered world-class treasures are stored in the treasure troves managed by the four major universities.

All of these artifacts are said to have spirituality and do not wait for their owners to choose them, but instead choose their owners and come to them.

Once an artifact finds its owner, it stays with them for the rest of their lives, after which it is returned to storage.

Sinclaire smiles broadly.

“In other words, you have to choose between artifacts that choose you. You can’t always have what you want. Apparently, if you go into a warehouse and you’re not chosen by any artifacts, you just have to come out empty-handed.”

But for Vikir, who has memories from before the regression, none of these restrictions mattered.

‘I just need to be able to get into the treasure room.’

He was right, for Vikir’s ultimate purpose was not to possess artifacts, but to destroy them.

Vikir had an idea of the object he should choose when he entered the treasury.

‘The Seventh Corpses. It must be sleeping in the treasury.’

Among the ten demons, he is the only one that exists in the form of an object.

That was the existence of ‘Decarabia’, the seventh corpse.

Chapter 236

National University League (3)

◆

Granola de Leviathan.

As the third son of the extremely venomous House Leviathan, one of the seven great families of the Empire, he has lived his whole life being respected.

Raised with the praise and expectations of being the greatest genius in his family, he has never allowed himself to be looked down.

…Until he entered the Colosseo Academy.

Second in the entrance exam rankings. Something was wrong from the start.

There are limits to achieving a mental victory just because the levels of Hot and Cold Class are different.

Granola looked at the woman who had stepped over him.

Sinclaire, a commoner without a surname.

Granola decided to ignore this impossible event as the first and last miracle of a lowly commoner’s life.

But the midterms didn’t change his ranking.

Looking at Sinclaire, Granola was filled with inferiority complex and hatred.

…But why? The more he struggled, the more strange feelings arose in Granola’s heart.

Or perhaps it had been there since the moment he first laid eyes on her.

The white hair that stood out wherever she went. The clear skin. Eyes as big as a deer’s. A tight nose and lips.

Every time he thought of Sinclaire, he found himself inwardly cheering for her.

It was ridiculous, he thought, but he couldn’t help it.

From then on, Granola diligently hovered around Sinclaire, hoping to get one more word in with her.

When he did, he kicked himself for not being able to say anything more than the stinging words “commoner…” out of habit.

And that’s when an unwelcome presence appeared.

Vikir. An ordinary(?) guy with nothing special about him.

At best, he’s a good student and has a pretty face, but he acts like every girl in the school wants his body, liver, and gallbladder.

Sinclaire, who has been watching for a long time, also approaches him with a hint of crush.

‘No way! This can’t be happening!’

Granola himself was speechless until now, but they are already in a relationship where they do volunteer work and study together!

So Granola made a decision. He was determined to be in the same group as Vikir in this competition.

And with his superiority, he would make Vikir’s inferiority even more obvious.

‘I’ll humiliate him in front of Sinclaire!’

Wouldn’t that make her look at himself a little differently? Wouldn’t she realize who the better, stronger man was?

That’s what Granola thought.

“…Keuhum!”

Granola took a seat at the head of the round table.

At the round table were the members of his group for this competition.

He handed his luggage to Vikir in front of him and told him to put it in the luggage locker above.

“Hey, commoner. Put my stuff on top of your head….”

But it was a little too much to ask.

It wasn’t the Vikir that scared him, it was the humans on either side of him.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro. The three Baskerville brothers.

They occupied the seats on either side of Vikir, and even Granola couldn’t help but notice them a bit.

But Granola steeled himself.

‘All right. Let’s not be scared by these guys. I am the person who will lead this group.’

The seating arrangement was in a circle: Highbro, Middlebro, Vikir, Lowbro, and Granola.

Granola skipped over Lowbro next to him and spoke again to Vikir next to him.

“Hey, commoner. Can’t you hear me? Take my stuff and keep it above your head.”

“?”

Vikir, his eyes closed and deep in thought, opened one eye.

Granola’s luggage was placed in front of him.

“What are you doing? You’re not taking it.”

“….”

“Look at this kid? What a dog? What are you doing, believing in your grades during the midterm exam? A lucky child …Where did you pick up some information about monsters?”

Then.

Lowbro, who was standing between Vikir and Granola, spoke up.

“Shut up, you two. It’s loud.”

Granola’s expression stiffened at the words.

‘Shut up? Is that what you’re saying to me?’ I thought.

This was the first time Granola had ever experienced an argument like this.

Even the seniors in the Noble Faction were frowning at him, and he was the heir to the Leviathan Family!

“What did you just say?”

Granola asked in disbelief.

When Lowbro closed his eyes in annoyance and didn’t answer, Granola became even more confused.

“No, I don’t know if it’s Highbro, but now you’ve got to come crawling up on me, even the smallest one?”

Of the Baskerville triplets, Highbro is by far the most famous.

He’s the strongest, and he gets the best grades.

His two younger siblings, Middlebro and Lowbro, feel like they’re always following in his footsteps, which is why Granola is feeling so much more bewilderment right now.

‘I can’t do this. If I’m going to take over this group, I need to show some charisma from the start.’

He closed his eyes and sighed heavily.

“…Ah, I just got on the train and these assholes are pissing me off again. Hey, commoner!”

Granola slumped back in his seat and jerked his chin at Vikir once more.

“Get a bottle of liquor out of my pack.”

Yes, Granola had sneaked a bottle of vodka, a drink that students are not supposed to drink, into his backpack.

Granola crossed his arms with his eyes closed and sneered inwardly at the silent Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

‘What do you think, I’m the kind of bastard who would open a bottle of alcohol in broad daylight on a train to a tournament, and I’m underage!’

Granola flaunted his bravery and bravado by casually committing dangerous levels of deviance.

“Hey, commoner. Get it out. There’s a bottle of vodka in my bag.”

“….”

But Vikir still didn’t respond.

Granola’s eyebrows twitched.

If you move here and take out the bottle yourself, everything will be ruined. Even if we drink it, there will be no saving face.

So I have to move that commoner somehow to get it.

“Hey, are you really deaf, hurry up and get it out~”

At that moment, Lowbro, who was beside him, spoke up once more.

“What a noisy bastard. You must have a lark in your mouth.”

“…What, what?”

“If you want to drink alcohol, you can take it out and drink it. This isn’t even a joke.”

Granola’s face flushed at Lowbro’s words.

Then.

“Stop.”

Something stood between them. It was Vikir’s hand, holding a bottle.

“Here’s your drink. Stop.”

Vikir took the vodka out of Granola’s bag.

Granola grunted and snatched the bottle away.

…Tsk!

Granola assumed the worst posture he could muster (being careful not to encroach too much on the space of his fellow Highbro and Lowbro) and opened his mouth.

“Ugh, I feel dirty, and I need a drink.”

But no one looks at him or speaks to him.

Unable to cool his temper, Granola gritted his teeth and unscrewed the cap of the vodka bottle.

“Don’t you people know how to drink?”

“….”

“Ha, that’s me. Why, are you afraid you’ll get caught by the inspector if you drink, or are you just a bunch of nerds and it’s no fun?”

“….”

“Well, I’m a bit of a drinker, so when I come to a place like this, I always wet my throat. Well, it’s only 70 percent alcohol at most, so it’s no different than water, but it’s good.”

Granola tilted the vodka bottle and poured a few drops into his mouth, puffing it up with air as if he’d drunk a lot, then gulped a few times.

Then he opened his mouth as if he had just remembered something.

“Oh, right. Hey, I’m in charge of this group. No complaints?”

His tone was casual and nonchalant.

But Granola’s nerves were extremely focused on everyone’s reactions.

….

But no one responds. Their eyes are closed, their arms are crossed, and they are simply meditating.

Granola shook his head, not sure if his words had worked or not.

‘Does this mean you recognize me as the leader? Does this mean I can do whatever I want?’

So I tried to drive the nail in the coffin one more time.

“Hmm. Well, it’s a formal event anyway. I’ll just take care of it. I think my performance in the competition will be good if I lead…… I also received this kind of education separately from my family, so I am somewhat specialized… And I’m from a noble family, so I’m used to being bossed around….”

Granola continues to reek of alcohol and stutter.

Just then.

“Keuheum.”

Vikir coughed once. He stood up and walked out of the room.

Granola frowned.

“I, I, I. Look at the way you move when the boss is talking. If you go to the bathroom or anything, and you don’t come back, I’m going to give you a stern warning. ….”

That was it.

…Puck!

A dull noise was heard.

Granola cocked his head.

“…?”

I saw an unbelievable sight.

Granola’s hand was on the round table. A dagger was deeply embedded in the back of his hand.

Flesh splintered, muscles split, bones shattered, and blood flowed freely.

Granola stood dumbfounded at the unusual sight before him, feeling no pain for a moment.

And then.

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!”

The scream comes a step too late.

Granola tried to move his hand, but the dagger had pierced the back of his hand and the palm of his hand and was now embedded deeply in the round table.

The one holding the dagger’s handle muttered irritably.

“I thought I told you to be quiet.”

It was a Lowbro.

He clicked his tongue and leaned back, picking up the bottle of vodka that Granola had dropped.

He then poured the clear vodka over the back of Granola’s hand, which was pierced by a dagger.

“Aaaahhh!”

Granola screamed in pain as his hand burned.

Next to him, Lowbro suddenly looks as scary as a ghost.

I used to think they were funny because they were always in the shadow of the Highbro, but they weren’t.

In fact, the grades of Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro had always been tied, with only a few points separating them.

As Granola sat there with his hands stuck to the table and tears streaming down his face, Highbro and Middlebro opened their eyes and began to giggle.

“You know, you’re actually pretty funny. Hey, do you want to be secret friends with us?”

“Let’s go like this without leaving until we reach the magic tower. It’s noisy, so try putting something like a sock in your mouth.”

“I’ve disinfected it, so it shouldn’t be a problem, even if it is. We can call the priest when we get there.”

It was a moment when Granola’s plan to take the lead early on was derailed spectacularly.

Chapter 238

National University League (5)

◆

“…, Huh, bro?”

Sinclaire looked puzzled. It was a rare occurrence.

Vikir looked down at Sinclaire wordlessly.

He had grown quite a bit since he had entered the school, and now there was quite a height difference between them.

Finally, Vikir’s mouth opened briefly.

“Door.”

For a moment, Sinclaire didn’t understand what Vikir was saying.

And then.

“Oh, get out of the way so I can open the door, okay, sorry!”

Sinclaire took a large step to the side.

Finally, Vikir nodded, opened the door, and stepped out across the compartment.

And then.

“….”

Vikir didn’t close the door after he crossed the divide, but kept it open.

Sinclaire nodded again.

“Oh, so you want me to stop arguing with students from other schools and just get over here?”

At Sinclaire’s interpretation, Vikir nodded in silence.

‘There are participants from Themiscyra Women’s University in the carriage back there, and I want you to avoid contact with them as much as possible before the tournament, in case they want to challenge you.’

I can’t pretend I didn’t see the conflict, given Dolores’ advice earlier.

And Sinclaire had been a regular source of help with the genealogy and scope of the note test.

Just then.

Vikir was grabbing Sinclaire to take her away.

“Wait! Who are you to interfere in women’s affairs!”

The female students of Themiscyra began to protest Vikir.

At the forefront of the chorus was Ms. Lovegood, the student council president.

She turned to Vikir and said sternly.

“This boy has insulted our school, and we need him to play nice with us. If you interfere with that, you will be held accountable. First, give us your class number, your affiliation, and your name. I’m making a formal complaint to the Colosseo Academy….”

Lovegood was just about to declare war on Vikir.

Whirring-

A gust of wind rushed in from the second floor window that Vikir had opened.

It rushed down the stairs and blew the hair of the people on the first floor all over the place.

And Vikir’s as well.

Fluttered.

The hem of his black coat fluttered, and soon his tousled black hair fell back as well.

Vikir’s bare face was exposed.

For a moment, the faces of the students at Themiscyra Women’s University went blank.

They didn’t know what they were seeing or what they were staring at.

“What is that?”

“Is that a human face?”

“How is it so small?”

“But it’s got all the features in it….”

“And it’s so clear and deep.”

“Isn’t it a painting or a statue?”

After a moment of silence, I hear a small murmur from behind me.

…But only one. Only Lovegood, the student council president of Themiscyra, remained unmoved.

“Oh, I forgot, in order to resolve this dispute with the University amicably, I need to ask you for some personal information again. First of all, your class number, your affiliation, your name, and….”

Lovegood remained calm, cool, and rational as she asked Vikir for the procedurally necessary information.

“Year, month, and city of birth. Height. Weight. Blood type. Hometown. Horoscope. Love interests. Hobbies. Specialties. Favorite foods. Animals you own. Do you currently have a girlfriend, and if not, do you have a crush? What type of woman do you usually idealize? When was your last relationship. How many relationships have you had so far. When do you plan to get married. What your parents like to receive as gifts. How many children you would like to have. Whether I want a boy or a girl. And whether I’m a good name match. And….”

Really. It’s necessary. It must have been a bureaucratic procedure to ask.

◆

The Magic Train had finally arrived at the Magic Tower in the eastern part of the continent.

[Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding~ The continental circulation, continental circulation train is now entering. This station is Magic Tower, Magic Tower Station. The exit door is on the left. For passengers who are transferring to Dortsmail Station, please transfer to the inner ring train here. Please be careful when exiting the train as there is a large distance between the platforms at this station. Thank you for riding our trains today. Goodbye]

The train stops for a while.

The passengers inside begin to trickle out.

Naturally, there were students from the Colosseo Academy, Varangian Boot Camp, and Themiscyra Women’s University mixed in with the crowd.

They were greeted by a welcoming crowd from Magic Tower who came out to greet them at the station.

Meanwhile. Vikir also got off the train and looked around.

Behind the masses of people, the city was quiet.

Dortsmile City in the southeastern part of the empire is also famous as the area where the Magic Tower exists.

The cozy city is bathed in a reddish sunset, making it even more dreamy and idyllic.

And in the center of the city, I saw a soaring tower that seemed to pierce the sun.

‘…That’s the Magic Tower.’

Vikir stared at the tower in the distance, overwhelmed with emotion.

At first glance, it is just a narrow and tall building.

But inside, the tower was filled with so many different rooms that its width and height were endless.

The interior space of the tower, said to have been created by a primordial mage, must be nearly infinite.

It involved a dimensional distortion of such a high order that even modern mages do not fully understand its principles.

‘I have something similar.’

Vikir looked down at the ring on his finger.

/ Ring

-Finit hic Deus -Off

-Finit hic Deus, the realm of the gods ends here.

It is a relic from Andromalius that can warp dimensions and create subspace.

However, once used, it is very costly in mana, and the time it takes for the power to return is very long, so it should not be abused.

Vikir is looking down at his ring, thinking about this and that.

“…Hey, bro.”

A hand patted Vikir’s back from behind. It was Sinclaire.

She hesitated for a moment, then smiled, looking like her usual self.

“Thanks for your help earlier.”

Vikir nodded, and Sinclaire let out a small sigh.

“Actually, I was very scared. They seem like strong sisters.”

“I was scared too.”

“Ahahaha- lie.”

Sinclaire smiled brightly as usual and pulled on Vikir’s collar.

“I know. You must have been nervous, too. It was Lovegood, after all.”

When Vikir didn’t respond, Sinclaire spoke up.

“Oh, look, there’s the welcome party from Magic Tower, meeting the contestants from Varangian and Themisqyra.”

Sure enough, the contestants from the four schools were gathering together.

At the head of the line was Dolores L. Quovadis, the student council president of Colosseo Academy.

She led the students with her calm, gentle charisma and soon found herself in the center of the welcoming crowd.

“It’s been a while, everyone.”

In the direction of Dolores’ greeting, the student council presidents of the other three schools stepped forward.

First to step forward was the student council president of Varangian.

He was tall, with shaggy long hair, muscular, and covered in scars.

“Wahahaha-it’s been a while, hasn’t it been a little less than a year?”

He was ‘Bakilaga Juragio’, the Varangian student council president.

He had been participating in the tournament since his freshman and sophomore years and had consistently placed in the top tier, but this time, as the third-year ace, he was going for the win in earnest.

And his fierce rival was at the forefront of the welcoming crowd at the Magic Tower.

His face is clean-shaven, his height is perfect, and he exudes a chilling aura.

“Eleven months and three days, to be exact. Eleven hours, 42 minutes, and 12 seconds. From the time I last laid eyes on you at last year’s tournament to the time I spotted your face in the crowd just moments ago.”

“Philippus Aureolus Theophrastus Bombast von Hohenheim,” the student council president of Magic Tower.

But instead of using the name Hohenheim or the surname Aureolus, he mostly used his baptismal name, which is unique to the Magic Tower.

‘A smart-ass with a high nose.’ This was Hohenheim’s current name.

There is a tradition at Magic Tower where seniors give baptismal names to their juniors, and the students at Magic Tower use these baptismal names more than their real names over the course of four years: “The Talented Piglet,” “The Curly Broom,” “The Baby Bird in the Lecture Hall,” “The Palm Tree in the Hallway,” “The Curiosity Clogging the Toilet,” “The Drunken Gorilla,” “The Dwarf in the Flask,” etc.

It was a culture that showed how much pride they had.

“This is actually why I didn’t go to the Magic Tower. …I don’t know if they’d call me a ‘fluffy cotton ball’ or not.”

Sinclaire whispered in Vikir’s ear.

Meanwhile.

Hohenheim and Bakilaga began to exchange glances as soon as they saw each other.

Bakilaga spoke first.

“Hahaha- we’re the aces this time. Last year we didn’t make it to the top 10 because the seniors played so much, but this year will be different. I’ve been training like crazy for the past year, the championship is mine!”

“Well, with your ignorant strength, you might be able to get a top ten finish, but no more than that. Our elite will take the first through ninth spots, and the artifacts are ours.”

Hohenheim is equally confident.

Naturally, a ‘warriors vs. wizards’ matchup was forming.

“….”

Vikir watched the confrontation from the crowd in the distance.

Sinclaire gave Vikir a quick rundown on the two men next to him.

“Bakilaga Juragio is a warrior known for his fierceness. Apparently he took over the school when he beat up all the fourth years in a senior-freshman assembly. I’ve heard that the only thing he lacks is experience, and now that he’s in his third year, he should have some of that.”

“Well, he certainly looks strong.”

“A combination of natural talent and hard work, I suppose. Rumor has it his grandparents were barbarians who lived in the depth of the Red&Black Mountains, but I’m not sure.”

Sinclaire shifted her gaze to look at the man beside her.

“Actually, Bakilaga is also a figure of interest, but… I’m a mage, so I’m more concerned about that Hohenheim guy.”

“I see.”

“That’s right. Not even the great President Dolores could beat him in the entire University League. And Hohenheim has already been accepted to graduate school. I’m told he’ll automatically be appointed to a professorship at Magic Tower, and I hear he’s aiming to become the youngest Magic Tower Master ever.”

A Master of the Magic Tower is a position that is comparable to the head of a House of the Seven Families.

Hohenheim was certainly an ambitious man.

Sinclaire continued.

“I’d like to see a first and second place tie between myself, Hohenheim, and Bakilaga, with a high probability of third place going to our President Dolores. Fourth place would be Lovegood of Themiscyra.”

Now that I think about it, I don’t see Themiscyra’s Lovegood.

Sinclaire looked up and around.

…?

And there it was.

Merelini Lovegood. And the female warriors of Themiscyra who followed her.

Their faces, usually solemn, stern, and serious, seemed slightly blank today for some reason.

Chapter 239

National University League (6)

◆

It wasn’t until after the opening ceremony, the welcome ceremony, and other showy events organized by Magic Tower that the students of the Colosseo Academy were allowed to go to their dormitories, which were really more for the professors than for the students.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire traveled to their dorms in a group.

“Man, the headmaster of Magic Tower is a jingle bird. What kind of hostess speech is he giving for over two hours?”

“The last time he said he had one more thing to say was over 300 times. Even my personal trainer doesn’t count like that.”

“I’m exhausted before the competition even starts. You say this is for students, but you don’t really care about them.”

“Where’s the principal of our school, I haven’t seen him in all my years of schooling.”

“I heard he’s been away a lot lately, so Professor Banshee, who just got promoted to vice principal, is here as acting principal.”

Everyone is tired as they walk away.

But the sight of the dormitory rejuvenates them.

“Wow, is this where we’re staying?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and the rest of the Academy’s first years couldn’t believe their eyes.

Buildings that looked like they’d been carved out of the inside of a giant mushroom dotted the landscape, high and low.

The walls, which are indeed mushroom-like, are so elastic and soft that you want to rub your cheeks against them.

Fireflies dot the narrow, winding alleys, and natural lanterns light up the streets, never going out overnight.

I felt like I was in a fairy tale village.

The interior of the building is also very spacious and cozy.

Long tables and chairs carved out of logs, and a buffet of food laid out on them, were still warm and steaming, waiting for guests.

The smells of grilled silver trout, steamed oysters, roasted pork and hard cheeses wafted through the air, both sweet and fragrant.

A glass of white wine and a glass of red wine, both nearly alcohol-free, greeted the students.

(Unfortunately, there was no wine buffet)

The 20 first graders, 30 second graders, and 50 third graders at Colosseo Academy sat down at their tables and began to eat.

We were divided into tables of 5 people to share the food.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire looked up from their delicious food to see what was going on around them.

“Where’s Vikir?”

“Oh, over there. At the table across the way. Diagonally.”

“He’s in a group with the triplets from Baskerville, do you think he’ll be okay?”

“Dude, is he a kid? What are you so worried about? Did you forget his grade on the midterm? He did way better than us. He’s not going to take a beating, so stop worrying.”

“He’s not the kind of kid to be pushed around. He saved me from the Themiscyra kids before, so let’s just focus on our job.”

For now, a thorough analysis of the upcoming competition is in order.

We don’t know what the venue will be, but the 400 people who will be competing for survival there have already signed up.

20 freshmen, 30 sophomores, 50 seniors. 100 total.

This is how the grades are distributed not only in Colosseo Academy but also in Varangian, Magic Tower, and Themiscyra.

And out of these 400 students, seniors are usually the highest performers, followed by sophomores, and then freshmen.

In fact, first-year students are participating for the sake of experience, so participation itself is meaningful, and second-year students are also encouraged to grow further by competing with third-year students from other schools.

And it’s the seniors who have the obligation to bring honor to their school by performing well.

In the history of the competition so far, the top 10 players, including the winner, have always been among third-year students, and in last year’s competition, the four geniuses who were unusually ranked in the top 20 despite being sophomores were the strongest candidates for the championship.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire each had a word.

“Let’s see. Guess who made it to the top 20 last year even though they were only sophomores?”

“Bakilaga Juragio from Varangian, Hohenheim from Magic Tower, Merelini Lovegood from Themiscyra, and our school’s president, Dolores.”

“Our president was a sophomore then, too, so now that she’s a third year, I guess you could say she’s a serious contender!”

“Well, sophomores must have made a good save even in the middle. The freshmen will have to mop the floor.”

“But we have to do better than the freshmen at other schools, so we can carry that ranking over to next year and the year after that!”

The unspoken math among seniors is that the ranking you get as a freshman usually carries over into your senior year.

So Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire were eager not to lose out to their peers from the other three schools.

“We’re one of the 20 most talented people in the first grade, hand-picked from the top of the class, and we can’t let this opportunity go to waste.”

“First of all, the first mission is a survival competition, where the ten people who survive to the end and get good scores will receive individual tasks, and if they clear them, they can receive legendary artifacts, right?”

“Let’s analyze the key players first.”

“That’s right. If we’re unfortunate enough to meet third years from other schools, we’ll be eliminated at lightning speed, so we need to be in the top 100.”

“First of all, Bakilaga, Hohenheim, and Lovegood. Those three must be avoided at all costs.”

Sinclaire had already had an argument with Lovegood on a train, so she knew her fears.

‘Honestly, I was really scared, because I thought I was going to choke to death just from the amount of momentum she was exuding,’

Soon, Sinclaire was passing on her analysis to other friends.

“‘Bakilaga Juragio’. 25 years old. A fighter who had already beaten all the fourth year students in his freshman year. In last year’s tournament, he was defeated by a combination of third-year students from another school due to his lack of experience, and the year before, he was stabbed in the back by seniors from the same school, which prevented him from placing in the top 10. Despite this, he was ranked 14th in the overall rankings of last year’s tournament. His main weapon is a greatsword. Last year’s power level was Sword Expert Superlative, and now it’s impossible to guess. There are even rumors that it is already on the Graduator.”

“Hmph. If you were defeated by a group of seniors from your own school, you were defeated by an ally, so your credibility within the school is not strong?”

Sinclaire shook his head at Tudor’s question.

“No. That was in first and second year. Bakilaga is said to be strong for the strong and weak for the weak, so he’s very good with his peers and juniors. He can’t stand injustice or bad behavior, so he fights for them when they’re being victimized. So even though he may not get along with the seniors, he is very close to his peers and juniors. He’s a senior now, which is actually the highest grade, and he’s the student council president, so he’s trusted by everyone.”

Bakilaga Juragio leads the men of Varangian with overwhelming force and trust.

Now that he has overcome his only two shortcomings, experience and teamwork, he is a stronger candidate for the championship than anyone else.

Pigi then spoke up.

“I’ve been analyzing the student council president of Magic Tower, Aureolus Hohenheim. He’s 22 years old. His baptismal name at Magic Tower is ‘A smart-ass with a high nose’ and he is, without question, the strongest student in Magic Tower, and no student in the last hundred years of Magic Tower’s history has ever outperformed him. Last year, when he was a sophomore, he ranked 13th in the University League, and everyone else was a junior. Even our president, Dolores, lost to him in the last two University League games… I suppose it’s inevitable since they’re different.”

Monstrous talent, arrogant temper.

Hohenheim is a genius who is considered the strongest among his peers in the Empire, let alone the Magic Tower.

Despite the university’s rankings, Bakilaga and Hohenheim were clearly the next generation of absolute powerhouses.

And there’s one more dark horse that can’t be ignored.

Bianca, who has a thing for pretty girls, opens up about who she’s been researching.

“Not to mention my research on the student council president of Themiscyra, Merelini Lovegood.”

“Oh, right. What have you been researching?”

“She’s… pretty.”

“?”

“Too pretty.”

“??”

“I don’t know how she can be so pretty, ha ha… I envy her. I want to be like her.”

“????”

Hearing Bianca’s words, Tudor frowned in disbelief.

“Hey, never mind. I’d rather have more detailed information about what I’ve been researching. Hmmm! Merelini Lovegood, age 23. Mage who specializes in grass, dirt, poison, and bug-type magic. She is the eldest daughter of the Merelini family, a very large and powerful family, and is rumored to have already reached the 4th class, although this is not confirmed. Last year’s tournament result was 16th place, and now that she’s in her third year, she’s hoping to win.”

“She’s also known for her beauty. I heard that she is a dancer in a famous theater troupe as a hobby. She might make her debut next year… I’m personally a fan.”

Sancho added some seemingly useless information to Tudor’s description.

By now, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire had finished their character analysis and began to share their thoughts on the competition.

“What do you think President Dolores will place this time? She was 15th in last year’s competition.”

“Of course she’ll win! I believe in her.”

“But Bakilaga and Hohenheim are too strong, and Lovegood is as good as President Dolores.”

“Well, it’s not the third-year aces, it’s us.”

“Yeah, we’ll just watch and learn and get ready for the league next year and the year after!”

Being freshmen, they didn’t seem to have high expectations.

…But.

There is one position in the competition where you have to finish in the top 10 to win a prize.

‘Don’t be too harsh…… I should rank within the top 10.’

It was Vikir.

Thinking that his classmates would be horrified if they heard it, Vikir made a plan for the future.

The seventh corpse, ‘Decarabia’.

The only one of the ten demons to take the form of an object.

Demons come in many forms and varieties, including worms, snakes, humans, bats, and trees, but the most unusual of them all is the one that takes the form of an inanimate object.

It must be sleeping somewhere in the human realm right now, waiting for someone to wake it up.

And Vikir had a vague idea of its location.

‘It is in the Treasure Vault, which is jointly managed by the four universities.’

This was why the demons had been so relentless in their invasions of the Four Academy before the Return.

But if Vikir could locate and eliminate Decarabia faster than the demons could, their bleak future would be much different.

The students, who would otherwise have died unjustly, would be spared.

‘With this, the age of destruction will be delayed one step further.’

With fewer demons, there is less power to feed the gates to the Demon World.

Vikir was lost in thought, contemplating the distant future.

“…I beg your pardon.”

A voice caught everyone’s attention, including Vikir’s.

It was the owner of the large inn, and he was looking very troubled and apologetic.

“There’s a problem with the water supply at the inn next door… and I was wondering if I could put the people staying there in the empty rooms here? I’m a bit short on rooms.”

The owner kept bowing his head and making difficult requests.

The inn next door is run by his younger brother, but the water pipe suddenly broke and there was no water, making it impossible to receive guests for the day.

The owner wanted to send the guests to the other inn as soon as possible, but the Colosseo Academy had already pre-booked all the spare rooms, so it was a difficult situation for the owner.

It was the peak vacation season, and there were no rooms available at other inns.

So the innkeeper bent over backwards to ask for a favor.

“Since you have booked a total of 120 rooms for students and staff of Colosseo Academy with extra rooms, I was wondering if you would be willing to change your reservation to a single room for two people… and use only 60 rooms in total. In return, I will only charge you 30% of the total accommodation fee and provide breakfast and lunch.”

It was a good offer.

The students weren’t too thrilled about the reduced rate, but the professors were.

“This will save us some money.”

“We could use the money to buy other textbooks.”

“That’s great, I was just looking for a new lab specimen to show my students.”

Professor Banshee nodded.

“Let’s do that. But only if at least 90% of the class approves.”

A vote was taken.

A straw poll was taken, and an astounding 93% of the students voted in favor of the double occupancy rooms.

Not only are the students at Colosseo Academy generally good-natured, but the friendships between students are also strong.

“Ahhh, thank you, thank you, thank you!”

The owner of the inn bowed his head several times, and then called the large group of guests waiting outside the door.

And then.

“…!”

The Colosseo students were faced with a group of people they hadn’t expected, and to a certain extent, had been anticipating.

Chapter 240

National University League (7)

◆

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire stopped eating and frowned.

“Ugh, those guests from outside were Varangians? I was hoping it was the Themiscyras.”

“Obviously, if there’s a large group of guests besides us at this time of year, they’re either Varangians or Themiscyra.”

“Wow. The inn seems so cramped now that the Varangians are here. Is it because they’re all so big? The average height must be about 195 cm.”

“Ugh, I’m suffocating. I smell sweat. I feel like it has become ten times narrower.”

“They must have been training somewhere, the way they’re sweating.”

As expected, the people who entered the inn were students from the Varangian Academy.

“Yikes. Thank goodness we found a place to stay.”

“I was already worried about being homeless before the tournament even started.”

“The kids from Colosseo Academy are nice. Thanks, guys!”

“Hahaha- I’m more worried about my stomach, so let’s eat!”

“Oooh, all-you-can-eat, great, ready for battle!”

The men of the Varangian made a beeline for the rice as soon as they entered their quarters.

The students of the Colosseo took up the eastern half of the spacious banquet hall, while the Varangians occupied the remaining western half.

“Now, let’s scoop up the food.”

At the head of the line of Varangian students was a man.

Bakilaga Juragio.

His massive frame and the scars all over his body made him look like a giant beast.

He stretched his pincers towards the meat on the large platter in front of him.

As he helped himself to the food, the students of the Colosseo Academy stared, secretly wondering how much meat he would devour.

…But.

“This should fill me up.”

With a single movement of his pincers, Bakilaga picked up a few pieces of meat and placed them on a small plate.

The Colosseo students gave him a surprised look.

They were surprised that Bakilaga, who looked like he could eat an entire cow by himself, only ate the average portion of a girl’s meal.

The Varangian students, however, had a different reaction.

“Oh, Mr. President, you’re eating a lot today.”

“You’re eating 1.5 times more than usual.”

“That’s not good for your stomach.”

“Well, maybe he’s going to work off some of that sweat with a personal training session later.”

What is this response? Does this mean that Bakilaga usually eats a little more here?

The looks on the faces of the students in the Colosseo became even more puzzled.

…Boom!

Bakilaga suddenly placed the meat on the small plate down on the buffet table.

Then he said.

“I’ll eat well then.”

He lifted all the remaining meat from the huge buffet plate.

With what seemed like dozens of kilograms of meat at his disposal, Bakilaga devoured them all in the blink of an eye.

“….”

A strange silence fell over the students of the Colosseo.

They were speechless with the fact that Bakilaga could consume what seemed like a month’s worth of food in a matter of minutes.

With that, the Varangian students began to raid the buffet in earnest.

“Food is all about turnover, so keep the meat coming!”

“The first five minutes of the meal is the most crucial time to eat as much as possible, otherwise you can’t eat much!”

“We are quantity over quality!”

“Meat after marching is the elixir of immortality!”

As the muscular hulks come and go, the food melts like ice cubes thrown in the sun.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Vikir watches Bakilaga eating at the table across from him.

Vikir’s attention was drawn to the choker stuffed around his neck.

“Did you say your grandparents were from Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain?”

The barbarian aura emanating from Bakilaga’s body was indeed vaguely familiar.

‘Perhaps there is some connection.’

Vikir fiddled with the choker around his neck.

Just then.

“Hey, what are we supposed to eat when you guys are done?”

“Is this dirty bastard crazy?”

The sound of arguing came from the center of the room.

Two boys were arguing in the center of the room.

A student from the Colosseo’s Cold Class and another student from Varangian were arguing over the line at the buffet.

“Why do you cut in and take the food! And sweep it all away!”

“It’s because I’m sick to my stomach at the sight of you carrying your food with tongs, and you’re not going to eat it all anyway.”

“That doesn’t mean you can ignore the line!”

“There’s no line at the buffet!”

When you’re in a long line at a buffet, and the person in front of you is munching away, and you want to eat something other than the food in front of you, should you push past him or her to get ahead?

This is a long-standing debate that goes back to ancient times.

Eventually, the two schoolboys from Colosseo and Varangian began to confront each other in a harsh manner.

“Oh, you meatball, your argument is nonsensical. Is your brain all muscle?”

“I was going to let it slide because I’m afraid I’ll lose muscle if I get angry, but I guess I’ll just have to chew on more anchovies.”

Their accusations weren’t directed at the other person individually, but at each others’ group respectively, so naturally, their friends joined in.

“This is why we shouldn’t have let those muscle fools in. We were being kind by turning a single occupancy room into a double occupancy room, and now they are not even thanking us for it!”

“What do you care? We paid our tuition and came here too. The inn we booked had a problem and the owner sent us here, so why should we care about you? We’re customers too!”

“If we didn’t make concessions, you guys would have to sleep outside!”

“Haha, you made concessions, your professors and our professors know each other and we agreed not to fight.”

“We voted on whether or not to let you in! 93% voted in favor, and you dare betray that favor!”

“Then you must be the 7% who voted against it, haha- we’re mercenaries in the first place, so we’re used to sleeping outside! Vote again if you want, we can leave!”

At this point, a burly schoolboy from the Varangian side stepped forward.

Boli Bollason. He was from a mercenary guild in the north and was currently a first-year student at the Varangian Academy.

At 217 centimeters tall and 150 kilograms, he was not far behind Bakilaga.

As Bollason stepped forward, the boys from Colosseo Academy flinched and took a half step back.

“What’s all the excitement about? Are these anchovies flapping around too much?”

Bollason purposely holds his head high and looks around, pretending to see no one.

The boys from the Colosseo are all looking at him with annoyance because of the huge height difference.

But there’s one who’s not too far out of his league.

“Can’t we have a quieter meal?”

It was Sancho Barataria, stepping to the front of his cowering friends.

With the big Sancho stepping up to the front, Bollason couldn’t help but feel a little smug.

But that didn’t end the argument.

“…Oho. Who is this?”

Bollason recognized Sancho’s face.

“Isn’t this the coward who ran away after Varangian’s entrance exam? How’s Colosseo Academy? Is it as cozy as a cradle? Are the people kind enough to be nice to a runaway coward?”

Apparently, he was unhappy that Sancho had gone to the Colosseo Academy even though he had ranked first in the Varangian’s entrance exam.

What’s more, Sancho had ranked first in Varangian Academy but only ranked fifth in the Colosseo Academy, and he had taken the risk of going to Colosseo Academy.

The fact that a talented freshman chose Colosseo Academy over Varangian made it seem like there was a clear distinction between the two schools.

The Varangians were understandably unhappy.

“Hmm, I guess you were in good shape when you took the Varangian entrance exam and you weren’t in good shape when you took the Colosseo entrance exam?”

Sancho nonchalantly replied to Bollason’s prodding.

“No, it was the other way around.”

“…What?”

“I was in the best shape when I took the Colosseo entrance exam, and I was in the worst shape when I took the Varangian entrance exam, and I still got those scores.”

At that, the fists of several Varangian hooligans, including Bollason, began to shake.

“Where did this bastard… sell his northern pride?”

“Are you crazy, Sancho, do you think you won’t come back to the North after you graduate?”

“If you come from a mercenary family, have the pride of a mercenary family, at least you shouldn’t be ashamed of it!”

“You’re such a dumbass after eating something warm and sleeping in the Imperial Capital, haha!”

But Sancho had friends who wouldn’t stand by and let him be criticized alone.

“Is there a barn around here where you can just hear the pigs squealing?”

“Tu, Tudor, cut the personal attacks…”

“Personal attacks, my foot. He’s right, the inn has been smelling like a barn since they came in.”

“It’s fine to be proud of your group, but don’t demean other groups.”

Tudor, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire were now standing in front of Sancho.

“Huh, look at these anchovies, are their heads well?”

Bollason opened his mouth in disbelief.

“Anchovies? Head? Is that what you are calling us?”

“Us?”

“Us?”

An eerie, low voice sounded from the side.

Across the table from Bollason, who flinched and backed away, stood the three brothers, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

With the National University League just around the corner, rumors of the three mad dogs of Baskerville were well known to the Varangian’s students.

This made even the most confident Bollason nervous.

Among the Varangian first-year students, there were not many who could meet the gaze of Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro with a straight face.

“Are those the tridents of the Baskervilles?”

“They’re assholes, just like I heard. Look at that murderous look in their eyes.”

“They’re the ones who got into a fight with that Varangian third year student at the last festival?”

“Yeah. He was a senior in our sports team, and he got beaten up … and was pretty beat up.”

“I heard on the train that they were giggling and laughing with a dagger in the back of one of the guys’ hands?”

Rumors of the personality and skills of the ‘Trident of Baskerville’ were already widespread among all schools. So most people see them as the top powers of Colosseo.

(Granola, who is secretly standing next to Sinclaire, may not agree with what they say)

Meanwhile, Bollason was annoyed that he had been pushed back from his confrontation.

He blurted out, not wanting to admit he was momentarily overwhelmed.

“I am Boli Bollason, a first-year Varangian student! I challenge Colosseo’s strongest first-year to a showdown! Let’s fight like warriors!”

Bollason scanned the room and glowered at Tudor, Bianca, Sancho, Sinclaire and the Baskervilles’ triplets, his fighting spirit blazing.

But.

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

No one answered him.

The brave aspiring knight Tudor, the always noble Bianca, the smart genius Sinclaire, and even the foul-tempered three brothers of the Baskerville family.

“…?”

Then the Varangian students, including Bollason, turned their heads.

Their eyes first followed those of the Colosseo students, who were all looking at the same spot.

And there it was.

“….”

There was a boy eating in silence, not paying any attention to the commotion.

It was Vikir.

Chapter 242

National University League (9)

◆

The reactions of those around him to Vikir’s victory over Bollason were quite mixed.

“Oh, that’s a shame. They were so close.”

“But he had a blank expression and Bollason whined a lot, so didn’t he actually lose?”

“Maybe he was just better at managing his facial expressions.”

“I think they were about equal in strength, so neither of their hands moved off the center.”

“Maybe he has lost his strength now, I should give him a try.”

However, some people saw this situation clearly.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, for example, knew of Vikir’s power.

“Vikir has been very generous.”

“That’s how you win.”

“But do you think even Vikir can beat all those people?”

“When I think about Vikir’s archery skills, I think he has really strong arms. But even then, facing that many challengers is too unreasonable.”

“I’m worried about my brother…… He has really provoked the fighting spirit of the Varangian Boot Camp boys.”

Meanwhile.

With all eyes on them, Vikir was reminiscing about the past.

‘It’s like the old times.’

Vikir was reminiscing about his time in the military before his Regression.

When the Age of Destruction first started, the Humanity Alliance Army Internal Affairs division had attracted all kinds of people.

Many among them were rough mercenaries from the north, most of whom were masters in arm wrestling.

Arm wrestling tournaments were a daily occurrence in the Internal Affairs division.

Vikir had seen many skinny and lightweight men took down men who were much more muscular and heavier than them.

Sometimes, comrades weighing less than 50 kilograms would go toe-to-toe with famous strongmen in their squad or platoon.

‘In arm wrestling, strength is important, but technique is more important.’

Or, more precisely, the skill of focusing strength only where it’s needed.

Of course, Vikir’s pure strength was also very strong, and he was able to overwhelm the Varangian Boot Camp students without using mana.

…Clatter!

In front of him, another muscular hulk grunted and twisted.

Vikir hadn’t even moved, his arm still pinned to his center.

‘He’s got a weak lower body, he’ll never be able to use the full strength of his arms.’

Even though Vikir could turn over, he kept his arm in place and didn’t move.

The big man squirmed as he held onto Vikir’s arm, and eventually gave up.

This time, just before the draw. It was the same scene as with Bollason.

“What the hell, man, why do you keep pulling out in tense situations?”

“The power was the same! His arm was stuck in the center!”

“These matches keep ending in nothing.”

“Yeah, that’s what happened with Bollason, but it wasn’t fun.”

These were the initial reactions of the students from Varangian Boot Camp.

But.

“…Forfeit.”

“Aaahhhh, he won’t budge at all, what is this power?”

“Geez, I’m forfeiting, let go of my hand!”

“…I, too, forefeit.”

All eyes were fixed on Vikir as one after another strong men challenged him.

“…Is that guy the real deal?”

“Are you forfeiting to him on purpose?”

“That’s ridiculous, how can he hold on like that, right in the center, without being pushed or pulled?”

“It doesn’t make sense, get out of the way, let me try!”

But when they tried their hand at it, all of them were unable to push Vikir’s arm back even a millimeter, and had to call it off.

When the number of forfeits exceeded thirty, a strange feeling began to rise in the room.

“All the first years were annihilated!”

“What kind of power is that? How is that possible at his weight class?”

“The sophomores are out too!”

“It’s like pushing a boulder, I can’t even move!”

“Oh my God, even the third year seniors lost.”

A clash of strength and power. But Vikir remained expressionless, taking them all in.

A mountain they couldn’t overcome, no matter how hard they tried, no matter how fast they ran. That was Vikir.

Vikir even tightened his grip and wouldn’t let go even if they wanted to, which is why the number of Varangians who struggled with all their might and then gave up in frustration was growing.

“…Oh my god.”

Dolores’ mouth was half open as she watched.

It was an unbelievable sight to behold.

To be able to fight on equal footing with the warriors of Varangian Boot Camp without using any mana, and to be able to overpower them.

As the student council president, she couldn’t help but chuckle as she watched the Varangian Boot Camp students, who she had secretly thought of as musclebrains, get beaten one after another.

“Euheum. Euheum!”

Dolores cleared her throat, covering her mouth, and glanced to the side.

Sure enough, there stood a stern-faced Bakilaga.

However, it was not humiliation that shone in Bakilaga’s eyes, but curiosity.

And then.

The massive grizzly bear stepped forward, shooing away the tiny puppies.

“Hey, freshman.”

Bakilaga stood in front of Vikir.

“You look like you’ve got a lot of energy. Do you want to have a fight with me?”

At his words, the mood in the room shifted drastically.

Every student from the Colosseo Academy and Varangian Boot Camp swallowed hard and turned to look at Vikir.

Even Dolores, the student council president.

…But.

“Line.”

Vikir’s reply was short.

A question mark appeared in Bakilaga’s head, and in the heads of all the spectators.

After a few seconds of silence, Bakilaga realized the meaning of Vikir’s words.

“….You want me to get in line?”

He nodded.

When Vikir nodded, Bakilaga stood for a moment with a dazed look on his face, then scratched the back of his head and said.

“Yeah. I’ll get to the back of the line.”

Bakilaga turned on his heel and walked to the back of the line of Varangian Boot Camp students who were standing in front of Vikir.

Everyone watching had to swallow hard.

The pinnacle of the Varangian Boot Camp, Bakilaga, was told to stand in line.

How confident does one have to be to say something like that?!

There were still a half-dozen Varangian Boot Camp students lined up in front of Vikir, but they all backed away when Bakilaga got to the back of the line.

Bakilaga chuckled and sat down in front of Vikir.

“Our school is a bit militant, like a giant mercenary army. There was a strict hierarchy, and a lot of people abused their power. People below a certain grade are almost treated like servants.”

“….”

“But since I became student council president, we’ve gotten rid of the power abusers and their bad practices, but the hierarchy is still strict.”

So when Bakilaga stepped forward, the other students fell back in unison.

Like wolves following their alpha.

And the trust the Varangian Boot Camp students had in their student council president was overwhelming.

“Can you imagine that person losing?”

“He’s a monster, he’s already beaten the 3rd graders as a freshman.”

“Our president will win no matter what!”

“Go! Juragio! Bakilaga! Go!”

Riding high on the cheers, Bakilaga smirked.

“Do you really think you can face me when you have taken on so many Varangian warriors before me? Do you really have that much strength left?”

“….”

Vikir did not answer. He merely rested his arms wordlessly on the stone table.

Bakilaga was still smiling. Bakilaga’s smile faded a bit as he took Vikir’s hand.

Tsk.

He could already feel Vikir’s strength and weight.

“…!”

Sensing that Vikir’s strength had gone far beyond the level of just ‘pushing’, Bakilaga gripped the table with his other hand.

It was the first time since he’d entered Varangian Boot Camp that he’d been surprised by another’s strength.

And then.

Poof! Kukugukuk…

The arm wrestling began.

Oh-oh-oh-oh!

Cheers from all around. Everyone from Colosseo Academy and Varangian Boot Camp cheered in unison.

Bakilaga and Vikir’s arms were locked together in the center of the table.

Only, Bakilaga is not giddy like the other Varangian Boot Camp students.

Vikir’s arms were twitching in a different way.

Their arms just swayed slightly in the center of the table. At first glance, it looked like they weren’t exerting any pressure on each other.

But in reality, between their grasping hands, great power and strength, grip and grip were fiercely clashing and mixing together.

A trickle of cold sweat ran down Bakilaga’s cheeks.

‘…This bastard, he’s strong.’

And Vikir was still glaring at Bakilaga.

‘At least it’s not at the student level.’

Vikir had a high opinion of Bakilaga, too.

In terms of pure strength, Bakilaga’s side was superior.

But Vikir had technique.

The angle of his arms and shoulders forced his opponent to use his arm strength and not his shoulder strength. The shape of his grip maximized the strength of his forearms, and the strategic placement of his fingers maximized the weight transfer through his triceps and shoulders.

Furthermore, the protection of the Styx River and the karma he had accumulated from slaying countless demons had made Vikir’s muscles even harder and sturdier.

Vikir’s delicate wrists hold up without even flinching despite Bakilaga’s enormous strength and weight.

Seeing this, Bakilaga smirked in admiration.

“You seem like a veteran who has seen it all. Calm and perceptive like my father. Who are you really?”

But… the smile vanished from Bakilaga’s face at Vikir’s next words.

…Tick!

Vikir unbuttoned his collar.

He showed off the choker around his neck and spoke in a low voice.

“Hunting grounds.”

Bakilaga’s eyes widened to the point of tears at Vikir’s words.

At that moment.

…Boom!

The table where Vikir and Bakilaga’s elbows touched cracked with a loud crack.

The heavy table that was made of thick stone was not a match for their strength and shattered into pieces.

Looking at the shattered stone table, the innkeeper muttered to himself.

“My God… this table was carved out of the rock that was originally on this spot when the inn was built.”

A rock that had been there since the beginning of time, and it had been smashed to pieces by two boys.

“….”

No one could speak in front of this amazing sight.

Then.

“Hahahaha-”

A cool laugh burst out.

It was Bakilaga, He was covered in stone dust and was looking this way, loosening his stiff grip.

His gaze was fixed on Vikir’s neck.

Then his mouth opened.

“??? ????? ????. ?? ???? ?? ??”

Words that were too fast to understand, words that were not even a language in the first place.

But Vikir understood it.

“You are the pride of Depth. Do not forget your roots.”

It was Ballak’s language.

Vikir remembered the information Sinclaire had told him about Bakilaga.

‘Did you say his grandparents were from the Depth?’

The choker Aiyen had filled Vikir with was a mark of the hunting grounds, something only the best hunters in the tribe could have.

Vikir remembered Bakilaga Juragio, one of the great heroes of the Human Alliance before his regression.

‘He said that he had been discriminated against since the first grade because of his barbarian blood. Did he feel a sense of kinship with me?’

It made sense why Bakilaga had fought with the fourth graders in freshman year.

And then. Bakilaga patted Vikir on the shoulder with a smirk on his face.

“That was a lot of strength, rookie! It’s getting late, so we’ll have to save our best power for tomorrow’s tournament! Hahaha-”

He leaned his head toward Vikir and spoke in a low whisper.

“I can’t even ask for a rematch, with your girlfriend over there glaring at me with her angry eyes.”

At that, Vikir turned his head with a puzzled expression.

There, Dolores stood, glaring at Bakilaga.

‘What on earth did you see that made you furious?’

Locking eyes with Dolores, Vikir shook his head.

“…?”

While Dolores was still trying to figure out what they were talking about, Bakilaga turned around with a smile on his face.

“That was a good fight, Colosseo! This first year’s strength contest was our defeat, but we will not lose easily in tomorrow’s tournament, for strength is not the only thing that makes a warrior!”

Bakariga called out as he walked towards his quarters, the Varangian Boot Camp students following him like a pack of wolves following their alpha.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and the others stood in awe at the scene.

“Wow, so this is a battle between men.”

“There’s something about Bakilaga, too. He’s a fine man.”

“This is exciting! I’m really looking forward to tomorrow’s match!”

And.

Bianca spoke up, a little distant from all the enthusiasm.

“They’re all gone.”

The students from the Colosseo Academy turned their heads in surprise.

The food on the buffet tables had all but disappeared.

Chapter 244

Survival Contest (2)

◆

Four hundred students were dropped in the jungle.

Despite the fact that they were separated by a wide distance from each other, it wasn’t long after the competition started that they were dropped one after another.

“Ugh… stomach, my stomach hurts so much. Wasn’t I supposed to eat that fruit earlier?”

“Yuck! Yuck! Yuck! I drank some stagnant water from the trough earlier and it made me vomit….”

“Ouch! Ouch! I’ve been bitten by something, my eye is tingling!”

The competition’s map, “Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain of Jungle,” was a harsh place in itself.

Poisonous mushrooms and fruits, contaminated water, insects armed with venomous bites, sweltering air and heavy humidity, vines and leaves that cut, sting, and sting, and the sheer density of it all was enough to keep them going for hours on end.

Sweat poured down their faces even when they stood still.

Simply holding on to the barrels of poisonous insects was a struggle.

Add to that the rapid dehydration, fatigue, and hunger, and if you eat something, you’re immediately poisoned or get food poisoning.

HP was melting like butter on a hot frying pan.

The HP stored in the specially designed suit increases and decreases with the wearer’s physical fitness and stress levels.

This means that the students must do their best to keep the HP in their suits from reaching zero in order to survive.

If it does, they will be forcibly teleported back to the waiting room.

Meanwhile.

“…Hmmm, hmmm, hmmm.”

Granola des Leviathans, the vice head of the Colosseo Academy’s Hot Class and a member of the aristocratic faction, was now sweating profusely and breathing heavily.

The reading on his HP suit read 74%.

Even though Granola hadn’t fought anyone since falling into this forest, 26% of his HP had already evaporated.

“This is insane, this jungle is hell. Are jungles like this really real?”

But no matter how much he complained, nothing changed.

Granola stared at the rainwater pooling in the hollows of the trees.

At first glance, it looked like drinkable water, but when Granola put his nose to it, he smelled a foul odor.

Straining his eyes, he saw tiny thread worms squirming and floating beneath the surface.

“…Ewww!”

Granola stepped back, suppressing nausea.

If I drink something like that for thirst, my stomach would immediately give a signal.

And I will lose a ton of water through diarrhea.

‘If I do that, I’ll have zero HP, and I’ll be eliminated before I can do anything.’

Granola turned away wearily.

He looks down at his waist and sees the fish he caught earlier.

As soon as I caught it, I scooped it up and dried it myself, but the humidity was so high that it didn’t dry quickly.

I put my nose and smelled it, and it smelled like it was already spoiled.

“Ugh, I can’t drink water and my food is spoiled. What can I do?”

Granola thought he could see why his seniors considered the Jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain to be the worst of the maps.

The real wilderness was terrifying enough to make Granola, the heir to the Leviathan, shudder.

Every poisonous mushroom or poisonous plant in the book looked a little different in real life.

They can be larger or smaller than they appear in the book, dusty, torn, upside down, dried, in the dark, or in the light.

And there are tons of variants, subspecies, and new species that aren’t even listed in the book.

“…Huh, yeah. If this body, which has mastered all sorts of poisons, can’t do this, I wonder what other lesser things it can do.”

Granola wiped the sweat from his brow and turned his head to see how his teammates were struggling.

…But.

“Oh, this is delicious.”

“Delicious.”

“Delicious.”

Over a roaring campfire.

The Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro are huddled over a bowl of white fish fillets cooked in boiling water on the trunk of a halved coconut.

And in the center of it all, a schoolboy sits with an expressionless face.

Vikir.

He was so nonchalantly, as if he were in his own home, adjusting himself to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

◆

‘It’s been a while.’

Vikir was feeling at home after all these years.

The jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain were familiar to him, both as a Ballak hunting ground and as a Baskerville hound.

The blade of a leaf cutting into flesh, the sting of an insect that made the bite swell, the heat and humidity that clenched his throat, all were familiar and nostalgic.

With a familiar gesture, Vikir found a flint and built a fire, soon warming the surroundings with a glow and not much smoke.

The sticky humidity was removed with spicy ash, and meals were made by roasting fish from the nearby river, mushrooms, and berries from the trees.

Water was purified with charcoal dust and baked earth, then boiled over an open fire for drinking.

The High, Mid, and Low Brothers also reported to Vikir and sought his approval before making their move.

“Hey. Vikir. Can we drink this water?”

“No.”

“Can you tell us why? It looks clear to me.”

“When I went upstream earlier, there were dead elk lying around.”

“I see, so even though the water looks clear, it’s full of microorganisms. What about these berries? Are they edible?”

“You can eat them if you steam them to evaporate the poison. If you just eat it, you’ll go blind.”

The group centered around Vikir.

Granola was amazed that ‘those Baskerville triplets’ were following Vikir’s instructions so obediently.

‘…That one. He’s a little more than I thought.’

Granola’s gaze drifted to the fish stew Vikir was stirring.

The reddish broth was boiling hot, with all sorts of vegetables and white fish floating around.

I can’t help but salivate under my chin as I stare at the spicy-looking soup.

‘Oh, no, I can’t beg a commoner for food.’

Granola fiddled with the spoiled fish wrappers in his pocket.

The thought of relying on a commoner now hurt his pride in being a member of the Seven Great Families.

In the end, though, there was no business before hunger. …

“Hey.”

At Vikir’s call, Granola turned his head, his eyes wide open.

A bowl of hot and spicy soup in a coconut bowl was held out in front of Granola.

“Eat as you want. I don’t know what you’re doing.”

Granola felt tears well up in his eyes as he listened to Vikir’s words.

‘…This commoner bastard. Maybe he’s a little nicer than I thought.’

And then Granola brought the spicy soup to his lips.

“…! …! …!”

His eyes widened to tears.

‘Delicious!’

Granola felt a shiver run down his spine at the shock of the tongue-melting flavor.

Anything tastes better when you’re camped outdoors.

Was it because I was so dehydrated and hungry?

Vikir’s spicy soup tasted better than anything I’d ever had from a top chef in the Leviathan family’s mansion.

‘I must ask him if he’d like to work in my kitchen someday!’

Granola gulped down the entire bowl of spicy soup on the spot.

Vikir stared at it, then threw some more mushrooms, fish, and dried worms(?) into the pot and let it simmer for a while longer.

Granola stared at it, drooling, as if having forgotten what he had just eaten, and then spoke shyly.

“There, there….”

“Eat more, there’s plenty.”

“Kuh, kuh, kuh, keuhm. Hm, thank you….”

Granola coughed a few more times, avoiding eye contact, then tilted the coconut bowl to scoop up the broth.

Mmmm, mmmm, mmmm, mmmm…

Granola gulped down another fifteen bowls before letting out a long burp as if to say thank you.

His HP, which had dropped to 41%, was now 92% full.

Granola patted his bulging belly.

Even with all the food he’d eaten, there was still a lot of spicy soup left in the big coconut.

Granola scratched his head and turned to Vikir.

“Hey, commoner… Vikir.”

When Vikir turned his head, Granola cautiously asked Vikir what he wanted to know.

“What is this fishy red stew, why did you make so much of it, from the looks of it you didn’t even eat much.”

Suddenly, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro turned to look at Vikir.

They didn’t say anything, but they must have been wondering.

“….”

Vikir was silent for a moment and closed his eyes.

Then, stirring the coconut pot slowly with a broad leaf, he answered.

“Fishing.”

Everyone’s heads tilted, including Granola.

Vikir making spicy soup with the fish he caught, and he’s going fishing again?

Vikir, in an unusual act of kindness, offers an explanation.

“I’m waiting for the prey to bite the bait.”

Even now, the leaf that Vikir is slowly stirring has become a fan, spreading the spicy and savory smell of hot stew.

It was slowly spreading across the jungle, accompanied by the faint glow from the residual fire.

And then.

…Rustle!

The prey, drawn to the warmth and delicious smell, had been trapped.

The sound of their approach to the bait grew louder and louder.

Thwack!

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro half-sheathed their swords at their hips.

Even Granola, who has removed his grimoire and staff, has a tense expression on his face.

“….”

Only Vikir remains calm, hiding behind a clump of bushes and watching the bonfire.

And then.

…Crisp!

A figure emerges from the bushes, drawn by the smell.

He looks exhausted and troubled, his tattered clothes covered in leaves and ashes.

The faces of Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro, and Granola turned in horror as they recognized the visitor.

And then.

“…?”

Vikir was just as surprised.

The voice from beyond the bushes was tired, but still clear as day.

“Whoa… what’s that smell?”

It was Dolores’s.

Chapter 245

Survival Contest (3)

◆

The sun sets quickly in the jungle.

The day was slowly turning dark, and the hot air was cooling down.

“Whoa… what’s that smell?”

Dolores emerged from the bushes, exhausted.

Her clothes were riddled with tears and stained with twigs, leaves, and dirt.

She had only 38% HP left.

Then.

“What?”

Dolores recognized the smell and the light that had been luring her.

A roaring fire, covered in ashes and emitting only warmth, and a red stew bubbling over it made her mouth water.

“Hey, why is this here….”

In her head, she knew it was strange. But her feet uncontrollably lead her to the source of smell.

The smell of the stew was too strong to ignore.

‘There are signs of human occupancy. There’s no sign of anyone lurking around, so it’s not like they’re preparing for an ambush. So someone made it to eat and then left?’

Someone prepared the food for a meal, but then had to leave for something urgent, or just abandoned the area.

That’s all she could think of.

Normally, Dolores wouldn’t have touched anything that belonged to anyone else, but….

‘I just have to stay alive, that’s the rule of survival.’

If that’s the case, I might be excused.

Dolores slowly reached for the stew.

Then.

Passasac-.

Someone stood up from the grass some distance away.

“Wait.”

It was Vikir.

Far enough away for a surprise, but close enough for Vikir, whose primary skill is the bow.

Dolores, however, was prepared for the archer’s surprise.

“…Was there an ambush again!?”

She quickly drew back, preparing her divine shield.

Vikir raised his bow and pointed it in her direction.

“….”

“….”

Vikir and Dolores faced each other.

Even if they were from the same school, the rules of the tournament made them enemies.

However, it would be inefficient for them to fight each other when the tournament was only halfway through.

So Dolores didn’t make a move.

“….”

“….”

The boy and girl, neither perfect allies nor perfect enemies, stared at each other in a strange silence.

And it was Dolores, or more accurately, her stomach, that broke the silence.

…Gurgle!

Dolores’s stomach, which hasn’t eaten in days, screams.

Dolores’s face immediately turned bright red.

Why did she feel so embarrassed when she got caught feeling hungry?

Especially when the one who caught her was a guy.

But the impassive Vikir didn’t care if Dolores’ stomach was singing opera or heavy metal.

The thirsty person digs a well. Eventually, Dolores, in a sorry state, raised her hand.

“…I think we should join hands for a while, since we’re from the same school. It’s still a long way from the end of the competition.”

“…Do as you please.”

Dolores’s brow furrowed once at Vikir’s lukewarm words as he drew back his bow.

With that, the atmosphere settled into a lull.

But there was more to Dolores than simply avoiding a fight.

“Hey, hey, hey, do you have any of that stew left, and if so, could you share some with me?”

She said with difficulty.

It was a pity that Dolores of all people had to beg for leftovers.

Dolores spoke quickly.

“Of course, I’m not asking for free! I can heal and buff you!”

In such a harsh environment, the presence of a healer would be essential.

So Vikir replied coldly.

“I don’t need one.”

“Okay, win-win… uh, what?”

Hearing Vikir’s answer, Dolores doubted her ears.

As it turns out, common sense doesn’t work for Vikir.

Hadn’t he burned more than half of the gnoll hides at the last bazaar because he found the alliance of aristocrats and nobles to be a nuisance?

Dolores looked at Vikir with a blank expression.

Then she realized why he didn’t need heals or buffs.

100% HP.

Vikir was in perfect condition, no fatigue, no damage.

In this jungle inferno!

‘How the hell is this possible?’

Dolores’s mind was spinning again.

“Hey, look, Common… Vikir.”

Granola poked his head out of the bushes beside Vikir.

He gave Vikir a puzzled look.

“Have you forgotten who she is? She’s a saint from Quovadis!”

“….”

“And she’s the student council president of the academy! As if that wasn’t enough, what….”

“….”

“Leaving all that aside, how can you refuse to help such a beautiful lady when she asks for help!”

Granola’s words were ones that any normal person could relate to.

…But Vikir was not an ordinary person.

Vikir twitched his ears once, as if he was annoyed, and three strong hands shot out from behind Granola to cover his mouth.

“Hey, bestie. Let’s have some bonding time together.”

“Let’s go.”

“Let’s go.”

Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro.

Vikir’s trident dragged Granola, who couldn’t even let out a squeak, and disappeared into the bushes.

The silent confrontation between Vikir and Dolores began again.

Then.

Dolores sighed lightly and raised her hands.

“I am not a saint of Quovadis, nor am I the student council president of the Academy.”

“….”

“I’m just a hungry lamb.”

It was a declaration of surrender.

Dolores remembered the words she had once heard.

-‘Who are you and why have you come to me at this late hour?’

-‘…I’m just a lost lamb.’

The first conversation with the Night Hound.

Deeply impressed with the Night Hound’s answer, Dolores had borrowed his words here.

And Vikir understood.

Vikir showed his approval by lowering his bow and stepping aside, and Dolores sat down at the campfire to eat the stew.

“Thank you.”

The stew that Vikir had prepared with his own hands had a pleasant smell.

Dolores’s nose twitched.

The oddly meaty smell of the stew must have come from the small garnish of mushrooms that Vikir had added as he handed her the bowl.

Gulp….mmm.

Dolores took a sip of the stew and her face lit up with surprise and delight.

“…Delicious.”

How could something taste so amazing in such a harsh environment?

It was the most delicious food she had ever eaten in her life.

Maybe it was the difference between a sweetfish and a snailfish, but that’s what it tasted like right now.

Dolores frantically emptied her bowl, oblivious to the red marks at the corners of her mouth.

A whopping thirteen times!

All this time, Vikir had been sitting next to Dolores without saying a word.

Finally, when Dolores was somewhat full, she turned to Vikir and said with a shrug.

“I’m afraid, I’m in this condition because I was attacked by Hohenheim of the Magic Tower right at the beginning of the tournament.”

Hohenheim’s nickname, ‘smart-ass with high nose’ was indeed a fitting one.

Dolores’s comrades rallied around her and fought to the end.

The death of a healer in a party would truly be catastrophic.

And as a result, Dolores lost all of her team members and survived alone.

Hohenheim, an excellent flame mage, was able to slaughter several groups on his own.

Dolores fought back by healing and buffing her allies around her, but she was ultimately defeated in a guerrilla war against Hohenheim, who was able to move in and out quickly on his own.

“Four of my team members were eliminated, because we were just chasing Hohenheim around and getting picked off one by one. It was a one-man show.”

They hadn’t asked, but it was valuable information nonetheless.

Granola and the Baskerville triplets’ eyes lit up as they listened carefully to Dolores.

It was not every day that they happen to meet a third-year ace in the middle of a tournament and getting her advice, so it was not surprising.

…But.

“Is that so?”

Vikir only nodded, his expression still blank, not showing any hint of his feelings..

The blank stare left Dolores speechless.

She began to observe Vikir carefully.

‘Why is he so nonchalant in the midst of this terrible jungle? How does he know how to cook this, and where does he get the ingredients?’

Vikir looks as comfortable as if he were in his own backyard and kitchen.

It was as if he was at home among Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Of course, Dolores didn’t knows that Vikir had been going in and out of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain for the past several decades, and that he lived there as his home for two years. Or the fact that he had stored fresh ingredients in his ring with a space magic comparable to the subspace magic of the Magic Tower. There was no way to know that ingredients and spices were being used little by little.

Meanwhile.

Fadak-fadak-fadak-fadak

Vikir continued to simmer the fish stew from earlier, fanning it with a broad leaf over the top.

The warmth and smell wafted across the jungle on the breeze.

On a dark night like this, the lights and smells would be even more intense.

Dolores scratched her head and asked.

“But who are you going to lure with the smell of this food? What if it’s a very strong one, like Hohenheim of Magic Tower, or Bakilaga of Varangian, or Lovegood of Themiscyra….”

Baiting prey with food was a good idea, but if the prey was too strong, the hunter could become the prey.

Dolores was inwardly worried that Hohenheim or Bakilaga would come.

Well, then.

With a plop-

Vikir replied, tossing an unseen mushroom into the coconut pot.

“I don’t care who comes.”

And then, as if waiting for those words.

Boom!

The grass in the front area was engulfed in huge flames and burned down.

Zap-zap-zap-zap-zap.

There was a louse walking out into the middle of the space where everything had been reduced to ash.

“What is this smell?”

A highly acclaimed genius produced by the Magic Tower.

The strongest contender at this point.

The top predator who had just single-handedly wiped out over 50 enemies.

A smart-ass with a high nose.

That was Hohenheim.

Chapter 247

Survival Contest (5)

◆

Aureolus Hohenheim. Who is he?

When it comes to the study of magic, it is not inferior to the Morgue family, known as the head of the magic family, when it comes to astrology, it is not inferior to the emperor of the empire, and when it comes to alchemy, Aureolus, who prides himself on being the best in the empire, is not inferior to the empire’s emperor. He is the eldest son of Aureolus family.

He has attended all of Mgic Tower’s prestigious higher education programs with distinction, and is now the student council president of his junior year, with an early graduation on the horizon, and a solid path to graduate school, and then to a professorship at Magic Tower.

In addition to the title of the youngest professor, there is even talk that he will become the next tower master of Magic Tower.

…Such an unattainable, ultra-elite genius began to moan so miserably and desperately that no one could open their ears and listen.

Poooooong…

It didn’t say it was a blowjob.

Soon, the moans that made one break out in a cold sweat just listening to it were followed by screams.

Pisisig-plop! Pussssss… pow!

This time, it didn’t come from his mouth.

“Kerr, kerrrrrrrrrrrr!”

Hohenheim clutched his stomach and began to stumble backwards.

His whole body twisted. His body began to curl like a shrimp thrown onto a hot plate of salt.

A damp, cold sensation, already drenched in sweat.

The internal organs in my stomach were fluttering and running wild so that I couldn’t control them even with magic.

‘I, I need to use Cure Magic….’

However, Cure Magic is a high circle magic that cannot be cast in such a chaotic situation.

Besides, he had been fighting too many battles with Bakilaga, so it was hard to manage his mana properly.

“…Poison. Poison?”

Hohenheim turned his head in disbelief.

A red stew was dripping from the coconut shell on the floor.

‘Boo, I’ve checked the ingredients, and there’s nothing poisonous in there. But why?’

Suddenly, something flashed through his mind.

‘A combination!’

His genius brain quickly realized the situation.

It exists sometimes.

Things that are harmless to humans when eaten separately, but turn deadly when mixed.

For example, honey and black tea, or eel and peach.

Other food combinations that are bad for the body (and usually induce excretion) include beer and peanuts, crab and red yeast, spinach and tofu, carrots and cucumbers, cheese and beans, and nori and salt.

Hohenheim desperately scanned the contents of the red stew.

In general, it was all okay, but why were these things included? There were also things I wanted to do.

Soon enough, Hohenheim singled out two ingredients that were extremely suspicious.

‘Chacachaca catfish, a man-eating fish native to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, and the bark of a sabac tree…?’

One by one, they are harmless enough, but together they cause a violent stomach ache.

‘Who the hell knows how to mix these things? What kind of son of a bitch….’

Hohenheim’s bloodshot eyes dart around the area, and then his eyes catch sight of a familiar face.

“…?”

There was a guy making a stupid expression beyond the bushes.

It’s just a kid from another school, a first-grader who doesn’t look like much, but Hohenheim’s genius memory recognizes him.

Granola de Leviathan. The heir to a family of extreme poisoners.

Although he is quite talented in his own way, he is still young and is a childish person who just wanders around laughing here and there.

…Yuck!

Hohenheim is convinced that it must be Granola who’s been messing with the stew.

Who else could have created such a poisonous stew?

Granola, meanwhile, is in a daze.

“Why, why are you looking at me like you’re going to kill me? What did I do….”

Then.

Tuck.

A hand gripped Granola’s shoulder.

It was Vikir.

“Congratulations, boss. Thanks to your poison, I’m catching Magic tower’s third-year ace.”

“Uh, huh? Me? My poison?”

“Yes. You and your poison.”

Granola can only shake his head, not quite understanding.

Unaware that behind him, Hohenheim’s gaze is growing ever more ferocious.

…Whatever.

Thud!

Hohenheim falls to the ground in an odd position, clutching his stomach.

Plop-plop-plop-plop.

Vomit and diarrhea. Fierce wailing from top to bottom.

“….”

Hohenheim trembles with his face buried in the ground.

…10 …9 …8 …7 …6 …5 …4 …3 …2

His HP was gradually dropping towards zero.

And in front of him stood Bakilaga of the Varangian with a bewildered look on his face.

“Hey …, are you okay?”

“….”

“…Okay. I get it.”

Bakilaga raised his hand, hesitated, and then moved it carefully again.

Thud.

Bakilaga laid a hand on Hohenheim’s fallen shoulder.

Blow it and it will go away, squeeze it and it will break, a very careful and deliberate encouragement.

But in spite of Bakilaga’s care.

…1

Hohenheim’s HP had just been knocked down by 1 with that blow(?).

“Meh, I’m sorry, I’m sorry. I didn’t mean to do that….”

“….”

“…Yes. I see.”

Bakilaga hastily dropped his hand from Hohenheim’s shoulder, and at the same time a drop of dew fell from Hohenheim’s eye.

As if they were longtime enemies, Bakilaga understood Hohenheim’s feelings.

No, it was something every human being could understand and empathize with.

We’ve all pooped our pants at some point in our childhood.

“…Tch.”

Bakilaga scratched his head and turned away, disappearing behind the bushes.

He didn’t know that the final duel he was looking forward to during his school days with his rival would end in vain like this, so he looked quite absurd and lonely.

…And.

A rustle!

A figure emerged from the bushes and stood in front of Hohenheim.

“…You!”

Hohenheim’s eyes lit up with life.

Vikir’s face was expressionless. Vikir stared at Hohenheim, who collapsed in front of him, holding his stomach.

Hohenheim’s eyes drooped and he smirked.

What’s there to be afraid of when everything has already shown its ugly face?

“Yes. In the end, the luck of catching me belongs to some unheard-of first year from the Colosseo.”

“….”

“Bastard. Yeah, well, when will you ever have the chance in your lowly life to take on a genius like me. Here, take my neck! Take my neck, and try to break the Hohenheim of Magic Tower with the weapons and special moves you are most confident in!”

Even in his final moments, he held on to his lofty pride, and embraced death with arrogance.

“Swords, axes, bows, any weapon you wish. You may break my body, but you will never break my pride and my heart.”

HP 1.

Only a handful of lives left.

Hohenheim glared at Vikir, his eyes narrowed in determination.

…But.

Vikir drew no weapon.

Just empty-handed. That was all he had.

“?”

Hohenheim’s brow furrowed slightly.

The instincts of genius, those keen senses, warned him frantically.

Some terrible weapon is being pointed at him.

But as he looked around, he saw no sword, no spear, no arrow, no magic.

‘What is it? This unexplained anxiety is….’

A cold sweat breaks out, drenching my lower back. My eyeballs were spinning.

For the first time in his life, Hohenheim was feeling a vague sense of anxiety and fear at the same time.

And at the sight of a mysterious new student from another school!

“….”

And then. A small change occurred in Vikir’s expressionless face.

His lips twitched, and his tongue moved for a moment.

And then the moment.

The coldest, sharpest word in the world stabbed Hohenheim right through the heart.

“You shit.”

Violence. And the most heinous violence of all.

It was verbal violence, but it was also factual violence.

It was Hohenheim’s pride, heart, and soul that could not be broken by sword, axe, spear, bow, magic, or any other weapon.

It ticks! It is being cut away with sound.

…0

Due to the extreme stress and anger, Hohenheim’s mental… No, HP has been depleted by 1 again.

That was the end of it.

◆

The end of Hohenheim, the ace of the Magic Tower.

It made everyone who was fighting for survival in the jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain anxious.

Dolores stared at Vikir, who had just killed Hohenheim with a single word.

“I… Vikir.”

“Yeah.”

“By any chance, was the spicy catfish soup I ate the same as the one Hohenheim ate?”

“Yes.”

At Vikir’s words, Dolores felt the back of her neck break out in a cold sweat.

“You were going to send me to … like that?”

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded again, this time in agreement.

Competitors, even if they were from the same school, they were still enemies to be fought over rankings.

Innocent Dolores’s face went white.

But the reason she was freaking out wasn’t because she was being eliminated from the competition or because she felt betrayed by her junior.

The original reason. That’s it.

“Oh, no, you can’t do that, please, please, please!”

I’ve already caused a similar(?) kind of trouble to Vikir.

If it was a small thing before, would it be a big thing now?

‘I’d rather kill myself!’

Dolores lurches backwards, covering her back with one hand and her front with the other.

Vikir thought it was as if he was seeing her before the regression, in the days of the Age of Destruction, when she was waging a desperate fight against countless demons during the age of destruction.

So he decided to make a quick correction.

Vikir pulled out a handful of dried mushrooms from his pocket and said.

“If you steam this and eat it together, you can neutralize the poison created by mixing the flesh of the Chacachaca catfish and the outer bark of the Sabac tree.”

“…!”

Dolores gulped as she remembered Vikir tossing a few mushrooms on top of the bowl when he handed her the stew.

“Well, what about what you said just now?”

“Just kidding.”

“….”

Considering that Dolores’ HP had evaporated by about 10% from what had just happened, it was possible to get some idea of ??how serious her mental damage was.

Chapter 248

Recap (1)

◆

The long, long college league is over.

<University League Rankings

1. Dolores L. Quovadis

2. Merelini Lovegood

3. Bakilaga Juragio

.

.

.

Dolores and Lovegood, who were expected to finish in the top three, finished first and second, respectively, and Hohenheim, the ace representative of Magic Tower, performed surprisingly poorly.

…But even these were not the biggest issues.

<University League Rankings

4. Highbro Le Baskerville

5. Middlebro Le Baskerville

6. Lowbro Le Baskerville

7. Vikir

8. Sinclaire

9. Granola

10. Hohenheim

.

.

.

The fact that there were first-year students in the top 10, and that there were as many as 6 of them, caused a great stir.

Up until now, the perception of first-years was that they were there for the experience and not really for the purpose of paving the way for upperclassmen, but this has completely shattered that stereotype.

The group that included Vikir fought hard and combined with Dolores to finish in the top 10.

Meanwhile, Granola was blamed for Hohenheim’s elimination and was relentlessly pursued by Hohenheim’s followers, eventually becoming the first member of the group to be eliminated.

(Granola was quite resentful, but he was also proud of himself for eliminating Hohenheim).

Then there’s the first-year who surprisingly single-handedly carried the team to a high score.

Sinclaire, a commoner with no family name.

Her entire background is shrouded in mystery, and she managed to place 8th on her own, completely unrelated to Vikir.

Considering that her teammates Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were all outside the top 20 (which is actually quite a feat for a first-year!), it was truly an amazing achievement.

Colosseo’s first and second years rode this momentum to a number of high rankings, beating out third years from other schools, with Dolores also taking the top spot.

Meanwhile, despite the tournament being hosted by Magic Tower, none of their students made it into the top 10 except for their top ace, Hohenheim.

And Hohenheim barely made it to the top 10.

He was eliminated quickly, but only because his previous battle performance was so good.

However, there was no way that such results would be noticeable to Hohenheim, who were aiming for the championship.

Moreover, following the tradition of recording the scene at the time of elimination on video and permanently recording it in the video box, Hohenheim’s final appearance was forever preserved in the tournament’s Hall of Fame.

‘Shit.’

Hohenheim would suffer forever even after the tournament was over.

◆

After the first round of the tournament, there was a brief after-party at the inn.

The students of Varangian had been relocated because the water pipes in the inn they had originally booked had been repaired, so it was only the students of the Colosseo Academy who were celebrating.

“Cheers to President Dolores, the number one ranked student this time!”

“Cheers!”

“Cheers!”

All the students raised their glasses high in celebration.

Amidst all the noise, Tudor raised his glass and looked over at Vikir next to him.

“Congratulations, buddy, I can’t believe you’re seventh in the first year, It’s amazing that there’s a guy like this among my friends!”

“That’s the hundredth time you’ve said that, Tudor.”

Sancho, next to him, smirked.

Pigi, who was in the front, continued.

“By the way, Vikir. How did you end up in the same group as the Baskerville triplets this time?”

It was a question everyone wanted to know.

But Vikir’s answer was simple.

“We teamed up once before for a Naphtali game and the midterm exam, and it worked out surprisingly well. After that, they often asked me to lend them a hand.”

Hearing that, Bianca said nonchalantly.

“And since you’re a commoner, they might have felt there was no pressure.”

“Hey, Bianca!”

“Huh? No, I’m not saying that! I guess that’s what they would do. Sorry if it sounded bad, I didn’t mean to….”

Bianca was slightly taken aback by Tudor’s point, but Vikir waved it off.

“You’re right. I suppose children of high ranking noble families can get on each other’s nerves.”

Being from a commoner’s family isn’t really a flaw, so who cares.

But Vikir isn’t the only commoner in the group.

Sinclaire, an honor student who finished eighth in her freshman year despite being a commoner.

“….”

For some reason, this girl, who usually joins in whenever there’s a topic about Vikir, is quiet today.

With her personality, it would be natural for her to say something cheerful like, ‘What! Why do you look down on commoners? You’re better than them!’ or ‘Brother Vikir, let’s support each other like us commoners!’

So, while everyone was thinking something strange.

“Come on.”

Vikir was the first to say something encouraging.

“Uh, uh…… huh. Go for it! Go for it!”

Sinclaire seemed to come to her senses and waved both her fists at Vikir.

His friends were quick to change the subject, as Sinclaire tends to be a little less talkative when the subject of his origins comes up.

“Well, that concludes the first round. The second round is only for those who finished in the top 10 in the first round.”

Pigi explained the rest of the competition.

Survival of the first round. From there, the top 10 will be assigned individual tasks for the second round.

If you successfully solve the ‘quest’ given here, you will finally be awarded a peerless artifact jointly managed by Colosseo, Magic Tower, Varangian, and Themiscyra.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca explained the rules and format of the second round for Vikir and Sinclaire, who advanced to the second round.

“The second round is about adapting to the apprenticeship system.”

Everyone nodded as Pigi explained.

The 10 people who survived the first round will each go outside the school and visit higher-ranking working groups to fulfill their requests.

The working groups are the seven great families of the empire and the imperial family, and the idea is that the students at the academy will be working for them after graduation, so they should get some hands-on experience beforehand.

In other words, the ten survivors of the first round will each go to Baskerville, the Iron Blood Swordsman, Morgue, the Mage Sect, Quovadis, the Faithful, Usher, the Divine Archer, Donquixote, the Creative Spear, Leviathan, the Extremely Poisonous, Bourgeois, the Tycoon, and the Imperial Family to receive different quests from each of these Houses, solve them, and receive a certificate with the seal of the House stamped on it to show that they were actually helpful, and their work is done.

The content and difficulty of the quests varied from house to house, ranging from the basic quests, such as hunting down a dangerous high-ranking monster or collecting a specific object, to the abstract, such as solving poverty in a particular region, answering a deep philosophical question, or designing a political system or method of diplomacy.

“If the student undertaking the quest is a member of a certain house, it is customary to avoid them. It’s not a rule that must be followed, but still.”

Everyone nodded at Pigi’s words.

For example, Dolores, who would be taking on the second round of quests this time, would not be able to take on the quests of the Faithful Quovadis.

It would raise questions of objectivity.

Pigi continued.

“As for Vikir and Sinclaire, neither of them belong to any of the Houses, so it shouldn’t matter, but if they do, they’d better take the easy quests from the Seven Houses, as they all have their own difficulty levels.”

For example, quests from the Faithful Quovadis family are generally rated at three and a half stars (★★★☆).

This means it’s an average difficulty level.

However, quests from the House of Morgue the Mage are typically rated four and a half stars (★★★★☆).

This is because, on average, tasks of that difficulty are required.

Soon, the friends were debating which House’s quests would be most advantageous.

“I think you should avoid House Morgue’s quests, they’re really tough now that they’ve had a change of leadership.”

“Personally, I don’t mind the Donquixote quest, as long as you like the sea and adventure!”

“I think your family will give you a task like ‘found a desert island’.”

“Well, if you look at the tasks in the second round of the tournament so far, the task from the Bourgeois family was the easiest.”

“That’s right, I think it’s a good idea to pick a bourgeois task.”

“Hmm, that’s going to be competitive.”

Just then, Sinclaire shyly raised her hand.

“You know, I already have a family in mind.”

Everyone’s eyes widened. It was rare for Sinclaire to state his opinion so clearly.

“Personally, I’m thinking of taking a quest from either the Imperials or the Faithful Quovadis.”

Puzzlement flashed across her friends’ faces.

This was because both the Imperials and the Quovadis had relatively difficult tasks compared to the other houses.

“Why the Imperials and the Quovadis?”

Bianca asked, scratching her head, and Sinclaire smirked.

“Because ….”

While her friends’ eyes were glued to Sinclaire.

With a swipe-

Vikir stood up from his seat.

He made his way to the terrace, away from the crowds.

‘It’s a task for the second round.’

All that remains is to cross the final gateway and retrieve the artifact from a treasure trove shared by the four universities.

The Seventh Corpse Decarabia, which will finally allow him to eliminate the fourth Tenth Corpse.

Vikir is sitting on the railing of a terrace in the dusk, contemplating what to do next.

From out of nowhere, he hears a voice calling his name in a calm, even tone.

“Vikir.”

In the midst of the noisy party lights, the ghost-like curtain is lifted and a blank face is revealed.

Dolores.

The winner of the first round of the University League had come to visit Vikir.

Quite secretly.

Chapter 253

The Grave of Swords (1)

◆

Vikir has entered the depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

From the Western Front at 207, he follows the ridge of the lowlands to the banks of the Salt River in the distance and sees a familiar place.

The village of Ballak. It was once a place where Vikir had spent much of his time.

…But there was nothing here now.

Ballak’s warriors had moved deeper into the jungle after the events of Ah’Heman, and Vikir hadn’t seen them since.

Even the occasional letters from Aiyen had ceased at some point, and there was no way to know their news.

‘According to Cindywendy’s testimony, Ballak’s warriors did not show up for the trade, either. What happened to them?’

The natives of Jungle all hailed Vikir as a hero and were fully cooperating with the Cindywendy’s trade, but Ballak was not among them.

Even the Cindywendy were puzzled by the recent loss of contact with Ballak.

But Vikir dismissed her concerns.

“…They are not a people to be taken lightly.”

There are many outstanding warriors in Ballak.

Their leader, the night fox Akwilla, is a fearsome force, and her daughter, Aiyen, is strong enough to cross into the realm of the dead at a young age, so they are not the ones to worry about.

‘Once they cut off contact and hide, there is no way to find them here.’

They say no news is good news, so it was best to believe that we would hear from them again soon.

“For now, let’s focus on finding the Wraith Tree.”

Vikir snapped back to reality.

The Wraith Tree. It was an ancient artifact, a type of mana alchemy that was now the stuff of legend.

A tree of mana that took root in a mage’s mind, nourished by the karma of the soul.

An incomprehensible being that feeds on abstraction and metaphysics and delivers its harvests to the material world.

It appears in a mythological book entitled The Return of the Magic Hound, an ancient text that tells the life story of Morgue Tzersi, one of the old ancestors of the Mage head Morgue.

The date of the myth’s creation is unknown, but it is believed to have occurred during a time when the continent was a collection of small states before it was unified into a single empire.

The story has been passed down through the Morgue family for so long that no one has given much thought to its authenticity.

But Vikir, who had seen the future, knew.

For when the Age of Destruction came, there was a being who had actually used this wraith tree.

‘…Snake, King of the Dead. Contractor of Seere. The Wraith Tree was originally an ancient artifact that was supposed to fall into his hands.’

This man, now lost to history, was the one who was supposed to be the owner of the Wraith Tree.

Seere used Snake’s body to control the Wraith Tree, which gave him terrifying powers.

On the surface, the Wraith Tree is nothing more than a dry, gnarled, dead tree.

But the plant feeds on the will of the dead, and after absorbing countless deaths and wraiths, the Wraith Tree grows trunks as tall as the world itself, and skull-like fruits dangle from its branches.

Wraith Tree seeds require a great deal of death to germinate.

As the Wraith Tree grows from the manure of countless wraiths, it hangs fruit at the end of its branches that contain the wraiths it has absorbed, and when eaten by humans, the wraiths’ powers and skills become their own.

As such, a mage with a wraith tree planted in his or her soul is inevitably drawn to the black magic, and is bound to walk a path marked by countless blood and lives.

When the pre-regression Snake gained possession of the Wraith Tree, he turned the corpses of the countless dead he had killed into an army and consumed them all, turning their souls into fruit.

‘…His mana was comparable to that accumulated by the once-in-a-millennium genius, Camus Morgue, through natural talent and hard work.’

Their battles were of such magnitude that they shattered the sky and turned the earth upside down.

Vikir, a lowly officer, didn’t dare to look them in the eye.

‘An entire island was wiped out in their fight.’

Whatever.

In times of peace, the Wraith Tree would remain hidden as a seed or small bush; in times of war, it would grow into a mythical thing, its trunk and branches as vast as the mythical World Tree.

This time, I will need this Wraith Tree to add to the power of my allies.

Therefore, it was essential to get it first before the Age of Destruction arrived.

‘Seeing as I am attracted to this, it seems that Pomeranian qualities are considerable.’

To show such obsession and affection for something that a normal black mage would never dream of, Pomeranian certainly has the potential to be a great black mage.

After all, there’s something to be said for having a connection with an ancient artifact like this.

…Chak-chak!

Vikir jumped down from under a large tree using the young madam’s thread.

“From here.”

Vikir’s current destination was a deserted area deep beneath the jungle.

It was an unusual desert with vast expanses of white sand.

The Yuuni Desert. A salt desert, one of the driest deserts in the world.

An area dominated by extreme dryness that doesn’t allow for even the slightest bit of moisture.

All that can be seen is white, salty salt and withered vegetation.

Hmph.

Vikir bent down and dug his fingers into the white sand at the bottom.

When I finally removed my finger, I saw that the tip of my finger was severely wrinkled.

It was a grotesque salt sand that sucked the moisture out of everything it touched.

Long ago, this vast salt desert was created from the dried tears of an evil god, and this salty dry season has claimed the lives of countless creatures.

The mummified corpses of countless monsters lay strewn across the white sands as proof.

Vikir walked in the center of this salt desert for a while.

Then he spotted something quite remarkable.

“…!”

It was the remains of a giant monster, nothing but bones and skin.

Danger Rating: S

Size: 44 meters

Found in: Ridge 10, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Named the Dragon of the Saha river.

A terrifying creature believed to be a hybrid of a dragon and a demon.

Its breath causes birds in the sky to fall to their deaths, and where its scaly body once crawled, a place becomes a desert where no grass grows for half a century.

Its mere existence is a terrible disaster, but for some reason it seems to have made its home on the Tenth Ridge of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, where it has remained motionless.

The moment it moves, mankind must be prepared.

No amount of spear and magic can slay this fierce terror!

Three disasters outside the world.

Adonai the Archer, Madam Eight-Legs, and the final one, the Basilisk, the dragon of Saha.

“I was worried that this thing would go on a rampage after Madame disappeared, but… why is it dead here?”

Basilisks and spiders are not natural enemies.

In this way, Madame and Saha have been bitter enemies for a long time.

With each holding the other in check, neither could move easily, and with Madam Eight-Legs gone, I expected that the other side would become stronger.

…But?

“I was going to go hunting anyway, but you’ve relieved me.”

I hadn’t expected to find a basilisk lying dead in a place like this.

The hunt had been carefully planned out.

Vikir carefully examined the basilisk’s corpse.

It did not appear to have died at the end of its life.

Not only was it much smaller than the ones Vikir had seen during the Age of Destruction, but it was also clearly riddled with sword marks.

Wounds were evident where the sword had torn through leather, dug into flesh, and broken bones, and where the wounds had rapidly regenerated due to the basilisk’s immense regenerative powers.

The scorch marks from the aura around it were also clearly visible.

The thick scales of the basilisk were densely covered with marks that looked like liquid splashes, indicating that the man must have been a highest level Graduator.

As I retraced all of these trajectories, a clear pattern emerged.

‘The Baskerville Four!’

It seems that long ago, a hound of the Baskervilles fought a lonely battle here.

Vikir searched the area around the basilisk’s corpse.

Sure enough, not far from the basilisk’s corpse, the tattered remains of a black wind whipped about.

A skull worn down by the cold wind.

The tattered uniform of a Baskervillian lay on the white salt sand.

His thick cloak was unmistakably a symbol of his affiliation with the Pitbull Knights.

A knight of the Baskervilles, long dead and unrecognizable.

Judging by the fact that he only had four teeth at the time of his death, he was probably from a lesser background.

However, he practiced the 4th Form for so long that he was able to single-handedly slay the Dragon of Saha.

Vikir was silent for a moment as he looked at the ashes, as if he were seeing himself before his regression.

Then he turned to the nameless pit bull in front of him and said a silent prayer.

“ …Go to a good place.”

Then, the gold badge symbolizing the Senator was carefully laid down in front of the remains.

It was as much respect as Vikir could muster.

Then.

“…?”

Something caught Vikir’s eye as he bent to pay his respects.

A flutter.

Something was visible between the ribs of the ashes.

It was a bundle of parchment that looked very old. It was a letter addressed to someone.

The seal was red, indicating that it was a top-secret military secret, written by the head of House Baskerville himself.

“…Is this Hugo’s?”

The letter had been buried in dry salt, so it was very well preserved.

Without hesitation, Vikir broke the seal and opened it.

Soon, the contents of the letter began to be etched into Vikir’s retina.

…It was quite an eye-opener.

Chapter 254

The Grave of Swords (2)

◆

Crisp.

The parchment, dried out by the salt, crumbled.

A familiar handwriting appeared on it.

‘Dear Brother C’ – With the concern of my younger brother Hugo.

Vikir first checked the letter’s sender.

As expected, it was Hugo Le Baskerville. This was not surprising, as the seal on the letter was for top military secrets that could only be handled by the head of the House.

But there was something odd.

“…And your brother?”

Hugo was clearly the eldest son of the Baskervilles and the head of the House. But was there anyone else he could call brother?

It was unthinkable, even within the family.

Suddenly, Vikir’s mind flashed back to something Hugo had once said.

‘It’s okay to eat for free.’

‘Hehehe. That is correct. This father also worked hard to become the eldest son when he became the head of the family.’

This was part of a conversation I had once when I was beating the crap out of the triplets Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

The first time I heard this, I wondered if being the oldest son could be considered trying.

But now I get it.

Hugo was not the eldest son, but he became the head of the family after killing or defeating all of his older brothers in a desperate power struggle.

In other words, he became the eldest son by accident.

Was there still anyone left that Hugo could humbly refer to as his brother and call him his brother? That’s the question.

‘If I think about it, there’s probably not much left.’

Vikir read the letter in its entirety, searching his pre-regression memory.

My fifteen-year-old son has just returned from two years of surviving alone in the jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Therefore, I am planning to organize a small dinner, and if you are able, I hope you will be able to attend and honor him.

It has been a long time since we have seen each other.

The return of my brother, the most powerful of the Seven Counts, would certainly be a great boost to the family in itself.

I look forward to hearing from you.

In short, the letter said that Vikir had survived from the jungle, and to come to the great banquet.

Vikir looked at the letter and stroked his chin.

It wasn’t as old as Vikir thought, and he’d never seen Hugo write so formally before.

Now he realized who this letter was supposed to be addressed to.

‘Dear Mr. C. And the Seventh Count….’

In iron-blooded swordman Baskerville, there are seven counts who spend their days in battle.

The world calls them the Seven Counts.

The position is a very old one, dating back to the Warring States Period, before the founding of the Rock Empire, when the continent was a mess of colorful jellies on a map.

Back then, kings were just small provincial lords, and the current empire unites them all into one empire, and the Seven Houses.

For example, Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman, controls the barbarians in the wilderness, and Donquixote, the spearman, controls the wandering tribes of the sea.

One House, One Nation.

A time when a single family was prosperous enough to function as a nation.

A time of chaos, when everything was gradually merging into one empire and seven families.

This was actually the heyday of the Seven Counts system.

The Seven Counts were able to fight throughout the Western Front by mobilizing their family’s military authority without the permission of the head of the family.

The seven-headed carriage that led the golden age of the Baskervilles, when monsters, barbarians, and other families were all afraid of the teeth of the crazy fighting dog.

But after the Empire unified the continent, the battlefield on a grand scale disappeared.

Smaller, localized wars have always existed, but not with the same chaos.

Chaos on a massive scale, where entire old bloodlines disappeared and dozens of castles collapsed in a single day.

With the end of the era of the great wars, the power of the Seven Counts naturally diminished.

So sometimes the old Baskervilles in the Senate would reminisce about the past and remember the ‘Seven Counts of those days’.

Anarchy. The seven teeth of the sword that ran through the battlefield without anyone paying attention, that freedom, that romance.

Their argument was that this was the true Seven Count. The current politicians who are only focused on political warfare do not deserve to be called the Seven Counts.

‘Certainly, those were the days when the power and might of the seven counts was truly household.’

Vikir thought back to the past.

When Vikir had returned to Baskerville after his time with Ballak, Hugo had held a great banquet in his honor.

Those invited at that time were the current Seven Counts, the seven knight commanders who enjoyed the most powerful power after Lord of the House and Young Lord of the House.

Each and every one of them wanted to take Vikir into their order, which is why they all wanted to attend the banquet, which was not usually attended.

‘Isabella’ Le Baskervilles, Leader of the Doberman Knights.

‘German’ Le Baskervilles, leader of the Shepherd Knights.

‘Metzgerhund’ Le Baskerville, Leader of the Rottweiler Knights.

‘Cu-Chulainn’ Le Baskervilles, Leader of the Wolfhound Knights.

And even Boston Terrier Le Baskerville, leader of the Pitbull Knights, and Great Dane Le Baskerville, leader of the Mastiff Knights.

However, due to distance and time, only the Count of Boston Terriers, the leader of the Pit Bull Knight, and the Count of Great Danes, the leader of the Mastiff Knights, actually attended the Great Banquet.

‘…Later, Cindywendy told me that the number of Seven Counts who wanted to attend was six.’

Indeed. In fact, when Vikir returned from the Depht of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, there were only six of the Seven Counts who wanted to attend the Great Banquet, not all of them.

That’s because one of the seven had turned his back on the world and gone into hiding.

Although he had long since lost contact, he was the strongest and oldest of the seven.

Countless letters and messengers were sent by the Baskervilles in an attempt to determine his whereabouts, but none were returned.

And even from those who went to deliver the letters.

So the perception was that there were really only six of them.

“…, The unreachable seventh count, this must be him.”

Vikir could clearly identify the person the letter was referring to.

A being that Hugo calls ‘Brother C’.

He was the only one of the current seventh counts to have a name among the old seventh counts.

He was the last of the original seventh counts, the one who lived through the turbulence of the Warring States.

Even Hugo, who had killed all his brothers and ascended to the position of Lord of the House, could not do anything about it until the end.

This was Cane Corso Le Baskerville.

◆

Vikir had a clear idea of why the unnamed pit bull that delivered his letters died.

Whiiiiing-

A terrifying storm sweeps across the desert.

The grains of white salt sand that twist along with the wind spread across like a huge castle wall, sweeping away and drying out everything.

It’s an extremely dry season, and everything that touches it is stripped of moisture and dried to a crumb, soon to be shredded by sharp grains of sand.

Vikir walked through it, wrapped in his black cloak.

‘It’s certainly tough, for sure Graduators will die.’

It was hard enough to simply survive, but if a Basilisk, an S-ranked Dangerous Monster, came at you, you would truly have no choice but to die.

Even if you’re a top-notch Combat Pro of the Graduator.

Caw!

A large crow flies across the sky.

They are targeting the corpse of Vikir, who died after being caught in a storm.

But even the crows in the sky can’t escape the power of the salt storm.

Failing to calculate the distance, the huge bird of prey’s neck and wings were snapped by the force of the storm, and soon began to be salted while floating in the air.

…Pow!

Soon, the crow’s dried-up mummy lay on the ground.

Its entire body was broken and crushed, but it had been killed by the rapid dehydration that had occurred before.

“…Hmm. If there were Basilisks, I wouldn’t have gotten in either.”

Vikir muttered as he made his way through the storm.

He was barely making it through with his body strengthened by the River Styx and the magical regeneration he had absorbed from Beelzebub.

…How many hours had passed?

As I broke through the salt storm, I saw something strange in the center of what had been a white sandy field.

A tower. A black tower.

It was a strange, bizarre structure that could only be described this way.

Shaped like an awl sticking out of the ground, contained both the black color of the night sky and the red color of blood.

The cold metallic material of its walls was unidentifiable, and its height was impossible to guess.

However, what was certain was that inside this tower in front of Vikir was an extremely high-level spatial distortion magic that was incomparable to the one in the Magic Tower.

“…This actually existed.”

Vikir had certainly seen this tower before.

Not with the naked eye, but briefly in his pre-regression childhood, when he had just escaped from the Cradle of Swords, in his infantile liberal arts classes.

It was a figment of imagination, a fictional entity that always appeared on the margins of textbook pages when we studied the family mythology of the Baskervilles.

But here it was, standing tall and real.

“…!”

Upon reaching the tower, Vikir saw the words crudely carved by someone with a sword in front of the supposed entrance.

‘The Grave of Swords.’

From cradle to grave.

It must be someone’s dying words.

Chapter 255

The Grave of Swords (3)

◆

From cradle to grave.

The life of an Ironblood Swordsman Hound consists of nothing but swords.

“A true Baskerville is born in the Cradle of Swords.”

Vikir quietly recited what everyone in the world knew.

…But the legend passed down in the family has a backstory.

“A true Baskerville dies in the Grave of Swords.”

It was written on a page of an old history book, faded and stained with faded marks.

An old myth that everyone thought was just fiction.

But the moment Vikir found the Grave of Swords, he knew it was true.

He realized that among the proverbs of the Baskervilles, none of them were lies.

Literally, from the cradle to the grave. The roads of Baskerville are made entirely of swords.

Once again, Vikir realized that this was the fate of the iron-blooded swordman hound.

Plod, plod, plod, plod.

Vikir walked up the steep stairs of the tower.

The stairs rose high, each one pointed like an awl.

A normal person would not have realized they were stairs.

If the inside of the Magic Tower was mysterious, beautiful, and dreamlike, the inside of this Black Tower was terribly lonely, suffocating, and isolating.

Every step felt like a flesh being sliced off by the surrounding rock formations, stalactites, and nameless rusted swords embedded everywhere.

Countless swords are glaring with their tips raised. If you were a prosecutor with a keen sense of energy, you could feel it even more closely to your skin.

Stinging – countless stabs, constant sharpened gazes.

The higher you go, the more you feel your whole body shrinking, little by little.

A staircase that is worn down, cut out, and chipped away, and can only be climbed by taking one step at a time.

If Vikir hasn’t reached the Swordmaster level, let alone climbing the stairs, he would have been ovulated to death upon entering the tower.

Finally, Vikir reached the upper levels of the tower.

It was a scene reminiscent of the Cradle of Swords, with countless swords on display, but something far more murderous and sharp filled the empty hollow.

…That is because of the man sitting on the throne in the center of the space.

A iron throne of sharp swords.

And there, a man in thick iron armor, with a long gray beard.

Beneath his gray eyebrows, what should be the whites of the eyes are filled with empty darkness, and in the center of those eyes, red as the sun burns coldly.

His nose was sharp as a sword, his lips tightly pressed into a line, and his dead, blue skin was so dry it barely covered his skull.

His dark heavy armor and massive greatsword made the throne he was building seem even more formidable.

“…!”

Vikir recognized the old man’s identity at once.

Cane Corso. Cane Corso Le Baskerville.

Even Hugo, who had killed all his brothers to become Lord of the House, couldn’t do anything about him until the very end.

A former Seven Counts who has been experienced difficult times, and the strongest of the current Seven Counts.

The average level of inactivity for the Seven Counts lies somewhere between the top grade of Graduator and the path to Master, but this is absolutely not the case in the case of the Cane Corso.

Cane Corso is Hugo’s older cousin by blood, but their ages are separated by nearly a generation.

Even before he turned his back on the world and went into hiding, he was already stronger than Hugo, the Swordmaster, and was literally the legend of the sword.

…Is that why?

Cane Corso never showed his face at family events, such as the Great Banquet or the House Council, and he refused all the attendants and knightly orders that a Seven Counts normally would have.

He never intervened in the affairs of the world, and in his later years he went into hiding, erasing all traces of himself.

His deeds have been recorded only in literature, and they are so unrealistic that even the direct descendants of the House of Baskerville do not immediately believe it.

However. There was still no denying that Cane Corso was Baskerville’s strongest swordsman.

‘If my brother had been greedy for the seat of Lord, I would not be sitting here today.’

Even the great Hugo had admitted as much.

…Meanwhile.

‘So here I am.’

Vikir thought quietly to himself.

Before Vikir’s regression, Cane Corso had not been seen in the world during the Age of Destruction.

However, there was one incident that suggested he was not dead.

On one occasion, a vast army of demons marched across Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Their purpose, of course, was to conquer the human world.

After crossing the mountain range, they gathered together and realized that several of the legions that were supposed to be there were nowhere to be seen.

The demons and the human alliance quickly tracked their location.

And what they found was astonishing.

Countless, uncountable numbers of demons had perished in their attempts to cross the Yuuni Salt Desert.

Sure, salt storms and basilisks existed, but it didn’t make sense for several legions to be wiped out.

So the Demon Soldier Chasers were dispatched to investigate.

…But none of the demons that entered the salt desert survived.

They were either missing or found as torn and tattered corpses.

And even then, they were only found after being blown far away by storms.

So the Human Alliance concluded that there was something unknown, powerful, and dangerous in the salt desert.

After much deliberation amongst the great heroes crawling putting their heads together for a long time, it was decided that a certain Absolute Master, who had turned away from the world and lived in seclusion, was responsible for the incident, and one of them was the Cane Corso.

‘Hugo must have already had some idea that Cane Corso was here, for one of the Baskervilles hounds died trying to deliver the letter.’

That was why Vikir had come here today, too.

Hugo Le Baskerville, a Swordmaster like himself, practicing the Seven Baskervilles.

And Cane Corso, who is said to have transcended Hugo long ago.

Vikir hopes to meet with Cane Corso for hints on the Eighth Baskerville and a way to surpass the Swordmaster.

‘And on top of that, to get the Wraith Tree.’

You can read about it in The Return of the Mage Hound. The Wraith Tree grows right here.

Vikir also knew from his pre-regression knowledge that the Wraith Tree was in the Yuuni Salt Desert.

He had seen the Eighth Corpse Seere gathering the fruits of the Wraith Tree, which had grown to branches far beyond the salt desert.

‘Back then, a great number of people were sacrificed to prevent the Wraith Tree from falling into the hands of the demons.’

And from the manure of those sacrifices, the Wraith Tree grew even taller.

It covered the entire desert and grew bigger and taller than the whole Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Its appearance resembled that of a mythical World Tree.

Countless fruits hung from its branches that stretched out across the mountain.

The skull-shaped fruits hung greedily, filled with the flesh of corpses and the juices of souls, and as they hung and swayed in the wind, it was like watching a line of hanging corpses.

Fruit of the Wraith Tree. Wraithflesh.

When a demon picked the fruit and took a big bite out of it, a thick, nether mana spurted out along with blood-like juices, and a high-pitched scream of agony resounded in the air.

There was no way that the Dead Soldiers, who were all dying, would be able to resist it, as a single bite of Wraithflesh would completely revitalize them.

The Wraith Tree has given the Demon Legion a tremendous boost of power, while at the same time being a disaster for the human race.

“….”

Vikir finished his reminiscence.

And now, behind the iron throne in front of him, he sees something else.

A throne of countless swords. A wicked malice growing behind it.

That’s it. That’s the Wraith Tree.

It seemed that there was no other tree in the world that could be called a wraith tree.

A tree of wraiths, nourished by the grudges, cries, and grief of the living.

Its skull-shaped flesh hardened with the power of the dead.

The way it stretched upward, trunk by trunk, was grotesque enough to send chills down the spine of even the greatest Vikir.

It is still small, but in time it will cast a shadow darker and greater than any other shadow this world has ever known.

Meanwhile.

Cane Corso raised his head and spoke in a voice as heavy as lead.

[This is the Tomb of Swords, the final resting place of those who seek the ultimate goal of the sword].

Inside the eye socket, where the white and black eyes are reversed, the old man’s red pupil has a youthful look.

He seemed to be curious about Vikir’s youthful face.

[…Child. What are you?]

Cane Corso is much older than Hugo, and is the eldest adult in the hierarchy, making him technically Vikir’s uncle.

However, Vikir has no intention of honoring his family’s laws or lineage.

Chang-

That’s why Vikir can draw his sword so casually.

“Find out for yourself.”

All Vikir cared about was the road to Baskerville 8th Form and the the Wraith Trees blooming behind the Iron Throne.

Chapter 258

The Grave of Swords (6)

◆

Danger Rating : A+ ~ ?

Size : ?

Found in : ?

-AKA ‘Death Knight’.

The result of a noble knight’s strength and spirit being devoured by the Abyss.

From beyond the gates of death, they draw infinite amounts of nether mana until their bodies are tattered and their souls worn out.

However, there is still nothing known about what happens when a being who fails to repay the debt passes through another gate behind the Death Gate.

Death Knight.

A noble knight who rose to the rank of superhuman died and was transformed.

The power they possess varies so greatly from individual to individual that it is meaningless to calculate the risk rating.

This is due to the varying degrees of strength and mental power of the knight who becomes a Death Knight, as well as the circumstances and process by which they are transformed into Death Knights.

Once it appears, it is certain that it will take on a Danger Rank A+ or higher, but no Death Knight has appeared in the last hundred years.

…But Vikir had an intuition at this moment.

He had a hunch that Cane Corso in front of him was definitely more than just an S-ranked Dangerous Monster like Madam Eight-Legs or Basilisk.

[I had crossed the threshold of death and entered it].

Cane Corso spoke of his own death with boldness.

He walked alone in a remote place where no one else in the world recognized him.

But he never regretted it, even to the last moment of his life.

For in exchange for his lonely death, he had gained access to the very core of the Supreme, a height no human being had reached in centuries.

“…It is a level that can only be reached by experiencing death.”

Vikir swallowed hard when he heard the requirements of the 9th form.

The 6th Form. A state that can only be reached by transcending all emotions.

The 7th Form. A state that can only be reached by reclaiming emotions that have been abandoned.

The 8th Form. A state that can only be reached by wielding a sword as if reborn, and fighting over and over again in a series of desperate battles.

And the 9th was the inaccessible zone at the core of the supreme realms that only those who had experienced death could ascend to.

After excluding and rejecting emotions to the extent that he had no one to love in his entire life, Vikir ascended to the 6th, and his reunion with Camus led him to the 7th.

And finally, Vikir’s devotion to Cane Corso led him to 8th form.

But somehow, Vikir still didn’t understand the 9th form.

‘You mean I have to be reborn and die again to rise above the Swordmaster? What a ridiculous way to train.’

Even as a Vikir who had reached the 8th form, it was hard to believe.

But now there was a human who had reached the 9th form. And then, surprisingly, he threw away his life.

Cane Corso, now a Death Knight, spoke with the darkness deep in his eyes.

[This is why I said it was impossible for you to ascend to the 9th Form in your lifetime. This realm defies all normal human understanding, empathy, understanding, faith, common sense, probability and causality. A being who has not experienced death can never set foot here].

“….”

[Ah, you certainly seem to have a lot of regrets about life, though I suppose you’re not old enough to have even contemplated death yet].

Cane Corso spoke while sitting on the iron throne.

[You are not ready.]

He drew a line with a single word.

It was the line that separated this side from that side, this world and the afterlife, differ.

As Cane Corso shook his head in disappointment, Vikir asked.

“What do you mean by ready?”

[To ascend to the full 8th form and become a Tower Lord].

Vikir couldn’t understand what he was saying.

However, he had one more question.

“…And what about the 10th form? Have you realized it is impossible to reach the 10th form? Does it even exist?”

[Of course, it actually exists. However, even I, the Tower Lord, have not yet realized it].

Cane Corso spoke in a heavy voice.

[Did I say that you have to experience death to get to the 9th Form?]

“That’s right.”

[To reach the 10th form, one must die and wake up].

Hearing Cane Corso’s words, Vikir opened his mouth halfway in disbelief.

There was a realm that could be reached by death, and then there was a realm that could be reached by death and rebirth.

It was bad enough that he had to die to reach the 9th form, but to reach the 10th form, he had to die and be reborn?

“It doesn’t say you have to die, it says you have to be dead, and then you have to wake up. What kind of nonsensical logic is that….”

Vikir frowned, unable to understand.

Then Cane Corso smiled faintly.

[I don’t understand the meaning of that either, I’m still stuck at 9th. How am I supposed to wake up when I’m already dead, and I may never reach 10th].

For him, not reaching the 10th form is the same as not reaching rest.

Cane Corso had died and become a Death Knight, but he didn’t know how to escape death and become human again.

Nor did he intend to.

So he would have to spend the rest of his life here, the rest of his incredibly long life, alone?

At an age when he should be tombstones on his own grave, he would be tombstones on other people’s graves?

Vikir suddenly questioned the purpose of this great tower.

And Cane Corso, as if looking into Vikir’s mind, began to speak.

[This ‘Grave of Swords’ is the resting place of a great Baskerville].

His words were astonishing.

The Cradle of Swords was the place where the Baskervillian ancestor who created the Baskervillian style of swordsmanship that Vikir had learned was born.

And the place where he died became the Grave of Swords.

[His birth was the birth of the sword, and his death was the death of the sword].

Vikir nodded silently.

Perhaps the ‘Lurking Ambush’ swordsmanship he mastered was also his creation.

Cane Corso said.

[This is ‘his’ grave and also the final destination for those who pursue the ultimate intention of the sword.]

He added at the end.

[A true Baskerville will come here at the end of its life.]

All Baskervilles are born in the Cradle of Swords.

But only the greatest of Baskervilles, the truly great Baskervilles, can close their eyes in the Grave of Swords.

[The end of all great Baskervilles is the same: they come from “his” cradle to “his” grave, and so will you].

And since children from the Cradle of Swords are destined to end up in the Grave of Swords, this is where Vikir will end up as well.

But Vikir snorted.

“I have much to do outside. I’m not coming back to this desolate, idle place.”

[Lots to do? Hehehe – life is not so great as you think, it’s just an expression between a problem and an answer].

Humans go through a lot of milestones in their lives. Births, coming-of-age celebrations, coronations, weddings, funerals, etc…. How many things are there to do?

It’s one long equation(方程式) that connects the question of birth and the answer of death.

[At this age, you’ll soon forget about all that bullshit].

Cane Corso merely stroked his beard.

And then.

Thung-

The tower shook once.

The Grave of Swords began to shake.

“…What?”

Vikir was suddenly caught off guard by a strong wind that blinded him.

Soo-Shusssssss…

Beyond the swirling storm, the figure of Cane Corso was gradually fading away.

‘I will see you again someday.’

Those were Cane Corso’s last words.

At the same time, Vikir noticed white grains of sand mixing with the storm.

The sands of the salt desert were somehow filling the tower.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

And then the wind calmed down.

“…!”

Vikir found himself standing in a desolate desert.

The Grave of Swords. The great tower had vanished without a trace.

It was like a long dream.

…But what happened to Vikir was no dream.

For suddenly, two solid saplings were in his hands.

Wraith Tree. A strange plant that had taken root behind the Iron Throne.

It was a black mage’s exclusive artifact that Pomeranian had longed to possess.

“…Not a dream.”

The aura that boiled from his body was clearly proving that Vikir had risen to the higher ranks.

Swordmaster of the Baskerville 8th Form. Now he could actually fight Hugo and not lose.

“….”

Vikir looked up.

He wanted to thank Cane Corso, but the man he was supposed to be thanking had already disappeared beyond the salt storm, along with the Grave of Swords.

There are no mirages in the sunny desert, let alone illusions.

Vikir bowed his head stiffly toward the Iron Throne that he had so vividly faced just moments before.

Then he turned away, holding the roots of two wraith trees firmly in his hands.

Towards the Baskerville and Colosseo Academy.

Chapter 259

The Inverted Pentagram (1)

◆

Iron Blood Swordsman / Difficulty [★★★★★]

-This student has excelled in solving all the problems presented by the House.

House Lord Hugo Le Baskerville ?

Baskerville’s certificate of quest completion surprised everyone at the Four Academies.

Vice Director Basilios of Varangian, Headmaster Hippolyte of Themiscyra, Master Blue Whale of Magic Tower, and even Professor Banshee of Colosseo were speechless.

“How long has it been since the Iron-Blooded Swordsman gave a passing certificate?”

“Hmmmm… if this is real.”

“Since the Baskerville family is so closed-minded, I have my doubts. Hehehe-”

Basilios, Hippolyte, and Blue Whale looked at the letter again and again in disbelief.

Then.

…Tap!

There was a hand that snatched it away with a cold look.

It was Professor Banshee.

“Are you doubting my student?”

The other representatives smirked at the openly displeased Professor Banshee.

Meanwhile, Professor Banshee looked back at Vikir in front of him and spoke in a sarcastic tone.

“You probably know that you are the last to return out of the 10 rankers, right?”

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded obediently.

Strange, a considerable amount of time had passed since Vikir had emerged from the Grave of Swords.

There was something in there that seemed to distort the flow of time.

‘I couldn’t even tell if Cane Corso was on the top floor of the tower. Maybe there’s something else up there.’

Professor Banshee continued to be sarcastic while Vikir’s mind wandered.

“Still, you’re good at answering questions.”

“Thank you.”

“Do I appear to be giving you a compliment?”

“Sorry.”

When Vikir gave the answer he needed, Professor Banshee’s brow furrowed.

“Vikir-kun, your late return has pushed back the artifact ceremony by ten days. In the meantime, Baskerville hasn’t heard from you, and we’ve been meaning to report you missing. Did you know?”

“The mission was so urgent that I didn’t have time to contact them along the way.”

“And what was the mission?”

Professor Banshee asked, and Vikir answered obediently.

“To retrieve a Wraith Tree.”

At that, the expressions of all four Academy representatives changed drastically.

“Wha, a Wraith Tree?”

“Nonsense, such a thing doesn’t exist.”

“Hehehehehe – that’s a funny joke.”

Basilios, Hippolyte, and Blue Whale dismissed Vikir’s answer as nothing more than a joke.

But only Professor Banshee remained silent, his expression hardened.

He knew Vikir’s character.

Then, in a stern tone, Professor Banshee asked.

“When you speak of the Wraith Tree, do you mean the mythical tree… of Tzersi, the greatest Morgue, and Ornati, the greatest Baskerville?”

“Yes.”

“And the …Baskervilles have commissioned you to retrieve it?”

“Yes.”

“…So. You mean you succeeded in retrieving it?”

“I can’t answer that.”

Vikir did not answer. He merely glanced back at the certificate, which bore the seal of Baskerville.

And as Vikir’s gaze shifted and returned, so did the gaze of the schoolmasters.

And then. Professor Banshee shook his head.

“I don’t know what it is. We’ll talk about this later. First of all, congratulations on completing the quest.”

The brief meeting with the principals ended.

And then.

All ten students, including Vikir, the last to return, have gathered.

They are now on their way to the warehouse where many of the artifacts are stored, beyond a gate that can only be opened by collecting all four keys.

The Tower Master, Blue Whale, smirked.

“You have one day to get out of the warehouse, or the gate will close and never open again. We won’t be able to open the door until the next competition, so be sure to follow the time limit strictly.”

Then, in a playful tone, he added.

“Oh, and by the way, don’t worry about the skeletons you see as soon as you step through the gate. They are the remains of those who failed to pick up an artifact in time to leave the warehouse.”

It was somehow a creepy joke.

◆

All ten students walked through the gate in front of the students from all four schools.

And exactly 23 hours later, nine students emerged from the warehouse.

All of them having been chosen by the artifact.

This was quite unusual, given that there are always one or two students in every tournament who, despite being ranked in the top ten, come up empty-handed, having not been chosen by any artifact.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca also gathered at the gate, waiting for their friend.

“Wow! He’s out! It’s here!”

“Sinclaire! Over here!”

“Oooh! Looks like you picked an artifact! Congratulations Sinclaire!”

“See, I told you you could do it!”

A tired but cheerful Sinclaire stepped out of the gate and waved to everyone.

Afterward, each student stepped out of the gate to report which artifact they had been chosen for, and which artifact they had chosen.

First up was Dolores.

Dolores was the first to step out, holding a small mirror in her arms that she could hug.

“My artifact is the Mirror of Truth. It is said to show the bare face behind the mask of the person it reflects, but only for those within its reach.”

As she spoke, she lifted the mirror and glanced at Lovegood’s face as he stood beside her.

In the mirror, she saw Lovegood’s makeup-free face.

“Gah! What are you doing, you! I’ve just finished putting on my makeup!”

“Why, you look beautiful!”

Lovegood hastily turns away from the mirror. Dolores watched and laughed.

She was next.

The student council president of Themiscyra and the newly formed leader of the Vikir fan club, she exclaimed in an ambitious voice.

“The artifact I got is called the ‘Shield of Love’ – it’s a hairpin with a heart-shaped brooch on it, and it’s said that when you wear it, it’ll stop any kind of powerful brainwashing or mind control magic for once – but it only works if you have someone you truly love by your side!”

At first glance, the artifact didn’t sound too good.

Usually, the artifacts that other students got were semi-permanent, while this one had a limited use.

But for some reason, Lovegood seemed quite satisfied.

“What are you going to use it for?”

“Shit, never mind!”

Dolores and Lovegood, who had become quite close by now, are having a bickering conversation.

Then.

“Hahahahaha!”

With a delightful laugh, Bakilaga pulled out an artifact.

It was a giant glove made of an unidentified metal.

“It’s a gauntlet that increases your strength. It’s called the ‘Magic King’s Hand,’ and it was worn by a legendary warrior named the Magic King who lived in another dimension a long time ago.”

“Similar to me. I got a staff that increases mana. It is said that a very small amount of ‘pink dragon scales’ were contained. Is there a dragon like that in the first place…?”

Hohenheim nodded in agreement with Bakilaga’s words.

Next up were the three brothers, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

“We got the triplet swords that are said to be stronger when united. It’s called the Three Swords.”

“Yeah.”

“Yeah.”

They held out three swords that looked identical but were slightly different.

Strangely, they say, the power of all three is increased when they are wielded together.

The trio, called the Trident of Baskerville, had been chosen first by the artifacts, and they seemed quite proud of that.

Then.

“…I’m the only one who knows what this is.”

A sullen voice said.

Granola. The guy walked out looking somewhat downcast.

In his hand was a small brooch in the shape of a lip.

“This artifact is called the ‘Righteous Lips.’ It’s said to tell you the truth, no matter what question you ask, but it only answers with ‘yes’ and ‘no,’ and you can only use it once in your entire life….”

Then. A hand tapped Granola on the shoulder.

“Why, I think it’s a very good artifact.”

It was Sinclaire.

“Sometimes I have a lot of doubts about whether I am living well. I think it would be a good idea to ask at that time.”

“…Tsk, why do you have such doubts? I’m always living well, you’re supposed to be proud of yourself!”

But despite Sinclaire grumbling, Granola felt much better inside.

Finally, Sinclaire reported her artifact.

“The artifact that chose me is the Money Hat, which is a hat that make your magic power becomes stronger the more you spend money on it.”

It was a strange-looking black hat, like something only witches would wear.

With a worn brim and a missing tooth it looked sinister and far from wealthy.

Everyone around her felt sorry for her.

Sinclaire is probably the most poor student in the Colosseo.

It was already widely rumored that while most students were supported by their parents for living expenses and tuition, she was paying for everything from tuition to living expenses with a part-time job.

To be chosen for such an expensive artifact in such a situation was nothing short of the grain of sand.

But Sinclaire remained cheerful.

“Hehe- money is power in this world. I’ll have to make a lot of money to afford this hat.”

Sinclaire just smiles, as usual.

◆

Time passes as other students come out one by one to register their artifacts.

And then. The hands of the clock have come full circle.

Time has passed since Sinclaire, the ninth student to come forward and report the artifact.

And now the clock is ticking down to the end. There was less than a minute left before the gates closed.

But there was still one student who hadn’t come out.

Vikir.

The students of all the academies have gathered here, waiting for this one unreturned student.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Sinclaire, Bianca, and all the other students mutter anxiously.

“Vikir… what are you doing, why aren’t you coming out!”

“It’s bad, time is running out.”

“Now it’s seconds! Oh my god!”

“Don’t worry, he’ll come out at the last minute.”

“He loves to play the main character, and he was the last one to show up for the second test.”

Everyone was looking at the gate, unable to hide their anxiety and nervousness.

…But.

No one came out of the gate after all.

Spot!

The gate’s duration was up.

It closed in vain.

“…?”

Everyone who was watching this suddenly swallowed the wind.

Stunned faces. Expressions of disbelief.

It was Professor Banshee who screamed first.

“Open, open! Open the gate! One of my students hasn’t gotten out yet!”

But it was impossible.

The rule of the four academies is that the gates are only opened once a year, when everyone is present, and only for 24 hours.

It was a system that had been in place for a very long time, and it wasn’t something that the deans could open at will.

In the first place, the warehouse and the portal itself are independent parts, and it is impossible for mages in this world to control it other than maintaining and repairing it.

Knowing this, the other Deans could only shake their heads with solemn, gloomy expressions.

Though extremely rare, it is not completely unknown.

There are those who are so greedy for so many artifacts that they cannot choose between it and let the time limit pass.

When the gates are opened the following year, they are found to be nothing but skeletons at the entrance.

Such is the price of greed.

“Oh, no….”

Tudor approached the gate.

Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca stood beside him, also looking bewildered.

“W-what happened now?”

“Vikir couldn’t get out? Really?”

“Is the gate closed? Can’t we get this thing open again?”

When entering the gate, the only things you can take with you are inanimate objects like clothes and shoes.

Everything else, except your own body, is burned when you go through the gate.

So there’s no point in bringing food or water along.

This means that those trapped in the warehouse can only starve to death from loneliness and hunger.

“No, Vikir!”

Lovegood and the rest of the fan club cry out.

But no matter how desperate they are, the gate is already closed.

“….”

Dolores stares at the gate in disbelief.

‘You’re lying, right? In fact, you were there before me, right?’

But looking around, there was no sign of it.

Vikir is trapped in there. He can’t get out now.

Dolores could only stand there in disbelief.

It seems like time around her has stopped.

A feeling as if her heart had dropped all the way to the bottom of her ribs and stopped there.

Her eyes were blurry and her legs were trying to give out.

Dolores opens her mouth to speak, dumbfounded by this confusing sensation she doesn’t recognize.

…Puck!

An unfamiliar sound came from somewhere.

It sounded like a sword tearing through very thick leather.

“…What!?”

The expression of the Tower Master, White Beard Blue Whale, changed drastically.

Dzzzzzzzzzz.

The barrier was being torn apart.

And a face is slowly revealed through the cracks.

“Sorry, sir. I’m a little late.”

It was Vikir, still looking nonchalant.

Chapter 262

The Season of Redemption (1)

◆

After a long journey, Vikir returns to his dormitory at Colosseo Academy.

“Wash up first, Vikir! I need to do something first….”

“What?”

“Oh, just to clean up some personal work that I’ve been putting off because of the University League.”

As soon as Pigi walked into his dorm room, he started fussing with something.

It was a piece of paper with numbers, diagrams, and graphs all over it, probably something related to finance.

Vikir went into the shower without a word.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

The cub stood still under the warm water, checking to see if it was good.

As the water flowed down its black fur, it seemed to melt into the water.

Normally, he would have patted its head, but… Vikir was silent now, his brow furrowed slightly.

It was the necklace that had been making so much noise earlier.

A red chain hanging from a choker around his neck.

It was the 7th Corpse Decarabia.

[K-hahahaha! I am Decarabia! A taboo being! A savior of the species! A mixture of great destruction and magnificent creation! And the lucky one to have a pretty, beautiful mistress for this activity period!]

His voice is set to be heard only by Vikir in the first place, and Vikir’s ears ache with the constant chatter.

Decarabia seemed to like the fact that it was hanging around Vikir’s neck and chest, and was in high tension the whole way back.

But the good feelings only lasted so long.

The moment Vikir stepped into the shower and stripped off his clothes, Decarabia’s chatter stopped.

[Hey contractor, don’t forget to carry me in the shower with you in case someone picks me up… eh?]

The pupils in Decarabia’s eyes, which were wide open in a nearly circular shape, were shaking.

[….]

Decarabia stares into Vikir’s face.

[…?]

And now Decarabia is looking down at Vikir again.

In the meantime, Vikir has taken a quick shower.

[….]

Decarabia has already become very quiet.

It’s been talking less and less, and now it’s practically inanimate, as if it hasn’t moved at all.

Its eyes, which had been looking up and down several times, had also closed.

Vikir, puzzled by the sudden stop in the chatter, taps Decarabia with a mana filled finger.

[…I am. Decarabia. Are. You. Going. To. Command. Something?]

“Not like that.”

[…Then.]

Its eyes open briefly, then close coldly again.

A very dry and bureaucratic answer comes back.

“…Well, that’s quieter now.”

Anything that works is good.

Vikir nodded with a satisfied expression.

◆

When Vikir stepped out of the shower, Pigi was getting ready to go out.

When Vikir was wiping the moisture from his hair with a towel, with his back turned to the cloudy steam coming out of the shower room.

“Hey, Vikir. I have to go out!”

Pigi said, clutching a stack of papers in his arms.

There were so many papers in Pigi’s arms that he wondered if he could even see.

Vikir sat back in his chair with a towel around his neck and asked.

“Where are you going?”

“Uh-huh. I’m going to show my personal work to my professor.”

Personal work refers to studies that students do on their own to improve their skills outside of what the academy assigns.

Pigi smiled broadly.

“We’ve got a ‘mock investment competition’ in a little while.”

“A mock investment competition?”

“Yep. It’s a competition where you have to research and invest in promising stocks and sectors in advance, and it’s organized by a famous Bourgeois family. There are many benefits to winning or being in the leaderboard!”

“I thought that was the end of the survival contest. There’s more.”

“Yes. There’s a swordsmanship tournament, an archery tournament, a magic tournament, a lead dancing tournament, an eating contest, a boxing tournament, a theater tournament, a singing contest, a painting contest, a contest to raise the best beetle… There’s been a lot of them lately, haven’t there?”

Ever since Vikir donated the money he made from selling gnoll leather to the scholarship foundation, there have been a lot more competitions of one sort or another.

It was all an excuse to give scholarships to students.

‘Professor Banshee is doing a surprisingly good job.’

Vikir nodded silently.

He’d doubted that the scholarship foundation would do the right thing, but the fact that they were producing visible results as soon as the survival contest was over seemed to indicate that they could be trusted.

Meanwhile, Pigi smirked as he finished.

“I’m a little short on grades, so I have to make up for it by getting extra credit for placing in competitions like this.”

The truth is, Pigi’s talent for combat is average to slightly below average, but he excels at everything else.

He’s skilled in administration, law, medicine, art, and finance.

He was especially good at acquiring, analyzing, and summarizing information, as well as keeping up with the latest news and happenings of prominent figures in society.

(Apparently, he had already won several contests for raising great rhinoceros beetles.)

‘If Cindywendy saw this, she’d be screaming for a scout right now.’

Vikir nodded silently.

“I’m sure you’ll do fine.”

For someone who’s usually a man of few words, the effect of Vikir’s compliment was stunning.

“…Thank you, Vikir. You’re always so inspiring.”

Pigi clenches his jaw, impressed. His eyes turned red and moisturized.

Pigi then pumped his fists at Vikir.

“That’s right, I’m going to beat that kid this time.”

“…That kid?”

Vikir asked, puzzled, and Pigi snorted and nodded.

“Yeah, Sinclaire, because she said she’s going to be participating in the Mock Competition this year too!”

Sinclaire. Top of the Hot Class. A freshman from a commoner’s background.

A prodigy whose name pops up all over the place at Colosseo Academy, a place where only geniuses come together.

In her major, magic, she has shown herself to be as talented as the mages of the Mage House Morgue, and in her minor, Cold Weapons, she has surprised everyone with her proficiency with swords, spears, bows, and other weapons.

And other than that, she was famous as an alpha girl who could do anything, such as theory if theory, handwriting if written, certificate if certificate, part-time job if it was a part-time job.

This time, she was a librarian with a part-time job at a cafe, but she still managed to take first and second place in various practical and written tests.

Furthermore, she had recently placed eighth overall in the University League as a freshman, proving her star potential.

Pigi said, fueling the rivalry.

“Sinclaire says she’s also really good at accounting and office work, which is why she’s working as a librarian at the library.”

“I see.”

Vikir simply nodded, not realizing that Sinclaire had a talent for economics and investments.

“This mock investment competition is sponsored by Bourgeois House, so there’s a lot of students who enter for prizes, scholarships, and maybe even a job after graduation, and I’m sure Sinclaire is one of them. I’m not going to lose! I’m going to go!”

Pigi waved, dropped a few papers, picked them up, and stood up.

But he didn’t see the one that fell behind his heel.

Vikir picked it up and tried to hand it to Pigi.

“Oh, it’s okay, it’s just a poster for the competition, I don’t need it!”

Pigi waved it off and ran down the hall.

The room was now empty.

Vikir sat down at his desk.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

[Don’t drool on me you dirty puppy… No, spider, what is this?]

A spider and Decarabia were on the desk.

The Baby Madam is circling around and looking around to see what’s so good about Decarabia.

[Hack! Hack-!]

[Ugh, I thought I told you not to drool on me, no, don’t touch me, no, don’t climb on me, just stay away… What, female?]

[Hack hack…]

[Oh my, are you a lady? In that case, I will turn a blind eye to this level of rudeness. In reality, I just close my eyes and surrender myself to your touch…]

Vikir breathed mana into Decarabia and gave a command.

“Open your eyes.”

[….]

Decarabia hesitated for a moment, then squirmed as if it had no choice.

[Mm. Yes. I open my eyes, to my new taste. Maybe I’d rather have a man in that face…]

“What are you talking about, open your eyes and tell me something about the ten commandments?”

When Vikir slapped him with the palm of his hand, Decarabia responded in a hurry.

[Oh, you mean the one you asked earlier? What was it… Yeah, it was about the 6th of the 10, right?

“Yes.”

Vikir was asking Decarabia for information about his next prey, the 6th of the Ten.

[The 6th Corpse, he must have been close to the 9th Corpse, they were always together].

Decarabia knows something about the areas that Cindywendy’s research hasn’t been able to uncover.

Even if it’s just a small piece of information, it’s a big help.

Vikir paused for a moment as he listened to Decarabia’s words.

“The 9th Corpse is Dantalian. He wears the skin of Quilt, the head of House Indulgentia.”

Dantalian’s puppet, Quilt, had close ties to the Old Testament faction of the religious hymn Quovadis.

And a demon who was close to Dantalian. The 6th corpse.

‘If we investigate the Old Testament Faction of Quovadis, we might get a clue.’

After the Indulgentia’s disappearance, indulgences were still being issued and sold by the Old Testament Church of Quovadis.

After a brief hiatus from selling indulgences due to the publicity surrounding Dolores’s 95 refutations, the Old Testament Church has recently resumed issuing indulgences due to public demand.

As we enter the new season, sales of ‘indulgences’ with new specifications are booming.

Surprisingly, they were even discounted.

‘It’s going to be a busy business since it’s been around all season.’

Vikir thought about investigating the Old Testament faction of the Quovadis once more.

Maybe he could find a lead to someone with connections there, maybe even somewhere else entirely.

At that moment.

Something like a hunch, something he couldn’t explain logically, flashed through Vikir’s mind.

“….”

Vikir’s gaze snapped to the front door.

There was the poster Pigi had dropped on his way out earlier.

The flow of the economy was created by humans, but cannot be predicted by human power.

However, the intuition of very few geniuses is able to connect with the great flow.

If you think you’re one of those few, this poster is for you.

This competition is held in a place called ‘the spine of the economy’.

And will be the staircase that will lead you to the big stage of the financial world.

Eligibility: All students of the Academy

Submission period: Until one week after posters are distributed (※Posters will naturally expire after one week)

Organizer: Bourgeois Family

Chapter 263

The Season of Redemption (2)

◆

The night sky is colored a deep blue.

The cloudy sky resembles a swarm of sharks rising to the surface from the depths of the ocean.

Thump, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump!

The sound of urgent footsteps echoed in the quiet of dawn.

Narrow streets between red brick buildings. An alley with stagnant puddles of water.

“…Huff, huff, huff!”

A man wearing armor under a black trench coat was wiping blood from the corner of his mouth.

“I would have been left out at this point.”

Clutching the hatchet at his waist, he stuck his head out of the building and looked left and right.

Finding the street empty, he breathed a sigh of relief and muttered.

“Damn it. Ms. Ouroboros, if it weren’t for that bitch, I’d be able to devour the Imperial City….”

The man muttered through clenched teeth.

Then. Something eerie flashed over his head.

“…!?”

The man looked up, startled.

He looked up to see a figure standing between him and the building, both feet outstretched, staring down at him.

A black cloak, a plague doctor’s mask. It was the Night Hound.

“What, what is it, you?”

The man looks up, confused.

But the Night Hound didn’t answer. He just kept his words short.

“Your name is Edward Bourbon Jr. Is that right?”

The man looked a little flustered at that, then asked.

“Who are you, Ouroboros, did she send you?”

He rolled his eyes for a moment, then exclaimed again.

“Oh, no, that bitch always moves alone, so is this really the Night Hound, the one she says she’s chasing…?”

He mumbled something under his breath, but judging by the way he was fixing his hatchet with the hand he had hidden behind his back, he wasn’t about to give an easy answer.

But the Night Hound didn’t seem to be expecting an answer either.

“Aka ‘St. Bourbon’. He’s an intermediate Graduator. A high priest of the emerging cult of Ohm, which is making quite a name for itself in the north. 25 years ago, he made his first contract with the devil by killing his cousin after molesting her and offering her as a sacrifice. Since then, he has continued his religious activities, destroying thousands of families through forced offerings. Toward the end of his life, he aligned himself with the Demon Army and confronted the Faithful Quovadis. Infiltrated the Church as a spy, using his knowledge and understanding of the scriptures as a weapon. Later, during the Holy War, he stabbed the Human Alliance in the back, mortally wounding heroes such as Tudor Donquixote and Usher Poe Bianca.”

The eerie howl of a Night Hound from behind a mask.

“ …I asked, is that correct?”

The man bellowed at the question.

“What are you talking about! The story about being a priest and my cousin is true, but I don’t have any ill will with Donquixote or the Usher family…!?”

But he didn’t finish his sentence.

The moment he looked up and opened his mouth.

Thud-

A single drop of blood from the tip of the Night Hound’s fingertip stretched out in front of him landed in his mouth.

“…Uhuk!?”

The man instantly struggled with the bitter taste and sickening sensation on the tip of his tongue.

No matter how much he vomited and strangled with his hands, the pain wouldn’t go away.

It was a poison so fierce that it curled around the roots of his tongue and lodged itself deep in his throat.

The man tried to envelope the hatchet he had drawn from his waistband with his aura, but it quickly scattered into thin air.

…Debag!

He fell to the ground, dead within seconds of a drop of blood entering his mouth.

It was a rather futile end for an intermediate Graduator.

“….”

Night Hound. Vikir glanced down at the dead assassination target lying face down in the alley.

He was the last assassination of the day, the 19th.

‘…Hey, what was he muttering earlier?’

Vikir recalled the last words the dead man had muttered.

‘Damn it. Ms. Ouroboros, if it weren’t for that bitch, I’d be able to devour the Imperial Capital….’

‘So is that really the Night Hound, the one she’s chasing…?’

The words were open to interpretation.

‘Ms. Ouroboros, was that crazy woman chasing me?’

Apparently, Vikir’s prey was also her target.

It seems that Ms. Ouroboros has her own agenda.

1. Confronting mysterious forces and hunting down criminals across the Imperial Capital.

2. Seeking to meet the Night Hound.

Vikir recalls a time when he was hunting gnolls to pay for school.

‘She attacked me as soon as she saw my face, so I thought she was just a psycho, but she must have a plan of her own.’

Whatever that plan was, there was a lot of overlap with Vikir.

What’s more, she seems quite eager to meet him.

“Tsk.”

Vikir clicked his tongue and dropped to the floor.

As he searched the body of the priest who had died after drinking Madame’s poison, he found a crumpled piece of paper in his pocket.

.

‘All sins of this faithful church member are forgiven.’

– This indulgence was issued and endorsed by the Old Testament Church, and counterfeiting it was punishable by death.

An indulgence sold by the Old Testament church in Quovadis Family.

It was crumpled on all sides, with only the words ‘sins forgiven’ being clean.

How ironic that this was the last remaining keepsake of a man who had made a pact with the demon and practiced unholy deeds.

Then.

[… Rise. Rise. Rise. Rise. Rise. Rise].

A red-hot, inverted pentagram light emanated from Vikir’s chest.

Decarabia opened his single eye and peered into the indulgence.

[Not the smell of a colleague…. It smells of what was once an ally, but is no longer an ally, is no longer an ally, is now a complete stranger, and is now an outright enemy!]

Decarabia looked at Vikir’s gaze and changed his words, wondering if he had missed it.

He seemed concerned that Vikir would draw his sword again, saying, “Demons kill,” or “I don’t believe in demons.”

But Vikir was too busy thinking about other things to pay attention to Decarabia.

“…You mean you smell the demon in the indulgence?”

Even though the demon ‘Dantalian the 9th Corpse’ of the Quovadis family was eliminated, the smell of the demon did not disappear.

It even.

[Yes. This smell is definitely the smell of ‘6th Corpse’. I was always hanging out with my old friend.]

I also got information that the 9th Corpse, who had already hunted in the past, was close friends with the 6th Corpse.

“…Good. I guess we’ll have to look through the Quovadis one more time.”

Vikir nodded and left.

….

And then.

A few minutes after Vikir left, another shadow lengthened in the alley.

“What?”

A helmet with two large snake scales sticking out like horns.

And shiny black tights and high heels.

‘Ms. Ouroboros.’

A villain whose true identity has never been discovered despite the fierce pursuit of the Imperial Guard, which is lined up with powerful men.

She stared down at the corpse lying at the end of the alley.

“Hmph… I’ve been chasing you so long and so hard, have you come and gone already?”

She lifted her head and looked across the alley.

Then her eyes, peeking out from behind her mask, softened.

“My diligent pursuit of the scum has paid off. I should follow him, and with any luck, he’ll show me his honored form.”

Ms. Ouroboros launched herself toward the opposite alley.

It was in the direction where the walls of the Colosseo Academy towered in the distance.

◆

Vikir turned into a dog and was just about to cross the tunnel beneath the wall.

Bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark- bark.

The sound of the wake-up call echoed throughout the dormitory.

“…Phew.”

Vikir dragged his tired body back to his room.

He pushed open his door and sat down on his bed to find Pigi rubbing his eyes.

“Uh-oh, Vikir. You’re up early?”

“….”

Vikir sat on his bed for a few seconds before heading out to the gym.

The whole school gathered in the gymnasium every morning to do gymnastics and then go to take a bath or eat.

“At least today is a weekend.”

Vikir was relieved that he didn’t have a morning lecture.

Weekend. A holiday.

Midterms and University League are over, and there is some time left until the final exams.

During this short break, students would be able to recharge their batteries before facing their final exams and then, finally, the sweet treat of a vacation.

After a quick wash in the bathhouse, Vikir had breakfast in the cafeteria.

Later, when he stopped by the newspaper club room to catch up on last night’s news.

“Wait a minute, Professor! That’s a notice posted with permission! Please don’t take it off!”

“Hohoho-shut up.”

Vikir heard an argument that could be heard outside the window.

Wondering what was going on, he opened the door slightly and peeked inside to see familiar faces.

Dolores and the rest of the newspaper department.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, all of them looking pretty pissed off.

On the other side of the room stood a rather unexpected figure.

Professor Sadi.

She was holding in her hands all of the signs that had been posted on the walls of the hallway and on the doors of the clubhouse.

These were the following

Bulletin Board

The Newspaper Club hereby corrects the part of the newspaper article published on January 0th regarding the criminal activities of the Night Hounds, attributing the crime to Ms. Ouroboros.

This error occurred because the authorities were not aware of the existence of “Ms. Ouroboros,” a copycat of “Night Hound.”…

-All members of the newspaper club, Ryukeion.

And now, Professor Sadi had torn down all of these wall posters related to ‘Night Hound’ and ‘Ms. Ouroboros’.

“Hohohoho, kids, I’m in charge of cleaning up the environment this week, so please don’t put up any of this nasty crap.”

She brushed her bangs and muttered irritably.

“Ugh, why do I have to suffer this annoying punishment in the first place?” “I just ran a ‘violent crime help and counseling center.’”

“The problem with counseling is that you don’t distinguish between victims and perpetrators, right?”

Dolores pointed out, but Professor Sadi didn’t even pretend to listen.

With that, she stormed out into the hallway.

In the meantime, Vikir remained silent and hiding behind the locker room.

He has a grudge against Professor Sadi because of the ‘left eyeball incident’.

There is nothing good about meeting Professor Sadi.

“…Uh? Bro!”

That’s when Sinclaire stuck her head out the window, spotted Vikir, and called out.

“Did you see that? Prof. Sadi just flipped the place upside down. It’s a total mess.”

“I saw it, too. She’s got a mean streak.”

“She’s always been weird, but she’s even worse today. Did she get dumped by her boyfriend last night? Why is she so hysterical? I can’t imagine she has a boyfriend who would put up with that kind of behavior.”

At Sinclaire’s whining, Vikir nodded.

With that, Vikir left the club room with the morning paper, which contained the events of the previous night.

Sinclaire followed him for a while, asking where he was going, but then he turned sullen and said he had to practice for the mock investment competition in the afternoon.

The place where Vikir headed was the laboratory of the professor in charge, Banshee Morgue.

Knock, knock, knock.

After knocking, he opened the door and heard Professor Banshee’s cold voice.

“Now you open the door before I answer? How arrogant of you. Deduct one point for attitude.”

Professor Banshee realized it was Vikir without even looking in the direction of the door.

“I’m here to ask for travel permit.”

Professor Banshee’s eyes narrowed at Vikir’s words.

“…Out of school? All the conveniences are on campus, what do you want to do?”

“I’m going to the Rune Church. For repentance.”

Professor Banshee’s eyes widened at that.

“Hmm. Repentance? That’s surprising, I didn’t think you were religious enough to go to mass on the weekends.”

Shaking his head slightly, Professor Banshee signed the excuse slip with a rare expression of satisfaction.

“Very good. That sincere attitude, I haven’t seen in a while, Vikir-kun.”

But beneath his expressionless face, Vikir was thinking about something else.

‘…I didn’t say I would do it.’

I don’t go out to repent, but to make people repent.

Chapter 264

The Season of Redemption (3)

◆

A peaceful weekend morning.

Vikir walks out into the street.

The streets were bustling with people at midday.

On the terraces of cafes, ladies are chatting, businessmen are meeting with clients, and young people are walking arm in arm, laughing and talking about whatever they’re having fun with.

As pretty women and handsome men walk busily, the surrounding eyes follow them for a few seconds and then turn to the front again.

The smell of flowers from a flower shop, sweet and savory from an egg bread shop.

From the railroad station ahead, where carriages rushed by with urgent news, came the clanging of hammers to announce the construction of an expansion.

“….”

Suddenly, Vikir stopped at the edge of the street.

Red brick buildings and narrow alleys between them.

At the narrow entrance, a line of Imperial Guard seals prohibited entry.

It was the same place where Vikir had carried out his assassination at dawn just hours earlier.

Two things had changed.

The bodies had already been removed, marked only by a white line on the ground.

The other was a deep gash in the floor.

“….”

Vikir stood at a distance and examined the marks on the floor.

It looked like a snake had slithered across it. It was definitely not there when Vikir carried out the assassination.

A crowd gathered, murmuring at the bloodstains on the walls and floor.

“They say a man died in there during the night.”

“They say he was horribly tortured and then poisoned.”

“Be afraid. Could this be the work of Night Hound, too?”

“No. They say the killer this time was that woman, Ms. Ouroboros.”

“What, there were other villains besides Night Hound?”

“This guy’s slow on the news.”

Vikir blended into the crowd and quietly listened to the conversations around him.

Vikir didn’t need to worry, he hadn’t left any clues, he moved in complex movements, turning into a dog in the middle of nowhere and slipping under narrow terrain, something no human could ever track.

It’s just that he’s a little surprised that Ms. Ouroboros has been there since he left.

‘…She’s a strange woman.’

Vikir became even more alert to Ms. Ouroboros.

She was no longer just a copycat.

She is a terrorist with an unknown purpose and seems to be chasing the Night Hound, so we need to keep a close eye on her.

…However, today’s outing was not about Ms. Ouroboros.

Vikir left the crowds and headed toward the center of town, wearing one of his hats.

“…There are so many people.”

When Vikir reached the main street of the Imperial Capital, the most important land he marveled.

There are so many people, it’s like looking at a dense mass of bean sprouts.

‘I could blend in and nobody would know.’

Vikir thought, If you want to hide the woods, hide it in the forest.

Vikir blended into the flow of the crowd and moved forward.

Soon he could see the White Shield, the holy symbol of the Quovadis Family.

The colorful and magnificent temple was maintained by a branch of the Old Testament Order.

At the entrance to the temple, there was a huge crowd of people lined up.

A white-robed priest shouts into a ram’s horn.

“Come on, repent, this is your chance to get your sins forgiven at half price! Come on, it’s not every day that you get this chance! Half price for misdemeanors, 30% DC for felonies, and for the really big crimes, you’ll have to consult the bishop! Here’s your indulgences, your indulgences, today only! Buy now and save even more on taxes! This is a special sale that ends tomorrow and we don’t know when it will happen again!”

The shouts of priests selling indulgences were mixed with the calls of cotton candy sellers selling cotton candy, corn sellers selling roasted corn, and bubble sellers selling bubble toys for children.

People coming out of the temple come out with bright expressions and walk with brisk steps.

All of them had bought indulgences.

A couple’s conversation caught Vikir’s ear.

“Ugh. I bought indulgences this time and I feel relieved. I’ve been scolded all this time because of guilt.”

“Oh, for that time when you were drinking and driving a carriage and hit a kid?”

“Yes. I haven’t been able to sleep since then, and now I’m here to repent because they’re offering a big discount on the indulgence.”

“But didn’t the child die? Did you apologize and compensate the family?”

“No? No, I didn’t. I bought an indulgence. I bought a really expensive one, so it’s okay, right?”

“I guess. Well. Whatever. You’re such a good person, anyway.”

Vikir turned his head and studied the man and woman for a moment.

‘They don’t smell like demons.’

They were not demon contractors. Surprisingly.

However, similar types of people were overflowing here in the Imperial Capital.

Right now, in this branch alone, the Old Testament Order of the Quovadis, there were tons of people lined up to buy indulgences, and on the other side of the line were people who had bought indulgences.

If you think about all these people who have sinned and all these people who have been forgiven, it’s kind of dizzying.

‘I wonder why the world is like this.’

Vikir shook his head with the sigh that older people usually make.

He’s been doing his best to prevent the end of the world, but somehow the task feels even heavier today.

And then.

Vikir joined the end of the long line and after a long wait was granted entry into the temple.

Once inside, passing between large white stone pillars that were so pristine and clean it was impossible to tell how much money was spent on them, Vikir was greeted by a group of well-dressed priests.

“Greetings, sir. What sins have you committed, and are there any indulgences you seek?”

One of the priests approached Vikir.

His youthful appearance suggests he hasn’t been in the service for long.

The priest clung to Vikir, explaining various things he hadn’t even asked.

“We have indulgences for misdemeanors – felony indulgences, of course – and special indulgences for the most heinous crimes that are punishable by death, but since you, Mr. …, look so young, it’s unlikely you’ve committed such a felony – would you prefer a misdemeanor?”

To the priest, who was struggling to come up with a quote for a customized indulgence, Vikir asked bluntly.

“If I can repent for sins I’ve committed in the past, can I repent for sins I’ll commit in the future?”

The priest smiled wryly, as if to say yes.

“Anything is possible if you buy indulgences in advance. What sins are you going to commit?”

“ …, Which is a heinous crime.”

The priest’s expression hardened at Vikir’s words.

What would the priest’s reaction be to a human foreshadowing a great crime to come?

…Now, with a serious expression on his face, the priest spoke in an even more serious voice.

“What is it. Hmm. In the case of extreme crimes, the price of indulgence would be very high. Are you okay? If you have the means, I will bring the bishop. Oh, first, would you like to go to the VVIP-only chapel over there and have a cup of tea while waiting?”

He’s making a calculation, not rebuking someone who’s about to commit a sin.

And with the tone of a sales promotion.

As Vikir chuckled, the priest asked again, more cautiously.

“ …, But what kind of a sin is it that you’re looking for such an expensive indulgence?”

Vikir replied.

“I think I will kill one of my neighbor’s pigs.”

Moment. The priest tilted his head as if he had heard wrong.

“One…. Pig… That’s a heinous crime?”

“Yes. Pigs are also living beings, and isn’t it a sin to take a life anyway?”

Then the priest sighed deeply.

He glanced at the long line of people behind him, then turned back to Vikir.

“Hey.”

Now the words were short.

“Just go. Okay?”

When Vikir still stood there, unmoving, the priest casually tore open a piece of indulgence paper in his hand and stamped it with his own seal.

“There, there. I’m giving it to you because it’s amazing that we came this far with just one pig’s life.”

“…Thank you.”

“Good. Next time, don’t sin. Be a good boy.”

The priest sighed heavily and slapped the roughly shaped indulgence into Vikir’s hand.

Vikir looked up and said.

“The money…”

“Tsk, tsk, that’s enough, man.”

The priest clicked his tongue and suddenly plunged his hand into Vikir’s pocket.

He pulled out a clinking coin.

It was a one-gold coin, copper with traces of gold.

It went into the offering box that the priest wore around his neck.

Tang-clank

“Yes, you have repented~”

The priest’s regular voice rang out in a deep voice.

That was it.

◆

Vikir left the temple.

In his hand, he held a small indulgence.

‘All sins of this faithful church member are forgiven.’

– This indulgence was issued and endorsed by the Old Testament, and counterfeiting it was punishable by death. –

‘…Is this how it is.’

Vikir synthesized the information he had seen, heard, and felt as he entered the temple.

The energy of the demons within, the faint but unmistakable smell.

[…I can definitely sense the aura of the Sixth Corpse, though it is still faint].

Even Decarabia, at his chest, was saying the same thing, sniffling with a nose that wasn’t there.

Vikir followed the rotting scent of the Sixth Corpse back to the main road.

‘It’s not in this temple, but… is definitely involved. It must be somewhere in the Imperial City.

Vikir had just turned his back on the temple and was about to head back to the academy.

“…!”

Suddenly, a familiar face caught his eye.

‘Iik.’

Vikir hastily pressed his bun hat to his head and went to the side of the pillar.

Even with the hood pressed down, Vikir’s sharp eyes could make it out.

Dolores.

Her face was seen as she quietly walked into the temple, looking around with suspicious movements.

Chapter 266

The Eucharist (1)

◆

The face of a cute black puppy.

Vikir was currently wearing a child’s mask sold by a street vendor.

As it is urgent, it is a Night Hound stopgap mode.

And in front of him stood Dolores.

Dolores looked dazed as if she couldn’t tell if this was a dream or reality.

“…Night Hound?”

Nod.

Vikir nodded in response to Dolores’ question.

Thump-thump-thump-

Dolores felt her heart pounding in her chest at the sudden encounter.

He acted as if he had the supernatural power to see into people’s minds.

The moment she thought she wanted to see him, he was there, like a lie.

If it wasn’t a superpower, then what was it?

‘…Or fate?’

A common theme in popular classic romance novels.

But Dolores, who was precocious for her age, thought all of that was childish.

But now that she’s in this situation, she can’t help but think about it.

Fated mates. An inevitable relationship, you know, all that heart-pounding stuff.

‘Well, come to think of it, even then….’

Dolores recalled a moment in the past when she was briefly assimilated into the spirit of Night Hound.

A cold, lonely, and difficult journey. A pilgrim walking through a thorny path carrying all his burdens alone.

The memory of that night, when she could feel his pain, his suffering, his numbing loneliness.

A soulmate who went through extreme situations together. Even though she doesn’t know anything about the outer shell, there is definitely an invisible tie between him and herself.

That’s what she thought.

Then.

“Come to your senses.”

Night Hound voice snapped her back to reality.

She looked up quickly to see Night Hound’s palm flicking back and forth in front of her.

“Oops. I’m sorry, I was a little dazed for a moment, I was a little surprised….”

Dolores blushed and apologized.

Then she looked at Night Hound, who had the face of a cute puppy, and frowned.

“What can I say? The atmosphere has changed a bit. It’s the same with the mask.”

“….”

Vikir didn’t answer, but the clever Dolores had already noticed. This meeting was not in Night Hound’s plans.

So he must have been too busy to prepare his mask.

“We must have met by accident.”

“….”

“Do you live around here?”

“….”

Vikir remained silent, but Dolores knew that she was interpreting it as a positive meaning.

“The fact that we met while looking around in casual clothes on a weekend means that you have a residence in this neighborhood. Moreover, considering that you are familiar with the geography of the Colosseo Academy….”

Previously, Dolores had thought that Night Hound had informants within the school.

However, looking at the current situation, the possibility that he was a person inside the school could not be excluded.

‘…Wait, why did I say that earlier?’

Dolores had just said the name ‘Vikir’ without realizing it.

Why, simply because of the hand covering her mouth?

Because it reminded her of the time she almost ran into Guality in the orphanage hallway?

Dolores felt a familiar sense of déjà vu.

But she doesn’t know exactly what it is.

It’s just a vague feeling that she’s missing something important.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Vikir watched the adjutant’s back as he walked away.

The scent of the demon was unmistakable on him, even faintly.

‘Even though Dantalian has been eliminated, the members of the Quovadis family still smell of the demon.’

That scent wafted throughout the Temple of the Old Testament, as he had confirmed when he bought his indulgence.

And Humbert, whom he had seen earlier from afar, also had a strong smell.

‘The New Testament priests at Quovadis Family don’t smell it at all, so the Old Testament and the Sixth Corpse must be involved.’

In particular, Humbert, the leader of the Old Testament, was a suspicious man in many ways.

The carriages he traveled in and the mansions he lived in were covered in precious metals and works of art, and his spending was enormous.

It was even revealed that he was receiving regular entertainment and bribes from Quilt of Indulgentia, but he was also a skilled politician who survived by having his tail cut off.

‘But he wasn’t a demon.’

Deeply intertwined with the demon, but not the demon.

No matter how carefully Vikir looked, it was the same conclusion every time.

‘Then we should investigate his new source of funding.’

Humbert still boasts wealth despite the extinction of the Indulgentia family..

‘If we can find out where he’s getting his money from, we might be able to find the Sixth Corpse, who is said to be close friends with the Ninth Corpse.

And Vikir sees a clue in Dolores’s words.

“They say that cults and sects are running rampant throughout the empire because of the conflict between the Old and New Testaments, so I thought I’d try to find a solution….”

Dolores revealed why she had come to spy on the temples of the Old Testament.

And Vikir reacted to the words ‘heresy’ and ‘cult’.

‘The Old Testament versus the New Testament, and they have the most to gain from it.’

Suddenly, Vikir’s mind flashed back to a target he had assassinated not long before.

The name Edward Bourbon Jr. Aka St. Bourbon.

A mid-level Graduator. A high priest of the emerging religion of Ohm, which has become quite powerful in the north.

A traitor who will betray the Human Alliance and join the Demon Army in the Age of Destruction decades later.

In the original fate, he would have wounded Tudor and Bianca and escaped, but Vikir killed him beforehand to eliminate any future worries.

The Indulgence Book was found as a memento of the dead cultist.

‘All sins of this faithful church member are forgiven.’

– This indulgence was issued and guaranteed by the Old Testament, and counterfeiting can result in punishment –

After some digging, Vikir came up with a pretty significant result.

‘Most likely, the Old Testament school’s new source of funding is cults and heresies.’

It was possible that the Old Testament faction was sowing ‘religious autonomy’ in the form of indulgences to gain an advantage over the New Testament.

Perhaps Cardinal Martin Luther recognized this to some extent, which is why he is here today.

Hearing Vikir’s words, Dolores covered her mouth with her hand in astonishment.

“…Oh my God! I didn’t realize that Cardinal Luther was watching! I must have been a frog in a well.”

“This is not the time to blame yourself.”

Cults and heresies were likely to be just the tail.

At best, they are ‘middle man’ who distribute and launder funds.

…The ‘real’ thing was behind the scenes.

The Old Testament of the Quovadis. And the cults and heresies running rampant throughout the empire. And a money trail that leads to a mysterious ‘dark side’.

In order for the Quovadis to be purified, the flow of dirty money must be cut off.

“Let’s start with the middle man.”

Dolores nodded at Vikir’s words.

What kind of outside force could be corrupting and manipulating the Quovadis?

Using the worldly weapon of money, no less, and quietly.

“…When heresies and cults take hold, it’s the poor and needy who suffer the most.”

Dolores continued, sounding indignant.

“I don’t think people need to believe in Lun to be saved, as long as they can find peace of mind by doing good to others in ways that are comfortable and familiar to them. But they’re not. They….”

Vikir was well aware of the dangers of heresy and cults.

During the days when the war against the demons was in full swing, he had seen many verminous things that roamed among the poor and sick, sucking the lifeblood out of them.

Money, food, body, blood, appetite, lust, pleasure, etc…… Most of the things that heretics and cults demand from believers are obvious.

“The one I killed yesterday was a similar case.”

Dolores paused for a moment at Vikir’s words.

As expected, Night Hound was fighting. Still alone, still hurting.

“…Let me help, too.”

Dolores held Night Hound’s hand tightly.

It was like that before, but now it was even stronger and more earnest.

…Aah!

A light of respect and affection that could not be hidden was radiating from Dolores’ eyes, which strongly demanded solidarity.

“I can be of help.”

At her strong assurance, Vikir asked curiously.

“That buff against Dantalian last time. Can you do it again?”

“…That, that is.”

Dolores quickly looked intimidated.

Apparently, it was only a temporary thing, and she couldn’t control the power yet.

‘Of course. If you could, you’d already be called the Ironblooded Saint.’

Vikir nodded.

Right now, Dolores is still just a young girl. She has a long way to go before she can awaken and become a great hero who will save all mankind.

It would be wrong to expect too much.

“I see. First, we’ll have to deal with the cults that are supposedly connected to the Old Testament.”

“Uh, how? Are you going to visit every single one of them in the empire?”

At that, Vikir shook his head.

“There’s not enough time for that. There is a way to overcome everything.”

A way to wipe out all the cults and heresies in the Empire in one fell swoop.

Dolores’ eyes widened at the mention of such a method.

Something that the young priests of the New Testament hadn’t been able to solve, no matter how many times they put their heads together.

An answer they had all given up on.

And yet, Night Hound was saying it quite firmly, his tone full of confidence.

“And what is that?”

Dolores asked with a twinkle in her eye.

Like a true honor student, she had a ballpoint pen and notebook in her hand, ready to take notes.

And then.

Vikir spoke, his voice flat and dry.

“I need your body.”

Chapter 270

Rich Friend (3)

◆

The Headmaster’s office, on the edge of the Academy.

Professor Banshee Morgue stepped into the dimly lit room and had to gasp in surprise.

In the darkness, a pair of blazing yellow eyes were staring at him.

“…Did you call me? Principal.”

Professor Banshee opened his mouth to speak with a trembling expression.

Then a face emerged from the darkness.

A middle-aged man with a vague look. It was a long-haired man who looked somewhat friendly with a young smile on his face.

Winston Smith, the Principal of Colosseo Academy.

Principal Winston said to Professor Banshee.

“I’ve heard that you’ve done a good job of cleaning up some of the messes in this University League.”

“…No, There were many shortcomings.”

“Not at all. You’ve done an excellent job of filling in for me as principal, and I don’t know what to thank you for.”

At Principal Winston’s words, Professor Banshee coughed once and looked away.

“You have returned to the Academy after a long absence. Have you accomplished what you set out to do?”

At Banshee’s question, Winston nodded with a faint smile.

“During training, I had a mana surge and had a difficult time, but I made it through.”

“…That’s good to hear.”

Banshee glanced away and looked at the hilt of a sword beside Winston’s hand.

The Winter Sword ‘Orwell’, Winston’s favorite weapon that looks like the horn of a unicorn. It is a legendary sword that only those who have attained the highest level of mastery are allowed to wield it.

Winston was in the midst of a grooming session when it slipped out of its sheath.

So the white lower part of the blade, the black middle part, and the reddish upper part were visible.

Then.

“…?”

Banshee noticed something strange.

There was a large scratch on the hilt of Orwell’s sword, a sword that was said to be able to break a thousand swords and not leave a scratch.

It looked like an arrow mark or a snake slither.

‘What in the world happened to that sword to cause it to be damaged?’

As Banshee stared curiously at the sword, Winston spoke softly to him.

“I heard that Professor Sadi got into a lot of trouble while I was away on sabbatical?”

“…More than I can say, which is why I’ve been putting together this report.”

Banshee reached out and slammed the mountain of papers onto the table.

With a thud!

A mountain of reports crashed onto the table.

Winston broke out in a cold sweat as he laughed in embarrassment.

“…Haha, ha. This must have been a lot for Vice Principal Morgue.”

“Sadi is not fit to be a professor, and to be honest, she’s a criminal who should be locked up in the far-off ‘Nouvelle Vague Prison’, not in a academy.”

“Don’t be so hard on her. Isn’t she the last descendant of the Marquises of Sade, who were so prestigious before the unification of the Empire?”

“The previous Marquis of Sade, who was the patriarch of that house, is also currently imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague.”

“….”

Winston sighed lightly.

Why shouldn’t he know about Professor Sadi, who’s been getting into trouble here and there.

“Still, it’s best to keep her inside the Academy. We can’t send her back to the imperial court, and we can’t have the descendants of high-ranking nobles living in poverty.”

“We’ve got finals and parent-observed classes coming up, and the final ranking battle is going to be a huge event with all the parents in attendance, and if Professor Sadi causes trouble again like she did during the midterms, we’re really going to be out of control.”

“Let’s just keep her out of the actual work as much as possible.”

“ …If that’s what the principal thinks.”

Banshee nodded.

Well, it wasn’t Professor Sadi that mattered now.

Winston, the Principal of Colosseo, had returned from a short sabbatical.

A legendary swordsman whose power is said to rival that of the Ironblood Swordsman, the Spearman, the Divine Archer, and the Mage Sect’s Lord.

It’s an uncomfortable silence for Banshee who has his sights set on becoming the next Principal.

Moreover, since he is from the Cold Department, he is in many ways the opposite of Banshee, who was from the Hot Department.

Final exams and parent-teacher conferences are the biggest events of the year.

The political battle structure within the school between the principal faction and the vice principal faction was once again becoming chaotic.

◆

Ryukeion, the newspaper club at Colosseo Academy.

Currently, the club room of Ryukeion was extremely busy.

The mana circulator was running nonstop. Newspapers were stacked and distributed quickly.

[Breaking News] Colosseo Academy’s Principal, Mr. Winston Smith, has returned!

-Winston Smith, the principal of Colosseo Academy, who suddenly declared a sabbatical and was away, returned to school last night.

There are many theories as to why the long-serving principal, who has been the spiritual leader of Colosseo’s Cold Class, suddenly declared a sabbatical and went into hiding, but the most likely explanation is that he was returning to his hometown to recover from a mana surge….

Meanwhile, Principal Winston, who has returned, looks even more intimidating than before his sabbatical… It was assumed that he had overcome his mana surge and had risen to a higher level.

“Did you hear, the principal is back!”

“Oh good! I liked Professor Winston, he was gentle.”

“I really didn’t like Vice Principal Banshee because he was cranky and cold whenever he went to take payment.”

“It’s going to be a sunny day for us Cold students, because Professor Banshee only favored the Hot students.”

“From the perspective of the Hot Class, I didn’t like the favoritism.”

“He must be in a hurry to get back here for finals and parent-teacher conferences.”

The newspaper students chattered away about the morning’s issues as they took pictures for the evening edition.

Meanwhile.

Amidst all the hustle and bustle, there was one person who was unusually busy.

Dolores. Student council president, newspaper editor, and captain of this year’s University League.

As student council president, she had to organize an event to celebrate the principal’s return, and as editor-in-chief of the newspaper, she had to report on it.

On top of that, the principal wanted to personally recognize the winner of the University League, so she had to prepare a winning speech for the awards ceremony and a pep talk for the juniors who would be participating in the University League next year.

There was even a ceremony to award various plaques and medals to the top 3rd graders who took the midterm exam….

‘Ugh, I wish I had ten bodies!’

Therefore, she was completing all these tasks by working all night long.

But despite the ongoing hard work, Dolores’ eyes glowed with life.

She had one transcendent goal that transcended all of these menial tasks.

‘I will eliminate the demon in the Bourgeois family and return the Bourgeois family and the Quovadis to normal.’

It’s been a long time since she’s had a desire.

Now it was time to make it a reality.

When Dolores had finished her work, she found an empty lecture hall and went inside.

She stared at the flyer for yesterday’s competition.

‘…A mock investment competition organized by Bourgeois Family.

Last night, Night Hound had given Dolores her instructions.

‘I will start earning money now, and get the attention of the Bourgeois.’

Night Hound had offered a sizable sum of seed money.

The plan was to roll this out and make a lot of money so that the Bourgeois could approach him.

‘In the end, you didn’t tell me how you were going to raise the money, but….’

However, Night Hound did ask Dolores for one thing.

He asked Dolores to do one thing: find a handful of competent people to do office, administrative, and other secretarial work.

Dolores happened to create a temporary club under the pretext of a mock investment competition hosted by the Bourgeois family.

The club was created apparently to participate in a competition organized by the Bourgeois family.

However, the money that is being funneled through it is all real money, and it will eventually become a sharp knife that will cut the throat of the demon lurking in Bourgeois Family.

When Dolores was thinking about various things in her mind.

Knock knock knock-

The door to the empty classroom opened and two students entered.

Two applicants were selected after defeating numerous competitors after a rigorous written test and interview.

They were Pigi and Sinclaire.

“Hey, guys.”

Dolores stood up from her seat.

Pigi, who had demonstrated exceptional intelligence and analytical skills despite being a freshman, and Sinclaire, who was nearly flawless in her administrative, office, and secretarial duties.

“Ms. Chairwoman, just like you said, I’ve been gathering all the information on the Bourgeois family’s celebrities and their latest happenings!”

“I’ve been analyzing the schedule, organization, and structure of the mock competition to perfection.”

Hearing their answers, Dolores felt reassured and smiled with pride.

The information and skills Night Hound needed were now in place.

Dolores was careful to make sure that the Oracle looked like a group of honors students from Colosseo Academy.

‘These children must never be caught in the act.’

Soon, the battle with the demon would begin.

Dolores even had a plan to get Pigi and Sinclaire out before then.

Then. Sinclaire asked.

“Ms. Chairwoman. It’s a mock investment, so why do you need seed money?”

“Well, actually, it’s just a mock investment, but we’re actually going to make an investment.”

“What?”

Sinclaire’s eyes widened at the audacity of the idea.

So did Pigi.

Dolores spoke again.

“Literally. We’re going to win the mock investment competition, and at the same time, we’re going to manage real money and make a huge profit. Of course, I’ll take full responsibility for any damage that might be caused.”

“I-Is there a reason you’re doing that?”

“First, because I’m sure of it. Second, to leave a strong impression.”

Sinclaire and Pigi exchanged glances at the certainty in Dolores’ voice.

If Dolores, the student council president, saying this, there was no reason not to do it.

In any case, the seed money is Dolores’s own money, and even if she loses it, Dolores takes responsibility.

Besides, isn’t she a genius who stands out in all fields?

“I can’t believe the chairwoman is saying this! I’ll contribute a small amount of seed money!”

“Me too! I’m entering the competition with the intention of winning in the first place, so I’ll show you what I’m made of! I’ll give you every penny I’ve got!”

In any case, Pigi and Sinclaire realized that they couldn’t do well in the competition on their own.

With Dolores on board, they were going to give it their all.

“…You guys.”

Dolores looked at Pigi and Sinclaire, impressed.

Then.

Sinclaire looked back at Pigi as if she’d just remembered something.

It made Dolores’ eyes widen.

“…Really! Should I ask my brother to join us? I’m sure he’d be a great help!”

It was a statement that was somewhat concerning.

Chapter 272

Money War (2)

◆

Late at night, when the excitement about earning a huge amount of money was slowly cooling down.

The night dew that had come out to greet the dawn hung heavily on the tips of the grass leaves.

Creak-

Dolores opened the door to the rooftop after a cautious glance around.

The rooftop of the girls’ dormitory was off-limits to students, so it was a cautious move.

She had just stepped through the door and onto the roof.

“….Hello”

A voice like scraping metal greeted her.

The Night Hound. He stood at the edge of the railing.

He stood at a height that was dizzying to look at, relaxed, as if he’d been there for a while.

“I’m sorry, I’m a little late, I was trying to avoid the housemaster. You’ve been waiting a long time, haven’t you?”

“Not really.”

Dolores stared at Night Hound’s cloak.

Judging by the lack of night dew, it hadn’t been long since he’d arrived.

“Did you get lost when you came? It must have been hard to find the girls’ dormitory, with so many similar buildings around.”

“It wasn’t that hard.”

Night Hound answered Dolores’s question nonchalantly.

For a moment, Dolores’s eyebrows twitched.

‘The dormitory buildings all look alike and don’t have any identifying markers, so it’s hard for a newcomer to tell the difference. Are you from the academy, Mr. Night Hound?’

If someone could find this hard-to-find place in such a short time without getting confused, they must be familiar with the internal geography.

Suddenly, Dolores remembered an incident that had happened not long ago.

The mysterious female black mage who had come into the academy during the festival, leading a group of undead soldiers.

She had said something strange.

‘Where did you take Night Hound? I found traces of Night Hound in your room.’

At the time, Dolores let the words slide.

Dolores, who values her privacy, doesn’t allow anyone to enter her space.

She even fixes her own furniture when it breaks.

‘Now that I think about it, why did she say that?’

Dolores wonders about their relationship, but she’s more concerned about the fact that Night Hound had been in her room.

At that time.

Rattling-

Something rattles in Dolores’s arms as she takes a step forward.

It was the Mirror of Truth.

It’s an artifact that shows the bare face behind the mask of the person it reflects, and it was the prize for winning first place in the University League.

‘…Shall I use this mirror to look at Night Hound?’

Dolores thought for a moment.

But then she squeezed her eyes shut and shook her head.

‘I brought it up just in case, but no.’

She didn’t want to learn his identity this way.

‘Let’s wait until Night Hound speaks first. It would be impolite.’

Dolores closed her eyes tightly, lost in her own anguish.

“?”

Vikir aka Night Hound was staring at Dolores curiously.

Finally, Dolores opened her eyes, took a deep breath, and spoke.

“I did everything you asked me to do.”

Dolores told Vikir everything that had happened.

The ten thousand people Pigi had known in finance. The letters Sinclaire had written, each one predicting the future.

Sometimes it was the price of gold, sometimes it was grains like soybeans and wheat, sometimes it was futures options on minerals like bronze or orichalcon, sometimes it was real estate or bonds.

The outcome was always either wrong or right, but the 30 or so investors who won that 50% chance in a row fell for the bait thrown by Night Hound.

Night Hound even made a fortune on his last investment, a merchant guild led by a dangerous figure named Cindywendy.

“You’re really good at investing, I didn’t know that.”

Dolores seems genuinely impressed.

Of course, Vikir didn’t care much.

“It was a trick that Cindywendy used a few years in the future.”

Vikir just had to apply it a little sooner.

“Now all that remains is to gather the members of the Bourgeois Family.”

It’s clean money, so there’s nothing wrong with that.

It was a bit of a scam, but there’s no problem with the current law anyway.

“And tell your friends thank you for their help.”

“Yeah. I will, but make sure they don’t get caught up in a fight with the demon….”

Dolores looked worried about Pigi and Sinclaire.

Of course, that had been on Vikir’s mind as well.

“We’ll just have to make sure they’re in a safe place when the time comes.”

With that, Vikir placed a vial in Dolores’s hand.

It was a sleeping pill.

Dolores looked nervous.

Vikir opened his mouth.

“Now we have the last step before the final battle.”

“When you say final, do you mean…?”

“We will bring in an insider.”

Vikir’s words made sense.

The Bourgeois family was shrouded in secrecy. They are untouchable unless an insider provides information.

“We need to find a Bourgeois who’s on the inside, and who’s at enmity with the current family.”

“Do you think there is such a person?”

“Of course. I’ve already researched them.”

The Bourgeois family lord.

It wasn’t hard to find someone in high places who was at odds with him.

“You can find out by looking at newspaper articles. You can find the answer by looking through old economic newspapers.”

For a moment, Dolores paused.

…Old economic newspapers?

‘…Also, he reads all the economic newspapers from a very long time ago, and his enthusiasm is really great….’

Dolores must have heard that somewhere in the back of her mind.

‘When was that?’

Dolores must have heard it recently, but she couldn’t remember when or who.

When Dolores was feeling déjà vu, Vikir thrust several newspaper articles in front of her.

They were clippings of economic news from a very long time ago.

[Economy] Who will be the lord of the Bourgeois family?

-A bitter dispute is brewing over the position of lord of the Bourgeois family…

The most likely candidates are the eldest son, Bartolomeo, and the second son, Damian……

[Economy] Deputy Director Bartolomeo becomes the target of a strong tax investigation!

-On October 0, Bartolomeo, the eldest son of the Bourgeois family and Deputy Director of the Mineral Futures Exchange, is responding to a sudden tax investigation…

Meanwhile, the Imperial Tax Investigation Team accuses Deputy Director Bartolomeo of treachery, embezzlement, and tax evasion, with instructions to make such unannounced raids more frequent. …

[Economy] Deputy Director Damian laughs at his daughter’s antics at her first birthday party

-On October 0, Damian, the second son of a Bourgeois family and Deputy Director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau, flashes his dad’s smile at his daughter’s birthday party…

[Economy] Deputy Director Bartolomeo, volunteering briquettes even in the bitter cold, ‘I convey my heart’!

-On December X, Bartolomeo, the eldest son of a Bourgeois family and Deputy Director of the Mineral Futures Exchange, went out of his way to help the less fortunate during the holiday season…

Despite the cold temperatures below freezing, he was sweating profusely as he delivered briquettes to the elderly living alone, showing his down-to-earth civic-mindedness…

[Economy] Deputy Director Damian, controversy over abuse of power

-On May X, Damian, the second son of the Bourgeois family and Deputy Director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau, was involved in a ‘gambling’ and became a hot topic…

At his daughter’s picnic, he insulted an attendant who was providing security, telling him to ‘do his job’ and causing mental damage…

If you look through the articles from a long time ago, right before the head of the Bourgeois family was decided, you can see who the rival of the current head of the bourgeois family, ‘Bartolomeo’, was.

Whenever there was a newspaper article accusing Bartolomeo of a negative image, there was a newspaper article promoting a positive image.

Conversely, when a newspaper article was published promoting a positive image of Bartolomeo, a negative image was published.

Thus, it became clear who the Bourgeois’s enemy was.

[Economy] Bloody shareholders’ meeting, who is the winner!?

-On the D day of the month D, the head of the Bourgeois family was decided.

The eldest son, Bartolomeo, was elected as the next family head…

The new head of the family promises to revitalize the family and announces a number of personnel changes…

The personnel changes are as follows

00 Department Head of the Administration Department 000 is transferred inside the family…

XX Director of an administrative department XXX transferred outside the family…

DD Director of the Management Department will go on a long-term regional trip…

Deputy Director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau, second son ‘Damian’ promoted to Director.

The younger brother who lost in Game of Thrones.

As a result, he was completely cut off from his family and taken as a hostage to the imperial family.

Bourgeois Ju Damian.

Once an aspirant to the throne. A former rival. A secret antagonist.

Vikir was paying attention to this ‘silver medalist’.

“Bourgeois Je Damian. Count of the Bourgeois family and current Director of the Imperial Money Manufacture. At the same time as he is eating away at the imperial family, he is also an advisory member and external director of several top branches run by the Bourgeois. However, since he is half-imperial, he cannot interfere in the internal affairs of the family.”

His promotion from Deputy Director to Director was likely the result of losing a political battle.

Originally, it was customary for talented members of the Bourgeois family to rise only to the second-in-command position in the imperial institution, learn only the know-how, then resign and return to their home family to take on important positions.

However, the abandoned dogs of the family have no one to call upon, so are left to sit at the imperial palace.

By becoming a hostage to the imperial family.

“…This is Damian. I know a little bit about him.”

Dolores flipped through the newspaper articles.

In her University League days, she had been on a quest for the Bourgeois in the second round.

Bourgeois / Difficulty [★★★★]

The Money Manufacturing Bureau has recently issued higher denomination bills, which have been plagued by a growing number of counterfeit bills.

From the perspective of the Bourgeois family, choose a product that would benefit from the monetary reform and suggest a new product or an improvement to an existing product.

Four stars for difficulty. This was a tough assignment.

Count Bourgeois Damian, the head of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau, had personally asked, Dolores had some acquaintance with him.

Vikir nodded and said.

“Now that we’ve made our pitch, it’s time to meet Damian.”

“How? He doesn’t seem to be selling meal tickets.”

Dolores asked with a puzzled look, and Vikir answered simply.

“Let’s throw a party.”

Dolores’s eyes widened as she looked at Vikir’s party quote.

“Huh! This is the budget for a party? Did I get the number of zeros wrong?”

The cost was so enormous that even the Saintess of Quovadis, one of the Seven Great Families, was shocked.

Vikir planned to spend the astronomical sum of money from this investment in a single party.

“I’m going to make it so lavish and extravagant. So extravagant that all the celebrities in the capital are rolling their eyes.”

Literally, money is just a means and not the goal.

Chapter 274

Money War (4)

◆

“This is the restroom, not the main building.”

Viscount Saltsail’s expression turned blank at Cat in Boots’ words.

“…You’ve got to be kidding, right?”

“No way.”

Cat in Boots raised a hand and pointed to the wall.

Suddenly, it made sense. Why there was a sink sticking out of the wall.

There was even a toilet just off to the side.

“You said earlier that you wanted to go to the restroom, so I led you here first.”

“Well, that was just a comment.”

“I see, then shall we go to the main building?”

Cat in Boots gestured to the maids in a dignified manner.

“The guest has been to the restroom, so bring him some fresh clothes and spray him with perfume.”

“Eh, eh, I don’t think that’s necessary….”

“No, we’re just doing our best, just in case you think you’re unclean just because you went in and out of the restroom. Don’t worry about it.”

Then the maids came over and exchanged Viscount Saltsail’s cape for another.

“We have several designs. You can choose the one you like best.”

Saltail’s jaw dropped at Cat in Boots’ words.

There were more than fifty Asbestos Capes, of which he had only two.

‘They’re the ultimate luxury, made from raw materials found deep in the western jungle, so even if you have the money, you can’t get them….’

Then.

Rattling-

The cocktail glass the maid was holding next to him made a sound. It was the sound of ice clinking together.

‘Eh, eh, eh, come to think of it…?’

Saltsail glanced at the cocktail glass he’d just half-finished and handed to the maid to hold.

Being an observant man, he soon realized that the ice cubes in the drink hadn’t melted at all.

“Hey, that’s not ice!”

To Saltsail’s exclamation of surprise, Cat in Boots spoke in a nonchalant tone.

“That’s right, it’s not ice, it’s a diamond. I keep them in a cold storage room so it doesn’t lose its cool, and of course, it won’t melt and make your drink bland.”

Saltsail’s mouth dropped open at that.

Cat in Boots then led him into the main building.

There, indeed, a spacious, grand, and luxurious interior, far beyond anything he had ever seen before, awaited him and all the guests.

The center of the Imperial Capital. The pinnacle of luxury.

Gorgeous lighting enveloped everyone.

The jewel lights of the chandeliers falling all over the place made everyone’s eyes intoxicated.

The gaps between the ceiling and walls were filled with spider webs, sprinkled liberally with gold dust, which glittered with every change of light.

The chamberlain-level servants who were busy coming and going were all wearing expensive asbestos capes over their uniforms, and theirs were black, different from those of the guests.

Viscount Saltsail exclaimed.

“ …What in the world is this interior, how can it possibly be this splendid?”

A truly avant-garde interior, far ahead of its time.

Even if you had the money, you couldn’t afford it because you didn’t know what it was.

The ceiling is high enough to set off firecrackers, and the spiral staircases connecting duplexes and duplexes stretch endlessly.

Rare and expensive ingredients of incalculable value are everywhere.

More than a hundred and fifty chefs were lined up in a circle, creating food for the guests in real time.

Elegant music from a triple keyboard. Musical instruments made of jade, pearl, and sapphire create glorious harmonies.

There were no words of moderation, frugality, or morality.

“Oooh, this is gorgeous!”

“I can’t believe they thought to build something like this inside a party hall.”

“I want to go in there too!”

“I wonder what I’ve been doing with all my money.”

“Kah! Yes, this is how money is supposed to be spent!”

There was even a pool inside the party room that was big enough to fit everyone.

What was in the pool wasn’t water, but a cherry-colored, low-alcohol fruit liquor, a mysterious drink that wouldn’t leave a sticky residue when it got on the skin and evaporated.

Perhaps because of its size, there was room for people to pass through it, and it was intricately crossed by seven ivory and gold bridges.

The bottom of the pool, which was filled with liquor, was made of glass, and large fish swam in an enclosed area below.

All of them were of the highest quality, and the chefs would pluck them out and cook them as guests requested.

Whether it’s a shark, a whale, or a whale shark.

This is like the main forest itself!

Everything you need to enjoy life was here.

Liquor, food, music, clowns, models, dancers, firecrackers, balloons, men, women… All of this fun and excitement was blazing and melting away in the midst of immense luxury and pleasure.

All of this is in the name of ‘compassion’.

A great show put on by three students of the Colosseo Academy with overflowing humanity, selflessness and compassion.

“I’ve never seen such a great party!”

“What kind of students are they to throw a party of this magnitude!”

“No, I mean, how much money did they make in the first place?”

The guests are all dumbfounded.

But it doesn’t last long, as they are soon overcome by the alcohol and the atmosphere.

Dancers covered in large, colorful feathers like flamingos put on a breathtaking show.

Tens of thousands of balloons are rising, and firecrackers are going off one after another.

Puff, puff, boom!

The balloons hit by the colorful sparks set off a secondary explosion, scattering the petals and gold dust inside.

This is the Oracle’s party. A party where everyone is drunk on the colorful lights of the party hall.

No one in the Imperial Capital, or indeed any of the renowned nobleman of the Empire, had ever experienced a party of this magnitude.

And then, the hosts of this party stepped forward.

“H-Hello?”

Pigi was the first to step forward with an awkward smile.

“You’ve waited a long time.”

Sinclaire was next, smiling in polite greeting.

“We are the members of Oracle who hosted this party today.”

Finally, Dolores, the representative, stepped forward.

Wah-aaaaaah!

The guests clapped and cheered.

Because the guests were older, no one stamped their feet or whistled, but they gave a warm welcome in their own way.

Then.

Dolores spoke up.

“I’d like to thank everyone for coming to our Oracle Investment Club party. I think it’s a great opportunity for us juniors to meet and greet our seniors.”

When it was revealed that she was the saintess of Quovadis, everyone exclaimed in exclamation.

‘Si, Sinclaire, what are we gonna do?’

‘Shhh. Pigi, be quiet. If we stay still, no one will know we’re commoners.’

Standing next to each other, Pigi and Sinclaire didn’t bother to give their names.

But, as Sinclaire had intended, most of the people around them naturally assumed that their lineage was nothing out of the ordinary.

Dolores, meanwhile, had the last word.

“I would like to take this opportunity to say that I hope that what we have begun today will continue. No, I don’t want it to just continue, I want it to be a steady march forward. Just like those nimble horses.”

She reached out and pointed to the center of the hall.

There stood a large, beautiful coral sculpture.

A magnificently sized and expensive coral, a statue carved out of it, how expensive and how much it must have cost to make.

…But it wasn’t a horse, it was a deer.

A deer with two antlers, not a horse but a deer.

But no one said anything else about the horse in Dolores’s words.

“Come on, junior, let’s run like horses!”

“Great! You’ve got guts!”

“They are very handsome young people!”

Jirokwima (referring to a deer as a horse).

What did it matter whether it was a horse or a deer in the first place, when they were already drunk with the splendor of the party?

Soon, the business world was swarming around Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire, showering them with praise, flattery, and curious conversation.

And.

“….”

The servant boy, who had been busy weaving in and out of the crowd, serving, ushering, and otherwise skillfully handling his duties, quietly made his way to the edge of the party.

Cat in Boots.

He looked at the crowd with his red eyes shining behind the mask.

‘End of the century. I’m glad the aesthetic I saw at the end of humanity worked.’

Night Hound. Vikir. This time, he became Cat in Boots.

Vikir’s mind flashed back to the time before his regression.

Just before the full-scale war of destruction against the demon army began, humanity began to exhibit numerous abnormal phenomena toward the end of the century.

One of them was luxury and pleasure.

Every nation, every country, is always on the brink of destruction, and extreme extravagance is always present.

Most of the most wealthy people in the world went insane just before the end of the world.

They began to pursue extremes of taste, fashion, beauty, etc., and began to indulge in luxuries beyond human standards.

The 3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th generations of rich people…… As each generation passed, the corruption and debauchery became more severe.

And whether he liked it or not, Vikir had witnessed their extravagant behavior many times.

‘In times of peace, people have money, but they don’t know how to spend it. They lack imagination.

The forms of interiors, designs, and other luxuries that humans could create with all their creativity and imagination when indulging in extreme luxury and pleasure.

Vikir had used his knowledge and experience to organize this party, even if only superficially.

‘By the way, I didn’t have enough money for the party, so I had to go into debt.’

As if this investment and dividend income were not enough, they also received new investment from numerous people and poured it into the party.

They had to make a strong impression on people in the business world somehow.

…Of course, Vikir had no intention of repaying his lenders.

Because all the rich people who lent money to Vikir were the demon’s agents.

They lent him money because they trusted the reputation of the Oracle Investment Club.

But of course, it was a fraud of identity theft, and Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire had no obligation to repay anything.

‘I’ll bankrupt them all. Try strangling yourself with the money you loved.’

These are the people who got money instead of power when they made a contract with the demon in the first place.

They were unscrupulous people who would betray the Human Alliance before anyone else if war broke out, so there was no need to feel sorry for them.

Above all, if I succeed in hunting the Six Corpse, they will lose their energy and fade away on their own, so there is no need to worry about the aftermath.

Then.

“…!”

Something caught Vikir’s eye as he silently searched his surroundings.

Long brown hair, pale skin, black eyes, and red lips.

An androgynous appearance that made it impossible to tell if it was a woman or a man.

He was dressed in a neat black suit and a red cape, but his attire somehow made him look more appropriate for a funeral than a party.

‘….Found.’

Bourgeois J Damian.

Director of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau and a member of the Bourgeois Landowners Guild.

Vikir closed his eyes once silently, then opened them.

He walked forward, his gaze firmly fixed on Damian.

With the eyes of a hound that has found its prey.

Chapter 275

Money War (5)

◆

Vikir pressed the cat mask tightly onto his face and stepped out.

His target was Damian, a man with long dark brown hair in the distance.

He holds the title of Director of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau and an outside director of the Bourgeois Landowners Guild.

An unusual position, half Imperial official, half director of a private company.

This is hard to understand without knowing the backstory of his exile after losing an internal family political battle.

He may have lost the Game of Thrones, but he was so capable and politically aware that even the Bourgeois family couldn’t completely disown him.

So, in addition to overseeing the work of the Money Manufacturing Bureau in the Empire, he also has a hand in the inner workings of the Bourgeois family’s largest landowning guild.

However, his status as a civil servant comes first, and he is not allowed to interfere in the affairs of his own family, so his position as a Director of the Landowners’ Guild is almost unnoticed.

His influence within the family is also minimal, almost non-existent compared to his title and social standing as an earl.

Vikir thought quietly.

‘Maybe his elevation to Director was a voluntary choice to survive.’

For those who challenged the throne and lost, there was only death, or worse, exile.

To avoid such an outcome, the brilliant and competent Damian would have instigated a promotion as soon as he realized he would not be able to hold the position of Householder.

To receive national protection.

‘Fearful of his own family, he volunteers to be the state’s dog.’

In other words, he was afraid of his family, so he turned to his job.

Vikir’s assessment of this choice was simple.

‘Wise.’

Vikir knew all too well that family can be your worst enemy.

You’re closer to them than anyone else, but they can hurt you more than anyone else.

In that case, Damian’s decision to turn his back on his family and join the imperial service was a wise one.

He was able to keep the Bourgeois in check, at least in a small way, by having the imperial favor.

‘Damian’s knowledge of the Bourgeois’s inner workings would be a great asset to the imperial family.’

We’ve already analyzed the newspaper articles and know that he’s at enmity with the Bourgeois family.

In other words, Damian is currently walking a fine line between the imperial family and the Bourgeois.

In addition to being a skilled merchant, he is also a skilled politician.

Vikir continued to move forward, passing out cocktail glasses to those around him like the other servants.

Even Dolores didn’t know that he was disguised as a servant here and now, so he moved more stealthily and discreetly.

The gap between him and Damian was now only a few meters or so.

He was chatting with the people who had gathered around him.

“Hahaha, money is such a great thing.”

“They say there’s nothing money can’t do.”

“I can’t believe you young juniors can afford such a luxury. Honestly, I’m a little surprised.”

“Indeed, money is something to be enjoyed once earned.”

“I can see why the phrase ”Golden Universalism“ came about.”

The people with drinks in their hands were laughing in a drunken way.

Then. One of them said.

“Ah, money is great, but it’s not everything. How many things in the world can’t you do with money?”

This is a response to the saying that gold is everything.

Then the other person next to him said

“Uh-huh. Don’t you know a saying that’s popular among young people these days?”

“Oi, what’s that?”

“If there’s something you can’t solve with money, you should think about whether you don’t have enough money, hahahaha!”

At those words, the crowd burst into laughter.

“That’s right. Having money doesn’t make you happy, but not having money makes you unhappy.”

“Sure. Eat good things, wear good things, ride in good things, sleep in good places, travel in good places, buy good toys, give good gifts to good people. Because if you’re full and warm in the first place, you have a much better chance of being happy than anyone else.”

“Hehe- when I was younger, I thought money was the best, but now that I’m older, I realize that money is even better than I thought when I was younger!”

“That’s right, when I was younger, I envied people with money the most, but now that I’m an adult, I still envy people with money the most.”

“One time I said, ‘I wish I had a lot of money,’ and someone said, ‘Money can’t buy happiness.’ ’ And I was like, ‘Who said I want to be happy? I said I want to have a lot of money.’”

“Really, money is a great invention. It’s the greatest symbol of humanity.”

The conversation soon turned to praising the greatness of money.

It may be an obvious topic since they are all figures in the business world, but in fact, there was another intention behind it.

It was also an indirect flattery towards Damian, the maker of ‘money’ itself.

Director of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau. The man who prints the currency of the land.

As the person most closely associated with money, it was assumed that he would have a certain pride and awe towards the item called money.

However.

“….”

Director Damian only laughed bitterly.

Then, without another word, he left the room and headed for the terrace alone.

The suddenly somber atmosphere had everyone wondering if they had said something wrong, but no one could put their finger on it.

“What, what, didn’t the Director look a little unhappy just now?”

“Hmm. Did we do something wrong?”

“Not really. We said all the right things.”

“Maybe he was just drunk?”

“You’re right. He seemed a little tired when he walked into the party in the first place.”

“…Plus, he’s got ‘daughter issues.’”

The others all nodded at the last one.

“Now that I think about it, his daughter has become like that….”

“You mean Juliet, I’ve heard the news.”

“She was so young and beautiful, it’s a shame.”

“No wonder he feels so bad, then.”

They talked about Damian and his daughter’s misfortune for a few minutes until the new dancers came in and captured everyone’s attention with their energetic dance.

Compared to the expensive liquor that went into their mouths, the sympathy that came out of their mouths seemed pretty cheap.

◆

“…Whoa.”

Damian. He was leaning against the terrace, staring out into the night.

Beyond the silken curtains, he could see the beautiful landscape of the Imperial Capital.

The blue night sky. It was cozy and comforting, the kind of place you want to curl up in and fall asleep.

But Damian only glanced at it for a moment before turning away.

Loud music and excited voices from the hall beyond. Everyone was talking about tonight’s party.

Suddenly, he remembered the story he heard in the hall.

“…Money.”

He was no stranger to money.

From the time he was born, he had a golden spoon of enormous purity in his mouth, and when he was young, he accumulated enormous wealth through numerous commercial ventures.

Now, in his twilight years, he was the head of a money printing institution.

In other words, a man who has spent his entire life around money. He was a being who had held an incalculable amount of money in his hands.

But even Damian flinched at the voice behind him.

“Do you think there’s anything in this world that money can’t do?”

Damian turned his head and looked behind him.

How close had he gotten? A boy in a cat mask stood behind him.

At first, Damian thought it was just one of the servants who had come to him out of admiration.

But then he realized.

‘…No presence?’

The boy approached without a sound and stood behind him like a ghost.

The movements were too subtle to be attributed to a servant who was simply trained in movement.

But Damian was indeed a smart man.

He didn’t show his displeasure or yell or anything.

He just tried to talk to him, to smooth things over.

“You know, a lot.”

Damian nodded, then turned his gaze to the night sky.

“Money is just one of many means to achieve a goal. And there are as many unfulfilled goals as there are stars in the night sky. That’s what makes us human.”

Damian replied in a casual voice, casually stepping away from the railing.

To return to the party hall.

Then. The servant boy said.

“So what’s the farthest and brightest of those stars?”

“…?”

Damian turned his head with a questioning look, and the servant boy was still standing there.

A star. Shining brightly in the night sky.

A lofty, distant goal that was truly desirable, but impossible to achieve, even for a man of Damian’s status.

“…Isn’t that what it means to meet your dead daughter?”

The servant boy’s words stopped Damian in his tracks.

There is a moment of silence, and the night air grows even colder.

Finally, Damian spoke.

“It’s about meeting the dead.”

He turned at an angle and looked at the servant boy.

His gaze, unlike before, was sharpened.

“…I can’t do it, but it looks like you’ll be able to soon.”

At the same time, a terrifying surge of murderous intent surged out.

Jizzzzt-

A flash of light. A golden stiletto flew out of Damian’s waistband and into the servant boy’s shoulder.

Damian thought briefly.

This spoiled servant boy will feel the fear of death, but his life will not be in danger.

But he will have to live with an uncomfortable arm for the rest of his life as a punishment for running his mouth at a high ranking nobleman.

But.

…Bang!

Damian’s thoughts were interrupted.

And the quick sword that was deployed quickly also missed.

A sharp crimson sword protruding from the back of the servant boy’s hand deflected his sword.

At the same time, Damian’s eyes opened wide as if they were torn apart.

“…N-Night Hound?”

Chapter 276

Money War (6)

◆

Vikir openly taunted Damian.

“…Isn’t that what it means to meet your dead daughter?”

There were stains even in his life that seemed to be nothing to envy.

His daughter, Juliet, died at a young age.

The Earl’s daughter was said to have drank poison herself in shame at being caught up in a scandalous affair.

Sure enough, Damian couldn’t bear the mention of his daughter, his only reverse, and pulled out his sword.

Siiiight.

A flash of light. A golden stiletto slices through the air at tremendous speed.

Vikir felt a small amount of admiration for Damian’s fierce sword strike.

‘Indeed, the all-powerful tycoon.’

Bourgeois, unlike Baskerville the Ironblood Swordman, Morgue the Mage, Quovadis the Faithful, Donquixote the Lancer, Usher the Archer, and Leviathan the Poisonous, has no special weapon to show off like sword, magic, holy power, spear, bow, or poison.

As a matter of form, yes.

But of course, the Bourgeois have a weapon that no one can ignore: money.

Money.

It was their vast financial power that made them one of the seven great families of the Empire.

…So, are the Bourgeois powerless?

Of course not.

Believing that there is nothing money can’t buy, the Bourgeois spent their money to acquire countless swords, spears, bows, shields, magic, and more.

They took over entire sword families or mercenary corps that seemed even slightly promising, and arranged marriages with members of prestigious martial families to produce excellent second, third, fourth, and fifth generation children.

These blood-born prodigies possessed all the qualities associated with swords, magic, divine powers, spears, bows, poisons, and more, and were given vast sums of money for early education, allowing them to develop their talents to the fullest.

Even if they didn’t have talent, they could create it with the help of expensive tutoring and elixirs.

The essence of the best of all families.

That is the true power of a Bourgeois family.

And Damian had attacked Vikir with the superior qualities he had inherited from his ancestors and the swordsmanship he had been thoroughly trained in from a young age.

But.

…Clang!

Damian’s sword deflected.

It was deflected by Beelzebub, the magic sword drawn by Vikir.

A stealthy presence, a terrifying power, and a sword as red as blood.

“…N-Night Hound?”

Damian’s eyes widened to the point of tearing as he deduced the conclusion from the target’s characteristics.

It seemed like he was genuinely shocked, as his characteristic expressionless expression was completely broken.

But Vikir was just as surprised.

‘You’re surprisingly strong.’

The sword that he had thought was just fancy on the outside was actually a real killing sword, not just for decoration.

Moreover, the sword technique that Damian had just deployed was clearly an old version of the Baskerville style.

It’s called the “Submerged Deep Sea Fish Style”.

It wasn’t technically 100% Baskerville, but rather a classical sword technique of the Bahamut family that had been absorbed into the Baskervilles quite some time ago.

The Bahamut family was one of the “Five Great Iron-Blooded Swordsmen,” a family with a long and storied history and a strong foundation in arcane swordsmanship, until they were all absorbed into the Baskerville family long ago.

‘A classic trajectory that looks like a mixture of fish scales and dog teeth, clearly a sword technique from a time when the Baskerville and Bahamut styles of swordsmanship had not yet fully fused. This must be a second-class military secret, forbidden to be taken outside the family. Did you pay to learn this?’

In Vikir’s opinion, Damian’s swordsmanship was still very sloppy.

Baskerville hadn’t absorbed all of Bahamut in the first place,

two things of different origins can never be exactly the same.

In the end, Baskerville had only taken what he could from Bahamut’s swordsmanship.

Like a dog swallowing a fish and spitting out the bones.

‘Trying to force the two together and fuse them is what makes them creak.’

As far as Vikir knew, the swordsmanship of Bahamut and the swordsmanship of Baskerville were only fully fused in Hugo later years.

So it’s not surprising that Damian’s weaknesses would have remained when he learned it.

Kiriririk-

Vikir dodged Damian’s attack with a quick tilt of his chin.

Damian retrieved his sword and sent it flying again.

The tip of the sword stabs like a tooth along a smooth and gloomy path like the scales of a deep-sea fish.

Puff-puff-puff!

Dozens of holes appeared in the blackout curtains as they fluttered in the wind.

“…!?”

But Damian couldn’t help but open his eyes wide.

Vikir’s body, which he could see through the fluttering curtains, was already gone by the time the curtains settled.

‘Huh, where?’

Damian closed his eyes and stretched out his energy.

The mana emanating from his body congealed into an aura that wrapped around him like a net.

But there was nothing to be caught.

Shhh-

The only thing that sent a chill down his spine was the sound of the wind whistling past his ears.

Damian gritted his teeth and turned around.

“There!”

There was Vikir, standing on thin air.

Underneath his feet was a spider web that was so thin that it was invisible to the naked eye.

Swiiiig-

Damian’s sword emitted a brown aura.

This time, it was a more skillful Baskerville Four.

A sharp killing move, complete with the Graduator’s aura.

Unfortunately for Damian, Vikir is a veteran of the Baskerville style.

‘Shallow.’

The Bahamut family’s deep-sea fish are not as effective in shallow water.

Whilick-

Vikir wrapped his hand around Damian’s stiletto and pressed it into the ground, then stomped on it to crush it.

…Clang!

A long sword shatters on the ground, and at the same time, the Graduator’s aura is smashed and scattered like water droplets.

“…Cough!?”

Damian jumped back in surprise.

The opponent was a rare villain, Night Hound that was known to kill even mid-to-high level Graduators.

His danger is comparable to or higher than Ms. Ouroboros.

Damian knew he couldn’t take this one on alone, so he couldn’t waste any time.

Damian quickly retreated backwards.

However, as a person who knows well that one should not show one’s back to a dog, he still kept his gaze straight ahead and once again displayed the Baskerville style with his stilettos cut in half.

This time, however, Vikir skillfully dodged the attack.

Kiririk- …Tsk!

The flying hound’s teeth are familiar as his own, so all Vikir have to do is gently wrap his arms around it and swallow.

Tarang-

Having deflected all of Damian’s attacks, Vikir rushed forward and slashed at his sword, sending it flying.

“!?”

Damian’s eyes widened to tears.

Vikir thought to himself.

‘No wonder you’re surprised.’

A deadly killing move that had never failed him before.

This technique was recognized even by Cane Corso in the Grave of Swords.

Clang.

The sound of Damian’s sword falling to the ground could be heard behind him.

“….”

Damian bit his lip in defeat.

No matter how much money you have, there’s no way you’re going to be able to defend yourself against a sword that’s right in front of you.

For the first time in a long time, Vikir remembered Hugo’s teaching.

‘The things rich people always say are the same. ‘Money is power.’ But they probably know too. When the proposition ‘A is B’ is put forward, A in front is always inferior to B behind. Phrases like ‘Time is money’ and ‘Silence is golden’ are just that. These are tearful attempts to somehow match what is in front with what is behind. Who would exchange gold for time and silence? Everyone chooses gold. In other words, those who say ‘money is power’ know it well. ‘Money is worse than power’.

The reason why Hugo, who was usually quiet, spoke a lot that day was because of his hatred for the Bourgeois.

‘If Hugo found out that Director Damian was learning Baskerville to the fourth form, there would be a war.’

Vikir clicked his tongue and stretched out his hand.

…Quack! Thud!

He grabbed Damian’s face with one hand and slammed it into the floor.

They say money is power, but in the hierarchy of things, power is higher.

The confidence of those with money is often shattered in the face of pure violence.

Is that why? Damian was currently on the ground, his eyes wide open.

And then.

“….”

He closed his eyes silently.

Not protesting, not screaming, just quietly accepting the sentence to come.

Vikir asked in a hoarse voice.

“No pleading, no threats?”

“….”

“Usually they’re busy telling me that they’ll pay me to let them live, or that if I touch them, I’ll be in trouble.”

After a few moments of silence, Damian spoke up.

“My back hurts, so I can’t talk.”

“….”

“Just kidding.”

Damian’s nonchalant demeanor in this situation speaks to the experience of a veteran who has been through a lot and survived a lot.

Damian looked up at Vikir and said.

“By the look in your eyes behind your mask, you are not a man to be easily persuaded. You must have a purpose.”

“….”

“If you’re going to kill me, kill me. There are no negotiations with terrorists.”

At Damian’s words, Vikir shook his head.

“You got a good look, but you didn’t see the whole picture. I had no intention of killing you in the first place.”

“….”

“But you seem to be full of thoughts of death.”

Vikir’s words stunned Damian for a moment.

His eyes slowly drift up to the night sky as he lies on the ground.

“….”

A brightly shining star. It was so far away, out of reach.

So far, so far away that not even its light could reach Damian’s eyes.

Then, a dry voice came out of his mouth.

“You’ve seen it. I’ve seen it all.”

Chapter 278

What Money Can’t Buy (2)

◆

“What if I told you that you could talk to your daughter?”

“…!”

“And what could you give me?”

Damian’s eyes widened at Vikir’s words.

If only he could get his daughter to come back and talk to him once more, what a price to pay as a father.

“I, if my daughter wakes up. I would never be angry with her again, and I would let her know that I love her no matter what, unconditionally, and I would respect whatever choices she makes, and I would forgive her for the rest of her life….”

“No. What can you give me?”

Vikir cut Damian’s confession short.

Vikir was not a priest, and he was under no obligation to listen to the regrets of an incompetent father.

“….”

Damian’s expression went blank for a moment, then returned.

He’d met countless people in his life who’d begged him to lend them money.

They wanted an investment, they wanted to pay interest, they wanted to delay the payment of a debt, or they had a sick family member – parent, spouse, child…

But each time, Damian thought to himself.

‘What the hell.’

That’s their problem, not mine.

In order to make a deal, you have to convince the other side, and an essential part of that process is convincing the other side that the deal is a win-win.

That doesn’t include the unfortunate party’s pathetic story.

Damian, who has made a lot of heartless trades in his life, finally snapped out of it.

“If you give me my daughter back, I’ll give you everything in my power, including….”

Damian said without hesitation.

It looked like he’d been practicing his resolve for a long time.

But Vikir shook his head.

“I didn’t say I’d give it back.”

“…?”

“To make conversation possible.”

For a moment, an anxious glint flashed across Damian’s face.

“You don’t mean you’re going to kill me and my daughter so our souls can talk to each other or something?”

“Well, that would be one way.”

“ …Look.”

“But that’s not a good idea, especially since it’s a money-back guarantee if you’re not satisfied with the results.”

Vikir stood up and turned to face the back of the fluttering curtain.

When Damian pushed himself out of the booth, Vikir was gone.

However.

“Dying is not an atonement, it’s an escape. Take responsibility for it to the end.”

He could only hear the muffled voice echoing in his head.

◆

Exactly one month later.

Vikir found Damian’s mansion.

On the outskirts of a strict border, gaps appear like threads.

Through the gap into the depths of the mansion, he saw Damian standing nervously.

He was spinning around in circles, restless like a rabbit with a pocket watch.

Finally, spotting Vikir, Damian spoke in a tightly held voice.

“…You’re late.”

“This is early.”

Brief greetings are exchanged.

Vikir was led by Damian to a bedroom deep in the annex.

At first, the big, fluffy bed came into view.

Temperature, humidity, light, and relaxing scented candles fill the center of the room.

A woman lay with her eyes closed.

Long, flowing white hair. Fair, clean skin, big eyes, long lashes.

Juliet. Juliet J Bourgeois. Damian’s only child and only daughter. One of two girls who tried to become the next head of the family. The genius girl who was once thought to be the closest to becoming the next head of household.

“….”

Vikir stared at Juliet’s sleeping face.

‘I think I recognize this face.’

Surely it was familiar.

Vikir wondered for a moment where he had seen this woman’s face before.

“Is this a necessary part of awakening my daughter, to stare so intently into a sleeping lady’s face?”

Damian asked in an uneasy voice from beside Vikir.

Vikir heard the words and pulled his gaze away from Juliet’s face.

“You can come out now.”

With that, Vikir’s cloak was lifted, and a figure stepped out from within.

It was Pomeranian.

Damian stared at Pomeranian in disbelief.

“ …What is this girl? She looks way too young.”

“She is the shaman who will summon your daughter. If you want to talk to your daughter, stay quiet.”

Vikir waved away all of Damian’s questions as if they were a nuisance.

Then Vikir turned to Pomeranian and spoke.

“Pomeranian. Your soul sensitivity is excellent. Can you do this?”

“Mmm! Samchun!”

“Uncle, not Samchun. Anyway, let’s do what I told you before.”

Vikir, Pomeranian, and Damian moved to the middle of the bed and stood looking down at Juliet.

After staring at Juliet for a moment, Pomeranian spoke.

“This sister. Have no soul.”

The words stunned Damian.

“What do you mean, no soul? What does that mean?”

“Mmm. … it away. It’s somewhere else.”

“Well, what does that mean, huh, kid, talk to me longer!”

Damian dropped to his knees and locked eyes with Pomeranian.

Then Vikir interpreted.

“Your daughter is now a living soul (生靈), wandering elsewhere. Neither in this world nor the next.”

“A living soul, what is that?”

“Her body is alive, but her soul is wandering elsewhere, assuming herself dead.”

Vikir glanced at the Pomeranian.

“The living soul thinks it is dead and wonders why it cannot go to the other side. Or even worse, it thinks it is still alive.”

“Well, then, what can I do!”

“Nothing. That’s why I brought the shaman.”

Vikir stroked the Pomeranian’s head.

“Hey, can you summon the owner of this body that has become a living soul here, in a visible form if possible?”

“Mmm… I can’t use the tree samchun (uncle) gave me the other day!”

Pomeranian replied cheerfully.

With that, she closed her eyes and began to draw upon her mana.

A natural born black mage.

Her skill at raising dead rats and scarabs with the black magic she’d learned over her shoulder had grown during her time in Baskerville.

Besides.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

A black aura rose up behind Pomeranian’s back, forming the shape of a tree.

A Wraith Tree.

It was an ancient artifact that Vikir had obtained from the Grave of Swords, one of the few artifact left by the legendary black mage Morgue Tzersi.

‘Finally it works.’

Vikir nodded.

The Wraith Tree, rooted in the Pomeranian’s mind, had sensed her talents and qualities and started to shake its trunk and leaves.

‘It had form then, and now it has no form.’

[Originally, the ancient artifact were both form and formless].

Decarabia interrupted.

Vikir pressed the creature back into his chest and focused on the Pomeranian.

And then.

“Meet me at the entrance to the forest, at the end of the road, under the big tree that was split by lightning!”

Then Damian’s eyes widened.

“That’s where she was in the carriage accident! At the end of the road, where the big tree was split by lightning!”

“I know, so be quiet.”

Vikir gave Damian a glare and turned away again.

Black mana began to gather at the Pomeranian’s fingertips.

The power to wield domination over souls, dead or alive.

The leaves, trunks, and roots of the Wraith Tree reached out, calling the living souls from far beyond.

And then, before their eyes, something semi-transparent appeared.

[…What? Where?]

Juliet. The tragic heroine appeared.

“Da, daughter!?”

Damian was about to jump out of his seat.

He froze in place.

“What? What a surprise. Sister brought him here.”

Pomeranian shook her head.

Tsutsutsutsutsu…

Another soul appeared next to Juliet with a bewildered expression.

It was Romeo.

◆

[…So that’s how it happened].

Juliet nodded.

She looked down at her own body lying on the bed as Damian told her the whole story.

A body that was breathing quietly. But she had lost her love and her soul, and living was no longer living.

Damian knelt in front of Juliet, tears streaming down his face.

“I’ve done wrong, daughter, and you may never forgive this ugly father for ignoring your feelings and acting so selfishly for no good reason.”

[…Rise, father].

Juliet reached out for him. Damian lifted his head involuntarily, drawn to her touch.

Beside her stood Romeo’s soul.

Damian offered him his deepest apologies.

“Even if I had ten mouths. I have nothing to say to you. I have been a bad father.”

Romeo’s eyes widened at the words.

Juliet did the same.

[Father! Are you sure…?]

“Of course, you two are already married. Whether my approval matters to you or not, I choose to think so.”

Then tears welled up in Romeo and Juliet’s eyes.

[Thank you, father. Thank you!]

“I… I am grateful. For growing so beautifully. For calling your ugly father ‘abeonim.’”

Damian poured out his regrets and apologies in a voice that sounded like all his insides were breaking.

Juliet and Romeo nodded and sobbed.

It was an emotional scene as father and daughter, father-in-law and son-in-law, unpacked years of resentment.

“There’s no time. Just hurry up and get the job done.”

Vikir dismissed the whole thing briefly.

Damian tilted his head in question.

“Wh, what do you mean, no time, my daughter’s soul has just returned?”

“Not your daughter’s. I mean the man.”

At Vikir’s words, both Damian and Juliet’s gazes turned toward Romeo.

[….]

As it turned out, Romeo hadn’t said anything since earlier.

Vikir briefly explained what he had heard from Pomeranian.

“Apparently, the man is completely dead and the woman is half dead, so they can’t be together for long. They have been brought here by force from the place of their death, and it is time for them to pass on once and for all.”

“What, what! Why are you saying that now?”

“Didn’t it matter if I could only summon your daughter’s soul?”

“Why doesn’t it matter! My son-in-law is going to the other side now!”

“You killed him, why are you telling me?”

Damian’s mouth twitched at Vikir’s words, unable to argue back.

Pomeranian shook her head.

“You have to go to the other side. That’s the way it is. It’s the law.”

True to his word, Romeo’s body blurred with each passing moment.

Unlike Juliet, whose body was still alive.

[…Darling, don’t leave me, please, I can’t live one bit in a world without you!]

Juliet sobbed into Romeo’s arms.

Damian ran his hands through his hair again and cursed himself.

“Alas, I have driven this couple apart again, what a selfish, foolish idiot I am!”

Now Romeo crosses the gates of death and leaves for the other world.

He will never return.

But Juliet, the living soul, cannot follow him.

Her bond with her living body has not yet been severed.

Juliet and Romeo can only caress each other’s faces and shed tears of longing.

And Damian is once again deeply regretting his choice to separate his daughter from her life twice.

“I swore I would never… cry for my daughter again… I swore I would never feel the same regret again… Alas, what a greedy pig I am.”

Damian thought he was already at the bottom, but there was a basement. The layers of regret are so deep and complex.

Just as Damian was drowning in his own self-pity.

…Tud!

A hand on Damian’s shoulder.

Vikir.

Damian turned, and Vikir opened his mouth to speak.

“It’s time to let her go.”

There are only two places a father will hear these words.

The wedding and the funeral.

In a situation where these two places that should not be related at all are perfectly in sync.

“ …………”

Damian’s pupils were shaking more violently than ever before.

Chapter 279

What Money Can’t Buy (3)

◆

Pomeranian was right when she said that time was running out.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

Suddenly, a large gate appeared in front of Juliet and Romeo.

The gates of death.

The gate was so large and heavy that it seemed to be incredibly difficult to open and close.

So once it was opened and once it was closed, there was no turning back.

Romeo looked back at Juliet with a sad face.

Juliet, too, weeps and looks at Romeo.

[I told you before, wherever you go, I will follow you].

That night in the pouring rain. The promise they made.

Romeo leaving to go where the dead deserve to go, and Juliet following him.

Then. Damian stepped between them.

“No! No! Never!”

Damian shouted in a seizure.

“Juliet, you are still alive! How can you follow a dead man!”

And Juliet replied in a sad voice.

[My father had said so that night].

Hearing his daughter’s words, Damian took a half step back, as if in shock.

He had said something similar the night before.

‘Juliet, you are the heir of the Bourgeois family, why would you entangle yourself with such a base and ignorant man?’

The memory of that night haunted Damian, and he stammered an excuse.

“Well, this is a different case! If it were a marriage, I’d allow it! The ugly father was all wrong, I admit it! But this isn’t… this! Romeo’s dead, and you’re alive!”

[Only ‘yet’].

“What, what?”

Juliet exclaimed, her eyes locking with Damian’s.

[Without him, I’m as good as dead].

“Daughter!”

[It doesn’t matter how many times you say it, I’m the same, and even if I woke up again, I wouldn’t change].

With those words, Romeo touches Juliet’s face with a sad expression.

Juliet wraps her hand around his, too.

Damian muttered in disbelief.

“My daughter, you are a living soul, and they say a living soul cannot go to the other side. Your body is still alive and connected by a strong thread. I don’t know about Romeo, who is already dead, but you cannot cross the threshold of death….”

A moment. Damian stopped talking and looked up at Juliet as if struck by lightning.

“Ju-Juliet. You don’t think…?”

[….]

And Juliet lifted her tear-filled eyes.

Soon. She knelt before her father.

[Father. Please let me go now].

Everything was the same as that night.

‘I’ve listened to you all this time’

[I’ve been a proud daughter, never letting you down].

‘So just this once.’

[Just this once, can’t you let me do as I please?]

Whether the voice now echoing in his ears was from the past or the present, Damian couldn’t tell.

All he could do was continue to shed tears that he thought had long since dried up.

“…Ah, yes, that’s it, I crossed the river of no return, yes, that’s it.”

Hearing his daughter’s voice, for just a moment, he feels illusory.

He thought he could make everything right.

But it was an absurd illusion because he hadn’t yet felt the full weight of his mistake.

And now. Realization struck, and Damian felt the true weight of his actions.

“What are you going to do?”

Vikir asked briefly.

Damian voice cracking.

“…Hours. How long do we have?”

“About thirty minutes.”

It was indeed a short time.

Damian hesitated for a few seconds, then nodded.

He quickly ran to the servants beyond the doorway and shouted as loudly as he could.

“Get ready for the wedding!”

◆

The wedding preparations were done simply, but quickly.

There was Juliet, the bride, and Romeo, the groom. With Damian, the father of the bride.

And according to the family law that relatives cannot officiate, Vikir officiated.

Pomeranian was to hold the hem of the bride’s dress and receive the bouquet.

Vikir adjusted his plague doctor mask once, then stood at the dais and spoke briefly.

“Always remember, I am here for you, not you for me. Live well the way you used to live.”

Unlike the hours-long ceremonies usually performed by high ranking nobles, this was a ceremony that left out a lot, but included all the essentials.

Juliet and Romeo look into each other’s faces and smile tearfully.

And then the bride and groom kiss.

Damian, who was sitting alone at the wedding table, cried as he watched that scene.

And then.

BAM!

Pushing his chair out of the way, he looked into his daughter’s soul and said.

“Live well.”

At the same time. He picked up the pillow next to him.

Where Damian’s gaze rested, he saw Juliet’s body lying on the bed, breathing quietly.

“Live well, daughter. Live well, really live well.”

A trembling hand. Damian’s grip on the pillow tightened.

He pressed the pillow firmly against Juliet’s face.

It didn’t take much force.

Juliet’s body, weakened from lying down for so long, simply lay there, offering no resistance.

The only sound was the tiny gasps of breathing that grew smaller and smaller until they were no longer audible.

Chuug…

Juliet’s body became even more limp.

Then something changed in Juliet’s soul.

Her body became clearer and clearer. And she could finally hear Romeo’s words.

[Oh, my God, Romeo, I can hear you now!]

Juliet smiled brightly in Romeo’s arms.

And then.

Juliet and Romeo stood before Damian.

Romeo bowed ninety degrees to Damian.

Juliet bowed her head slightly in the manner of a noble lady.

[Father, we will live well].

“…What’s the point of living when you’re already dead.”

Damian muttered in a somber voice.

His red, bloodshot eyes were already filled with tears.

Ding- ding- ding-

Twelve chimes of the Great Clock strike midnight.

Juliet and Romeo said their final goodbyes to Damian and then, holding each other’s hands, they walked across the carpet to the distant door of death.

Eventually. The bride and groom have crossed the line.

The line on the other side that separates this world from the afterlife. They opened the heavy door of death, crossed the high ledge, and left for their own world.

…Thud!

The heavy, dull door closed as if it would never be opened again.

Death and life, the afterlife and this world are cut off.

….

A silence as quiet as a tomb weighs down the hall.

Damian lowered his head and muttered.

“…Be happy. Be happy, daughter. You two must be happy there. You must.”

His face twisted and hardened. The restrained tears were falling thickly, dripping onto the red carpet.

…Just then.

BANG!

The gates of death suddenly burst open with a loud bang.

[Dad!]

Juliet, who had just kicked open the heavy door, stuck her head out.

[Hello Dad! Hi! Love you! I really love you! We will definitely meet again someday!]

Juliet was crying.

She was calling out to her dad with the most brilliant smile Damian ever seen on her face, and she was really crying.

At the same time.

…Thud!

The door to death closed completely.

It slowly faded away, just as it had appeared, and soon disappeared from everyone’s sight.

And then.

Bug-

Damian dropped to his knees.

He opened his nose and mouth wide.

“Huuuuuuuuuuu-”

His solemn expression completely collapsed.

His face was a complete mess, with tears in his eyes, snot in his nose, and drool dripping from his mouth.

He leaned against the bed where his daughter’s body lay and sobbed like that for a long time.

“….”

Vikir only stood still.

Pomeranian came to Vikir’s side.

“Samchun. Why is he crying?”

Vikir stared into Pomeranian’s face.

“I don’t know.”

“And Samchun doesn’t know either?”

Pomeranian’s words made Vikir look away again.

‘If death were to separate us, I wanted to be together even after it.’

Why? A woman’s face comes to mind.

Vikir spoke in a low voice.

“There are things I don’t know, of course.”

“If you don’t know, you have to learn!”

“Hmm. I didn’t really want to learn originally, but….”

Pomeranian gave him a questioning look, and Vikir looked away.

And then he spoke briefly.

“I suppose it wouldn’t hurt to get to know it.”

Just then.

After a long sob, Damian raised his head.

Vikir waited patiently for him to gather some of his emotions.

When he did, he looked up and saw Vikir standing like a ghost near Juliet’s bed and asked.

“…Are you really alive?”

“If you’re dreaming, keep it to yourself. It’s settlement time.”

Vikir said firmly, snapping him back to reality.

Damian nodded at the words.

“Right. I suppose it’s time to settle our trade, but before we do, there’s something I need to tell you.”

“What?”

“Thank you.”

It was a sudden thing. Damian bent ninety degrees at the waist toward Vikir.

After a moment of silence, he raised his head and spoke.

“You’re the reason I was able to let her go, completely.”

It was an ambiguous situation as to whether he meant was married her off or sent her to the underworld, but it was true in either case.

Damian said with a slight smile.

“Haha, I’m feeling pretty good now that I’ve sent my disobedient daughter off to wherever she’s going. It’s like a wedding or a funeral, isn’t it? Marriage is a tomb, after all.”

“Wipe your face and then speak.”

“Oh, no. I’m sorry.”

Damian pulled out a handkerchief and wiped away the tears, snot, and drool.

Once he was back to his serious, solemn self, he asked Vikir straightforwardly.

“What do you want from me?”

“The head of the Bourgeois Family.”

“Head of the family.”

A conversation like lightning.

It was a cool transaction that was too quick.

Chapter 283

Power inflation (3)

◆

“Is there anyone in this world who can scare me?”

As the Great Evil raises its head and views the world.

“Here I am.”

The pilgrim raised his hand and answered.

At the same time. Dolores felt her body, which had been about to be crushed, suddenly lighten.

The pilgrim. Night Hound.

Vikir stared at Bartolomeo.

“…!”

Bartolomeo felt the hairs on the back of his neck stand up.

Jzzzzz!

As he tilted his neck back, a crimson slash flew out and split the mountain of gold coins behind him diagonally.

Sssssshhhhh, clatter, clatter, clatter, clatter!

The torn and crumpled gold coins crumble to the ground with a loud clatter.

“…Oho.”

Bartolomeo rubbed the black blood flowing lightly down his cheek with his thumb.

He straightened his stance and asked in a hard voice.

“Are you Night Hound, the one who killed Quilt the other day?”

“Not Quilt, exactly, but the 9th corpse, Dantalian, the Thousand Faces.”

At the mention of the name Dantalian, Bartolomeo’s expression tightened and loosened for a split second.

“…The 9th what? The Thousand Faces? What is Dantalian? You’re talking about something I don’t understand.”

He tried to play it off, but once the demon hunter had gotten this far, there was no escaping the situation.

“Andromalius, ‘Inferior Second Son’. Dantalian, ‘Thousand Faces’. ‘King of the Undead, ’ Seere. ‘Wall of Wailing,’ Decarabia. I took them all away. Do you understand now?”

“….”

At Vikir’s words, Bartolomeo fell silent.

There is no need to show off to someone who knows everything.

Slurp-

With that, he pulled out a sword that was haphazardly buried in a pile of gold coins.

Bartolomeo stared at the red sword that extended a meter below Vikir’s wrist.

“Maybe should I use a sword?”

“….”

“I’m here.”

Bartolomeo smirked and held up the sword.

Vikir recognized it at a glance for what it was.

A black edge. A blue gemstone that glowed grimly at the end of the golden handle. A longsword with a golden cord hanging down.

Balmung.

Also known as ‘Balmung of the Deep Sea’ or ‘Balmung of Bahamut’.

That is one of the magic swords that have been handed down from ancient times to the Iron Blood Swordsman Baskerville.

Sharp enough to cut through steel with a mere touch.

However, it is a fearsome sword with a legend that it corrupts those who wield it and turns them into tyrants.

It once belonged to the Nibelungen family, renowned for their mastery of the sword during the Warring States Period, and became a sacred object of the rival Bahamut family. After the Bahamut family merged with the Baskerville family, it would have been stored in the deepest part of the Baskerville family’s armory.

‘…Why is it here?’

Vikir was puzzled for a moment.

But the question was soon answered. Bartolomeo spoke first.

“In his youth, this body was a very promising swordsman. So much so that the previous Lord of Baskerville, was so impressed with my talent that he gave me this sword as a gift to become his apprentice.”

“….”

“You’re pointing a sword at this body like that? Hehehe, well.”

Bartolomeo tilted his feet sideways and stood in front of Vikir.

And.

Fit-

He leaped up with tremendous speed and landed on top of Vikir’s body.

Boom!

Sword and sword. Bartolomeo and Vikir’s auras collided in midair.

The impact shattered the jewelry and gold coins around them into dust and shards, which soon turned into a dense mist that spread in all directions.

…Boom!

Two shadows crossed over the two half-collapsed hills of gold coins.

Bartolomeo and Vikir each shifted to where the other had been standing.

It was Bartolomeo who flinched first.

Blugh-

Dark blood dripped from his nose and mouth.

In his youth, Bartolomeo’s body was comparable to that of Hugo the Ironblood Swordman’s patriarch.

But much time has passed.

His untrained body has grown old, and rust has set in on the qualities that once shone so brightly.

“…But.”

The corners of Bartolomeo’s mouth twitched.

“Form may be temporary, but class is eternal.”

At the same time.

Plugh-

A fountain of red blood erupted from Vikir’s waist.

Clearly, Bartolomeo’s counterattack had been effective.

The sharp sword edge of the Magic Sword Balmung had pierced through the protection of the Styx River and the regenerative powers of the Danger Rank S Monster Basilisk.

Vikir was forced to retreat with a wound so deep that his internal organs were visible.

…Thud! … Thud! … Thud!

Hot blood drops stain the cold, golden soil red.

Bartolomeo frowned at Vikir.

“Financial relationships are give and take, aren’t they? I’m the kind of person who doesn’t take on debt, so I always pay it back right away.”

“….”

“You know what they say, there’s no such thing as a free lunch. Everything has a cost, a consequence, a balance of totals. Some things you seem to get for free, some things you seem to lose because you’re down on your luck, all end up costing you something in the end… hmm?”

Bartolomeo paused before speaking.

When he did, Vikir said briefly.

“I agree.”

At the same time.

…Puff, puff, puff!

Fountains of blood gushed out of Bartolomeo’s body with tremendous force.

“Huh?”

He had been so sharply impaled that he hadn’t even realized that his body had been wounded.

The hound’s teeth were indeed sharp. So sharp, in fact, that blood bled lazily from the wounds they dug.

Bartolomeo staggered back.

“Hehehe… This is such a cliché scene.”

“You should be ashamed of yourself if you didn’t realize you were cut.”

Vikir remembered a time before the regression.

Of all the comrades he had shared countless battlefields with, there were a few who were exceptionally skilled with a sword.

Their swords were so fast and sharp that after a slash, blood would only drain after a few steps.

One time, he made a small cut on his thigh during a tournament and was puzzled that it didn’t bleed, but when he walked back to his quarters after the tournament, a fistful of flesh fell off and a fountain of blood gushed out.

That happened even when he wasn’t using his aura.

Vikir had been training in the Academy’s Gravity Chamber for quite some time now to reach such a state, and it was paying off in a significant way at this moment.

…Snap!

Finished with his thoughts, Vikir swiped his magic sword, Beelzebub.

Despite colliding with the legendary magic sword Balmung, Beelzebub did not even receive the slightest scratch.

No wonder. The sword was forged from the remains of an ancient demon who had long ago ruled the demon world a long time ago.

Instead, Balmung over there just screams.

“Die now.”

Vikir imbued the sword with an aura.

Swordmaster.

The solid aura stretches out, creating a slash of ridiculous size.

Swash! Swash! Swash! Swash! Swash! Swash! Swash! Swash!

The Eight Forms of Baskerville.

Thanks to his encounter with Cane Corso in the Grave of Swords, Vikir has learned to summon the Eight Teeth.

Dolores, meanwhile, was stunned.

‘…You’re even stronger than the last time I saw you!’

When they met in the orphanage, Night Hound had only managed to use six of those strikes.

It was only when she awakened and buffed him that he managed to use the seventh and slay Dantalian.

Although she doesn’t know what kind of swordsmanship it is that is moving so strangely now…, what she does know is that Night Hound has become much stronger than before Dantalian.

“Kughh!”

Bartolomeo twisted his body and stepped back.

But with Madame’s poison already in his blood, he didn’t get very far, slipping under a pile of gold coins.

“Die.”

Vikir plunged the sword deep into Bartolomeo’s abdomen.

Phuuk-

Bartolomeo held Vikir’s arm tightly even as blood spurted out.

“You think you’re going to get away with this? As soon as the vault doors open, my men will be here. And I’ll call the Imperial Guard….”

At that time.

Szzzz.

A white light descended from above and enveloped Vikir and Bartolomeo.

While the wounds on Vikir’s body quickly closed.

“Kuahhhh!”

The wounds on Bartolomeo’s body began to grow worse and worse.

It was like being set on fire.

“Do you think people will believe you after seeing this?”

Dolores stood on a mountain of gold coins, radiating white light.

She was holding up the Mirror of Truth, the prize for winning the University League, to Bartolomeo.

In the small mirror, Bartolomeo’s true form was clearly visible.

An infinity deep and infinity black evil. That’s its true nature.

“…!”

Vikir quickly turned and walked away from the mirror.

Dolores didn’t bother trying to figure out who Night Hound was.

And then. Bartolomeo began to laugh.

“Hohohoho… Indeed, you’ve prepared a lot.”

The screams of agony from a moment ago were nowhere to be seen.

Vikir retrieved his sword and backed away.

Dzzzzzzzzzzz….

A black aura enveloped Bartolomeo’s entire body, lifting him into the air.

Decarabia, on Vikir’s chest, warned in a gravelly voice.

[The play is over, the 6th Corpse is about to show its true colors].

“I know it when I see it.”

Vikir pressed Decarabia back into his chest.

Then.

The 6th Demon King descended upon the golden hill in front of Dolores and Vikir, who looked uneasy and nonchalant.

Danger Rating : S

Size : ?

Found in: Deep within the Gate of Destruction, ‘Serpent’s Womb’

-Nicknamed the Sixth Corpse.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Your body and your barns will boil with lice.”

– 『Ten Commandments』 10: Top –

Belial, lord of greed and lies.

He was the 6th leading figure in the Age of Destruction.

Chapter 284

Power inflation (4)

◆

Belial.

‘The worthless one’. The Sixth. The sixth of the ten demons who descended to destroy mankind.

An ambitious man who teamed up with 9th Corpse Dantalian to consume both the Quovadis and the Bourgeois.

At last he showed his true colors.

‘The most beautiful being among those expelled from heaven.’

He decorate the outside with extravagant decorations and flashy wealth, but in reality, the appearance behind it is extremely ugly.

The horns of a mountain goat on the head of a giant pig, teeth as sharp as swords beneath gums exposed by the absence of lips.

Eyes glowing with fire, eyes that billow like the smoke of a beacon, and breath that reeks of disgust.

His mouth gaped like a crevasse on an arctic ice wall, and his horns and wings spread out to either side, large enough to cover the entire battlefield.

This gigantic and hideous figure, floating like a white mist above the puppet-like body of Bartolomeo, was the true form of Belial.

…Czssss!

Vikir lifted his magic sword, Beelzebub.

‘I’m glad I met him before he formed an army.’

Deception, distraction, incitement, disorientation. Belial’s talents are especially valuable in large-scale battles.

As such, the best way to hunt him down is to fight him one-on-one.

Meanwhile, on Vikir’s chest, Decarabia continues to offer advice.

[It’s been a while since I’ve seen you, that guy. The name ‘Belial’ means ‘worthless’ in the dead language of an old magic monarchy that is now extinct.]

[Hack-hack-hack-]

The cub stood upright, fur all over her body, and clung to Vikir’s shoulder.

Judging by the way her bushy eyebrows were arched upward, she seemed to regard her master’s enemy as her own enemy.

“Saint, come here.”

Vikir motioned Dolores to stand behind him.

Dolores cautiously moved toward Vikir.

Then. Belial’s mouth opened.

He looked straight at Dolores.

[When the priests renounced God and turned into a group of blasphemers, no one was worshiped as often as this body in temples and altars.]

A mocking tone.

True to his word, Belial had already absorbed nearly half of the Faithful Quovadis.

‘…Humbert.’

Dolores gritted her teeth.

Did Cardinal Humbert of the Quovadis know that Bartolomeo was actually Belial?

Even though he knew that, did he conspire with Belial and make the family fall into disrepute?

Dolores shuddered, remembering her stepfather’s unpleasant glance.

Humbert was human, sure, but he was more terrifying to her than a demon.

Just then.

“You have nothing to fear.”

A voice said in a nonchalant tone.

Dolores turned her head to see Night Hound standing steadfastly by her side.

For a moment, Dolores remembered the time before Dantalian.

‘…Yes, I was like that then.’

When Dantalian had turned over the grotesque sack and pulled the vision of Humbert from within, Dolores had been momentarily overwhelmed with a sense of suffocating fear and pressure.

And then.

‘Nothing to be afraid of.’

Even then, Night Hound’s words of encouragement were enough to put all her fears to rest and give her peace of mind.

“Thank you, Night Hound!”

Dolores murmured in prayer, clinging to Vikir’s back.

As Belial drew upon his demonic powers and prepared to attack, Dolores chanted as well.

“Lord Lun is a strong castle, a shield and weapons; he will save us from great trouble!”

Passs-

White light burst forth like flames and enveloped Vikir.

It burned with fierce intensity, but did not feel hot at all to Vikir.

“The old enemy, the demon, is using his strength even at this time, using plots and power as his weapons. Who in the world can stand against him? If I rely only on my own strength, I have no choice but to be defeated. A powerful general comes out and fights on my behalf. Who is this general? That holy name…”

For a moment, Dolores paused in her chanting.

After some hesitation, she continued.

“…‘Night Hound’! Pilgrim of the Lun, Lord of hosts! Who will suffer? I will definitely win!”

When Dolores had finished, she placed her trembling hands on Vikir’s back.

Then she spoke in a voice that trembled even more than her hands.

“I think the buff would work better if I knew the real name of Night Hound here….”

Names have power.

The mere act of being called affects cause and effect, generating strange energies that cross over into the negative and positive dimensions.

For this reason, demons do not reveal their true names lightly.

Nor do the demon hunters who hunt them.

“This is enough.”

But Vikir interrupted Dolores.

It was partly to prevent her from becoming even more entangled with him by giving him a name, but it was more for another reason.

Swash swash swash swash!

Belial began to attack in earnest.

Belial’s body, which was somewhere between intangible and tangible, was clearly giving off both spiritual and physical impacts at the same time.

[How dare you insignificant humans!]

Belial spat out arrogant lines, as demons are supposed to do.

But Vikir is a skilled hunter, having slain four demons so far.

“It’s going to be a little shaky.”

Vikir says to Dolores, who places a hand on his back.

Before Dolores could reply.

…A flash!

Vikir’s sword began to emit a crimson aura.

Spinning at high speed, the aura formed seven large teeth and an eighth, slightly smaller tooth.

The teeth moved furiously, spinning like wagon wheels as they flew toward Belial’s body and embedded themselves in it.

Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!

Baskerville’s Eighth Form.

A blow that turned the body of Bartolomeo, one of the strongest in the human world, into a rag in an instant.

It contained a level of power that even a full-bodied Belial would not dare to underestimate.

[Grrr! How could a human possess such power…!?]

Belial took a step back in bewilderment.

Vikir was not about to let this opportunity he had been forced to create slip away.

‘If there’s no gap, I’ll twist it open with force.’

Eight teeth were tearing at Belial’s entire body without releasing.

Furthermore, the buffs that Dolores unleashed with all her might made Vikir’s 8th tooth grow even larger.

…Dzzzz!

Belial’s teeth and horns shattered.

His armor, once so ornate and fleshy, cracked and shattered to pieces.

Worst of all, Bartolomeo’s body didn’t seem to be holding up.

‘My eight tooth is incomplete. I must settle this in a short time!’

Vikir gritted his teeth and pushed forward.

In his mind, he replayed Hugo’s slaying of Andromalius and Cane Corso’s blow that had shaken the entire Grave of Swords.

And behind him, the power of Dolores’s buffs washed over him like a tidal wave!

…Flash!

Vikir ignored the pressure on his body and pushed Beelzebub all the way down.

Ku-kung!

A massive tremor ripples through the air, shattering the mountains of gold coins around it.

[Grrrr… Kuaghhh!]

Belial staggered back, every inch of his body destroyed.

Vikir raised his sword once more, receiving a heal from Dolores.

It was then that Dolores spoke with a pitying tone.

“…The buff isn’t as good as it was in the Dantalian battle.”

She seemed deeply disappointed in her lack of power.

That’s because the power of the buff has become incomparably weaker than when hunting Dantalian at the orphanage.

“I’ve been working on myself a lot since then… and I feel like I’ve degenerated.”

But Vikir thought that was to be expected.

‘Awakening doesn’t come that easily.’

Dolores’s demonstration of divinity before Dantalian was a “miracle,” one that advanced her understanding of divine power by decades.

The exact cause and conditions of her awakening were unknown, but progress was never made by relying on such luck in the first place.

Vikir continued to swing his sword, pressuring Belial.

Just then.

[…Hohohoho. Indeed. Killing my colleagues wasn’t just luck.]

Belial pushed himself up.

Surprisingly, while our eyes were apart for a moment, Belial had recovered from most of his wounds and damage.

“…!”

Vikir swung his strike once more.

Zzzzzzzzzz-

It once again carved a deep scar into Belial’s chest armor.

[Hohohoho… It’s no use, human, you lowly creature].

But Belial was not intimidated at all.

Soon, he stretched out his two large hands to both sides.

Then something unpleasant began to happen.

Clang, clang, clang, clang, clang, clang, clang, clang, clang, clang.

A loud metallic clang could be heard everywhere.

When Dolores turns her head in surprise, she sees a golden stream flowing.

Clink-clink-clink-clink-clink…

The sound of money moving.

Countless gold coins rippled on the ground, crawling like giant snakes.

The gold coins, jewelry, and other treasures were then absorbed into Belial’s body.

Druszt! Thud! Kwazizik!

Belial’s broken horns grew back, and his cracked body was restored to its original form.

What’s more, his already massive body grew even larger.

[All the riches in this vault are my life force! Money is power! Money is life! In a world dominated by mammonism, wealth is vitality!]

Dolores was stunned.

Such a vast amount of riches in such a vast vault.

Belial’s plan to store all of these as extra vitality was truly meticulous and thorough.

Only then did Dolores understand why Belial always dragged outsiders into the vault.

It wasn’t just to kill the spirit of his visitors.

Because this is his ‘home ground’ where he can exercise absolute authority, power, and vitality!

…But.

“I already knew that.”

Vikir said in a nonchalant tone, causing Belial’s face to crumple.

…Crunch!

The magic sword Beelzebub lengthened a bit more.

The crimson aura beneath the hem of his black coat began to flare once more.

Eventually, the light from the red eyes condenses on the black mask and glows dimly.

“If money is your life….”

A boiling voice breaks through the hound’s sharp teeth.

“I’ll bankrupt you completely.”

It was a declaration of war to the ruler of the vast golden realm.

Chapter 285

Power inflation (5)

◆

[Gahahahahahaha-]

Belial laughed, his mouth open so wide that his lower jaw sank into his chest.

It was a mockery so loud that the golden mountains around him crumbled.

[Bankruptcy? Is that really what you’re saying in the face of my wealth?]

Mountains and mountains of gold, jewelry, and other priceless treasures.

Each time Belial is wounded, he draws upon these treasures to restore his vitality.

These treasures fill nearly half of the vast vault, and as long as they are there, Belial will live forever.

Decarabia on Vikir’s chest, blinked his single eye, said.

[Belial is a weak demon when he has no money, but a powerful demon when he has a lot of money. It’s not so strange to humans, isn’t it? There’s a saying in human society: ‘Money brings in demons’. The same logic applies in the demonic world].

“It’s a nuisance ability.”

[It’s not a nuisance. As I said before….]

Decarabia began to list Belial’s powers.

[Belial’s main powers are ‘Jealousy’, ‘Destruction’, ‘Oppression’, ‘Exile’, ‘Famine’, ‘Disturbance’, and ‘Desolation’].

Jealousy, which disrupts the enemy’s vision with a dark aura emanating from his body; Destruction, which replaces gold power with muscle power and unleashes it with his fists; Exile, which blocks the enemy’s movement and keeps them away at a distance with a vortex of gold coins; Famine, which scatters them and gnaws away at the opponent’s gold; Disturbance, which emits powerful waves from his mouth; and Desolation, which devastates the surroundings with its enormous weight….

Kuoooooooooooo!

Vikir had to retreat again and again to avoid the power of destruction swirling everywhere.

At that time.

Whiss-

Dolores hugged Vikir hard from behind.

Vikir looked back and tried to say something, but Dolores’ shout was faster.

“Dodge, Night Hound!”

As Vikir fell to the ground, Dolores fell on top of him.

At the same time.

…Quack-quack-quack-quack-quack! Jzzzzzzz!

Belial’s fist narrowly missed, smashing the gold coin hill on the other side and collapsing it.

Then.

“Kyaaah!”

Dolores, who was attacked by Belial, began to scream.

‘Destruction’ was avoided, but ‘Famine’ could not be avoided.

Dzzzzzzzzzzz…

Everything made of gold, including buttons, pins, and gold thread, attached to her luxurious nun’s clothes turned into crumbs and were sucked into Belial’s body.

This is Famine, Belial’s ability to rob and suck out all the wealth of others and use it for his own power.

It dries up the other person’s wealth, no matter how much they have.

Then, as the buttons, pins, and gold threads disappeared, the garment lost its shape and fell apart.

Dolores was horrified.

The nun’s clothes, which had not been exposed at all, were torn in several places, exposing her bare skin.

‘Wha, Night Hound is watching!’

Her face and ears were redder than ever.

…However, Dolores’s suffering did not end there.

[Your body and your barns will boil with lice.]

Belial’s famine powers don’t just take away the wealth of others.

It is said that health is the most valuable thing, and the body is an asset.

The ability to devour an opponent’s wealth, but also their body and blood.

That’s the nature of the ugly power that Belial wields.

Gurgle, gurgle, gurgle…

Soon, they started crawling on Dolores’ body.

The white bloodsuckers burrowed into every inch of her white, soft skin, sucking out blood with their sharp teeth.

“Ugh, ouch!”

Dolores couldn’t help but scratch all over her body with her hands without realizing it.

Her expression is grim.

The sight of Dolores desperately holding on to her flowing clothes with one hand and scratching various parts of her body with the other made Vikir think, even if only for a moment.

‘Grotesque.’

Dolores exclaimed as Vikir stood still, speechless for a moment.

“I mean, it’s not fair, I bathe and shower every day, obviously, so why do I have lice…!”

“I see, for now.”

“Now, wait! What do you mean, for now? What does that mean?”

Vikir neatly ignored Dolores’s excuses as she cried out in embarrassment and frustration.

Dolores was trying to defend against Belial’s attack and ended up in that shape, so of course he should help her.

‘You go help her.’

Vikir called to his friend on his shoulder.

[Hack!]

Little Madame. The little creature arched a bushy eyebrow and struck a salute pose.

The trusty little fellow bounced across the floor with a snap and clung to Dolores’s back.

And then,

KOOOOOOO!

It began to exude its pride as an absolute leader standing at the pinnacle of the insect ecosystem.

Shivering…

Spiders. The natural enemy.

In front of that fearsome peer, they began to tremble and escape from Dolores’ body.

Even though it was in front of Belial, the orders of the Madame race were absolute.

At least in the insect world.

‘The Madam Eight-Legs was a force to be reckoned with, even by the high ranking demons of demon king level….’

Vikir nodded,

‘Although she is young, she certainly has the qualities of a Monster King.’

If she is raised well, she will be a great help in the fight against demons in the future.

Meanwhile.

…Bang! …BANG! …DZZZZZZ!

Belial was on a rampage, using up all of his tremendous funds and strength.

[Hahahahaha! Quilt if you don’t have money, no guilty if you have money! Who can stand against this boundless power of money!]

The vast vault is full of riches.

Belial gazed at the golden horizon of the mountain range and exclaimed as if drunk.

[When this vault is full, I’ll be able to open the Gate all by myself! I don’t need those generous companions!]

Belial did not hesitate to blaspheme the other Ten Commandments.

He was extremely self-righteous and equally strong.

Money. The value of money, to be precise. Or more accurately, the greed of men for money.

Money is important because it has value, and value is human greed.

As long as there is greed in the human world, Belial’s power is limitless and its potential for growth is limitless.

How much wealth and how much greed has Belial accumulated while wearing the mask of the Bourgeois family patriarch?

[Die, insects!]

Belial succeeds in cornering Vikir in the vault and swings his massive fist.

Boom!

It was as if a meteorite was falling.

The only difference was that its tail burned black instead of red.

Just then.

“There is a demon in this land, trying to devour us!”

Dolores stepped in front of Vikir once more.

“Do not be afraid, stand, and with truth you shall win! Relatives, riches, honor, and life may be taken from you, but the truth shall live, and the kingdom will last forever! Lun!”

White flames rose and formed a wall.

Rumbling, boom!

The firewall of holy fire knocked Belial’s fist back as soon as it touched.

Chiiiiiiiizzzzz…

Soon, the ultra-high temperature burning white light began to burn Belial’s fist.

[…Kughh!]

Belial, who had been pushing forward in a ferocious manner, stepped back, though only slightly.

Belial’s power had been neutralized by the pure flame, which lacked even a hint of greed.

But. With his fist drawn back, Belial’s cunning tongue began to tease.

[Saint. What did I tell you, money is not a bad thing?]

Suddenly, Dolores’ mind flashed back to the words Belial had once put into Bartolomeo’s mouth.

‘In fact, wealth is a colorless, scentless, tasteless thing. It has no form, no taste, no scent. It’s extremely value-neutral. It’s good when it’s used for good and bad when it’s used for bad. It’s like a fire that can burn a whole mountain, but it can also save a dying little match girl in a winter alley.’

At the same time. Belial grinned, twisting his gruesome mouth even more hideously.

[That’s right, money is neither right nor wrong, it’s value-neutral].

With that, Belial stretched out his massive fists and slammed his palms into the ground.

…Grack, zizizizizi!

With that, Belial clutched an enormous amount of gold coins in his hands.

[So your shields against the bad things will be useless, eh?]

Dolores broke out in a cold sweat at the sight of Belial’s massive, surging hand.

And then.

Clang, clang, clang!

An enormous amount of gold coins began to fly down.

Each piece of money contains enough destructive power to pierce several people.

They tear apart the saint’s defense shield so easily and dig deep into it.

‘Oh no, the Wall of Holy Fire has low physical defense!’

Dolores stumbled back in panic.

But it was impossible to escape the shower of gold coins that rained down over a vast area.

And then.

Clang, clang, clang!

The entire area was devastated. The hills of gold collapsed and the landscape changed dramatically.

The smoke of gold dust fluttering in the air.

…But.

[Hmm!?]

Belial hadn’t gotten what he wanted.

Vikir stands tall, holding Dolores, whose legs are weak, with a mesmerized expression.

Floating in front of Vikir is a translucent red inverted pentagram shield.

The Wailing Wall.

[…It’s been a while, Belial.]

The 7th Corpse Decarabia flashed his single eye.

Chapter 292

Confessions (2)

◆

The night sky was turning blue.

A small knocking sound echoed in the hallway in the dark early morning.

Click-click-click!

The sound of the doorknob turning is low.

But even so, the door didn’t open immediately.

Vikir looked around for a moment.

The girls’ dormitory was eerily quiet at night.

There’s a faint smell of footsteps or improperly dried laundry, snoring that can be heard even through the closed door, and shared lockers that show signs of destruction.

All in all, it’s a scene not unlike the hallways of a fraternity house.

Vikir double-checks that no one else is awake.

Hmm…

The door opened softly and shyly.

“Hyung-ah?”

Sinclaire stuck her head out from inside.

Seeing the look on Vikir’s face, Sinclaire smiled widely and said in a low voice.

“Come on in.”

The door swung open and the warm air inside felt good against his skin.

The room, smelling sweetly of some unknown berry, wasn’t very decorated, but it seemed quite serene with a few decorative items that gave it a cozy, antique feel.

“Bianca, aren’t you in the same room?”

“I think she was sleeping in another friend’s room. She’s not really on speaking terms with me lately.”

“I thought you two were best friends, why all of a sudden.”

“…It’s just. It’s all my fault. Hehe-”

Sinclaire greeted Vikir with a cool smile.

She was wearing a white T-shirt and pink dolphin pants and had a wet towel around her neck.

Her short, still-dry hair smelled faintly of shampoo.

“Come on, hyung-ah!”

Sinclaire threw something at Vikir.

Vikir caught it out of the corner of his eye and realized it was a can of beer with cold droplets on the surface.

Sinclaire smirked and pulled out the snacks.

“It’s getting late, so we can’t eat. Please bear with me even if the snacks are a bit meager.”

“No problem.”

“Good. By the way, are you good at board games?”

Sinclaire clapped her hands and pulled out various board games from under the bed.

Simple games with simple rules, like Jenga, RummyCube, and Uno.

“How is it? Would you like to play for the first time in a while?”

“…It’s been a while.”

Vikir nodded.

Board games were something he’d played tirelessly with his comrades in the Internal Affairs Squad before the regression.

But for some reason, the memories of that time came before the memories of his old volunteer work at the orphanage.

‘I must have gotten dull,’

Vikir realized how much things had changed since his regression.

Both in his surroundings and in himself.

Whoosh.

Sinclaire ran her hands through her hair as she looked at the crumbling Jenga.

“Ah~ Really. Why does it always have to be me!”

“It’s all about the center of gravity. If you don’t lean to one side or the other and keep your center, you’ll never fall.”

“Tch. Easier said than done.”

Sinclaire pouted her lips and stacked the next jenga, only to knock it down again shortly thereafter.

“Hyung-ah, I can’t play board games with you, I swear. Why are you so good? You look like you’ve been doing this since you were a kid.”

“There was a time like that.”

“Huh?”

Sinclaire’s eyes widen like rabbits.

Instead of answering, Vikir simply closed his eyes in silence.

Soon, the number of empty cans of beer crinkling together began to increase.

Sinclaire’s expression relaxes slightly as she sobered up.

The reddish blush on his exceptionally white skin was deepening.

“I want to go see the Milky Way.”

Sinclaire mumbles, and Vikir thinks for a moment.

‘When I’m feeling down, I always come here and look at the Milky Way.’

This is what Sinclaire once said.

‘Now that I think about it, this girl said she goes to the rooftop if he has any worries.’

Drinking canned beer on the roof with a clear view of the Milky Way was probably Sinclaire’s only stress relief.

But now that Milky Way viewing spot is off-limits.

Student Body President Dolores has personally blocked it off.

“…It was our meeting point while we prepared to hunt Belial.”

Vikir stroked his chin, then spoke in a low voice.

“You must be disappointed that Student Council President Dolores blocked the rooftop.”

For a moment, Sinclaire noticeably flinched at the mention of Dolores’ name.

Her eyes, as wide and clear as a lake, looked deep for a moment.

Vikir didn’t miss the agitation.

“What happened with the student council president?”

Vikir asked again.

There was no way Vikir didn’t know what had happened in Bourgeois the day before.

But there was something strange about it, and he wanted to go over it again.

‘I thought you weren’t the kind of character who’d have a mental breakdown just from witnessing a demon and a demon hunter fight.’

Vikir looked at Sinclaire with a bit of disbelief.

Sinclaire, however, kept her head down and remained silent, mute.

“….”

“….”

Silence settled over the room. Vikir waited patiently, carrying a heavy silence.

Finally, the answer came.

“I’m planning to drop out.”

It was so unexpected, so far from the intent of the question, that even Vikir’s eyes widened.

‘What? In the world before the regression, Sinclaire would have dutifully completed all four years and graduated from the Academy….’

Literally.

Sinclaire is an Alpha Girl who hasn’t missed a beat since her freshman year, when she was ranked first in her class, until her senior year.

Along the way, she has risen to the position of vice-president as a sophomore and student council president as a senior, only to disappear from the world as soon as she finishes her senior year and graduates from the Academy.

But now the reality has changed.

Sinclaire has announced her dropout just before the end of her freshman year, with only one final exam to go.

“Of course, I haven’t told anyone yet. Hyung-ah is the first person I’m telling.”

Sinclaire smiled weakly.

Vikir asked briefly.

“Is it because of the student council president?”

“No, it has nothing to do with the president, of course. It’s just that I’m so exhausted and tired….”

It was obvious that Sinclaire was lying.

Vikir knew that before her regression, she had graduated straight and at the top of her class from freshman to senior year without taking a single leave of absence.

“I think it was burnout. I’ve been wanting to quit school for a while now, so I’ve been acting cold to the kids on purpose to keep them away and….”

Sinclaire continued.

But Vikir didn’t listen to her.

He just cut to the chase.

“Apparently, you had a problem with Student Council President Dolores.”

“Uh, no. It’s just that I’m a little….”

“Is it because of what happened at Bourgeois?”

For a moment, Sinclaire’s expression hardened before Vikir could finish his sentence.

‘Of course.’

Vikir realized he’d hit the nail on the head.

It had happened in Bourgeois. The night of the hunt for the 6th corpse, Belial.

Sinclaire looked particularly shaken.

“Oh, no, nothing happened that day….”

She waved her hands in the air in great embarrassment.

But.

Tuck-

Vikir wordlessly reaches out and grabs both of Sinclaire’s hands.

“What happened.”

“…!”

“What’s got you in so much pain.”

“….”

Sinclaire’s pupils dilate for a moment, then tremble slightly.

Seeing it, Vikir was once again convinced.

Demon battles are always a terrible memory for humans.

The more high ranking the demon, the longer and more intense the battle.

Vikir was no stranger to this type of counseling, having seen many of his comrades-in-arms suffer severe after-effects after demon hunting.

‘If it’s post-battle trauma, I can help you overcome it.’

Vikir didn’t want Sinclaire to go into hiding from the world when she could be a great help to the Human Alliance in the future.

But.

Sinclaire’s next words were certainly not what Vikir was expecting.

“…He killed.”

“What?”

Vikir asked, and Sinclaire spoke again, her voice shaking violently, her pronunciation uncharacteristically inaccurate and slurred.

“Night Hound killed my father.”

Hearing those words sent a bolt of lightning through Vikir’s head.

There was only one thing Night Hound had killed that night when it had bitten Bourgeois from within, and that was Belial.

And the human body it had taken, the host. It was none other than Bartolomeo, patriarch of the Bourgeois family.

‘That means….’

Vikir began, trying to organize his many thoughts and open his mouth to say something.

Walag-

A weight leapt into his arms.

Sinclaire leaned forward and wrapped her arms around Vikir’s body.

The warmth on Vikir chest suggests that Sinclaire has been crying.

Vikir froze in place, unable to push her away or hold her.

“….”

“….”

They stayed like that for what seemed like forever.

…How much time had passed?

Eventually, Sinclaire’s trembling gradually subsided.

The hound’s mouth was half open, but he hadn’t yet found the words to say to the lamb that had burrowed into his arms.

Just then.

Sinclaire lifted her head from burying it in Vikir’s arms and looked up.

“Now it’s your turn to answer.”

And then, with watery eyes and a trembling voice, she asked.

“…What do you think of me, hyung-ah?”

Chapter 296

Last Semester (3)

◆

“Oh my, I’m thirsty. Where is the well here, old man?”

A plain-looking old woman asks.

But Vikir couldn’t treat her like an ordinary old woman.

“…Nabokov L Quovadis I.”

Pope of the Lun Order. Quovadis Family. The oldest of the few remaining Classical Saints. A literal ‘living legend’ who has been alive for over 200 years, from the time of the Warring States of the Unified Empire to the present day.

‘Before the regression, she was only a figure in history books.’

Pope Nabokov had been dead and buried before Vikir’s regression, when Vikir joined the War of Destruction as a middle-aged man.

She was originally thought to have been poisoned by Humbert, a man blinded by power.

But now that Humbert is missing, her life has been extended beyond the future she was supposed to live.

‘The future has changed.’

That’s why she was the biggest variable in the parent observation class.

How much will Pope Nabokov help the future of humanity?

It was something Vikir didn’t know, as it hadn’t happened to him before his regression.

‘Seeing it in person like this…I don’t think it will be of much help.’

In person, Nabokov I was not in good shape.

It’s hard to tell from appearances, but Nabokov I had a small physique, sunken eyes that could barely recognize things in front of her, and a slight hint of dementia.

Then.

“Water, where’s the water~ you old man!”

Pope Nabokov began to protest.

She slapped Vikir’s head with a trembling hand.

Vikir was momentarily silenced by the attack, which lacked any real power.

“ …Among the comrades who crossed the front lines of destruction together, those who were priests always lamented whenever they got the chance. If only Pope Nabokov were still alive, the Humanity wouldn’t have fallen so far.”

Of course, Vikir was at a time when he didn’t believe in anything unless he had experienced it himself.

But no matter how he looked at it, he saw no strength or power in the woman with dementia in front of him.

It was a far cry from when he’d met Count Cane Corso, who was of a similar age.

Finally, with a small sigh, Vikir shook his head.

“The drinking fountain is this way. I’ll get you some water.”

“I’m thirsty old man. Hurry up!”

Vikir led Nabokov to the water fountain in front of them.

It was a large jar-shaped drinking fountain, filled with crystal clear water, and beside it was a bowl hanging on its side.

It looked like an ordinary spring.

Vikir grabbed one of the bowl.

With it, he scoops up clear water.

…Jruuukk!

Water began to leak out from under the bowl. There was a hole in the bottom.

“Oh no. It’s leaking, let me get you another one.”

Vikir puts down the bowl and picks up another one.

With a plop-

The bowl sank into the water.

“?”

Vikir turns his head and sees Nabokov standing next to him, tossing the cracked bowl into a jar of water.

“This way it won’t leak.”

“….”

Nabokov is laughing hysterically, and Vikir stares at her.

The cracked bowl was indeed not leaking, because it was completely underwater.

Nabokov turned to Vikir and said.

“Old man. Whatever is natural is best.”

“…Natural? What is that?”

“What is natural is natural. Do I really have to tell you that?”

Nabokov’s eyes curved in kindness as she studied Vikir’s face.

“The answer is to leave the cracked or holed bowl as it is. A hole or a leaky bowl can be filled by wrapping it in something bigger and embracing it. Holholholhol-”

But.

“But won’t that make it undrinkable?”

Nabokov’s eyes narrowed at Vikir’s words.

“If this happens, the bowl will sink to the bottom of the water and you won’t be able to drink it.”

“Huh? So what….”

“And since this is drinking water that everyone drinks together, you should not engage in such unhygienic behavior.”

“…….”

Nabokov’s mouth is half open, at a loss for words.

“Pope!”

In the distance, Dolores could be seen running toward them, panting.

Behind her came a contemplative-looking Mozgus.

“Pope! You’re here! I’ve been waiting for you for ten years!”

“Holholholhol….”

Mozgus quickly approached and picked up Nabokov.

“And Luther?”

“Unfortunately, he couldn’t make it, as he has a performance for the elderly today.”

“Eih- so typical of him.”

“Are you here for water? Would you like me to pour you a glass?”

“No thanks. I’m not drinking.”

“Then why are you here….”

Nabokov pulled her gaze away from the bewildered Mozgus and looked back at Vikir.

Vikir stood still, Dolores shuffling beside him.

Nabokov’s eyes curved more benevolently once more as she watched them.

“Don’t try to force the gap, It’s best to embrace everything naturally.”

“?”

“Thank you, young man. You’ve put my mind at ease.”

Nabokov patted Mozgus on the shoulder as she finished speaking.

As she turned away with unintelligible words, behind her was a cracked bowl filled with water that had sunk into a water jar.

“….”

“….”

Vikir and Dolores were left alone.

“Bye, Samchun!”

A moment ago, even Pomeranian had taken Nabokov’s hand and left.

….

After a moment of silence.

“Hmm. Hey….”

Dolores was the first to speak.

“I thought you were talking about filling a cracked bowl with water earlier. The Pope is a bit distracted these days. Don’t pay too much attention to her. She has been saying strange things a lot lately…”

But as she says this, Dolores seems to be pondering Nabokov’s words from earlier.

‘I need to be able to manipulate the ‘resonance’ phenomenon that I felt when I put the blessing buff on Night Hound, and to do that, Pope advice is essential.’

The Pope. The oldest of the Classical Saints, and the one with the highest divine power.

‘You know, the old classical saints often talked about awakening back in the day, and I wish I’d taken them to heart instead of dismissing them as empty words.’

It’s something that Dolores realized when she fought Dantalian.

Ever since then, Dolores has needed Nabokov’s advice to be more helpful to Night Hound.

Nabokov was showing signs of dementia, so her advice was limited.

Dolores set her jaw in a serious expression.

She thought back to the fight with Belial not long ago.

‘Don’t be so hard on yourself. We’re allies.’

Night Hound’s words made her cry and laugh at the same time.

The moment he recognized her as an ally had ignited a fire inside her.

But it was a world away from the resonance she’d felt in her fight with Dantalian, so Dolores plucked up the courage to ask.

‘Night Hound, tell me your name!’

Dolores asked for his name in order to close the distance between her and Night Hound, to understand him more deeply.

‘I need that ‘resonance’ phenomenon to increase my divine power! It doesn’t have to be your full name, I don’t mind, but could you at least give me a small portion of your name… that I can call you?’

…And with a little selflessness, of course.

And that’s when she heard his name for the first time.

‘…Van.’

His name, the one She was curious about.

The touch of his hot breath, which she could still remember clearly, made her ears burn red once more.

A common name. The process of getting to know each other through their names.

There was indeed a mystical power in names.

Just by hearing it, Dolores could propel her exhausted body to perform incredible miracles.

‘Yes, that’s it, that’s it!’

A phenomenon that could not be done to anyone else and could not be explained.

A miracle that could only happen when she was with Night Hound… or Van.

Dolores felt her heart beat rapidly once more as she recalled that moment.

At the same time, her mind raced.

‘When I heard the name ‘Van’, which is part of Night Hound’s name, the resonance width increased dramatically. Perhaps the distance between us was the problem. The closer the distance, the stronger the effect of the divine buff. How can I reduce the distance between Night Hound and me further, so that we can create a stronger resonance….’

Night Hound and Dolores, the gap between them is still wide.

As long as there is this gap, Dolores’ divine power cannot resonate perfectly with Night Hound’s soul.

Soul Mate. The element for a saint’s awakening.

Soul resonance requires the assimilation of emotions, and that can only happen with an understanding of each other.

Dolores wanted to get to know the character of Night Hound.

She wanted to understand his fate, empathize with his pain, and be ready to sacrifice herself for him.

And yet? Dolores was getting impatient.

And the more impatient Dolores became, the more impassable the road ahead became. It’s true of dreams, hopes, futures, and relationships.

‘Night Hound. I want to know more about you, I want to meet you.’

A look of determination that reporters once mistook for a declaration of holy war.

Now it’s a look of pity.

Right then.

[…Yep! That’s it, we have a winner of the second year ranking battle, and now it’s on to the much-anticipated third year – the final ranking battle to determine the third year head of class!]

In the distance, the announcement for the third year finalists could be heard from the training center.

Dolores gasped and said.

“Ouch! Vi, Vikir, over there. I was actually looking for you because I had something to tell you, but alas, I’ve run out of time.”

“I was intending to go down, too. Why don’t you tell me as you go?”

“Uh, sure, thanks. Actually, it’s about Sinclaire. I’d like to talk to her, and I was wondering if you might be able to arrange a meeting with her….”

Vikir nodded in agreement with Dolores.

‘Even if we talk, there probably won’t be much gain.’

Sinclaire’s mind was already made up. A few words would probably not change it.

So instead of focusing on Dolores’ words, Vikir looked at other things.

“…A tree, and a magic stone.”

The trees that lined the path down to the training grounds, and the magic walls that rose up along the Academy’s outer walls.

Vikir scanned them with a sharp gaze.

‘The arrangement of the tree roots and magic stones is quite exquisite.’

If the trees and magic stones were placed separately, it wouldn’t matter, but if they were mixed together in such a clever way, it would be a security risk.

Moreover, these newly arrived magic stones had a very slight but distinct ‘scent’ to them.

A ‘demonic scent’ that only Night Hound could smell.

‘It’s time to leave the academy.’

A considerable amount of time has already passed since I stayed here. A place that I have become attached to in my own way.

“….”

But even so, Vikir turned his head resolutely away.

Making all his wishes come to nothing.

A terrible fight will soon take place from which he may never return.

Chapter 299

The Age of the Warmonger (3)

◆

…Puff-puff-puff!

The aura’s trajectory spun like a wheel, slicing through countless criminals like fish meat.

A man stood silently in the rain of blood and flesh.

Everyone swallowed hard when they saw the bloodshot eyes shining through his long black hair.

“So this is the Iron Blood Swordsman….”

“Swordbird Osiris. Young patriarch of the Baskerville family!”

“How can he be such a swordsman at his age?”

It was Osiris Le Baskerville who froze the steps of countless criminals in their tracks.

That Iron Blood Swordsman was the next patriarch of the Baskerville family.

Kiririk.

A neat circle with a radius of fifteen meters was formed with Osiris at the center.

The outside of the circle was covered in torn bodies and blood, but the inside was pristine.

Flutter.

With the hem of his broad blood flowing like black wings, he was like a grim reaper descending to punish criminals.

“…What kind of confidence did you show? You bastards.”

Osiris’s question to the raiders was valid.

Something similar was currently happening all around the Auditorium.

“You guys! Did you come here knowing who I am? I don’t think you came here without knowing? Because if you did, you wouldn’t be here in such small numbers.”

“…For once, I agree with you.”

The big man smirked and beat the criminal to death with a single strike.

Donquixote’s patriarch, Cervantes, smirks in disbelief.

Next to him is Roderick of the Usher family, looking grim and gloomy as he shoots criminals with a large bow.

Parents from other prominent families also took up weapons to defend their children.

“No one touches my daughter!”

“Whoever touches my son, I will cut his head off.”

“How dare you filthy criminals run amok in the sacred halls of education.”

“Oh no, I bought a house next to the Academy for my children’s education, and now I’m going to lose all my property value. I won’t let it happen!”

Parents are the ones who will stop at nothing for the safety and education of their children.

Professors were also on high alert, trying to keep the criminals at bay.

Osiris, standing at the front of the line, turned to the triplets behind him, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

“You three are to take Pomeranian to the Knights, and stay in the safe zone.”

“Yes, brother.”

Osiris, seeing his younger brothers nod, flew away like a bird and jumped into the battle line again.

His six fangs were once again tearing at everything around him with ferocity.

This inspired the parents and professors to join the onslaught.

“Hahaha- the young man from the Baskerville family is very energetic, I’ll help him!”

“I can’t be outdone by a younger fellow, my daughter’s safety is at stake.”

Cervantes Donquixote and Usher Roderick were also pushing to the front lines.

The criminals were seemingly being pushed aside.

…But.

“Hohoho, guys, you’re gonna have to blow up too!”

Sadi’s order came out so fast that the raiders’ eyes began to glaze over.

Boom!

Their bodies inflated like balloons.

Everyone on the Academy’s side gasped in disbelief.

“Mana surge! Self-destruct!”

Ominous predictions are always accurate.

Boom, boom, boom!

An explosion of unprecedented power swept through the area as the Named Villains self-destructed.

It was enough to destroy the huge auditorium in half.

◆

…Rumble! Boom! Boom! Kung-!

Aftershocks linger and shake the ground.

The criminals who turned into minions became bio-bombs and exploded in unison, creating countless collapses that scattered the crowd.

Students, professors, and parents are trapped in the debris, unable to tell where they are or where they are going.

However, unsurprisingly, there was no agitation on the part of the criminals, as if this was all part of the plan.

“Whoohoohoo… bomb squad. Aesthetic.”

“Alas, I’d like to be impaled by one of the Queen’s heels and explode.”

“Me too! I want to be a sow and explode!”

“Kehehe- Kehehehe-”

The bloodshot-eyed criminals emerged from the dirt and rubble.

And in front of them were first-year students who were still inexperienced in combat.

“Kkyaaaaah!”

The criminals rushed toward the direction of a female student’s scream.

And then there were those who stood in their way.

Pug!

The head of one of the criminals snapped back.

Tudor. The young hero, who was the first to hear his classmate’s screams, stood at attention and blocked the criminals.

Behind him were Sancho, Bianca, and Pigi.

“Hehehehehe- Academy students, let’s see how soft you are!”

One of the criminals, who looked like he had tasted human flesh, lunged at them with his mouth agape.

Pow!

Tudor and Sancho raised their spears and axes, and smashed at him.

But they failed to control their strength, and the criminal’s head and stomach exploded, killing him instantly.

“Ewww, ugh. Did I commit murder….”

Tudor’s pupils shake. No wonder he missed the criminal lunging at him from behind.

But Bianca wasn’t going to stand still.

Pfft!

The arrow she fired pierced the criminal who was trying to attack Tudor, killing him.

He crumpled to the ground in a failed attempt to hug Tudor and create a mana surge.

“Kill him or you die! Come to your senses!”

“…Ah!”

Tudor gritted his teeth in momentary embarrassment, realizing that Bianca had saved him.

Next. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca find themselves in a circle of criminals.

“There are too many of them….”

“Every single one of them is from the wanted list. They’re strong.”

“Ugh- what do I do, what do I do?”

“Don’t show your back! Stay close!”

There’s venom on their faces.

Just then.

“Ooh, we don’t want to fight either!”

One criminal stepped forward.

He had tears streaming down his innocent face.

“We’re all being used by that crazy bitch Sadi, and there are innocent civilians in the middle of this!”

“…What, is that real?”

Bianca asked in disbelief, and he pulled up his shirt to show her the magic stone bomb planted on the body.

“That monstrous bitch kidnapped not only criminals but normal people and planted these bombs, threatening to kill our families if we didn’t listen to her!”

“….”

“Even this guy who was dragged here said he was a priest, what’s his name, Humbert, or something… but he’s an innocent priest!”

Then I see a middle-aged man standing naked among the criminals.

He’s got his hands and tongue cut out, and he’s crying, and of course he’s got a magic stone bomb planted in his stomach.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca all look at each other, their faces blank.

“I don’t know what to do. There are a lot of innocent civilians involved.”

“But sympathizing with them will get you killed.”

“By the way, guys, don’t you think you recognize that priest with the severed hand… over there?”

“Does it matter now, It looks like we’re all going to die.”

The kids argued back and forth.

The criminal who was the first to shed tears took advantage of that opportunity and smiled.

“…I see the Academy’s kids are simple-minded.”

As soon as they finish speaking, criminals rush towards them, causing a surge of mana from their entire bodies.

They didn’t miss the gap the students had left.

“ Argh!?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca express their frustration.

Flutter-!

A red cloak fluttered long.

And then.

Puff-puff-puff-puck!

Black metal skewers protruded from all over the ruins, piercing the bodies of the charging criminals.

“…Eh?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca looked up, dumbfounded.

Then they saw a black stocking leg wiggling out from under the crumbling rock.

“…, I came to tour the school I’ll be attending and this is what I see.”

A low, husky voice, full of annoyance, but sounding quite charming.

An unrecognizable first-year female student landed on the ground, wrapped in a cloak, the symbol of Colosseo Academy.

Upon seeing her, a criminal once again burst into tears and exclaimed.

“Wu, we’re innocent civilians, forced to do this because of that Sadi bitch’s threats…!”

“Innocent civilians carrying ghosts around behind them like that?”

“…?”

The mysterious female student who suddenly appeared pointed to the backs of the innocent criminals.

A cold sneer escapes her lips.

“Rapists, arsonists, murderers, kidnappers, pedophiles…, they’re all over the place.”

There’s a look of horror in the criminals’ eyes as they’re quickly identified.

But before they could react, the girl made the first move.

Qua-gigi-gi-geek!

A series of sharp black metal skewers shot up from the ground, piercing the criminals from the groin to the crown of their heads and sending them flying upwards.

As they lay there, flames roared out of the ground, creating an inferno all around them.

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhh!”

“Kkieeeeaaaaaak!”

“Kuaghhhhhhhh!”

In an instant, the criminals were dead.

Soon, something like black smoke emanates from their bodies and is sucked into the girl’s grasp.

The female student closed her eyes, pursed her mouth slightly, and then her expression slightly wrinkled.

“They’re not very nutritious, I guess because they’re low class.”

And then.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

Above the girl’s head, white gases converged to form a strange shape.

It was a thin, dead tree, and unpleasant-looking fruits were beginning to grow in clusters at the ends of its branches.

[Hueheehee…]

[Kkiyaik-kkiyaaaak!]

[It hurts- It hurts- It hurts-]

[Help me… get me out of here…]

The berries were carved with the faces and expressions of the criminals they had just killed.

These ominous fruits were dripping with juices that were like tears of blood, and they were howling.

“Mmmm. The flesh, the juice, and the taste are all so-so. It’s not that good either.”

The female student stretched out her long white fingers, grabbed the fruits that were growing at the end of the branches, and crushed them.

…Squish, splatter!

Hearing the horrific screams of the criminals, the female student smirked and turned around.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca stared at the girl’s face with blank expressions.

Their minds flashed back to something the professor had said at the end of class the other day.

‘Do you all know, we’re about to have a new friend in our school! She’s a girl. Her age is 19, which is one year younger than the average first-year student. Her institution is the Hot Class Department. She’s transferring from the famous Mage Family Morgue, so I think you guys can learn a lot from her. Her name is….’

At the same time, the transfer student greeted them with a bright smile.

“Nice to meet you. I’m Camus Morgue.”

Chapter 303

The Age of Warmonger (7)

◆

‘What is it?’

Even with her eyes closed, Dolores felt an unexplained anxiety.

And soon, that anxiety becomes tangible through the ears.

“Uub, uubh, ueubhh!”

A familiar groan. How could she forget that horrible voice?

Dolores’s eyes widened in surprise.

Before her was a familiar face, but a man with a strange look.

‘Humbert Humbert L Quovadis’.

He was struggling towards Dolores with a gag in his mouth.

He has no hands to free himself from his bonds.

He was no better than any of the other criminals enslaved by Sadi, already wrapped in bombs of magic stones.

Those pitiful eyes.

“Aa….”

Dolores froze in place at the sight of Humbert.

The man she had feared ever since she had become his foster daughter, so long ago, simply because she was born with divine powers.

A man she loathed and feared, even to the point of facing him in the sack of horrors Dantalian had pulled out.

…However!

Grrttt-

Dolores gritted her teeth hard.

She could not remain afraid forever.

When she had gone to the temple of an Old Testament that sold indulgences to investigate Belial, she had shivered helplessly and barely escaped with the help of Night Hound.

It was the same before Dantalian.

‘I won’t be his burden anymore!’

Dolores looked up at her foster father for the first time.

She’d learned the last time she’d been in the orphanage with Night Hound that the presence in front of her was no longer frightening.

It was time to be brave, to protect the person next to her.

To give back a little of what she had always received.

And in that moment, Dolores realized her heart.

A being that gave her the courage and will to face what she was so afraid of.

And she realized how she felt about it.

“Eis!”

She gritted her teeth and punched Humbert in the face as he approached.

Pugh-

Humbert’s eyes rolled back in his head.

The trauma and nightmares that had been holding Dolores back were shattered so easily that it seemed like nothing.

At the same time, a white light different from before began to explode from Dolores’ body, which was surrounding Vikir.

“What!”

Dolores’ eyes widened.

She is still far away from Night Hound standing behind her.

She still doesn’t know anything about him.

But what could it be? Right now, Dolores’s mind was filled with an enormous amount of divine power that she had never known before.

“Have you awakened?”

“Well, I guess so, though it’s a little hard for me to say this myself….”

Dolores answered Vikir’s question in a confused voice.

She didn’t know what the harmony was, even to herself.

Then.

“Holholhol – yes, that is natural.”

Suddenly, a strange sound came from behind her.

Dolores turned to see Pope Nabokov I looking her way with a subtle smirk on her face.

“What is love? Just because you forcefully close the distance doesn’t mean you’re kicking someone. It naturally permeates and fills up the distant space in between. It’s like filling a broken bowl by submerging it in water.”

Vikir scratched his head, but Dolores seemed to realize something.

‘Yes. There’s something the Pope said about that.’

A snippet of conversation from the old well.

‘Old man. Anything natural is best.’

‘…Natural? What is that?’

‘The answer is to leave the cracked or holed bowl as it is. A hole or a leaky bowl can be filled by wrapping it in something bigger and embracing it. Holholholhol-‘

Love. An affectionate feeling that flows naturally toward an object.

It transcends class, status, age, race, gender, and all other gaps and distances.

That’s what philanthropy is.

The stage where all this happens naturally, like the flow of water, is called ‘naturalness’, which is an essential process of mind cultivation, not only for religious people but also for martial people.

“And that love is something that you naturally realize without anyone telling you. Holholhol – it’s only natural that they are both young men and women.”

As Nabokov’s voice echoed in her mind, Dolores prepared her divine shields.

There was no time to congratulate herself on the success of her soul resonance.

…Quack, quack, quack!

The horn of a unicorn falling like a lightning strike.

Amdusias’s attack began to continue fiercely.

“Eugh!”

Dolores winced as she felt the pain in her wrist.

The power contained in Amdusias’ horns and hooves was so great that even Dolores, the Saint of Steel, could not easily block it.

[It would be best to step back. That guy’s attack power is the highest among the Ten Corpses.]

Having absorbed nearly half of Vikir’s mana, Decarabia steps forward, and the battlefield scales are finally equalized.

Whoosh!

Dolores retrieved her shield and focused all her buffs on Vikir.

‘…It’s definitely on a different level than before.’

Vikir marveled at his increased mana and physical strength.

The Swordmaster Intermediate, at the end of his seventh form, had risen a level in an instant.

It wasn’t his own strength, but it felt like he’d broken through one of the walls above.

‘I can fully realize the Eighth Form now.’

He recalled Cane Corso’s voice from the Grave of Swords.

[Even after stepping into the realm of the supreme, only those who continue to run without resting with the same mindset as when they first picked up the sword will gain something.]

Baskerville’s Eight Forms. A stage that must be supported by a desperate desire to survive, a thirst for life, and extreme practical experience.

A narrow gate that only opens when a person who has lost and regained their emotions has found an attachment to life at the threshold of death.

After becoming a Swordmaster, one rarely has to fight for their life, and this is where stagnation occurs.

Therefore, Cane Corso’s words were the most theoretical and closest to the correct answer.

In fact, it could be said that the 8th Form is a stage that is difficult to experience unless guided by a senior at the upper level of the supreme realm.

Or it takes a lot of hard work.

And Vikir is currently being pushed to the crossroads of life and death after a fierce fight.

Also, although she is not a senior, she has an equally strong supporter who is desperately sending buffs.

‘It’s said that the 9th Form is an area that cannot be reached in one’s lifetime, so the strength I can muster now is actually my last resort.’

The highest of the supreme realms, the 8th Form.

Vikir, who had risen to the pinnacle of Baskerville under Dolores’ blessing, did not miss the moment.

…Flash!

Eight massive teeth that engage, erupt, stab, cut, dismember, slice, dice, and crush.

A solid aura emanated from the magic sword Beelzebub, creating eight storms that tore through everything in their path.

[Kuh-Aaaah!]

Amdusias the first to scream in agony.

Its broken single horn makes a loud noise as it collides with Vikir’s slash.

Whistle. In a tense tug-of-war where no one side has the upper hand.

Tsk-tsk!

The one who started shaking first was Amdusias.

Crack!

The cracks in the tip of the horn began to widen with a loud crackling noise.

Cracks that started from numerous arrowhead marks on the surface of the horn eventually split the horn into three pieces.

BANG!

Thrown back with a loud bang, Amdusias revealed a puzzled expression for the first time since his descent.

[No way. How could a mere mortal…!?]

The mighty Amdusias lost his grip on the reins.

At the same time, Winston’s bloodshot eyes widened as he grabbed at his oily hair.

Meanwhile.

Kwa-kwang- Ujijijijik!

Vikir sliced Amdusias’s horns lengthwise, and they fell to the ground in that state.

“…Cough.”

Vikir opened his mouth, and several bars of hot blood immediately poured out.

A strike that sucked every ounce of power out of him.

And Vikir witnessed it in the process.

“…The 9th Form. Was it really there?”

The 8th Form, a level above the 7th Form, which is generally considered to be superhuman.

In that split second of reaching such a high level, Vikir did not waste time looking down and falling into self-absorption.

When you reach such a high point, you might have looked down at least once, but Vikir chose to raise his head and look up without wasting any time.

…And there it was.

The gate of the 9th Forms, looming high above.

“…!”

So high and far away that he didn’t think he’d ever dare to reach it.

Still, just knowing that it exists, and in which direction it is, is an incredible feeling.

[You will never reach it in your lifetime, for the realm of the 9th Forms lies beyond the threshold of death].

According to Cane Corso, the end of the living is up to the 8th Form.

From the 9th Form onward, ordinary human understanding, empathy, conviction, faith, common sense, probability, and causality are all denied.

The realm of the Absolute currently rules the Grave of Swords.

The state of enlightenment demonstrated by a great man who threw his life away for the sake of a sword.

A place where those who have not experienced death cannot enter.

…But.

‘I can reach it.’

Vikir was about to carve out a path a little different from the one Cane Corso had taken.

‘If it’s death, I can experience it without dying. Surely, it’s a hidden ability of that damned demon in front of me!’

Staggering to his feet, Vikir looked at Winston and Amdusias as they straightened up before him.

‘…The problem is time.’

Vikir rolled his eyes and looked beyond the crumbling ruins.

A spot in the sky visible between the ruins showed that the sun was just setting.

Vikir needs a little more time, as he is currently waiting for some sort of ‘event’.

‘We need to bring in a heroic figure from beyond the ruins… or even just one of the parents from Donquixote or Usher Family would buy us enough time.’

However, unfortunately, the collapsed object completely covered the large space, making it difficult to call for help.

Even Sadi, who could bite the criminals, was knocked unconscious by Amdusias, so in many ways they were very unlucky.

And that’s a good thing for Amdusias, who has just reorganized his stance.

[For a human, I’m honestly surprised, young demon hunter].

Amdusias stared down at Vikir, his eyes wide.

Winston gave Vikir a pitying glance.

“But you, too, will eventually suffer the same fate as me. You will deny God, humans, and yourself three times.”

Demon. And the shadow of the person who abandoned humanity casts a long shadow.

Vikir and Dolores, who had exhausted all their strength from the clash just now, had no choice but to make a final decision.

…Just then.

“Holholhol- But you’re saying you’re going to deny three times over and over again?”

There was no hint of tension in the voice.

A small shadow stepped in front of Vikir and Dolores.

An old woman of small stature.

An old saint who looked as if she might collapse at the slightest touch, she blocked the massive bust of Amdusias without the slightest hesitation.

Pope Nabokov I.

Before Dolores, who had a shocked expression, could even step forward, she opened her mouth with a calm expression and a comfortable voice.

“Are you talking about your mother?”

Chapter 304

The Age of Warmongers (8)

◆

“You mean your mother?”

The moment. The atmosphere in the room suddenly turned sour.

Nabokov smiled gently at the somewhat dazed Amdusias.

“Holholholhol – even demons are creatures of God after all. To dishonor a god is to dishonor your mother.”

[Get lost, you demented woman].

Amdusias snorted, as if he were not worth the trouble.

Then he stretched out a huge hoof and slammed it down on Nabokov.

“No, Pope!”

Dolores leapt forward, but it was too late.

…Bang! Ujikkeun!

Too late to stop Amdusias’s front hoof from snapping off with a terrifying bang.

“…?”

[…?]

The result was so unexpected that it froze both Vikir and Amdusias in place.

Amazingly, Nabokov, standing there with a gentle smile on her face, broke Amdusias’ front leg into an L-shape just by lightly extending her hand.

Originally, it was a direction that could not be broken.

“…Holholhol. That’s right. You are right, we Quovadis are descended from ‘those who denied the gods three times’.”

The first patriarch of the Quovadis family and the first pope. The First Apostle.

He apparently betrayed the prophet Rune and denied God three times before the first rooster crowed.

“…But there’s a story behind it.”

Nabokov said, her voice crisp and clear like never before.

The moment he betrayed the prophet for the third time, the first rooster crowed and the apostle burst into tears.

He returned to his home in the backwoods, where he worked as a stonemason with his eyes, ears, and mouth closed until Lun the Prophet was resurrected.

He carved a tower out of the bedrock at the base of the mountain.

Time passed, and one day he was called by the resurrected Lun.

‘Do you love me?’

‘I love you.’

‘Do you love me?’

‘I love you.’

‘Do you love me?’

‘I love you.’

When the question was repeated three times, the apostle shed tears of repentance and bowed his head.

Then, with a satisfied smile, the Prophet Lun turned and began to walk down the mountain.

The apostle followed him, barefoot and panting, and asked.

‘Lord, Quo Vadis, Domine where are you going??’

The Prophet Lun replied, ‘Back to the place where I died to be persecuted again,’ and the apostle was deeply ashamed of his pettiness for caring about his life.

“This is where our family name comes from, our surname.”

Pope Nabokov Lun Quovadis I. The first saint to hold the position of Pope. …To be exact, a monk among saints.

She slipped her hands into the pockets of her flounced skirt.

And soon enough, Nabokov’s hand slipped out of her skirt again, holding a mace so terrifying that it gave you goosebumps just by looking at it.

Buuuung-

Nabokov swung the mace, the weight of which was unknown, as lightly as if he were handling a knitting needle.

Bam!

Amdusias’s front foot bent in a strange direction again.

[Kuhugh!? You, you crazy old woman!?]

Amdusias jerked backwards and pulled the reins forward at the same time.

Then Winston, with bloodshot eyes, grabbed a sword that was rolling around and charged.

“Die, old man!”

The solid aura of the Swordmaster’s characteristic shouted out.

But.

“Oh my gosh, it’s so hard to carry something like this, how can I survive? I’m just thirsty for no reason-”

Nabokov easily dodged Winston’s slash by simply pulling her chin back a few centimeters.

At the same time, her normally gentle eyes flashed with the sharpness of a sword.

“Being a nun is not a profession that makes a living solely through divine power, young man.”

At the same time, Nabokov caught Winston’s sword with the back of her hand, flicked it diagonally away, and stuck her fist into the gap.

Pugh-Ujig!

The sound of the clavicle being forced to open a locked door.

Winston’s eyes bulged as if they were going to explode.

Boom!

An iron ball flying at a tremendous speed smashed into Winston’s skull.

“Eih, eih, old man dies.”

“Kuhugh!?”

While Nabokov was making a death sound, Winston was also making a dying sound.

“Kuhugh! Gurgle… gurgle!”

Blood and pieces of intestines are sticking out of the lips.

Amdusias hastily transformed his black mane into flames, but they dried up in an instant upon contact with the brilliant white light emanating from Nabokov.

Even the mighty 5th Corpse Amdusias was unable to show his courage in front of Nabokov.

And watching all of this, Vikir looked slightly dazed.

‘I can’t believe it, is this who she is?’

When Vikir first saw Pope Nabokov, he thought she was just a demented old woman with a short time left to live.

…But what about this?

The pressure felt by the small old woman in front of him is reminiscent of Cane Corso on the throne in the Grave of Swords.

[Ughh…How, how could this happen?]

Amdusias hadn’t realized Nabokov’s power was so great.

Around that time.

“Hahahaha – here it is! The place where the most powerful aura is felt! The blood of the Great Knight boils!”

“…Don’t let your guard down. I’ve already sent word to the imperial court for reinforcements, and I’m sure they’ll be here soon. Until then, we’ll hold them off.”

Cervantes of the Donquixote family and Roderick of the Usher family arrived.

House Leviathan and House Baskerville, as well as numerous other parents, emerged from the ruins into the center of this place.

Professors and elite students had since been arriving one after another.

Among them was a transfer student from Morgue with an excited expression on her face.

“Vi…Eup!”

Camus, who was about to call out Vikir’s name, closed her mouth and waved her hand.

Almost simultaneously, Camus’s brow furrowed as she recognized Dolores’s face next to Vikir’s.

“…What? Wind? Are you going to conduct an on-site inspection?”

Vikir didn’t bother to answer.

‘Now it’s the final chapter.’

Camus’s inexplicable low-pressure was bothering him a bit, but the stage was set.

And now all that remained was Winston’s choice.

“….”

Vikir stepped to the back of the crowd, quietly waiting for the time.

Then.

“Night Hound, You too are under urgent arrest for treason!”

A hand clamped down on Vikir’s back from behind.

Banshee Morgue, a determined look on his face as he grabs Vikir’s wrist behind his back and snaps it.

Behind him, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca stood at their teacher’s side, each holding a weapon with a determined look on their faces.

“Ni, Night Hound, you are under arrest! Receive the aura of the great Tudor!”

“Eh, ehem! Ehem! We have to help the professor, don’t let your guard down!”

“Uh…My legs are shaking!”

“I should take this opportunity to arrest this vicious criminal as well, won’t I become a total celebrity!”

In front of them is a huge demon and the worst villain in the Imperial Capital, Night Hound.

In the eyes of the public, they were both enemies of humanity, so it couldn’t be helped.

Just then.

“…Hmm?”

Professor Banshee noticed something strange.

It could only be seen by those who were close to Night Hound’s back, holding his wrist.

A bracelet.

A bracelet that was only distributed to students of the Colosseo Academy.

‘It is the key to passing the new magic wall. It’s a bracelet type. I make them by hand whenever I have time. I’ve already made enough for the students, I just need to distribute them. I’ll make some for the professors when I can afford it.’

The bracelets, made of gray, sprouting and rooted grass seeds, are specially crafted artifacts for the Academy’s students to use when entering and exiting the magic wall at the main entrance, and have been carefully crafted by Principal Winston.

…Why is it on Night Hound’s wrist now?

“Are you kidding me?”

Professor Banshee looks up with a furious expression.

[…You will not get what you want, nothing].

Black energy began to surge ferociously from Amdusias’s entire body.

At the same time, Vikir had a hunch.

‘It’s here.’

At last, the demon made its final move.

Each of the Ten Corpse that he have faced so far had their own unique abilities.

The 10th, Andromalius could turn water into blood.

The 9th, Dantalian, spreads disease and boils to spread.

The 8th, Seere, turns livestock and humans into corpses.

The 7th, Decarabia, sucks mana like a hungry grasshopper.

The 6th, Belial, sucks up wealth like a bloodsucker.

And now, Amdusias, the 5th Corpse, was also about to show a strange miracle.

<Amdusias, the ‘5th Corpse’

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: The Serpent’s Womb, deep within the Gates of Destruction.

-Nicknamed ‘5th Corpse’.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“I will take away the lives of the first born that year.”

– The Ten Commandments 10:High –

Hunting children.

Against the countless parents gathered here, Amdusias performed the worst deed.

…Kurrrrr!

A strange sound could be heard from all around.

It was the sound of seeds germinating. It was the sound of plants growing at a rapid pace, sending out roots and stems.

…The problem was, they were coming from the wrists of students at Colosseo Academy.

“W-what!?”

Professor Banshee took a step back in horror.

The bracelets on the wrists of all the students at Colosseo Academy, including Vikir, began to vibrate violently, and all at once they began to emit a blast of black light.

The small seeds attached to the bracelet soon take root and sprout stems at an amazing speed.

“What!”

Parents panicked and tried to cut off the plants that had taken root on their children’s wrists, but it was impossible.

It was too strong and too fast.

Then.

The mysterious black plant devoured the students of the Colosseo Academy.

They began to stretch out their stems and roots and intertwine with each other.

It was like watching a giant intertwined branch.

Sa-sasasasasasa…

The trees that were densely planted throughout the Academy dried up and died at an alarming rate.

It was as if they were trying to squeeze all their nutrients into this one black tree rooted in the center of the ruined Auditorium.

“…Oh, my God.”

Professor Banshee stared at the giant tree growing rapidly.

Shhhhhhhhhhh.

The entire student body of Colosseo Academy was sucked into the trunk of that giant tree.

“No! My son!”

“Kaaaaaa! Give me my daughter!”

“Oh no! Give me my students back, please!”

But no matter how hard the parents and professors tried.

Quack, quack, quack.

The explosion was loud, but the tree didn’t budge.

“Son, this father is coming!”

“Aaaaaaah! My daughter! Give me my daughter!”

Even as Donquixote’s patriarch, Cervantes, and Usher’s patriarch, Roderick, frantically threw blows with all their might, the tree remained unmoved.

Principal Winston’s worst creation.

‘Naraksu (Hell Tree)’.

It was the moment when a cursed giant tree that shouldn’t exist in this world swallowed up the entire Colosseo Academy.

Chapter 306

Hell Tree (2)

◆

The fairy said in a bizarre tone.

[Fr om no w on, fir st co me, fir st ser ved ?]

And mechanical voices rang in his ears one after another.

-Tingling!

[Tower rules apply]

[Vikir, ‘Warrior of Level 1’ has been made part of the ‘Leveling System’]

[Your status window powers will be unlocked]

Vikir nodded.

‘That’s why I didn’t stop the Hell Tree from appearing.’

With that, Vikir opened his status window.

Within this tower, his physical body is quantified and visualized in numbers called ‘stats’.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: (none)

-Stats

Strength: 178

?Agility: 203

?Stamina: 207

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

The levels of combat power were displayed at a glance, as if they were characters in a TRPG board game popularized in the Imperial Capital.

Vikir’s attention was drawn to the section labeled ‘Level’.

‘It’s said that you can’t properly demonstrate the power of reality inside the tower, and the amount of power you can demonstrate is about 1%… per level, but as you level up and get closer to 100, you’ll be able to use the power of reality.

Importantly, when you return to the real world, the extra power you’ve gained here is added as a bonus perk.

In other words. If you level 10 here, you’ll be able to use about 10% of your real-world strength, and if you escape the tower and return to the real world, you’ll be about 10% stronger in the real world than you were before you entered the tower.

Similarly, if you level up to 100 here and return to the real world, you’ll get a 100% power-up.

This means that the combat power is doubled.

‘It means you can forcefully break through the stagnation in the real world.’

Vikir remembered the Gate of the 8th Form, which he had forced through with Dolores’ buff not long ago.

If he could get out of here safely, he might be able to reach the 8th level without Dolores’ buffs.

‘First, I have to leave this room and go downstairs. There was also a saying that it was first-come-first-served.’

Vikir discovered that there was a long, winding hole in the black floor leading down.

It looks like a bizarre looking slide.

He climbed down it and found himself in a slightly more spacious room.

Unlike the room upstairs, it wasn’t empty.

[Kiiig- kiyaaaag!]

Several angry monsters were pacing around the room at high speed.

Vikir recognized them immediately.

<Norvegicus, Gutter Rat>.

Danger Rating: F

Size: 50 centimeters

Found in: All continents

-A rat that has been transformed into a hideous creature by magic.

Full-grown adults have the intelligence and size of a small dog, making them an object of disgust for women and girls.

They are surprisingly edible when gutted and roasted over a fire or boiled in water.

Tutorial Monster.

The average student at the academy would be overwhelmed by the sudden change of location and 100x weakened body, and would be unable to deal with this creature’s attacks.

…But not Vikir.

Vikir was a Swordmaster before he was sucked into the tower in the first place, so even if he was weakened by a hundredfold, there’s no way he’d be defeated by a rat.

Crack! Woof!

Vikir reached out and snapped the necks of every single one of the rats.

Only then did he realize that the ceiling above him was slowly descending.

Gigigigigigeek…

The ceiling is coming down very slowly.

But if he stayed here, he would one day be crushed to death by that ceiling.

‘Either way, I can’t stay in this room forever.’

It’s not just this floor, it’s every floor of the tower.

There’s some sort of device that keeps you from staying in your room because you’re afraid.

You can’t feel safe at any moment, you can’t feel comfortable in any place.

It’s a world where you have to run for your life. If you stand still, you’ll be wiped out in an instant.

This tower was such a cruel world.

…Snap!

Vikir has just snapped the neck of the last rat.

-Ding!

The notification sounded again in his ears.

[Vikir, a ‘Level 1 Warrior’, has successfully hunted the ‘F Rank Monster Gutter Rat Norvegicus’ for the first time in the Tutorial Zone!]

[‘Rare’ achievement rewarded!]

The grotesque flesh fairy from earlier reappeared before Vikir’s eyes.

It dropped its wrinkles in an unpleasant beat and opened an embarrassing hole that could hardly be called a mouth.

[Oh? Is th is the fir st ti me I’ve ev er se en su ch a fa st pas ser, I’m so go od, th ere mu st be a rew ard for a go od stud ent, rig ht?]

Having finished speaking, the creature gaped open the hole from which its voice came, and began spitting out a vomit that looked harmful at first glance.

…Gweapug! Gweapug! Gweapug! Gweeeelg-!

Most of the disgusting vomit that flowed from the fairy’s mouth was blood and bits of guts.

But there were also the odd glittering orbs mixed in.

Vikir stooped down and picked them up with a careful look.

Most people would have been offended and hesitated to touch them, but Vikir didn’t hesitate at all.

Chiiiiksss-

His fingertips burned as he touched the vomit.

The vomit is extremely acidic, and the moment it touches his flesh, he feels a fierce pain.

But Vikir persevered, sifting through the vomit and picking out the beads.

‘Thank goodness. I got them before they melted.’

These turned out to be candy. If he had been deterred by the ghastly appearance of the fairy, the disgusting smell of the vomit, or even the acidic air that burned his fingers, these candies would have simply melted.

Even.

“Hey. Give me the ones stuck between your teeth, that’s my reward too.”

Vikir grabbed the disappearing fairy and opened her mouth, pulling all the candy out, including the ones stuck between her pointy fangs.

[…A re y ou fru gal ? ]

The fairy stuck out its stubby tongue as it watched Vikir retrieve every last bit of candy that was stuck in its teeth.

Then, as abruptly as it had appeared, the fairy vanished, and Vikir examined the contents of his hand.

Beaded candies. They were colored red, green, and blue.

-<Strange Candy>/ Strength / Red

A candy that increases your Strength stat by 1.

Tastes salty.

– Strength +1

-<Strange Candy>/ Agility / Green

Candy that increases Agility stat by 1.

Tastes bitter.

– Agility +1

-<Strange Candy>/ Stamina / Blue

A candy that increases Stamina by 1.

Tastes astringent.

– Stamina +1

‘…Is this stat candy? It looks exactly as I heard.’

A candy that can be obtained as a reward for clearing the floors of a tower.

Eating them will increase your body’s stats.

The more you collect, the better, as it’s a simple way to increase your stats, and it’s separate from your combat power gains from leveling.

Naturally, the stats gained from these candies also apply outside of the tower, so in some cases you can get a truly massive boost in combat power.

Moreover, this candy also functions as currency in the later stages, so the more candies the better.

‘Perhaps this tower is not a trial, but an opportunity.’

Amdusias built this tower to test the humans, but that’s a result of his lack of understanding of the human race.

Some humans actually feed off of trials and tribulations to become stronger.

Humans are the only creatures that can turn a crisis into an opportunity.

Perhaps this is the land of opportunity where those who are unlucky enough to be born with talent, those who don’t have an early advantage in the race after birth, can turn their lives around.

Right now, Vikir doesn’t have a lot of natural talent. He’s only gotten this far through hard work and practical experience.

‘At least I was able to handle the difficult time because I received the blessings of the River Styx.’

However, Vikir have never thought, ‘It would be nice if I had been born with talent in the first place.’

If Vikir had something more innate, wouldn’t he be at an even higher level than he is now?

‘Let’s find out here.

Vikir put the obtained candies into Andromalius’s barrier.

With his usable mana reduced to a hundredth of its value, he could only use it to store things.

Not having to lug around heavy equipment is a great privilege.

‘…There are currently three types of stat candy available.’

Strength, Agility, and Stamina. The most basic core abilities within this tower.

But there were more types of stats.

Vikir checked the status window once more.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’ (NEW)

-Stats

?Strength: 178

?Agility: 203

?Stamina: 207

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

A new title has been created.

-Title: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’

? Deal small additional damage to creatures in rat form.

Taunt, Confuse, Blind, Bleed, Burn, Poison, and other status conditions last a bit longer.

Perhaps a small ability to deal extra damage when killing a rat-shaped monster will be granted as a perk.

But what was important were the letters ‘Locked’ that appeared in the stats section.

Stats other than strength, agility, and stamina.

‘These are the ‘three major stats’ that cannot be obtained in the tutorial zone. Candy that can unlock and raise those stats is needed first.’

It was most likely a reward for completing more difficult tasks.

Vikir thought back to before the regression.

‘…Most of the heroes who were active during the Age of Destruction were from this Hell Tree.’

Among the students who were trapped in the Hell Tree and forced to play a game of survival, there were some who became exceptionally strong.

They later rose to the ranks of great heroes through the levels and stats they gained here.

Familiar names like Tudor, Bianca, Sancho, Dolores, and Camus were among them.

And of course, the triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

And in this life, Vikir was aiming for more than half that.

‘Camus’s failure to enter Hell Tree is a factor, but she’s already strong enough that she doesn’t need it.’

After absorbing the power of the Demon King Seere and acquiring Morgue’s sacred item, the ‘Wraith Tree’, her potential is already comparable to her pre-regression prime.

Perhaps as time goes on, she will grow stronger and stronger, surpassing her pre-regression level.

She’s strong enough that she doesn’t need to be in the Hell Tree, so she won’t have to lament it for long.

‘However, before the regression, Camus destroyed the Hell Tree and saved everyone. In this life, I’ll have to do the same.’

Since it was Camus who had destroyed Amdusias’s plans before regression, Vikir was a fitting replacement.

Through her memoir and the reviews of many others, the strategy is already well-known.

Now all that’s left is to keep pushing forward.

Chapter 309

Hell Tree (5)

◆

“I’ll get them all.”

Vikir said to the hellhounds in front of him.

Granola’s response was short and to the point.

“…Are you out of your mind?”

Granola’s reaction is understandable.

Every single one of the hellhounds in front of him has powerful bones and massive muscles.

Their teeth and claws are sharper than the edge of any great sword, and the sulfur dripping from their eyes and mouths will burn and melt anything it touches.

Moreover, there are so many of them that you can’t see them all at once.

What on earth can one person do in such a situation?

But Vikir remained nonchalant.

‘I already knew hellhounds would come out.’

Vikir’s attention was drawn to the luxuries left behind in the ruined academy: perfume, cigarettes, and cosmetics.

Such a brazen arrangement of scented items must have foreshadowed the trap to come.

Vikir tried to think of a few creatures with an unusually sensitive sense of smell, but there weren’t many.

One of them was a hellhound.

‘Gnolls are very easy opponents, goblins are not difficult, and if they come out, they will probably be land sharks or hellhounds with a sensitive sense of smell.’

All the props and terrain were designed by demon, and if you messed with them, you’d die.

…Chwaag!

Vikir drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, and faced the horde of hellhounds.

Pugh-

One hellhound, confident in the power of the pack and gaining momentum, bravely charged in and suffered a serious injury to its nose.

The big nose and the fist-sized chunk of flesh behind it fell to the ground.

[Kkegaeng! Kang! Kiiing-]

A hellhound with its entire nose and bridge cut off struggles backwards, spraying hot blood and oil.

Vikir takes advantage, slicing the lower jaw off another hellhound as it tries to bite at his side.

And after that, another hellhound that tried to claw at Vikir’s buttocks lost nearly half of its right front leg, and the one next to it was pierced through the throat and died.

[Grrrr…]

[Kaeaeng! Kaeng!]

[Kkieeeeing-]

Only then did the hellhounds notice.

The other side wasn’t trying to kill them, but rather maim them.

This, of course, was a planned move by Vikir.

‘Hellhounds are rare in the early levels. Their hunting rewards are very generous.’

Vikir heard a beeping sound in his ear.

-Ding!

[Vikir, a ‘Level 1 Warrior’, has successfully hunted the first ‘B+ Rank Monster Hellhound’ in the Tutorial Zone!]

[Rewards are given for ‘difficult’ achievements!]

Just killing one gave you the reward.

Roll…

It’s a red bead. It was a ‘strange candy’ that increased your strength stat by 1.

‘I wonder what they’ll reward me with if I kill them all.’

Even in the memoirs of the pre-regression heroes, there was no mention of killing all of these monsters.

That means Vikir is tackling a quest that no one else has ever attempted.

All for the sake of the greatest reward of all!

Swash, puck, swash, puck!

Vikir moved at breakneck speed.

Parts essential for movement, such as fingers, toes, joints, and internal organs, are thoroughly protected.

Those parts that weren’t necessary for combat were boldly surrendered, and in return, he made sure to grab his opponent’s eyeballs, tongue, legs, etc.

Behind him, Granola frowned at the terrifying sight of Vikir fighting as if possessed by an evil spirit.

‘What the hell, that guy. Is he a level 1? Why is he fighting so well….’

Granola knew he wasn’t a normal guy from the University League, but he didn’t expect him to be this strong.

If he’s 100 times weaker now, how strong was he originally? How much was he hiding?

…But really, a debuff is a debuff. Vikir’s entire body was soon covered in blood.

The Hellhounds, on the other hand, are still largely intact.

There were maimed creatures everywhere, but they were also fighting against Vikir with the crazy vitality and fighting spirit that are typical of monsters.

‘Indeed. I’m tired because I’m 100 times weaker. Do I have to use some shortcuts?’

Vikir shrugged as he stepped back.

He turned to Granola behind him.

“Okay, the path is clear, run over there.”

“What? Where is the escape route….”

Before Granola could finish his sentence.

Boom.

Vikir lunged at the hellhound that was hesitating next to him and cut off its upper and lower jaws at the same time.

A hole opened up in the encirclement as the hellhound retreated with a whimper.

“Let’s go.”

“Uoh!”

Vikir grabbed Granola by the scruff of his neck, threw him forward, and followed him.

“Hoaaaaaaaaaaa!”

Granola screamed as he ran away, and he was such a good bait that he even attracted other hellhounds who were wandering nearby.

‘Now that’s a talent.’

Vikir thought to himself as he watched Granola’s back, strangely targeted by the monsters.

Well, more prey is a good thing for Vikir.

Soon enough, Vikir and Granola arrived at the storefront.

“Hey, hey! Where do you think you’re running to? It’s a recycling center! There’s no cover!”

Granola shouted in frustration.

But Vikir continued on his way to the recycling center.

There were various sorted sacks of trash lying around there.

‘…There was always an impressive janitor here.’

As it turns out, the janitor’s room is also home to an old broom, a dustpan with a hole in it, and more.

But there’s no time to admire the scenery.

[Grrrrrrrrrrr!]

A bunch of hellhounds are charging toward Vikir.

Just then.

Buuk-

Vikir lifted the bulging sacks next to the broom and dustpan and slit open their sides with his sword.

And then he threw the things inside to the hellhounds.

“Here, eat this.”

The contents of the sacks rained down on the hellhounds’ heads.

It was a hairy, yellow-skinned fruit.

And the hellhounds, covered in it, began to scream and struggle like crazy.

[Kkaegaegaegaeng! Keong! Kkeuang!]

[Keuaaang! Keoheong! Geeg-]

[Weeeeg! Guwag!]

Granola watched in disbelief as the hellhounds wrapped their front paws around their noses and gagged.

“…Bank?”

Yes. Dozens of sacks of it, piled high in the recycling bin.

Ginkgo trees are favored as street trees because they repel insects, but the only downside is the stinky fruit that falls on the road every season.

And this is an exceptionally smelly ‘sabik’ ginkgo. Its aroma is so strong that it wipes out the earthy smell of Morgue’s potatoes.

When you go to the school’s recycling center, you’ll always see them stacked in bags.

Ujik-

When several hellhounds stepped on the ginkgo fruit, yellow juice began to spurt out and an even stronger smell began to spread.

Hellhounds, who already have a sensitive sense of smell, cannot tolerate this foul smell and vomit.

It was then that Vikir drew his sword.

…Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!

Each time the red awl flicked back and forth, one hellhound inevitably closes its eyes and sticks out its tongue.

Several hellhounds tried to fight back, but there was no way a proper fight was possible with sulfur flowing out of their eyes and noses.

Dug, dug, dug, dug.

As Vikir killed more hellhounds, stat candy continued to drop.

Red candies for strength. Green candies for agility. Blue candies for stamina.

Red candies were the most common, followed by blue candies, and then green candies.

“The agility stat is really hard to get.”

Vikir thought as he looked at the pile of candies in front of him.

‘If the candy store opens later, I can exchange 300 stat candies for 1 level candy, so I’d better start saving up for that.’

Just then.

A fairy appeared in front of Vikir’s eyes.

They usually appear out of nowhere, but this time it was even more sudden.

[Wow, did you kill all th ese child ren ? Are yo u qu ite irre gular ? ]

The fairy stuck out its tongue as it looked at the dead bodies of hellhounds spread out on the floor of the recycling bin.

Then, in a soft voice, it gave Vikir a choice.

[ Sin ce you ha ve ma de su ch a gr eat ach ieve ment, you sho uld take the gr eat rew ard, rig ht ? ]

At the same time, something appeared in front of Vikir’s eyes.

-Tingling!

[‘Level 1 Warrior’ Vikir has successfully hunted down the ‘B+ Rank Monster Hellhound Pack’ for the first time in the Tutorial Zone!]

[Rewards will be given out for ‘great’ achievements!]

[You will be able to adjust the difficulty of the mission for one time]

[Would you like to increase the difficulty level?]

[The mission with the increased difficulty will be a ‘bonus stage’]

[If you clear the ‘bonus stage’, you will receive additional rewards!]

Asking if I want to increase the difficulty.

That means. Now that the entire group of hellhounds has been killed, will you allow a more dangerous monster to appear?

“How could you possibly allow this, you idiot!?”

Granola raised the middle fingers of both hands and shouted at the fairy.

But Vikir, standing next to him, had a different idea.

“I’ll do it. Send something.”

A more powerful boss monster. This was what Vikir wanted.

The stronger and more dangerous the monster, the better and more valuable the reward.

The fairy laughed unpleasantly next to Granola’s astonished expression.

[I li ke it, I li ke it, I li ke it so mu ch? Are you will ing to ta ke on th at chal lenge? Th en we can get star ted rig ht aw ay , rig ht ? ]

At the same time, a black hole appeared in the fairy’s back.

It was similar to the hole that had appeared when the hellhounds had been summoned earlier, but there was only one, and it was much wider in diameter.

And.

A monster of adjusted difficulty began to appear before Vikir’s eyes.

“…Ah, this must be a dream.”

A magical beast that was enough to make even Granola, who had somehow managed to hold on until now, lose his mind.

But Vikir’s comment was short.

“Long time no see.”

Three heads emerged from the gate. Only one body.

<Cerberus(Κ?ρβερο?)>

Danger rating: A+.

Size: 7 meters

Found in: Ridge 7, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-A.K.A. ‘Hell Watchdog’

This dog has no interest in wraiths trying to enter Hell, but will immediately tear them to shreds if they try to escape.

It lives in the depths of the Oil World, the final destination for all wraiths, and is considered the ultimate of oil world monsters.

Cerberus the Hell Watchdog, the boss of the bonus stage.

It’s glaring at Vikir with a fiery, intimidating gaze.

Chapter 311

Hell Tree (7)

◆

…Pow!

The last of Cerberus’ heads exploded.

Kung-

As the monster’s massive body fell to the floor of the ruins, a slight earthquake occurred.

The sulfur and blood that spewed from Cerberus’ bursting belly swept away the perfume and ginkgo scent from the floor of the shop.

-Ding!

[‘Level 1 Warrior’ Vikir has successfully hunted the ‘A+ Ranked Monster Cerberus’ for the first time!]

[Rewards are given for ‘awesome’ achievements!]

A loud beeping sound erupts.

“…Huu.”

Vikir sat down with a tired expression.

Catching Cerberus with a body that was 100 times weaker was definitely hard work.

Then Granola, who was beside him, said with a tired expression.

“You’re usually called persistent, aren’t you?”

“No. I’ve never heard of it.”

Vikir turned his head toward Granola and continued.

“I killed them all before they could say that.”

Granola felt a shiver run down his spine.

Just then.

[Ehhh? Did you cat ch th is on e ? ]

The fairy who had appeared out of nowhere began to fuss.

[Huh la la? Is th is yo ur fir st ti me pass ing li ke th is ? ]

The fairy’s attitude is that it didn’t expect Vikir to actually complete the mission.

That’s why the fairy seemed to be quite flustered.

[Wh at sho uld I do? In the begin ning, the rew ards th at can be giv en are limit ed? ]

Then Vikir spoke up eagerly.

“Do you happen to have any artifacts or items that you can give away? I don’t mind if they’re consumables.”

[ Mm mm mm mm mm mm ? ]

It looks like it isn’t there.

Vikir opened his mouth as if there was nothing else to do.

“Oh well, it’s not a mission I’m supposed to complete, so I guess they didn’t think of a proper reward, just a way to make fun of the people trapped in the tower.”

Then Vikir spoke up, sounding very offended.

“But you know what? A craftsman who could create such an elaborate system would be very particular about his output. He must have selected only masterpieces for each floor.”

[ Mmmm mmmm mmmm ? ]

“But isn’t it a little strange that such an error occurs from the very beginning of such a result? Could it be that the one just now was an extra-standard mission that someone did for fun? He exercised his authority purely out of his own power….”

At those words, the fairy looked extremely hot.

It was trying to look calm and avert its gaze, but you could see the heart pounding furiously in its cleft stomach.

Vikir cut in.

“You don’t need any rewards for this bonus stage. Instead, I will file a claim against the tower’s administrators when I see them later. I’m going to complain, and I’m going to complain loud and clear.”

Then the fairy cried out urgently.

[ Is the re a rew ard? Are you rea dy for yo ur rewa rd ? ]

It was only at the mention of a reward that Vikir smiled.

“Then give it to me. Reward.”

[But the rew ard th at can be giv en in the begin ning is limit ed ? ]

Vikir knew very well that the only reward a fairy could give in the beginning was a strange candy.

So Vikir was able to say firmly.

“I’m quantity over quality.”

[You do n’t hesit ate to say th at ? ]

“That’s right. As long as you don’t mind the quantity.”

Before Vikir could nod, the fairy opened its mouth so wide that the corners of both mouths were torn open and blood gushed out.

[ Bweh ee eek ? ]

Then, the fairy began to spit out a huge amount of candy from its mouth.

Red, green, and blue candies poured out of her mouth.

Granola’s eyes widened at the number of candies, which must have been hundreds.

“Oh my God! Look at all these stats! If I eat all these, I’ll be strong in no time!”

But Vikir just shook his head as he picked up the candies.

‘…Not even close.’

The color of the falling candy is random, but red candies are the most common, followed by blue, and then green.

This means that strength stats are the most common, stamina stats are common, and agility stats are rare.

In fact, most of the candy the fairy spit out was red and blue, and not much green.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes widened.

Vikir quickly reached out and grabbed a candy that was stuck at the bottom of the pile.

It was the only other color among the red, green, and blue candies.

‘I can’t believe I got this here!’

Vikir exclaimed inwardly, examining the candy with a nonchalant expression.

-<Strange Candy>/ Physical Resistance / Black

A candy that increases Physical Resistance by 1.

Tastes spicy.

+1 Physical Resistance

Black, like a concentrated form of darkness. At first glance, it doesn’t look like any other stat candy.

Vikir regained the knowledge he had gained before his regression.

‘According to the Memoirs of the Great Heroes, there are six types of stats that can be raised inside the tower: Strength, Agility, and Stamina, which can be raised early on, but the other three stats can only be raised later in the stage. The drop rate of candy is extremely low to begin with, so it’s possible that you won’t get any at all on your way to the top.’

Six stats. Three of which are Strength, Agility, and Stamina. They were ‘ultra-rare talents’ that even the most heroic of heroes had never managed to blossom on their way out of the tower.

And one of them, Vikir had already gained.

‘Physical Resistance. A stat that reduces the damage taken by an attack.’

Without thinking twice, Vikir ate the black candy.

Gulp!

As he passed the candy down his throat, he felt a pungent flavor that burned his tongue and throat.

-Ding!

The status window changed.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’, ‘Hell’s Dog’ (NEW)

-Stats.

Power: 230

?Agility: 219

?Stamina: 244

?Physical Resistance: 0 (+1) = 1

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

Unlike the base stats, which are above a certain number from the start, the special stat, Physical Resistance, starts at 0.

This is because this stat is an innate talent that cannot be raised in the real world.

It can only be raised in this tower.

‘Once you’ve eaten the candy and unlocked it, your stats will naturally increase as you level up. If you leave it alone, it will grow with your level.’

To be able to bloom and grow this stat so early on was an incredible stroke of luck.

Plus, it gave us a new title: The Hell’s Dog.

-New Title: Hell’s Dog

? Deal massive additional damage to creatures in dog form.

Taunt, Confuse, Blind, Bleed, Burn, Poison, and other status abnormalities last slightly longer.

‘Title perks aside, unlocking the Physical Resistance stat early on is a huge opportunity.’

In fact, the whole point of trying to get to the bottom of the tower is to complete the big six stats.

While leveling up is important, it’s actually more important to complete these six stats.

Six types of stats that you can take with you outside the tower. But collecting them all was a feat that none of the great heroes before the Regression had ever accomplished.

Then.

A fairy spoke to Vikir, who was sitting still and lost in thought.

[Ov er the re ov er the re? Do you by any chan ce ne ed a can dy sto re ? ]

After speaking, the fairy stretched out a finger and brought up a status window.

-<Fairy’s Candy Store>

Selling and buying unused candy!

-Strange candy (golden color): Can be exchanged for 300 candies of any color.

The fairy stuck out its tongue and showed the golden candy that was sold in this shop.

-<Strange Candy>/ Level / Golden

A candy that raises your level by 1.

Tastes sweet.

-Level +1

A golden candy with a brilliant glow.

Granola looks at it longingly.

“Oh my. It’s going to level me up? Each one of those will restore 1% of my real-world strength, so if I eat 100 of them, I’ll have 100% of my strength back! And when I leave the tower, those stats will be added to my original strength! This is the best candy ever!”

For survivors weakened by a hundred times, this is the candy they need most of all.

But it’s too expensive. You can get it in any color, but it costs 300 pieces, making it a rare commodity that’s hard to find in the early stages.

…This, of course, doesn’t apply to Vikir, who had a bunch of hellhounds on the last stage.

“Hmm.”

When Vikir looked troubled, the fairy encouraged him even more subtly.

[ Won’t any one be ab le to use the can dy sto re, and if you rai se yo ur le vel, yo ur sta ts will natu rally go up as well ? ].

Literally. Leveling up will give you back some of your strength outside of the tower, so it makes sense to try to level up quickly in the beginning.

…But Vikir shakes his head.

‘Leveling up is still taboo.’

Vikir stared at the number 1 on the level marker for a while.

A younger chick would be all-in on collecting stat candy and turning it into level candy, but not Vikir.

Vikir hadn’t been leveling for a while, for quite some time.

‘This tower favors lower levels.’

According to the memoirs of great heroes, there are some rules about rewards within this tower.

If a strong person does a great deed, they get a modest reward.

If a weak person performs a small feat, they receive a modest reward.

When a strong person performs a small feat, they receive almost no reward.

…But.

When a weak person does something great.

In these cases, the reward is something that goes far beyond the common sense.

Vikir noted the notification he had heard earlier.

[‘Level 1 warrior’ Vikir is part of the ‘leveling system’…… ]

[Vikir, ‘Warrior at Level 1’, has killed the first F-ranked monster in the Tutorial Zone…]

[‘Rare’ achievement rewards…]

[Vikir, a ‘Level 1 Warrior’, killed the first B+ ranked monster in the Tutorial Zone…]

[Reward for ‘Difficult’ achievements…]

[Vikir, a ‘Level 1 Warrior’, kills his first B+ ranked monster… group…]

[‘Great’ achievement…]

[Vikir, a ‘Level 1 Warrior’, successfully hunted the first ‘A+ Ranked Monster Cerberus’…]

[‘Awesome’…]

As part of the leveling system, Vikir is considered an ‘underdog’.

Even if his stats are superior to those of others, he is still considered to be of the same class.

‘If a ‘Level 1 Warrior’ continues to clear difficult missions, the rewards will get better and better.’

Vikir was stronger than the other students, and even at level 1, he was able to make up for his shortcomings with his stats.

‘So it’s better to stay low in the beginning and take on the harder missions to maximize the rewards.’

This was a very different strategy from the typical survivor.

And Vikir knows one more reason not to level up.

‘There will come a point in time when all those levels won’t matter. I don’t know exactly when that will be, but… I think it’s better to save my candy levels until then.

The uneaten stat candies (red, green, and blue) could be exchanged for level candies (golden) at the candy store later, so there was no reason to rush to level up.

After organizing his thoughts, Vikir stopped trading with the fairy.

[Ah hing ang eh? Ah shhhh? ]

When Vikir did not give in to fairy coaxing, the fairy let out a strange, meaningless groan and closed the trading window.

And that moment.

Cuddleddleddled…

A strong earthquake occurred, and the ground in this area began to sink.

“What! 108 minutes must have passed already!”

Granola was right.

-Ding!

<Mission over>– Number of survivors: 69 people.

The same status window popped up in front of Vikir and Granola.

Probably all 69 survivors of hellhounds’ attack.

Kuoooooo!

A black, swirl-shaped gate opened, sucking in everyone who fell below.

-Ding!

[Leaving Underground Level 2 ‘Familiar Ground’]

[Entering Underground Level 3 ‘Familiar Ground (2)’]

It looked like all the survivors of the second floor were going to fall to the same place.

Chapter 312

Surplus Man (1)

◆

<Mission End>– Number of survivors: 69 people

*End condition: Survive an attack by 108 Hellhounds for 108 minutes

-Ding!

[Leaving Underground Level 2 ‘Familiar Ground’]

[Entering Underground Level 3 ‘Familiar Ground (2)’]

It was still a dull notification sound.

The 69 survivors of the second floor had fallen into the third floor.

“ What, this place?”

“It’s the Imperial Capital.”

“We’re outside the Academy!”

For a moment, the students’ faces lit up as they realized they were outside the tower.

But their faces soon turned grim as they realized that the landscape of the Imperial Capital was similar to that of the Academy.

Cold, desolate ruins. Imperial Capital used to be more vibrant and bustling than any other city, but now everything was broken and cracked.

Broken windows and rusted doors, leaning roofs and half-broken pillars.

It was still daylight, so the sun was shining, but the dry, barren cold was still there.

Then.

“Hey, hey, what’s that?”

“Ugh… It’s huge.”

“It looks creepy.”

“Don’t you think we shouldn’t approach it?”

As the students cautiously walked through the city, they soon noticed something strange.

The central clock tower, symbolizing the center of the Imperial Capital. A structure that had once been destroyed by Miss Urobors and lost its form.

Yet here it stood, still standing.

Chipped and cracked in places, but still standing on a grand scale.

But that wasn’t the most surprising thing.

“There’s something wrapped around the clock tower.”

“It’s a plant vine, or maybe a root.”

“What’s that on top of the tower? It’s huge.”

“…It looks like a flower.”

A plant wraps itself around the clock tower.

It was a huge flower blooming on the roof of the tower, with shriveled leaves, roots, and vines hanging down.

‘The withered flower’.

The students could soon see that the huge flower was completely dead on top of the clock tower.

“Hey. This flower is subtly warm.”

“I’m not cold next to it. We can spend the night here.”

“What is this, a leaf? No, the air sacs have dried up and shrunk.”

“Is there something like a little air inside? It’s soft so we can use it as a pillow.”

The students split into two groups.

Those who would search the ruins for safety, and those who would stay near the flower’s remains to avoid tonight’s bitter cold.

Those who chose to stay around the flower covered themselves with dried roots and leaves and began to rest.

Those who went to the ruins sought shelter among the collapsed rubble, in sewers, basements, iron trash cans, and on roofs.

In most cases it fell into the latter category.

The memory of hiding from hellhounds in the previous stage was still fresh in their minds.

But for Vikir, it was the former.

The dried leaves were warm because they contained the warmth of the sun.

To the touch, it felt tough and dry, with a hint of air inside.

Vikir covered it and lay down half covered. This is because he want to regain his stamina.

…Time passed, and as the day wore on, it turned out that Vikir was right.

“You’re too cold.”

“Why are you so cold?”

“I don’t have anything to keep the cold out….”

“You’re going to freeze to death.”

Cold concrete, glass, and rail could not block the cold.

Students who had been hiding in various parts of the ruins crawled out, shivering, and gathered at the ‘withered flower’ of the central clock tower.

“Ah, it looks like we’re finally going to live.”

“Strange. It’s warm around this flower.”

“It must have had a lot of energy when it was alive.”

“It must have had a lot of energy when it was alive to be able to retain this much heat even after death.”

“But why is a creature of this size lying dead in a place like this?”

“I don’t know. What the hell am I supposed to do here?”

“No fairy, no mission.”

With a bit of a breather, the students began to complain about their current situation.

Then. The second crisis hit.

Growling-

Now that the cold is gone, hunger is a problem.

The students left their seats again and searched throughout the ruins, but as expected, they found almost nothing that could be used as food.

A chocolate bar with an unreadable expiration date, some bloated canned foods, some rotten-smelling meat, and a few withered bunches of weeds were all that was available.

Even then, the amount of food was ridiculously small for everyone to eat.

Everyone is frustrated by the food shortage.

…But there was one person who was cooking alone, out of sight, out of mind.

It was Vikir.

Bubbly, bubbling…

Vikir lit a barrel of used oil and placed a dented pot over it.

He caught rainwater from the tents and boiled it.

“Hey. Why are you boiling water?”

Granola, who was watching from the side, asked.

Vikir answered quietly.

“I need to eat.”

“Really? Is there food?”

Granola asks, swallowing hard, and Vikir nods.

With that, Vikir stretched out Beelzebub’s sword and held it to the withered stem of the flower.

…Poof!

He stabbed with his aura, and the plant’s stem began to chip away, bit by bit.

The stem of the plant was extremely tough, and even with Vikir’s aura, it wasn’t easy to cut through it.

The other students probably couldn’t even dream of it.

Soon, Vikir held two broken pieces the size of his little fingernails on his fingertips.

Granola shook his head.

“You’re going to eat that, and it’s going to be so little?”

But what happened next made Granola’s jaw drop.

…Pongdang!

A piece of the plant’s stem was placed in boiling water and an amazing transformation occurred.

Bubbly, bubbling…

The stem piece, which was the size of a little fingernail, soon swelled to an enormous size.

It was as thick and long as an adult man’s forearm.

“It looks small because it’s dried out. If you eat it, it will expand to a huge size in your stomach.”

Hearing Vikir’s words, Granola swallowed hard.

The stem was too hard and tough to cut through, but even if he could, his stomach wouldn’t be able to handle it if he ate it just because he was hungry.

“De-definitely. If I ate that much, my stomach would burst and I would die.”

Granola watched, then dipped a minute stalk into the water.

Vikir didn’t say anything.

Granola seemed to have noticed this as well, so he began to nibble on the stem of the plant while observing Vikir’s perception.

“You, by the way.”

“Hmm?”

“Why are you being so nice to me?”

Vikir had saved Granola’s life from a pack of hellhounds in the previous stage.

Now he’s feeding him.

Vikir gazed at Granola in wonder.

To be precise, he was looking at the necklace hanging on Granola’s chest.

“…Well, we’re friends.”

Vikir said nonchalantly and looked away.

In essence, the word friend cannot be used to refer to people of similar age and in the same class.

Vikir knew this, but he said nothing.

But for some reason, the corners of Granola’s eyes became moist.

‘…Friend.’

Granola hadn’t made a single friend since entering the Colosseo Academy.

Everyone in his class followed him around, watching for anything to drop.

The seniors are the ones to approach for connections.

Moreover, he was always craving attention and recognition from his father, the patriarch of the family, and his older brothers.

However, being the youngest, he was treated like a child, and no matter how great his achievements were, he could never achieve anything new because his older brothers had already gone through it all before, leaving him lonely and dull.

That hadn’t changed since he’d entered the Academy.

But now. Granola was feeling complex emotions that he couldn’t quite put his finger on.

‘I want to be friends… with this guy.’

Granola had felt this way in the University League, but this kid in front of him was like a big brother, even though he was younger.

And when Vikir told him he was a friend, he felt recognized.

When Granola was blushing with a pride he didn’t recognize.

“Hey. Isn’t that you, Granola?”

A voice called out from behind him.

Granola turned to see a group of third-year Aristocrat Faction seniors standing there.

“I thought you were killed by hellhounds earlier, but you weren’t.”

“Thank goodness you’re alive. A Leviathan, after all! Strong and reliable.”

“Hurry over here. Ah, it’s good to have the youngest again.”

“I’m sorry I couldn’t save you earlier. I’ll take you out of the tower and give you a big drink instead. Haha-”

They were gesturing toward Granola as if what had happened in the previous stage was no big deal.

Granola hesitated. These were the same people he’d gotten along with before entering the tower.

‘What do I do?’

Vikir had his own group outside the tower.

Granola was torn for a moment, not sure which way to go.

“That… I….”

After a brief deliberation, Granola opens his mouth to say what choice he just made.

[Hot hot hot hot hot ? ]

A bizarre laugh suddenly came from nowhere.

At that moment, all the students turned their heads with wide eyes.

A bizarre ball of flesh could be seen floating in the air.

It was a fairy.

[Hell o to all 69 peo ple surviv ors ? Is th is the appear ance of yo ur cu te fai ry ? ]

The fairy gave a mission when it appeared.

<Mission>– Survive 1~69 days in the ruins!

※ ??? Avoid!

[Is the miss ion you wi ll perf orm sim ple th is ti me too ? Can you ju st sur vive ? ]

There was a stir among the students.

“Really? Are we really just supposed to stay alive?”

“But what’s 1 to 69? Does it mean we just have to survive one day or 69 days?”

“Yeah. The time frame is unclear.”

“Common sense says you can’t survive 69 days in this cold, hungry place. But then again, it would be too easy to just survive one day….”

Just then.

A student who seemed to be a leader stood up.

Usually a sharp analytical and critical thinker in class, he had once again found a flaw in the fairy’s explanation.

“Wait a minute. Something doesn’t add up. What’s the small print under the mission?”

Sure enough, all eyes turned to the direction his fingertips were pointing.

※ ??? Avoid!

A puzzling message. What could it be?

Then the fairy who was about to disappear came back in a hurry, as if forgetting something.

[Ah cha cha cha? Did I for get to un lock it ? ]

Forgot? What do you mean forgot?

The student who had pointed out the fairy snorted pathetically.

“If you’re going to bring all these people to play pranks, do it right, you demon, do you have to be so sloppy?”

[ Sor ry ? Did I alm ost ma ke a big mis take ? ]

The fairy apologized to all the students, including the model student, in a sheepish manner.

And then.

…Snap!

The fairy lifted up a finger and let a drop of black blood fall into the air.

“?”

A single drop of blood dripped down, sticky as tar, in front of all the students’ puzzled faces.

It fell onto the dried roots of the plant on the ground and quickly soaked in.

And immediately, a terrible accident occurred.

Kkuddeuk-deuk-deuk-deuk!

A bizarre noise began to echo throughout the giant clock tower building.

The vines that had been dry and dead just moments before were slowly moving.

At the same time.

Ttugak-

The model student back who had who had given a warning to the fairy, suddenly broke.

A long, tough vine that had been hanging from the wall of the clock tower had suddenly wrapped itself around his waist and grabbed him.

“…?”

He barely felt the pain from his broken back.

He was overwhelmed by the sight of a huge flower on the roof of the tower, opening its gaping mouth.

The mouth, which was wide open as if smiling, was filled with teeth that were terrifying to look at, sticking out all the way up, down, left and right.

…Pujig!

It took less than a second for a human to be transformed into an insignificant piece of meat in the flower’s gaping mouth.

Blood flowed out of the gaping mouth.

At the same time, the mission window changed.

<Mission>– Survive in the ruins for 1-68 days!

※ Avoid ‘Daylily of Blood Tree’!

The fairy chuckled.

[Now you on ly ne ed to sur vive for a maxi mum of 68 da ys, rig ht?]

Chapter 313

Surplus Man (2)

◆

“Oh. You’re finally awake.”

Vikir said as he stretched.

A giant flower bloomed atop the clock tower. It opened its gaping mouth like it was laughing and chewed on a human.

Crunch- crunch- crunch- crunch…

Bones and bits of flesh mixed with the gurgling blood.

As the blood soaked in, the surrounding vines, which had dried up like mummies, seemed to wrinkle ever so slightly.

All the students stepped back in horror at the ghastly sight.

The fairy chuckled and said.

[ Do es th is pla nt eat a per son onc e a day ? It’s st ill sm all, so one per son a day wo uld be eno ugh, rig ht ? Do it eat th e liv ing and th e de ad ali ke ? ]

Danger level S. ‘Daylily of Blood Tree’.

A powerful demon tree that, although it is an immature creature, must eat a person a day.

It was a dangerous creature that could not even be compared to the hellhounds they had encountered in the previous stage.

Realizing this instinctively, the students stared at the cannibalistic flower on the clock tower in disbelief.

“No way! You expect us to spend 69 days in a place where such a monster lurks?”

“Oh, no, it’s only 68 days now!”

“Damn it, whatever!”

“Calm down! It’s not important that one day is shortened, but why it was shortened!”

“Maybe we can reduce it further here!”

With the death of one person just now, there are fewer days to endure.

But even so, 68 days was not a short time.

With limited food and water, and with one person a day falling prey to the monster, it was a long time to wait.

Everyone is watching with fear and anxiety.

Meanwhile, Daylily stretched out its long tongue and pulled out the bits of meat stuck between its teeth, then went back to sleep.

[ Did you see it ? It’s ok ay as lo ng as you don’t att ack it ? ]

However, the fairy’s words that followed caused the students’ expressions to stiffen once again as they breathed a sigh of relief as soon as Daylily fell back to sleep.

[ We ll, I gu ess it wi ll wa ke up aga in, rig ht ? ]

The nightmare had only just begun.

Now, the students have to fight cold, hunger, and blood-sucking daylilies for 68 days here.

Some of the students gritted their teeth and tried to attack the stems of the daylilies, but there was no way they would be able to make a dent in the body of a Dangerous Class S monster in the first place.

Especially since they were a hundred times weaker than their strength outside the tower.

“That’s wrong, I can’t even gather enough mana.”

“Ahhhhh! I don’t want to be in the same room with that monster! I don’t want to!”

“But the ruins are so cold. Even if you don’t like it, if you don’t stay close to that monster….”

“Ewww! I’d rather freeze to death in a concrete sewer!”

“Do you think that plant won’t find you? Didn’t you see the roots and vines growing out of it earlier?”

“Alas, what am I supposed to do, I’m hungry and thirsty and… how am I supposed to spend 68 days here….”

The students were frustrated. They were so confused and scared that they didn’t know what to do.

Then. The fairy said good-naturedly.

[Do not be so discour aged, I will br ing you a spe cial gi ft ? ]

At the same time. Strange things appeared before the eyes of all the surviving students.

…Pop, pop, pop!

With a loud firecracker sound, a box fell into each of the students’ arms.

It was a black cube the size of a human head, with a red symbol ‘?’ written near the lid.

[ I’m afr aid you wi ll be uncomfor table if the re’s noth ing in it, so I’ve prep ared a spe cial gift for you – Wh at’s inclu ded is ran dom ? ]

According to the fairy, it contains “items,” tools that are called artifacts or Ooparts outside the tower.

What’s inside is random, and if you’re lucky, you’ll pull out a powerful and useful item; if you’re unlucky, you’ll get a piece of junk.

“Great! I’m good at these gacha draws. I’ll show you my luck!”

One student was the first to open the box.

The box was designed to be opened by lifting the lid, sticking your hand inside, and pulling out what was inside.

You couldn’t turn it over or break it to get at the contents.

“Let’s see. What’s inside?”

The student stuck his hand inside the box.

At that moment.

…Wham!

An unpleasant crackling sound was heard.

“Huh?”

He pulled his arm out of the box and saw that his hand had been severed from around his wrist.

“Ahhhhhh!?”

As the student fell, holding his bleeding arm, the black box naturally disappeared.

[Do es ‘bang’ al so co me out occasi onally? Some th ing li ke Mim ic? Is it li ke th is ? ]

The fairy’s words once again turned the faces of the students, who had seen the random box and had the slightest glimmer of hope in their eyes, into dead faces.

The students were now divided into two groups.

There are students who open the random box in front of them and students who do not.

Most of them didn’t open the boxes because they’d seen people get their wrists blown off trying to open them earlier.

However, there were quite a few students who opened the box anyway.

“What if I don’t open it? I can’t just sit there and starve to death.”

“We have to get something before we die of hunger.”

“Damn it. I’m going to slit my wrists!”

“Weapons, come out! Please! Something to defend myself….”

The results of the randomized box were then revealed to the sound of loud fireworks.

The most popular item was the “strange candy”.

Red, blue, and green candies, in that order.

After that, someone had a fan full of feathers like those worn by noble ladies, someone had a scary-edged iron sword, someone had a small harmonica, someone had a mace too heavy to lift, someone had salt and pepper, and someone had beef jerky. Some people provide drinking water, some people use farming tools….

There was no shortage of items dropped in the randomized boxes.

In addition to the group opening the random boxes, some of the more intelligent students began to analyze the situation.

“At the beginning, the number of days we had to survive here was 69, and then it was reduced to 68, right?”

“You don’t think 24 hours have passed since then, do you?”

“I think the time we have to survive here is up to us.”

“What does that have to do with the fact that there were 69 survivors when we first got here?”

“Surely the fewer people we have, the fewer days we have to survive?”

“A plan like that is certainly possible in the minds of the demons.”

The number of survivors who first came here was 69. 69 days to live here.

But after a student was eaten alive by a daylily, the number of survivors dropped to 68.

At the same time, the number of days they had to survive here was reduced to 68.

Eventually, the students came up with a frightening deduction.

The number of days to live here is equal to the number of survivors.

…What if the number of survivors decreased, the number of days they would have to endure decreased as well?

“After a while, some of them will die of cold and hunger, and maybe before that, there will be more deaths due to violence over food and grudges.”

“That’s not so bad. It means we’ll have fewer days to live.”

“Still, I’ve been scouring the ruins and there’s not a whole lot of food. It’s just that most of it is spoiled or rotten.”

“If anything comes up, let’s eat this fat guy first. Kkkkkk–”

“What? What kind of joke is that, it’s not funny!”

“…Do you think it’s a joke?”

“….”

The amount of time a person can go without eating is between three and seven days at most.

If you have access to some water, you can go up to 20 days.

So 68 days without food in a cold, desolate ruin like this is a long way to go.

And if the daylilies wake up at this time tomorrow, that’s a problem.

“It only takes one to get eaten and then it goes back to sleep, so why don’t we all run for our lives and let the slowest ones get eaten first?”

“That seems like the fairest thing to do. It’s called natural selection.”

“Yeah, right. If you’re slow, you die.”

“Is that daylily so strong in the first place? Can’t we all just fight it?”

The students are talking to each other.

The fairy added, as if she had forgotten something.

[Isn’t th at rig ht? Daylilies get annoy ed wh en you mo ve a lot ? Th ey can eat six or eig ht pe ople in a sing le bi te ? It’s bet ter not to mo ve a lot, isn’t it ? ]

After speaking, the fairy pointed to the inside of the window of the building next door.

Where everyone’s eyes turned, there was a pile of bones.

All large, thick bones.

They were the remains of hellhounds, shattered all over the place, along with the surrounding terrain.

The fairy chuckled and pulled up a hologram window.

It showed scenes of the hellhounds from the previous stage fighting against the Daylily of Blood Tree.

Nearly a hundred hellhounds, each baring their teeth and claws, lunged at the Daylily of Blood.

…And the results were devastating.

-Bam!

The 100 hellhounds didn’t last 10 seconds against the Daylily of Blood.

In the three-second window between 10 and 8 seconds, 50 of them were hit by the whip-like stems, separating their upper and lower bodies.

In the span of 4 seconds, from 7 seconds to 4 seconds, 40 of them, slightly less than half, were hit by roots protruding from the floor, turning into blood clots and stuck to the floor.

From 3 seconds until the count reached 0, the five surviving Hellhounds were hit by the poisonous breath that spewed out from the central tassel of the flower on the clock tower, melting into a handful of blood.

From then on, the daylily ate the hellhound’s corpse for a while, but soon got tired of it and moved to another location.

Annihilation.

“….”

A silence descends among the students.

Even the Hellhounds that had harassed them so much in the previous stage were like this.

If it’s true that Daylily grows more ferocious the more it moves, this means that in a worst-case scenario, it could kill all 68 of them at once.

That’s one person a day, one human sacrifice.

An eerie silence falls over the ruins. The 68 surviving students begin to fight for attention.

Cold, hunger, and the risk of being chosen to be sacrificed to the monster.

What’s more.

“That cannibal flower. If we throw a corpse at it, it will eat and sleep, right?”

“Of course it will, it said earlier that it eats both the living and the dead.”

“So it doesn’t just eat one person a day until everyone dies.”

“No. If everyone’s going to die, then all we can say is to die.”

“…Okay, that’s it. Anyway, it also eat corpses, right? It will make things easier.”

“I’m thinking the same thing, maybe even easier than the last stage?”

Some of the students cast dangerous glances at the others.

The atmosphere in the ruins was getting increasingly out of control.

Chapter 317

Surplus Man (6)

◆

[G-Gigikigeek!]

Daylily’s hunger had reached its limit.

It was rampaging with its mouth so wide open that the flower’s head looked like it had been snapped in half.

In a mouth as deep as the abyss of hell, misshapen teeth were protruding and eating up rebar and asphalt.

Kwakwang! Pusyuug-

The attacks grew more furious and diverse.

The focus on cutting and smashing vines of stems and roots has now changed.

Tsutsutsutsutsu… Paaksak

The rocks where the roots touched shriveled and dried up, then turned to sand and crumbled.

‘It sucks the moisture from where it touches, a troublesome ability.’

Of course, it’s not a particularly moist environment, so it’s more like it’s twisting and squeezing water than sucking it up.

It’s an inefficient strategy because the amount of energy it expends is greater than the amount of water it gains.

However.

Swilililig! Kwang! Pasasag…

The Daylily continued to extend its roots toward Vikir.

Snap!

No blood flowed from the wound where the tip of its root sliced through.

That’s because a huge amount of blood was taken away in that short moment.

Also.

Peoeong! Pusyug-

Every time the Daylily’s leaves hit the ground, it made a sound like a giant balloon popping, and a poisonous gas spewed out.

The shriveled and spread out leaves would burst open upon impact, and the cloud of poisonous gas inside would rise up in the shape of a skull.

On contact with this gas, the flesh would boil into bubbles and eventually melt away.

As such, Daylily was the worst biological weapon, armed with a variety of lethal functions.

…But.

“No matter how powerful an attack is, if it doesn’t hit.”

Vikir was retreating backwards, avoiding all the flying whips, dry energy, and poison gas clouds.

A clearly different movement. This was not a matter of agility or stamina.

Hwiing- kwang! Pasasag!

Dodging sweeping roots with minimal effort, and sweeping away flying debris with a few shakes of the head.

No need to move much, no need to move fast.

Time seems to slow down.

A realm where the time it takes for a small dot approaching from a distance to change into a large dot in front of you feels boring!

<Vikir>

-LV: 1 (%)

-Titles: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’, ‘Hell’s Dog’

-Stats.

Strength: 260

?Agility: 229

?Stamina: 269

?Physical Resistance: 1

??: (Locked)

?Reflexes: 0 (+1) = 1

Reflexes, the most difficult of the “Big Three” stats to obtain outside of the base stats, has blossomed.

It is a realm of innate talent that is impossible to obtain outside of the Tower.

Vikir had acquired it.

‘With this, I have collected five of the six major stats. This is already a feat in the third level of the underground. It can only be said that I was lucky….’

Even those with heroic potential and luck had already obtained two Hidden Pieces, which were obtained much later in the tower, deep, deep down.

Vikir’s steps were getting stronger and stronger.

Thud.

Beelzebub, carrying a sticky liquid aura, cut off the dried leaves of the Daylily.

‘It’s an air sac.’

What looked like a dried, shriveled leaf was actually a gas sac.

It was similar to the structure of a water plant, a species of daylily.

The only difference is that the Daylily of Blood Tree contains a lot of toxic gas in its air sacs.

Pusyug-

The amount of poisonous gas emitted was not very large because it was originally a shriveled air sac.

The roots and stems that were swung like a whip were also tough enough to not even cut with an aura-coated sword, but since they were dried up and twisted, the range was narrow.

‘It’s a good thing it’s a degraded version, because if I’d encountered one that lived in the blood swamp where it originated….’

Who knows, but it would have been just as grueling a fight as the one against Madam Eight-Legs in the past.

What’s more, the Daylily of Bloodswamp tends to live in colonies, and each individual is capable of exterminating the human race.

A lake of blood located deep in the abyss of polar hell.

Vikir had no idea how big the unknown darkness would be, where things like Daylilies of Blood Tree lived together.

Then.

[Human. Think about other things later!]

Decarabia’s voice warned.

Vikir snapped to attention and quickly reached out his left hand.

…Flick!

The madame cub’s web clung to the top of the collapsed tower.

Vikir soared high on it, avoiding the Daylily’s roots.

[Gigig- Kkeugigigig!]

The Daylily was growing increasingly hungry and could barely hold its head up.

However, Vikir was also unable to land any effective blows due to the Daylily’s dried and hardened skin.

Just then.

[Gigig!?]

Daylily began to react strangely.

A delicious smell wafted in from somewhere.

It smelled of blood and musty flesh.

It wasn’t a hellhound scent, but a soft, tender, savory scent.

Yes, this is the smell of human blood and flesh!

[Gya gya gya gya!]

Daylily began to move hurriedly.

The prey that had been annoying earlier also heads towards the place where the scent is emitting.

Soon, Daylily is standing in front of a large pit.

The odor was coming from below.

A freshly slaughtered piece of meat lay beneath Daylily.

Daylily quickly stretched out a vine and probed at the bottom of the pit.

…Pungdeong! Kkeunjeog-

Something warm and thick is wrapped around the tip of the vine.

Daylily thought it was right and quickly sucked them up.

Moment.

[…Giig?]

Daylily’s head tilted greatly.

The taste is somehow strange.

Daylily had been expecting tender, flavorful blood and flesh, and the smell was similar, but the taste was bland.

Daylily lifted the vine and examined its contents.

It was a large leather sack.

Expecting to find a human corpse inside, Daylily stopped dead in its tracks.

The smell was unmistakable: human blood and flesh.

The weight, too, was just about right, though slightly lighter.

But.

The leather sack contained something other than a human corpse.

Chwaaag- hududug- hududug-

Human blood, flesh, and bones spilled onto the floor.

But there was no human body in it.

What was spread on the floor was a considerable amount of blood, as well as saliva, snot, tears, and urine.

Also, there was hair that had been shaved off, nails from the hands and feet, calluses and dead skin cells removed from the elbows and heels, dirt removed from the entire body, and a significant number of teeth.

“Is it good?”

Vikir appeared like a ghost behind Daylily.

“Quite a bit, when all the byproducts of the human body are collected.”

Vikir opened his mouth to show the teeth he’d pulled from it.

Of course, it was growing quickly due to the Basilisk’s regenerative ability.

“Whenever you eat something, your skin becomes softer.”

With that, Vikir swung his sword at the Daylily as it sucked the blood from the floor.

Quack.

This time it struck.

The sword pierced the surface of the tentacle and went right through.

[Gyaaaaagh!]

As Daylily lifted its heavy flower head and roared, a single bloodshot eyeball could be seen deep in its throat.

It was blinded by extreme impatience, hunger, and anger.

“It’s finally been revealed. A vital point.”

Vikir dove into the Daylily’s gaping mouth.

At the same time, the aura swelled by the increased stats stretched out to the end of Beelzebub.

In order to inflict a fatal wound in one go, especially at the exact point, stabbing is more effective than cutting.

And because the magic sword Beelzebub had the shape of an awl, it was optimized to perform this role.

Narrow but deep. Vikir intended to end the battle with a single fatal blow.

And then the Daylily chewed him up and swallowed him whole.

Quaduk-

Just before the upper and lower jaws forcefully engage, which cannot be the case in a plant.

Phuuk-

With all his might, Vikir drove his magic sword, Beelzebub, deep into the Daylily’s throat, right into the center of its eyeball.

Pizizii!

The sound of the membrane of the eyeball being torn away and the pupil inside being punctured.

The long aura penetrated Daylily’s throat and eyeballs and extended out of the back of her head.

Udeudeug! Udeug!

Plant dietary fibers, which are much stronger than animal muscle fibers, try to crush his entire body.

Teeth harder than polymer alloys were somehow trying to squeeze the blood from Vikir’s body.

“If you want blood, I’m willing.”

At the same time, Vikir’s aura thinned and his entire body spewed Madame’s poison.

The venomous blood trickled down the inside of Daylily’s throat, through its scarred eyeballs.

[Geugig!? Geu- gi- gi- gig!]

Only then did Daylily realize something was wrong.

But it was too late.

The awl and aura that pierced the core of life, and Madame’s poison spreading to the veins of the entire body through the wound, had already decided victory or defeat.

…Thud!

The pressure on his body seemed to weaken, and his vision tilted drastically.

With a slight earthquake, the Blood Tree Daylily laid its massive body on the ground.

-Diing!

[‘Level 1 Warrior’ Vikir has successfully hunted the first ‘S-ranked Monster Blood Tree Daylily’!]

[‘Impossible’ achievements are rewarded!]

A loud notification ringing in his ears.

A mere Level 1 Newbie had defeated an S-ranked monster.

An achievement that even the tower’s system recognized as ‘impossible’.

One by one, the students who had been watching Vikir’s fight from afar appeared.

“Wow, that’s amazing…”

“I can’t believe this strategy actually works.”

“Damn, my teeth are starting to hurt.”

“I don’t have nails… Sheesh, I’m glad I’m still alive.”

They were talking about 60 kilograms worth of hair, eyebrows, beards, body hair of all kinds, blood, saliva, dead skin, grime, feces, nails, and teeth.

Some of the senior students had even cut off their own flesh.

“Good job.”

Vikir recognized their hard work.

It couldn’t have been easy to give up 500 grams of flesh each.

In the end, it was a combined effort.

A grotesque, fleshy creature appeared in front of Vikir.

The creature twitched its swollen lips and made a fuss.

[ Oh my god ? Oh my god ? A new bie fr om the 3rd under ground flo or is tak ing do wn the Blood Tree’s Daylily? Is th is my fir st ti me see ing a sce ne li ke th is ? ]

The fairy rolled the eyeball that protruded from the center of its lip and looked at Vikir.

[ Wo uld you li ke a rew ard to celeb rate? Wou ldn’t th at be gr eat? Wo uld you lo ok for ward to it? Wo uld it be a re ally gr eat rew ard ? ]

With that, the fairy closed its eyes, mumbled something, and brought its hand forward from behind its back.

In its hand was a large sack.

Whoosh.

The fairy flipped the sack over and spilled its contents onto the ground.

It was a colorful array of glowing candies.

300 red candies.

150 blue candies.

75 green candies.

That’s a whopping 525 candies.

There were also other colored candies among them.

-<Strange Candy>/ Levels / Golden

A candy that increases your level by 1.

Tastes sweet.

-Level +1

A brilliant shine that has never been seen before, and a sweet taste that can be perceived through the nose even without putting it in the mouth.

There was a golden candy that could be exchanged for 300 regular red, blue, and green candies.

There were 10 of them!

525 regular candies and 10 level candies. This was a reward so splendid that any survivor who had endured hardships so far would turn a blind eye.

In fact, Vikir had a similar reaction.

“…I can’t believe I can get this here!”

The joy, the exultation, the exhilaration, the exhilaration that would make even the most veteran of veterans tremble at the end of his voice!

Vikir’s face was even brighter than it had been when he’d gotten the silver candy, and it was clear what a tremendous sense of accomplishment he now felt.

The fairy, too, responded to Vikir’s emotion, spreading its arms wide.

[ Co me on ? Hurry ? Do you wa nt to ke ep all of th is ? It’s all for you ? ]

With that, the fairy slowly stepped back, allowing Vikir to devour the pile of candy.

As soon as Vikir had the candy in his hands, it looked like it would vanish.

However.

…Kwasik!

Vikir lunges forward and stomps on the pile of candy right in front of him.

Hududug- hudug- deguldeguldegul…

Red candies, green candies, blue candies, and golden candies scattered in all directions.

Vikir walked over to the panicked fairy and grabbed onto its body as it tried to run away.

[ Ke heulg ! ? ]

The fairy struggled to escape, but to no avail.

Vikir grabbed the pitifully shitty-looking creature by the hair and jerked it to the side.

“Where are you going? You have to give compensation.”

What caught Vikir’s gaze sharply was the worn-out sack that was in the fairy’s hand.

It was the candy bag that had spilled out a large amount of candy just moments ago.

Chapter 318

Surplus Man (7)

◆

[ Kekek? Why are you doing this? ]

The fairy shuffled about in a daze.

Vikir looked down at the puzzled expression on its face, as if it really didn’t understand.

‘It’s disgusting.’

Fairy are basically scammers.

Not only does it try to live off the achievements of the participants in the survival competition in the tower, but it also often tries to steal their rewards.

The most common type is called “pingtang”. It means embezzlement.

If you’re a newbie and you’re not getting the rewards you deserve for completing a tough mission, it’s almost always because these scammers have done something along the way.

It is common for them to steal more than 5 out of 10 under the pretext of commissions and other things, and sometimes they even boldly steal the entire reward.

The main pattern is to appear in front of the challenger, whose judgment is impaired, immediately after clearing a difficult mission, lure them in with a appropriate reward, and then disguise the real reward as scraps, scraps, by-products, or trash, remove it from the reward list, and retrieve it.

By rule, the fairy must show the challenger all of the rewards they have earned in full view of the challenger, so they can’t hide them.

Therefore, the challenger must carefully consider everything one by one.

Any rewards that the challenger fails to pick out will naturally belong to the fairy.

‘So, if you see an ultra-rare item like this, you will naturally try to steal it.’

Vikir grabbed the sack of candy from the fairy’s hand and snatched it away.

[ Ah ah ah … ]

The fairy let out a frustrated whimper.

It will be like that.

For the sack Vikir now held in his hand was an extremely rare Hidden Piece, one that was rarely found in the tower, and even the fairies had no idea how to obtain it.

-<Strange Candy Pouch ‘Conversion Worm’>/Exchange/S

Ultra-small bugs that live in the bodies of small creatures. Although it has the shape of a sack, it is actually the egg case of a parasite.

It does no harm to its host and feeds primarily on ‘strange candy’. If it doesn’t consume more than a certain amount of candy on a regular basis, it will die off naturally.

The amount of excretion is as large as the amount of food consumed, and the excrement is said to have slightly different properties from the food consumed.

-Candy Conversion (Special)

This creature eats 100 candies of the same type and excretes 1 candy of a different color.

※The color of the excreted candy is random.

‘…Pull out.’

Vikir ripped open the sack. Sure enough, there is a small parasite inside.

A small creature infected with this parasite has no health problems, but it does have one unusual ability.

It is the ability to eat candy and wrap candy.

For example, if Vikir feeds the parasite 100 red candies that increase its strength stat, the parasite will spit out a randomly colored candy.

It could be a golden candy that increases your level, a silver candy that increases your reflexes, a black candy that increases your physical resistance, a green candy that increases your agility, or a blue candy that increases your stamina.

In the latter part of the tower, you’ll find a lot of strange candies, and if you use the worm correctly, you can even turn the most common red candy into the most valuable golden candy.

If you’re lucky.

‘…Before the regression, Camus got this.’

Before the regression, Camus was obsessed with getting white candy, which boosted her Magic Resistance stat, from all the candy she got from the Conversion Worms.

As a result, she had a ridiculous Magic Resistance stat, which allowed her to ignore Mana Surge and break through dangerous limits several times.

‘But that was also obtained at the end of the journey, on the lowest floor of the tower.’

Even Vikir himself hadn’t realized he’d accomplished such a feat on the third floor.

Vikir turned his head to look back at the little madam perched on his shoulder.

“…It’s hard enough to find a small animal you can trust, so I’m glad you’re here. I would love to be the host, but my size makes it impossible, so do me a favor.”

[Hack-hack-hack-]

As Vikir stroked her, the little madam rubbed her cheek against his hand to show that she was happy.

Soon, a harmless parasite clung to her body. It settled under her chin.

She scratched at it for a while, but then forgot about it, as if it hadn’t happened.

It seems to have no effect on the host, as the description says.

“I’ll give you the stats I get in the future.”

The little madam who will eat the stat candy will also grow rapidly.

Eating and excreting are two different things.

Vikir turned his head just in case, but the pile of candies behind him had already been collected.

When the fairy was deprived of the real reward, it seemed like it was in a hurry to retrieve the rest.

Perhaps that was its entire fortune.

Still, there were a few candies still scattered about, as if it had been done in a hurry.

Vikir deliberately targeted them, kicking them as hard as he could.

“You should be grateful even if it’s just a crumb.”

Vikir picked up the candies, which were embedded in various parts of the Daylily’s body.

The fact that the daylily’s mouth had oddly shaped jagged teeth was a great help in this case.

Once he retrieved the candies that were stuck between his teeth, he had quite a collection.

15 red candies, 6 green candies, and 11 blue candies.

There were no golden candies.

Since they’re so precious, it seems like they’re the first to go.

…Poof!

Vikir pierced the Daylily’s body with the sword of Beelzebub.

After a long climb through the popped eyeballs, he could finally see out through the hole in the back of the Daylily’s flower.

When Vikir emerged, covered in all sorts of nectar, there were gasps all around.

“Oh my God, you were alive!”

“We caught a cannibal flower! We caught an S-class monster!”

“And with a body weakened 100 times!”

“What the hell is he doing, that guy….”

All the students of Colosseo Academy were shouting with joy.

However, none of them got close to Vikir.

The hound, who had just finished a bloody battle, hadn’t quite gotten the hang of his vicious aura yet.

Only one.

“Vi, Vikir, use this ragged towel, I found it in the ruins! Ah, this is a scented oil, but you can use it to wash away dirt….”

Only Granola would come up to Vikir and tend to his needs.

But Vikir didn’t mind the stares.

The first thing Vikir did when he stepped out of the Daylily was to grab two items.

-<Sunflower Seed Shrew’s Tooth Hoe>/ Farming Tools / D

A hoe made from the teeth of a large shrew.

If nothing else, it’s useful for digging up plant seeds.

-<Oil Paper Pouch>/ Pouch / D

A pouch that is quite tough and does not dissolve well in water.

It’s good for holding things because it keeps moisture out.

Vikir picked up a hoe made from a shrew’s teeth and climbed up to the flower at the head of the Daylily.

Sure enough, the center of the flower, which was supposed to be just ordinary, was densely packed with sharp seeds.

The seeds were incredibly tough and hard, and he dug them out one by one with his hoe.

…Thwack, thwack, thwack, thwack, thwack!

The seeds didn’t fall apart under Vikir’s aura and sword blows, but they came out with relative ease with the hoe made of the shrew’s teeth.

As soon as Vikir extracted the seeds, he stored them in an oil paper sack that did not dissolve well in water.

The paper sack repels moisture, so the seeds will not absorb moisture and germinate.

Looking at the silent figure, the students felt a chill run down their spines.

“Is it really possible for a level 1… to capture an S-class monster with a body weakened by 100 times?”

“Then how strong were you before you entered the tower?”

“I’m saying he was at least a Swordmaster… Is that possible at his age?”

“You know that with your own eyes.”

“So you’ve been hiding your power all this time? Why?”

“I don’t know. How can we know what a master is really like?”

A group of chickens and a crane (群鷄一鶴). Vikir didn’t pay any attention to the clucking of the many chickens.

Just then.

The fairy they thought had disappeared reappeared.

This time, the fairy seemed to be angry.

[Is th is a miss ion con trol ? Are the re 68 surviv ors ? Are th ey all go ing to st ay ali ve for fr ee ? ]

Perhaps it’s embarrassed and annoyed that it was caught trying to scam Vikir.

At the same time, a status window pops up to inform you that the mission is complete.

<Mission>– Survive 1~68 days in the ruins!

*Avoid the Daylily of Blood Tree!

Since the Daylily of Blood Tree is dead, it’s easy to survive for 68 days by gnawing on the corpse of this giant plant.

Knowing this, the fairy simply forced the mission to end.

[ Wo n’t I get in trou ble if I go on li ke th is ? Is the re a slig htly mo re challeng ing miss ion wait ing for you on the next flo or ? ]

Having finished speaking, the fairy snapped its fingers in the air.

Then a rope-like thing suddenly twitched down from the sky.

[Wo uld yo u li ke me to he lp you get to the ne xt flo or as quick ly as possib le, or do you thi nk we sho uld let so me of the peo ple who don’t deser ve to sur vive the fi re do wn a litt le bit ?]

The fairy tugs at the rope from the sky.

…Kuleuleuleuleug! Cheolsseog!

A strong current of water rushed down from the other side of the ruins, as if a toilet lever had been pulled.

“Whoa, whoa, whoaaa! What is this!”

“It’s a tsunami! Everyone run!”

“Over there! The gate to the lower level is open over there!”

“Huh! It’s small! It’s only for one person!”

“Quick! Quick! Quick! Quick! Quick!”

Students ran like crazy to avoid the approaching tsunami, sweeping away everything in the distance.

The students ran frantically to escape the oncoming tsunami that was sweeping everything away in the distance.

Looks like everyone will be swept away when they get downstairs.

[ So good bye ? ]

With the fairy’s voice ringing in their ears, all 68 survivors leapt through the gate.

It was a leap to the fourth floor.

Chapter 320

Underdogma (2)

◆

Dogma, a third-year student at Colosseo Academy, Vice President of the Student Council.

…No, Dogma, now the leader of the commoner faction.

He took the long stick he had gotten from the random box and climbed up the vine.

He sucked out the sap accumulated deep inside with a straw and put it in the bottle he had brought with him.

As he descended from the root of the Hell Tree, he was met with loud cheers from the other commoner students.

Dogma poured the sap from the jar into a rain barrel.

“It’s a little watery, but we’ll all have to share, right?”

Dogma smirked, and the other students all smiled and nodded in agreement.

However, the warm atmosphere belongs to the commoners. It was completely theirs alone.

Surplus humans who were right next to each other, but not sharing any of the warmth.

They had been nobles not so long ago.

Chained like slaves, they crawled across the floor in chains, picking up scraps of wood, guarding the campfire and sweeping up the ashes around them.

They were triplets.

Highbro Le Baskerville. Middlebro Le Baskerville. Lowbro Le Baskerville.

The trident of Baskerville’s family was here.

“….”

“….”

“….”

All three were badly beaten.

Dogma’s shadow loomed over the triplets as they labored in silence.

“Hey, you guys want some of this?”

Dogma waved a vial of watered-down sap at them.

“Then crawl over here like a dog.”

Dogma plopped down on a rotten log and snapped his fingers.

Highbro was the first to drop to the ground.

And then, crawling, crawling to the feet of Dogma.

Pugh-

Dogma kicks Hive in the face.

“Why, does it hurt to be kicked in the face by a commoner you’ve been treating like a worm?”

“….”

“You were lucky enough to be born into Baskerville, and you’ve had a nice, comfortable life of eating and wearing nice things, haven’t you?”

“….”

“But not me, I was born to penniless, powerless parents, and I’ve spent my entire life on the outside looking in. I’ve been unlucky.”

“….”

“But since I’ve been in the tower, I’ve been able to use that luck to my advantage, and I can’t believe you’d drop it after the guys next to you died.”

As he spoke, Dogma rolled a single round bead between his fingers.

Red. It was a strange candy that boosted his strength stat.

“I got lucky in the tower that I wasn’t born with. I grew stronger by consuming the candy that my friends dropped as they died. It was in this tower that I was reborn, and it taught me the hard way how important it is to start somewhere.”

Afterward, feeling a little, just a little, stronger than the students around him, Dogma worked frantically to keep that initial slight advantage.

He snatched up any candy in sight. Later, he would spearhead conflicts with the commoners who resented the nobles in exchange for a small share of their candy.

After creating and destroying a few groups, he became overwhelmingly powerful.

“You aristocrats and barons have always sucked our blood, so we should expect nothing less.”

Dogma continued to kick Highbro in the head and side with his foot.

“You told me to bring up water every time, didn’t you?”

“….”

“You told me to borrow your textbooks and gym clothes, didn’t you?”

“….”

“You copied my assignments every time, and you even turned them in before me, accusing me of plagiarism. My freshman year was the worst because no one sat next to me on school trips, no one showed me their genealogy during exams, and everyone around me just stared. It was a really bad, lonely time.”

Dogma is in third year. When he was a freshman, Highbro wasn’t even at Colosseo Academy, but no one made a big deal out of it. Because that’s not who he is.

“Gordon… I should have met that bastard inside this tower. I mean, he’s a douchebag who has nothing other than good parents, so I’m sure he’s already been dumped by hellhound or Daylily. Haha-”

Suddenly, Gordon’s voice echoes in Dogma’s head.

‘Wow, Dogma! You’re so good at drawing! Who is this? Oh, Dolores? Hey, Dolores! Look! He drew you! He likes you! Attention, classmates! Our friend Dogma has a big announcement to make! Well, he drew Dolores, and it’s …! Wow, the face is similar, but the body is a bit different from the real thing~ Isn’t it a bit exaggerated in certain areas? Aah- It’s a bit of a personal preference… Eh? Hey, what’s the matter? Why are you mad? Why are you so upset? It’s a joke. What are you going to do about the atmosphere? Why are you making a bad person out of a joke?’

A moment.

…Poof!

Dogma’s eyes lit up.

He’s capable, he’s ambitious. He was capable and ambitious.

But he’s always been held back by bad luck.

But not in this tower.

Slaves, commoners, bastards, and illegitimate children. Everyone is given equal opportunities.

The poverty and incompetence of the hated parents no longer hold them back.

You won’t fail your exams because you studied hard and the son of a rich family who gave a shit to the professor stabbed you in the back, and you won’t get pushed down in the practical evaluation by the son of a nobleman whose body is filled with all kinds of nutrients every time.

There is no longer any need for the achievements made through hard work to be treated as worthless just because the rankings were recorded low or just a few numbers were pushed out.

Everything is in your power, and you are rewarded for your efforts, and you are rewarded fairly.

We are moving away from a society where putting in even a little effort was a punishment, to a world where even if you put in a little effort, you can get a little reward.

What a wonderful world.

‘The world of demons is much more fair. It’s the right one for me.’

Dogma shuddered slightly, delighted by the reality of now.

Then.

A gurgle.

A sound from his stomach caught his attention.

Of course, it wasn’t Dogma’s stomach.

It was coming from Highbro’s stomach. No wonder he hadn’t had a sip of water in over three days.

Dogma smirked.

“Dude, if you want this, you’re gonna have to beg flatter.”

Highbro banged his head on the floor without another word.

“More.”

At Dogma’s words, Highbro sank deeper and deeper.

Until his forehead was buried beneath the sand.

And then.

“Tsk-”

Dogma spat into the sap in the jar.

He looked back and smiled.

“Friends. My friends here are hungry, too, so let’s all chip in and help them out.”

“Oh? Great!”

Then the commoner students gathered around.

More than twenty of them spit into the jar.

“I’ll give you my good stuff. Kaak-cuih!”

“Kughhhh- cuahhh.”

“You’re giving too much, there won’t be any left, haha- tcuihhh!”

“Kuaghhh! Cuahhh!”

As dozens of saliva are added to the jarred sap from the roots of the Hell Tree, bubbles bubble up.

“If you want to eat, eat. Scum.”

Dogma set it on the ground and walked away, smirking.

“….”

“….”

“….”

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro huddled around the jar.

“…Damn it. Do we have to do this, eat this? I’d rather be dead, and I’ll give my stats to my brothers. At least then we can cut off one of his wrists.”

A boiling sound came from Lowbro’s mouth.

Middlebro was silent, but seemed to agree with his brother.

But.

“….”

Highbro simply gripped the spout of the jar wordlessly.

And then.

Gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp.

Highbro drank exactly one-third of the bottle and set it down.

Middlebro and Lowbro stared at him wide-eyed, and Highbro replied nonchalantly.

“What do you think I hit you in the head for?”

His voice chillingly cold.

Highbro’s eyes flicked to his siblings.

“If you die, it’s over.”

“….”

“The idea that heroes risk their lives for their pride is an illusion created by the lesser beings. The real heroes who have made their mark on history have laughed off the humiliation of the present for the sake of the opportunity.”

The Warring States Period.

Before the continent was united, in the maelstrom of warfare that saw hundreds of countries rise and fall in a single day, many great men and women made their mark on history.

Among them were those whose personal lives were less than honorable.

They sold their bodies to old sodomites to raise money for the military, crawled under the crotches of tramps to catch their enemies off guard, changed fathers three times, boiled their sons to satisfy the tastes of their monarchs, ate their enemies’ feces as physicians, tended to their health, and sought out assassination opportunities,

These men willingly endured humiliation to become the great heroes of history.

“They say revenge is a fruit best eaten cold. Better late than never.”

Middlebro and Lowbro nodded at Highbro’s words.

“ …I wish we hadn’t discriminated against or harassed the commoners in the first place.”

“Well, we didn’t, the others did, and we had a pretty harsh childhood too, with some of our brothers dying.”

Middlebro and Lowbro swallowed the sap, which was even more phlegmatic.

They had to eat something like this to survive.

“…I suppose this is better than the haggis we used to eat back home.”

“Mmm. I’d have to agree with you on that.”

“Me too.”

And then.

“ …Well, maybe not.”

An eerie voice came from right behind them.

The triplets turned to see the underdog they’d thought was gone, staring down at them with bloodshot eyes.

“I came by just in case, but I didn’t think you’d actually eat it.”

“….”

“You’re a dangerous bunch. You know how to endure the now for the future….”

The underdog is also a smart guy. He came from a humble background and served as the vice president of the student council.

That’s why he knows better.

‘Some people with good origins have venom as well? That can’t be possible! Venom is the exclusive preserve of underdogs like me! Why do you guys even have this! You already have it all! At least get fat and be stupid! Only then can I despise you and be mentally superior to you!’

Several thoughts raced through Dogma’s mind.

A moment.

“…!”

Dogma’s eyes met Highbro.

But Highbro’s gaze was not on Dogma.

His eyes were on something farther away, something much higher. What could it be?

The Great Work? A great destiny? Something sublime, born of nobility, something he, a commoner, could not even know existed?

The eye of dreams. The dimensions of virtue. The strength of guts. Different levels of looking at the present and envisioning the future.

Dogma felt it in Highbro’s dying gaze.

And he struggled once more.

‘Trash who has nothing but luck!’

But Dogma himself knew better.

He saw himself looking down on the achievements of people from noble families, treating them as nothing more than luck, and even viewing them in a reverse discriminatory way.

He also realized that the character, grit, guts, discernment, pride, and other intangible assets that some of the noble factions in the tower had displayed… could not be replaced by stats.

‘From here on out, we, the Aristocrats and Barons, will take over.’

‘Stay out of the way. The stronger ones will lead the way.’

‘Run, you weaklings! You’re dead! I’ll show you what Noblesse Oblige is!’

‘…Everyone, avoid me while I become a prey!’

Several familiar voices rang in Dogma’s ears as he fled from hellhounds, and the Daylily of Blood Tree, their backs glimpsed in his frantic flight.

“…No, it can’t be, this world is perfectly fair. I will be compensated for everything.”

Dogma drew a well-honed longsword from his waistband.

He was ready to cut the triplets down at a moment’s notice.

Seeing the fleshy tip of the sword, Highbro shrugged, as if he had no choice.

“There is no choice. The only way is for two of us to die and have our stats go to one person.”

“ …There is no choice.”

“…There is no choice.”

Finally, the triplets agreed for the first time in a long time.

Just then.

“Hey! What are you!?”

The shrill cry came from beyond the pile of rotting bushes.

It came from the guys who had gone to scoop up the sap.

“Who the hell drank that sap!”

“This time it was our turn!”

“Wherever he came from, he stole ours!”

The sap is the only food and resource on the island. Touching it is the biggest taboo.

Even Dogma turned and ran in panic.

And then.

“…!”

“…!”

“…!”

The Baskerville triplets’ eyes widened.

A familiar face. A lord they would follow for the rest of their lives, even if he was their half-brother. A man who, despite his level, stats, and anything else, was strong in his own right.

“…Where are the rest of the survivors?”

Vikir had appeared.

Chapter 323

Underdogma (5)

◆

‘Fucking world.’

Dogma, a freshman. He was on his way out of the professor’s office after receiving a D grade on the assignment he had spent three nights working on.

Explaining that someone else had plagiarized his work didn’t work.

Instead, despite being the victim of plagiarism, Dogma received the lowest grade and failed the class.

‘Is this what life is like for commoners, to be trampled underfoot by nobles? Fuck this world.’

On a deserted road, a few stray dogs run away from human footsteps.

Dogma curses at the sky in the pouring rain.

Suddenly, the rain stops.

He turns around and sees a white umbrella wrapped around his head.

A female student with a bag of dog food in her hand was putting the umbrella on Dogma.

Dolores, the nameplate on her chest patch read.

‘That’s not true.’

Dolores opened her mouth with a smile that felt somewhat sad.

‘Everyone is the hero of their own life, and the hero is often burdened with troubles, worries, guilt, and burdens. It’s the same for everyone in the world, noble or commoner.’

Dogma was stunned.

Is that true? Is that really true?

…No. I’ve been fooled by that sort of thing before. I’m not falling for it anymore.

‘You can say that because you have everything. You’re pretty, you’re fit, you’re young, you’re well educated, you have money, you come from a good family. I’m sure you’ll graduate with flying colors and go back to your family and make it big, and you’ll meet someone equally handsome, tall, fit, good-natured, rich, and from a good family, and you’ll live happily ever after!’

Dogma’s rant, echoing through the rain shower, was like a scream.

A sharp hatred that shot out like an arrow without a target.

But Dolores only smiled bitterly.

‘…No.’

A short answer.

Dogma couldn’t help but go blank again at the sight of Dolores’ smile.

He couldn’t help but feel a chill run down his spine whenever he saw that look on her face.

‘Don’t smile like that.’

For the next three years, Dogma tried his hardest to keep a straight face.

Always hovering around Dolores, desperately trying to stand in the same place, at the same eye level.

Second in class. Student Council Vice President.

He rose to a remarkable position from a commoner background.

…But inside him, a thousand fires of unknown origin simmered, never extinguished.

Why? Why?

After pondering for a while, Dogma soon realized the reason.

The reason was…

◆

[ What was that? ]

Dogma’s mouth opened and a grotesquely distorted voice spilled out.

The pronunciation from the mouth, which was no longer human, was similar to that of a grotesque flesh fairy.

[ Why was I getting angry? ]

Dogma, who had become a majin, seemed to have lost much of his vaunted intelligence.

“…Hmm. You’re getting quite a bit bigger.”

Vikir lifted his head, resting his chin.

Dogma’s body had become quite grotesque.

Two of its limbs had grown longer than its legs, and a whip-like tail had grown from its buttocks.

Its entire body is covered with large shark scales, its forehead has a large single horn, and underneath it is a feast of teeth sticking out of its lipless mouth.

Most impressive of all was the massive mane of flames that burned Dogma’s entire body.

<Majin ‘Inferiority complex like deterioration’>.

Danger rating: A+.

Size: 8 meters

Found in: Hell Tree, Underground Level 4 ‘Black Sea Island’

-Also known as ‘Inferiority Complex’ or ‘Underdogma’

The perverse form of a student who has always been at a disadvantage in school.

They harbor a hatred so powerful that they want to set the world on fire.

There seems to be no possibility of ever becoming human again.

‘This is how they would be described if they were in a book.’

Information on humans who have been transformed into monsters is so fragmented and varies greatly from person to person that it is not included in the monster encyclopedia, but Vikir was able to infer enough information on his own.

[Geu-aaa… geugigig!]

Meanwhile, Dogma, who had become a Majin, stood on the sandbank, spewing out terrifying killing intent.

Cheolsseog! Puswiiiig-

A large wave crashed into Dogma’s body, vaporizing it into black water vapor in an instant.

“You’ve become a nuisance.”

Vikir pressed his temples.

He had defeated the Daylily of Blood in the previous stage, but it was only a Degradation Version, and the Cerberus he had defeated in the stage before that had been aided by Ginkgo and Perfume.

“…There isn’t much manpower available.”

The students of the commoner faction were too low in level and stats to be of any help, and the insectking were shivering in the distance as if they were afraid of fire.

[Hahahaha- the insectking are basically insect and afraid of fire, moreover, it is more vulnerable to fire due to the wax component coated on the surface of the exoskeleton.]

“Not very useful information.”

Vikir held Decarabia in one hand and the Beelzebub in the other.

“Well, fire can be put out with water.”

Fortunately, isn’t this a beach?

Then.

Whoosh.

There was the sound of something moving next to him.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro. The three of them were running backwards, away from Vikir’s side.

[What? Are they running away? You say lord, lord, but you have no faith. This is what humans are…]

“Probably not running away.”

[What? Then what…]

Decarabia is about to express disbelief.

Behind him, he hears Highbro shouting.

“You worthless bastards, get out all the candy you’ve got!”

The three Baskerville brothers regained their strength after drinking from the blood fountain.

However, they themselves knew well that their weakened bodies were of little help to Vikir.

A person who understands a topic well can be of great help in solving problems, regardless of their level of power.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro created an atmosphere of fear and tore up all the extra strange candies the commoner students had in their possession.

The insectking were happy to oblige.

“My lord, we’ve got candy, come on!”

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro placed the candy at the mouth of the sandbar and quickly retreated.

[Those guys, they’re good for something?].

“So you reaped.”

Vikir nodded toward the triplets.

He could see their faces light up.

Quack, quack, quack!

The flames of inferiority spewed by Dogma began to burn the entire sandbar.

The grains of sand melt into a sticky substance, emitting a glittering light.

“You’re quite strong for a majin who appeared so early in the game. I hope we don’t have to face you again.”

If it’s bad enough that a mere Dogma-level human was demonized, what if a human with hero-level power and potential was demonized?

It was horrifying to think about.

Soakduk-

Vikir unleashed an aura and severed one of Dogma’s ankles.

Grumble!

As soon as he felt his body was on fire, he jumped into the shallow water and took a dip.

The water of the Black Sea was cold and heavy enough to chill even Dogma’s hot inferiority complex.

…Boom!

Waves bursting with explosions, and a huge amount of water vapor.

Vikir ran across the sandbar to avoid it.

Grabbing the candy the triplets had thrown at him, Vikir swallowed it whole.

The status bar immediately changed.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’, ‘Hell Dog’, ‘Daylily Lumberjack’ (NEW)

-Stats.

Strength: 260 (+40) = 300

?Agility: 229 (+31) = 260

?Stamina: 269 (+31) = 300

?Physical Resistance: 1

??: (Unlocked)

?Reflexes: 1

For now, he has his Strength and Stamina at 300, and his Agility stats up as high as they can go.

‘I’ll save the rest of the candy and use it to get the ‘big three’ stats.’

The little remaining candy was stocked up for now.

For now, it was enough to raise his strength and stamina to 300.

…Wiggle!

His strength was much stronger than before, and he was ready for the day of Beelzebub.

Even though he hasn’t leveled up, his stats have risen considerably, making him more powerful.

This was enough to inflict a fatal wound.

Flash!

4th Baskerville Form. Compared to the 8th, it’s child’s play, but Vikir’s 4th is different.

Even Cane Corso, a master of the 9th Form, recognized the 4th Form of Vikir.

His skill was unrivaled.

Puff-puff-puck!

Four teeth ferociously ripped at Dogma’s throat.

[Gigi- keugh!]

Dogma vomited up a huge amount of blood.

The bubbling blood immediately sank to the bottom as it hit the surface of the Black Sea.

[He-agghhhhh!]

Enraged, Dogma relentlessly chased after Vikir.

Vikir calmly entered the sea and lured the dogma away.

Bwaek-bwak!

Dogma, whose wrists and ankles were cut off by Vikir spinning around his body, fell into the water of the Black Sea.

“Cool off there.”

Vikir cut off the rest of Dogma’s limbs so that he could not escape.

Struggling.

Dogma struggled with tremendous force, but with only his head, body, and tail left, he was unable to pull himself up.

The water was just deep enough to completely submerge Dogma’s body, so he continued to sink until he was less than half a foot from the tip of his nose.

“They say the water in the Black Sea is not buoyant.”

Vikir swam up onto the sandy shore.

He could see the water bubbling in the distance, indicating that Dogma was struggling.

But the water is just deep enough that Dogma can’t keep his head above water.

Black water, water that must sink once it falls into it.

Vikir stood on the beach, keeping a close eye on Dogma.

…Finally, how much time has passed?

Bubble Bubble Bubble- Puswiiiiig-

The water stopped boiling.

The erupting steam was gone.

The water was once again calm.

The thing struggling inside was dead.

“…Drowned.”

Vikir muttered in a hushed voice.

-Ding!

The sound of mission completion was heard.

-Ding!

[‘Level 1 Warrior’ Vikir has successfully hunted the first ‘A+ Ranked Majin, ‘Inferiority Like Deterioration’]!

[‘Awesome’ achievement reward granted!]

<Mission End>– Let’s kill a Majin!

-Majin (1/1)

※…??? …How did you really catch this one?

Next, a fairy appeared, its complexion hardened.

It lifted Dogma’s cold body from the black water and stuck out its tongue.

The fairy swooped down to Vikir and offered him his reward for capturing the demon.

[ Ah, you did it all by yo ur se lf ? ]

It was 10 level candies.

A strange, golden, glowing candy fell into Vikir’s hand.

[ Th at’s it ? ]

“Wait.”

Vikir called out to the disappearing fairy.

“Do you have access to a candy store?”

[ Wh at ? Why ? ]

“I want to sell level candy, with normal stats.”

The fairy scratched its head.

A normal challenger would collect 300 normal stat candies to buy one level candy.

But for Vikir, it was the other way around.

At most, Vikir would trade 10 level candies for 3000 regular candies.

For the fairy, it was a transaction that had no reason to refuse since it was a surplus business.

Soon, Vikir had over 3,000 regular candies in his hand.

Most of them were red strength candies, as candies are traded at random.

Including the ones from the commoner students and the insectking, there were just over 3100.

‘It’s gacha time.’

Vikir continued to feed the little madam on his shoulder with stat candies.

[Nyamnyamnyamnyam- hack hack hack-]

The little madam ate the candies, excited to see if it tasted good.

Eventually, she ate all 3,000 candies and pooped out 30 candies.

Vikir was disappointed when he saw the colors of the candies coming out of the little madam’s butt.

Mostly red strength candies, blue stamina candies, and the occasional green agility candy.

But it’s obviously better to increase Strength by 100 than to increase Agility by 1, so Vikir’s gacha continues to take a heavy toll.

By this point, Vikir had burned through all 3,000 candies.

The harvest is about 10 agility candies.

The rest were all power and stamina candies that were no better than crap.

There are only 90 candies left, so he can’t run the gacha anymore.

“No luck this time. No, this is how it’s supposed to be.”

Vikir decided to give up cleanly. He knew his expectations were too high in the first place, so he shouldn’t be too disappointed with the outcome.

…Just then.

“Lord. I still have 12 candies left.”

Highbro grabbed a bloodstained candy from somewhere and held it out.

“What’s this.”

“These are the students on Dogma’s side that he killed when he was demonized earlier. I dug them out from under a pool of sap.”

Vikir nodded. He hadn’t realized it, but this would allow him to spin the gacha one more time.

‘I hope it’s not Strength or Stamina again. If it’s any of the three stats, it’ll be great….. and if it’s not, it should at least be Agility.’

Vikir fed the little madam another 100 candies.

Then.

[Kkeung-]

The little madam began to twitch.

And then.

…Pop!

A candy dropped onto Vikir’s palm.

It was the purest, whitest candy he’d ever seen.

-<Strange Candy>/ Magic Resistance / White

A candy that increases your Magic Resistance stat by 1.

Tastes sour.

+1 to Magic Resistance

Eventually, Vikir’s mouth drew a line, even if only slightly, when he saw the candy’s explanation window.

“Lucky.”

Good, but not just good.

Chapter 325

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea (2)

◆

“Doesn’t that mean you don’t actually have a ship?”

Highbro asked in disbelief.

The Insectking flinched slightly, then retorted.

[… Of course there is, because it’s sunk beneath the sea].

It seems like they have decided to go out shamelessly.

“No, what do you think you’re doing with a sunken ship, you beetles, trying to scam me!”

Highbro snarled, and the beetles glanced over at Vikir.

Then.

“Enough.”

Vikir interrupted them all.

That wasn’t what mattered now.

“Did you know that the Black Sea has no buoyancy, so everything sinks?”

[That’s right, that’s why very few creatures can survive in the Black Sea].

Hearing the Insectking words, Vikir turned his head and looked at the black horizon.

The bottom of that vast sea must be utterly empty.

Even if unique creatures occasionally live, the distance between each individual is probably very long.

A dark sea of emptiness. Down there, the ships of the Insectking are sunk.

“If it’s sunk, isn’t it a ship that can’t sail in the Black Sea?”

[No, our ships float on the surface of the Black Sea].

The Insectking unfolded their black armor and the thin wings beneath it.

They were light and strong, with a waxy coating on the outside that helped them float.

[The long-standing conflict between the stag beetle tribe and the rhinoceros beetle tribe resulted in numerous casualties. We collected the remains of the fallen and built a ship, which was light and strong enough to sail even on the surface of the Black Sea. It sank after a dispute over ownership….]

“Why exactly did it sink?”

[Well, that’s because… one day a group of Insectking ambushed the ship, seized it, and set sail, only to stop after crossing the center of the Black Sea…]

The story of the Insectking that followed was unbelievable.

“…Hmm. Now I know what’s been happening.”

He could see why the elders looked troubled.

Vikir sprang into action.

“First, we will raise the sunken ship. Tell me exactly where the ship sank.”

◆

The Black Sea was calm.

But off in the distance, on the horizon, a fierce gale is raging.

It’s like a wall that keeps challengers out of the area.

But Vikir did not cross the sea.

…With a plop!

He simply sank deeper into it.

Gurgling.

Foam and bubbles crashed before his eyes, and within seconds, his vision went black.

But it didn’t matter.

Vikir could see dozens of meters in the dark.

It was a secondary ability he’d acquired after two years of honing his archery and hunting skills in the jungles of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Kkuleuleug- gulug…

The further down he went, the more the pressure on his body.

The heavy space seemed to want to crush him.

He felt like he was falling into a pool of ice-cold water.

There is almost no buoyancy, so even if he stays still, he sinks.

Huuk-.

The oxygen was getting low. Due to the high water pressure on his lungs, his oxygen consumption was much faster than normal water.

‘At least it’s not as bad as the Styx, where I almost drowned.’

Vikir searched his arms, thinking about various things in his mind.

Then, in his hand, he felt a bulging pouch.

-<Oil-blotting paper pouch that does not dissolve well in water>/ Pouch / D

A pouch that is quite tough and does not dissolve well in water.

It repels moisture, so it’s good for holding things.

The bag was full of air.

Vikir sucked on it with a straw and then put it back in his arms.

He didn’t float, even with the air-filled pouch, because it wasn’t buoyant.

Often, when he couldn’t breathe, Vikir sank deeper and deeper into the sea, sucking in the air in his pouch.

Then.

Decarabia clinging around his chest pocket called out to him.

[Hey, human].

‘Why.’

[You didn’t really need to join hands with the Insectking, did you?]

Decarabia pointed to the mission status window floating in the corner of Vikir’s vision.

<Mission>– Capture the Sap Pool!

※Steal the sap pool from the scary ship owners and survive!

It was a struggle to steal the sap fountain from the previous guests who had arrived inside the tower first, that is, the Insectking race.

That’s actually the mission on this floor.

But Vikir had a different interpretation.

‘I think it means something different. Perhaps it refers to the ship’s owner, the master of the ship.’

[Hmm. In that case, the completion of the mission would definitely depend on the presence or absence of a ship].

‘Right. I’m sure there are other ways to clear this floor. Like I did with the Daylily of Blood Tree on the 3rd floor.’

As he continue the conversation, he suddenly saw the floor.

A forest of dead trees. Formerly otherworldly terrain, sunk beneath the waters of the Black Sea.

It was like looking at a forest of skewered trees rising above the dead coral reefs.

It was a grim scene that seemed to symbolize the evil intent in the demon’s mental world.

As he descended to a certain depth, Decarabia on his chest responded.

[Human, look down the hill].

There, in the deep valley beneath the towering trench, was something.

It was the ‘ship’ that emerged from the darkness of the deep sea.

A black, glossy ship, its sails woven from insect wings, still flapping in the current.

The black ship, still and submerged, looked quite sleek and sturdy.

Vikir pushed through the heavy current and approached the stern.

The bow began to reveal its overall outline, starting with its massive, pointed tip.

There were some pretty nasty scratches here and there, including on the deck and hull, but the keel, the ship’s spine, was still intact.

Despite being in the water for so long, there was very little seaweed or sphagnum moss.

The only serious problem is the large hole in the hold and lower part of the ship wall.

‘Water must have gotten in through those holes and sunk the ship.’

Vikir glad it didn’t sink due to lack of buoyancy.

It’s a hole, it can be salvaged and filled.

Then Decarabia asked.

[But how are you going to get that huge ship up there?]

Decarabia didn’t seem to understand Vikir’s plan.

[It would be impossible with human strength, even with all the twenty men on the island and the thirty Insectking. They wouldn’t even be able to get down here in the first place…]

‘Hmm. I’ve thought about that.’

Vikir swam a little faster.

There wasn’t much air left, so he had to hurry.

‘…And there’s one other thing we need to watch out for.’

Soon, Vikir was standing in front of a huge sailing ship.

A ship that sank at the bottom of darkness, in a vast void.

The creaking planks and ominously fluttering sails beneath the quiet seabed make this ship look like a ghost ship.

‘Okay then, let’s carry out the salvage work as soon as possible.’

Vikir throws up his arms.

Kii-gigigigig…

An unpleasant noise came from somewhere.

A mysterious sound from the other side of the ship.

Vikir looks up and sees something emerge from the darkness in front of him.

“…!”

Shark scales covering its entire body, a horn sprouting from its forehead, a gaping mouth full of teeth.

This was Dogma, who had been transformed into a Majin.

The flames that wrapped around his body like a mane had already been extinguished, but his hideous appearance remained.

‘No wonder it sank to this place.’

Vikir clicked his tongue and readied himself for battle.

….This?

Thud-thud-thud-thud-thud.

Something was strange.

Dogma appeared through the darkness, trembling slightly with only his upper body sticking out, but other than that, he showed no movement.

And then.

…Tud!

Soon, Dogma’s head, buried in the darkness, fell to the bottom of the sea.

The upper body disappears in an instant, buried in darkness, and only the head, with only the horns and teeth remaining, rolls down the trench and disappears from view.

‘….’

Vikir tore his gaze away from Dogma’s head and stared into the darkness again.

Sssssss…

Upon closer inspection, the darkness in which Dogma’s body was buried seemed to be moving slowly.

It wasn’t a shape, but the darkness itself, rising up from the bottom.

‘Now that I think about it, strangely, that part is particularly dark.’

There is a faint light on the other side, but the enormous darkness approaching this direction is pitch black, with nothing visible.

And Vikir recognized it immediately.

The darkness that was now overtaking them was an absolute terror that could not even be compared to hellhounds, Cerberus, or Daylily from the previous stages.

‘…I see, so this one was living here.’

Danger level S rank, a real threat that has not been affected by deterioration or anything like that.

This was the moment when the ‘core of darkness’ was revealed.

Chapter 326

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea (3)

◆

[The long-standing conflict between the stag beetle tribe and the rhinoceros beetle tribe resulted in numerous casualties. We collected the remains of the fallen and built a ship, which was light and strong enough to sail even on the surface of the Black Sea. It sank after a dispute over ownership….]

‘Why exactly did it sink?’

[Well, that’s because… one day a group of Insectking ambushed the ship, seized it, and set sail, only to stop after crossing the center of the Black Sea…]

Vikir remembered the conversation he’d had with the Insectking.

Before diving into the depths of the Black Sea, the Insectking had made him a few promises, promises that a lesser challenger would not have believed.

[I met a monster].

‘You’re a monster, too.’

[‘It’ was more than that. It was a primordial creature that had been dragged here from a very, very long time ago … and as long as it remained at the bottom of the sea, it would be impossible to cross the Black Sea, even with the best ships].

From the sound of it, it seemed that the Insectking were trapped in the Black Sea, four levels underground, and it wasn’t just because of the winds that swirled around the area.

And now Vikir was seeing with his own eyes that it was true.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

A great darkness loomed before Vikir’s eyes.

It looks like a part of the abyss has broken away, like a mass, and is swimming on its own.

But closer inspection reveals it to be a translucent mass that penetrates the darkness on the other side.

A hemispherical mass with an unimaginably large diameter.

It had a translucent, shapeless body and was approaching with countless tentacles dangling from the base of the mass.

A being that floats aimlessly in a dark void that cannot see an inch ahead, with its body stained by the darkness of the deep, deep sea.

<Shadowless King of the Black Sea>

Danger Rating: S

Size: ?

Found in: Polar Hell, the five oceans ‘Black Sea’, the ultra-deep part of the ‘Great Heart Sea’

-Aka ‘Shadowless King of the Black Sea’

A large jellyfish that inhabits the Black Sea, one of the five oceans in the Polar Hell.

It is a primordial creature that lives in the Great Heart Sea, an area that even high-ranking demons are reluctant to enter, and its ecology is completely shrouded in mystery.

It is also unknown where it came from, where it is going, and why it is floating in the void of nothingness.

‘The Shadowless King of the Black Sea’

This massive jellyfish exudes an aura of menace that is almost as intimidating as that of the “Madame of the Eight Legs,” a foe he once faced in the Red&Black Mountain.

‘…Hmm, I don’t think this one can be controlled even with the power of Amdusias.’

Vikir thought for a moment.

The Daylily of Blood Tree that he had faced in the previous stage had been degraded by prolonged starvation.

Also, since the demon Amdusias itself is naturally friendly to plants, it would not have been too much of a problem to catch and control the Daylily of Blood Tree.

However, the Shadowless King of the Black Sea in front of him was different.

It was an absolute power on the same level as the Madam Eight-Legs he’d fought before, and even if it was an unintelligent monster, it wouldn’t be able to be controlled by a demon at this point.

In other words, the giant jellyfish in front of him is not under the control of Amdusias, but is a pioneer creature that lives here on its own.

As such, it was unlikely that there would be any reward for capturing it.

Then.

Shiriririk…

Suddenly, Vikir felt a tickling sensation on his cheek.

Instinctively, Vikir jerked his head back, and a translucent tentacle fluttered past his eyes.

Crunch!

The tentacle clung to a boulder for a moment, then shattered it with tremendous force.

‘This won’t be fun if I get caught.’

Vikir quickly stepped back and drew his magic sword, Beelzebub.

Thwack!

He swung the sword randomly, and it hit in several places.

Three tentacles were cut off and fell to the ground.

‘They were wrapped around me without a sound.’

They were translucent and hard to see.

Vikir strained his eyes.

Then he saw three tentacles with severed ends, stealthily drawing back.

Kkumulkkumulkkumul…

New tentacles sprouted from the severed ends.

Apparently it has the ability to regenerate.

‘If so.’

Vikir pushed on the end of Beelzebub’s tentacle.

…Snap!

One of the tentacles that had been sneaking up on his back was sliced off again by Vikir’s blow.

However, this time, the severed tentacle did not regenerate.

The end of the tentacle dried up and curled into a ball.

Seeing this, Vikir flicked the edge of his magic sword, Beelzebub, once.

‘That’s good enough for now.’

The ability to dry up a jellyfish’s tentacles was a relatively recent skill.

<Binge Fly ‘Beelzebub’>/ Awl

-Slot 1: Deadly Venom -Madam Eight-Legs (S)

-Slot 2: Unkillable -Basilisk (S)

-Slot 3: Starvation Drought – Blood Daylily (S)

The Starvation Drought ability is obtained by capturing a Daylily of Blood.

Beelzebub’s sword, which grants dryness through its Drought and Starvation abilities, was evaporating a large amount of moisture every time it grazed the jellyfish’s tentacles.

The jellyfish’s hydrated tentacles curled up as if they were about to be roasted.

Puff, puff, puff!

The Shadowless King of Black Sea stopped trying to get closer to Vikir and began to whip it tentacles, creating a giant windstorm.

‘The waves on the surface are being created by this thing?’

The giant jellyfish’s turbulent currents spewed out of its twisting tentacles, creating a whirlpool.

The current, as heavy as molten iron, spun around, creating an effect like a saw blade.

…Ppuppug! Ujijijijig!

Vikir’s flesh bursts open.

His entire body was torn apart, as if he had been sliced open by countless blades.

However, Vikir was able to recover most of his body thanks to the Unkillable ability he extracted from the Basilisk’s corpse.

In addition, the large amount of blood that Vikir spilled immediately turned black and flowed into the waters of the Black Sea.

Even the Shadowless King of the Black Sea couldn’t help but be stunned as the “venomous” blood of Madam Eight-Legs spread around it.

Meanwhile, Vikir took out Decarabia’s shield and used it like a surfboard.

…Kurrrrr!

Vikir blazed through the raging water currents.

Vikir swam toward the sunken ship on the ocean floor with his momentum.

Decarabia looked puzzled.

[Human, you don’t stand a chance against that jellyfish, not in your current form!]

“I know.”

[If you knew, you’d run away, but why are you going towards that ship? You can’t even salvage it with your current strength!]

Literally.

A giant ghost ship in front of him, and the Shadowless King of the Black Sea behind him. Neither of them are within Vikir’s power.

The ship is too heavy for him to lift alone, and the Shadowless King of the Black Sea is too powerful for him to face alone.

But Vikir was nonchalant.

‘We still have a little time.’

Pulling the pouch of air from his arms, Vikir inhaled the last of it.

Kkugis-

And with that, the pouch was empty.

-<Oil-blotting paper pouch that does not dissolve easily in water>/ Pouch / D

A pouch that is quite tough and does not dissolve well in water.

It has the power to block moisture, so it is good for storing things.

Vikir crumpled it in his hands and tossed it into the hole in the sunken ship’s hull.

Shhhhhh…

Even at that moment, the Black Sea Shadowless King was casting countless tentacles toward Vikir.

Decarabia spoke a little more urgently.

[Human, they’re coming from all directions, I don’t want to be buried in a place like this!]

‘Neither do I.’

[What are you going to do, then? Escape is out of the question! We have no choice but to salvage that ship! But you are powerless…]

However, Decarabia could not persuade Vikir to stay.

…Kukung!

With a heavy noise, the ship sunk in the depths of the ocean began to shake.

[Huh?]

As Decarabia rolled its eyes in bewilderment, the ship slowly began to rise from the bottom.

Koo-koo-koo-koo-koo…

Rocks and mud rained down from the bottom of the ship.

The ghost ship, which had been sunk for a long time at the bottom of the deep sea, floated on its own, heading for the surface of the Black Sea without any buoyancy.

‘It’s about time.’

As if he had been waiting, Vikir grabbed the anchor line hanging from under the ghost ship’s dock.

And then it began to rise toward the surface, following the ship at an incredible speed.

Ts-ooooooh…

The tentacles that had been curling toward Vikir flailed about, lost and disoriented.

[Uh, what’s going on, human, why is this ship floating on its own?]

Decarabia squinted its single eye at Vikir for an answer.

But soon, Vikir didn’t need to answer.

The answer was right there in front of him.

…Pow!

Something jutted out of the hole in the ghost ship’s hull.

It was like a giant balloon.

It was filling up the inside of the ship, pushing it upward!

It didn’t take Decarabia long to realize the identity of the balloons filling the ship’s interior.

[…Air Sacs!]

That’s right.

They were air sacs that aquatic plants such as water hyacinth built into their bodies to create buoyancy.

“Daylily of Blood Tree”.

Its seeds were now germinating in the belly of the ghost ship!

Chapter 327

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea (4)

◆

-<Oil-blotting paper pouch that does not dissolve easily in water>/ Pouch / D

A pouch that is quite tough and does not dissolve well in water.

The phrase “does not dissolve well in water” can also mean dissolves in water.

Vikir sucked air into this pouch and waited for it to dissolve.

Slowly, like a lump of starch thrown into water, the sachet dissolves, slightly sticky.

Time after time, it was unraveling, crushed by the heavy water pressure of the black water.

And when the air had been sucked out of it, Vikir crumpled it up and tossed it into the ghost ship, which was actually loaded with one more item besides air.

Seeds from the remains of the Daylily of Blood.

The pouch was filled with daylily seeds that had been plucked out with a hoe made from a shrew’s teeth.

The pouch was a Grade D miscellaneous item, so it didn’t last long in the harsh environment of the Black Sea.

And when the pouch was released into the grass, the seeds inside met the waters of the Black Sea.

‘…For an item from a rarity box, it was useful.’

Vikir thought to himself as he watched the Daylily seeds grow in the hold of the floating ship, sucking up water at an alarming rate.

Swoosh!

In the blink of an eye, the Daylily seeds stretched out their stems and roots, creating a series of plump balloons.

The Daylily of Blood Tree that Vikir had dealt with hadn’t been able to grow their air sacs properly due to the extreme dryness, but the Daylily that bloomed in the Black Sea was different.

Once it had absorbed the water, the Daylily inflated its air sacs at a tremendous rate, and they were filled with light gases that gave it enough buoyancy to float even in the black sea water.

‘It’s salt water, so it won’t grow much, but it’ll grow enough to make an air sac.’

[…Yes, indeed! This is the Black Sea, heavy, cold, briny water. The Daylily will not grow to a dangerous size. They’ll grow just enough to be useful. Good choice of location].

While Decarabia admired in a rather chatty tone, Vikir was already soaring into the heart of the sea.

And then.

…Thunk!

The ship suddenly tilted sideways.

Vikir, who was hanging on the anchor line hanging below the dock, also almost fell to the bottom.

Kkigigigigigig-

An uncomfortable sound is heard throughout the ship’s body.

It tipped sideways, its contents raining down on them.

The heavy cargo of crates and oak barrels, swords and halberds, sank over Vikir’s head.

Vikir charged his sword with aura and swung, clearing away the debris that fell like snow.

[There’s something up there!]

Decarabia shouted.

Vikir nodded in agreement.

‘It’s the Shadowless King of the Black Sea. It must have come up and blocked the ship.’

The rising ship was halted by a giant jellyfish blocking its path.

But it didn’t matter. It was just what Vikir had hoped for.

Grabbing the anchor line, Vikir scrambled up the ship’s mast and jumped onto the watchtower.

Pupupupug!

He landed dozens of blows on the jellyfish’s body, which appeared to be a dark mass.

[…! …! …! …!]

The Black Sea Shadowless King jerked back in surprise at the stinging sensation.

But it was too late.

‘I’m glad I kept some spare.’

Vikir’s awl-like strike burrows deep into the jellyfish’s slimy body, planting the daylily’s seeds deep within.

Soon, the moisture-sucked seed began to germinate.

Syuleuleuleug-

The roots that grew inside the body pierced through the flimsy flesh of the jellyfish and took root firmly.

And the stem that grew out of the jellyfish’s body formed a cluster of air sacs with extremely strong buoyancy.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

Shadowless King of the Black Sea was the first to show signs of panic.

The air sacs that had grown outside its body were buoyant and soaring upward.

Firmly embedded in its body, the roots were connected to the air sacs by tough stems.

The Black Sea King struggled to control its body as it was forced upward, flailing its tentacles.

However, it was unable to stop the upward flow, as the jellyfish’s body does not allow it to swim fast and strong.

It was also useless to use its translucent body to hide in the darkness.

The Daylily’s air sacs and roots revealed the location of its body.

Kugung- gugugugugugu-

After a brief pause, the ship began to rise again.

This time, Shadowless King of the Black Sea was also there.

Vikir, which pulls the entire ship and the King of the Black Sea to the surface!

However, the King of the Black Sea would not be deterred.

Shurirok-

It extended its tentacles in a much more vicious and aggressive manner than before.

It seemed like it was going to wrap around Vikir’s body and crush it at any moment.

However.

…Poof!

The tentacle in front of Vikir’s eyes was instantly torn apart by an unidentified force.

The other tentacles did the same.

Poof! Poof! Bang!

The Black Sea Shadowless King floundered like a marionette with a broken string as explosions ripped through its body.

Decarabia was stunned and asked.

[Human! Did you do this?]

‘No.’

Vikir shook his head.

What was now breaking down the giant jellyfish’s body was ‘hydrostatic pressure’, the difference in pressure as it floated from the depths to the surface.

When you go from deep to shallow so quickly, the difference in pressure causes all sorts of bizarre things to happen.

This is why deep-sea fish caught by fishermen and dragged to the surface are often oddly bloated.

In addition, the ‘diving disease’ that kills divers is also a phenomenon that occurs due to this pressure difference.

Vikir barely suppressed the dizziness in his head.

The protection of the Styx River, his management of his mana, and the regenerative powers of the Basilisk protected him from the pressure.

But the mollusk’s sensitivity to water and air pressure hadn’t adjusted well to the sudden change.

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea tried to return to the trench in the deepest part of the ocean, but the Daylily that had already bloomed all over his body made it impossible.

In the end.

…Boom!

The ship and Shadowless King of the Black Sea broke the surface of the water almost simultaneously.

Up in the breezy air, they could see the island in the distance, where the three Baskerville brothers and the Insectking were waiting.

“Hooray! The Lord has saved the ship!”

“He has!”

“He has!”

We see the triplets waving their hands.

[Oooh! The ship is finally back!]

[Finally! We can finally get out of here!]

[Our mission, ‘escape the island by boat’, is no longer a dream!]

The Insectking are overjoyed, too.

However.

Pfft!

The appearance of a jellyfish so gigantic that it filled the entire surface of the water turned everyone’s cheers into shock and silence.

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea.

It dragged itself to the surface, spreading its enormous body across the surface.

Just as jellyfish usually spread out like pancakes when they come out of the water, the same was true for this one.

…If anything is different.

Shurorororock!

Unlike normal jellyfish, which become lethargic as soon as they are dragged out of the water, the Black Sea Shadowless King began to extend its tentacles in a much more aggressive manner.

Parts of its body exploded and became tattered, embedded with Daylily seeds and roots, but it didn’t seem to mind as it attacked Vikir.

Hultteog-

The Black Sea Shadowless King chased after Vikir with the covers pulled back over its body.

Hundreds of gigantic, slitted eyeballs, like the eyes of a corpse, stared at Vikir in unison.

Decarabia asked.

[What are we going to do now, human? I think it’s best to run away now, right?]

If we fight this way, we will surely lose.

The size difference is too great, and this is not a good place.

If he was outside the tower, he could have fought across the sea using his master solid aura, but that’s not possible now.

Besides, he already has the ship, so there’s no need to gamble with his life.

But.

“I don’t do things without certainty.”

Vikir didn’t seem the least bit willing to back down.

“Drive the ship!”

The Insectking were there when Vikir barked the order.

They flew through the air and approached the ship, clinging to the masts and sails one by one.

[We will push the ship as it is!]

[To the island! To the island!]

[The storm is passing! Ride the wind!]

The Insectking followed Vikir’s orders and pushed the ship toward the island.

They were quite desperate, as their mission on the 4th floor was to “escape the island by boat”.

Shurororock-

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea, who interfered with the mission, stretched out its tentacles and tried to catch the Insectking race this time as it did in the past.

Ssagdug- ssagdug- ssagdug-

Vikir struck a blow, slicing off all of its tentacles.

His Graduator-class aura was a bit too weak to cut off the Shadowless King’s tentacles, but it was strengthened by the Starvation Drought ability he had stolen from the Daylily of the Blood Tree.

Swoosh.

The blurry eyeballs beneath the jellyfish’s lampshade erupted in blood.

Shadowless King of the Black Sea, was peering in their direction with roots and air sacs scattered all over its body. The far-off killing intent it exuded was enough to make even the Insectking race flying away with their ship faint for a moment.

And.

Vikir’s response to that fierce gaze was just as fierce.

…Hiss!

A single flame rises from Vikir’s fingers.

-<Fire of Inferiority ‘Fire’>/ Flint / A+

A stone that allows you to get hot embers anytime, anywhere.

It burns with the inferiority complex deep within you as firewood.

-Hotness +1,000

※Temperature may be higher or lower depending on the extent of your inferiority complex.

The last spark of Dogma’s life before he became a majin.

Vikir was holding it in his hand and digging towards the Black Sea Shadowless King.

“Let’s see how well it burns.”

Toward the air sacs of the daylily that had taken root in its body.

Chapter 330

Draw (2)

◆

[ Wh at I me an, can’t you ju st dr aw all the ne xt flo ors bef ore us ? ]

The fairy’s suggestion was outrageous.

Vikir is currently on the 4th floor, on an island in the Black Sea.

The next level he would encounter would be the 5th, and then the 6th.

But the fairy wants to make all of these levels a draw.

[ See wh at I me an ? ]

The point is this.

As Vikir goes down the floor, he will clear all the hidden stages, and there is a high possibility that he will monopolize all the monsters placed so that he cannot be caught and the hidden pieces that are placed not to be obtained.

After receiving the continuous special rewards, it is clear that he will become a power beyond the standard.

So the fairies were willing to let him skip a good portion of the floors under their jurisdiction in exchange for an average stage-clearing reward.

“So as long as I play nice, you’ll let me get to a certain section quickly, without wasting any time?”

[ Is that right? Is that what it is? ]

“What are you going to give me?”

At those words, the fairy folded two of its twelve fingers and extended the other ten.

Vikir understood immediately.

“Ten golden candies.”

[ Yes ? ]

The fairy nodded nervously. Then it added one more comment.

[ Ple ase ju st ta ke a lo ok ? If th is conti nues , wi ll I re ally go bank rupt ? ]

Then Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro shouted out.

“You bastard, where are you coming from, our lord does not compromise with such an easy path!”

“He does not compromise!”

“He does not compromise!”

But the triplets’ determined cries fell on deaf ears.

“Use more.”

Vikir was intrigued by the fairy’s deal.

“How many floors do you think you’re sending me to, and you’re only giving me ten golden candies?”

[ That that that that …… can it be a lit tle bit mo re ?]

Vikir added to the stuttering fairy.

“I’ve had enough of the candy. I have an item I want, can you get me one?”

Up until now, Vikir had always said candy was the best, but he had never needed an item.

Items that he couldn’t take out of the tower had always been low on his reward priority list.

It was a bit unusual that Vikir was now asking for items,

[ Wh at it em do you ne ed ? ]

The fairy asked in a questioning tone, and Vikir answered firmly.

“A scale of forced equality.”

Vikir says the exact name of the item he wants.

Hearing that, the fairy looked puzzled.

[ Is that a hid den pie ce that can on ly be fou nd on the 3rd flo or of the under ground ? Oops ? ]

For a moment, the fairy closed its mouth, not wanting to speak.

But Vikir had already gotten the information from the fairy’s stutter.

“I see, the item can be found on the 3rd floor of the underground, in the area with the Daylily of Blood.”

[ Haha, but that’s already the 3rd floor, right ? ]

The fairy was relieved that Vikir had already passed the 3rd underground level.

The ‘Scales of Forced Equality’ is a Hidden Piece that drops only on the 3rd underground level, guarded by the Daylily of Blood, so if you don’t get it early on, you’re done for.

However.

“In case you forgot, this is given to all who challenge the tower.”

Vikir pulled out a piece of paper.

-<Return Scroll>/ Scroll / Rank: ?

A scroll that allows you to return to the Tutorial Zone for one time only.

The answer to the question ‘Lord, where are you going?’ is written.

※Using it will reset your level

It was a scroll to return to the Tutorial Zone.

A one-time use item that allows you to start over from the first floor of the underground.

Vikir’s level is 1 anyway, so it’s not a big deal. The scroll doesn’t reset his stats.

Vikir spoke in a menacing tone.

“Thanks for the information. I’ll use this scroll to return to the tutorial floor, and once again, I’ll devour all the tricks and hidden pieces I came this far to find. Of course, I’ll have to stop by the third floor as well, because I need to find the Scales of Forced Equality.”

[ Hic ? ]

The fairy realized that it had been tricked and sulked.

Finally, with a sullen expression, the fairy dug into its bosom and pulled out a thick booklet.

<Item Catalog-Hidden Piece Edition

1. Demon Calling Flute (Stock: 8) – 500 Red Candies

2. Retribution Iron Armor (Stock: 3) – 250 green candies

3. Super Regeneration Potion (Stock: 15) – 400 blue candies

4. Sneaky Pickpocket’s Gloves (Stock: 5) – 50 green candies, 50 blue candies

5. Sword of Ten Thousand Swings Two-Handed (Stock: 2) – 1,000 red candies, 800 blue candies

6. Hourglass of Lust (Stock: 1) – 1 golden candy.

.

.

A paperback booklet containing a number of rare items.

In between was a description of the item Vikir had mentioned.

<Item Catalog-Hidden Piece Edition>

203. Scales of Forced Equality (Stock: 0) – 20 Golden Candies

An item with an incredibly high price tag. The number of golden candies required is 20.

[ More over , th ere are 0 ite ms in sto ck ? ]

The fairy looked very disappointed.

But Vikir was adamant.

“I’m sure there’s more than enough.”

[ Wh at ? No way ? ].

“I’m not asking for it, I’m paying for it.”

Vikir held out all 20 of the golden candies he’d gotten earlier.

Plus a few extra candies from the commoner students.

[ Hmmm ? ]

The fairy began to look troubled.

Vikir added a threat in a low voice.

“I’ll use a return scroll and devour all the Hidden Pieces on every floor, and then I’ll complain to the higher-ups later. I think the person in charge of the fourth floor embezzled the hidden pieces, so please conduct an inventory investigation.”

[ Ah, do I under stand ? Do you wa nt me to se ll it ? I ju st ne ed to se ll it , rig ht ? ]

The fairy cried and took the candies from Vikir.

And soon, the pages of the catalog slowly turn.

What he thought was a single page was actually two pages, cleverly stuck together.

With a murderous look on it face, the fairy tore off one of the catalog pages and handed it to Vikir.

<Item Catalog-Hidden Piece Edition

203. Scale of Forced Equality (Stock: 0) – 20 Golden Candies

※ Vendor Comment: A Hidden Piece that can only be obtained on the 3rd floor of the tower.

It has a pretty good ability, but is rarely used due to its poor price-performance ratio.

It’s pretty much useless in the early game and only comes into its own in the late game, but it’s safe to say that no one will survive the latter half of the game with this item in their possession.

Ok.

…Peong!

With a loud sound, the page in Vikir’s hand is transformed into an item.

-<Scale of Forced Equality>/ Scales / S

Your stats change according to the value of your highest stat.

The values ??of all stats gradually and slowly increase according to the value of the highest stat, and this change continues until the values ??of all stats become the same.

The scale looks quite ominous at first glance, with its skull-shaped weights and embossed scale plates.

However, the description reveals that it’s actually a pretty good stats item.

For example, if your strength stat is 10 and all other stats are 1, if you possess this scale, all of your stats will gradually increase over time along with the strength stat’s 10.

After a very long time, when all stats reach 10, the scale will be destroyed.

However, the time it took for the stats to increase was so long that the item was ultimately useless unless you were willing to spend years in the tower.

Knowing this, the fairy hesitated before accepting Vikir’s offer.

Then.

“Hmm? This?”

As Vikir placed the item in his hand, he noticed a small note enclosed.

It was about the ‘proper’ way to obtain this item.

<Item Catalog – Hidden Piece Edition>

203. Scales of Forced Equality (Stock: 0) – 20 Golden Candies

Item requirements: Challengers who have encountered the Daylily of Blood must vote to sacrifice one person per day.

However, the order in which sacrifices are selected is not from weak to weak, but from strong to strong.

Unintentionally, I even learned how to obtain the items.

‘So this is how it drops.’

Before his regression, Vikir had learned of the item’s existence from the memoirs of the tower’s former heroes.

There was a villain who had been disrupting order in the tower, a villain who had been unnoticed in the early days of the tower, but who had risen to prominence later in the tower.

The heroes of the time investigated how the villain had gained such power and soon discovered the existence of this item.

But no matter how much they researched, they couldn’t figure out how to get it, and now Vikir understood why.

‘The method of acquisition must be so gruesome that no one could have gotten it.’

It was amazing that before the regression, there had been just one person who had gotten this item.

And now.

The fairy grumbled and said.

[ Are you afraid you’re going to be taken to the 5th floor of the underground? Different fairies from the next floor? So, more vicious upper managers have emerged? It’s scary, isn’t it? Do you know that you have been fortunate enough to have met me until now ? ]

The fairy opened its mouth and a gate to the 5th floor appeared before everyone’s eyes.

Only one person could enter at a time, and it was clear that they would all end up in different places.

[ Go in one by one ? ]

The fairy looked at all the challengers, but only focused on Vikir.

Then it spoke, almost inaudibly.

[It was dirty because we were together? Let’s not see each other again ? ]

Chapter 331

The Mating Room (1)

◆

With the sound of waves hitting the sandbar and breaking into foam.

[It was dirty because we were together? Let’s not see each other again ? ]

A fairy’s voice echoes in my ears.

-Ding!

[You have left the underground 4th floor ‘Island in the Black Sea’]

[You have left the underground 5th floor ‘Martyr Desert’]

[You have left the underground 6th floor ‘Flooded Forest Submerged Zone’]

[You have left the underground 7th floor ‘Snail Slime Ruins’]

[You have left the underground 8th floor ‘Remains of the Headhunters’]

[Entered the underground 9th floor ‘Ryu Majin (Demonic Dragon)‘s Laboratory’]

At the same time, Vikir felt his body slide downward.

‘Is this what it feels like to skip four floors at once?’

A chill ran down his spine from the bottom of his groin to the top of his head, the kind of sensation you get when you go down an elevator in a tall castle, or on a ride that drops you from the top down, or when you train to jump off a cliff.

Vikir’s vision in front of him changed rapidly, and several bloody scenes passed by like a panorama.

A desert where the temperature is so high and dry that nothing remains except sand and burned trees.

Tall trees rising in dense clusters and swamps that were waist deep.

Ruined cities covered in grotesque slime.

Ancient civilizations overrun by savage cannibals.

After passing through them, Vikir finally fell through a gate into the 9th level of the underground.

From here on out, the area would be controlled not by fairies, but by their superiors.

…Thud!

As soon as Vikir hit the ground, he rolled on the floor to minimize the impact.

When he looked up, he saw something strange.

A rectangular room surrounded by translucent walls.

The large interior space was half-filled with fluffy sawdust.

The wood chips that had been cut to the size of a fingernail were as thin as pieces of paper.

There were so many of them piled up that it felt cozy and fluffy.

There was a large bowl in the corner with several red, green, and blue candies rolling around.

Across from it was a pipe dripping with water, and off to the side was a large hamster wheel that you could run around in.

It looked like…

[It looks like a hamster farm.]

[Hack-hack-]

Decarabia and the Madame cub said a word each.

Vikir could only nod.

If it’s narrow, it’s narrow. If it’s wide, it’s wide. Sawdust piled up quite high. Waterer in feed trough. Even treadmills.

No matter where you look, it is a hamster breeding farm.

Papapapapak-

Just as a hamster digs sawdust and builds a den, Vikir did the same.

A den on a sawdust hill ramp made by instinct.

When he went inside and laid down, he felt cozy and warm.

‘By the way, the floor is called Laboratory.’

An aviary set up by a Ryumajin for experiments.

Presumably a place to grow and breed things for experiments.

Vikir quickly recalled the description of this floor from the records of the heroes he had read before his regression.

‘The home of the Ryumajin, the descendants of the dragon kin who joined forces with the demon. An existence that even the lowest levels dare not confront.’

This place is basically a research lab, a laboratory. Run by an absolute being.

Just as humans keep lab rats in cages, there is always a cage in a lab or laboratory.

‘…I’ve heard it before. A place where all Challengers will randomly encounter at some point in time. A place where research is conducted using the precursor creatures that exist on every floor of the tower. A laboratory where boss and normal monsters are bred and breed to create subspecies, subsraces, and variants for the stages.’

This floor doesn’t have to be the 9th floor. Someone might enter from the 2nd floor, someone might enter from the 13th floor, and someone might enter from a floor even further down.

But one thing is for sure: the difficulty of the missions on this floor is “all or nothing”.

It’s either extremely easy or extremely difficult.

Vikir flexed his hands and slammed them against the translucent wall in front of him.

…Boom!

As expected, the wall was solid.

It would be impossible to break it unless you were a master.

[Also. There was a part of me that believed in fairies. They seem to have thought that sending us right here would put the brakes on us.]

Decarabia was right.

If Vikir had just taken his time and broken through the fifth, sixth, seventh, and eighth floors, he would have gotten a much larger reward, and the fairies would have gone bankrupt.

“The gamblers who were frightened by the newbie’s undefeated streak invited him to a game where they would win.”

[If that’s not it, then I don’t know what is. They’ve laid out the deck very well].

Within this, Vikir was perfectly trapped. He was like a rat in a poisonous trap, or a hamster in a cage.

“…No hurry.”

You can’t break down this wall even if you go on a rampage.

Vikir, who already knew this from the memoirs of heroes, began to stroll leisurely around the cage.

Over a knee-deep mound of sawdust, past feeders, waterers, and wheelbarrows, he came upon a high wall.

Vikir pressed his face against it.

Then, beyond the translucent wall, the scenery outside the aviary began to be vaguely visible.

“…Is it an ancient language?”

There were signs in the language of the long-extinct Magic Kingdom.

Vikir stumbled over the words on the signs, using what little knowledge he had from his liberal arts classes.

<Incubation Room>

<Gathering Room>

<Spawn Room>

<Blood Collection room>

<Fighting Room>

.

.

And behind the signs were rows of cages, each with translucent walls.

They looked similar to the place where Vikir was currently being held.

In what was labeled an incubation room, numerous unidentified eggs lay.

Under the gloomy lighting, the veins on the outside of the eggshell are pulsing and pulsating as if they are about to hatch at any moment.

In what was labeled the gathering room, creatures that had apparently been captured from each floor scurried about.

Bugs, wild beasts, flying beasts, fish, crustaceans, and more… There were a few Insectking among them, but judging from the fact that they were all sitting in the corner of the Gathering Room with blank expressions, they seemed to have already lost their minds.

In the area labeled as the Spawn Room, a number of seemingly pregnant creatures were taking a breather and preparing to give birth.

Everyone’s stomachs were grotesquely swollen, probably because they had been injected with some kind of strange drug.

In a place marked as a blood collection room, numerous monsters were being desiccated like mummies and their blood was being drawn.

They are all subjects who long for death at any moment and are in a situation worse than death.

“….”

But it was the room opposite that caught Vikir’s attention the most.

In a place marked as a fighting room, numerous monsters were fighting with their teeth, claws, and horns as if they were going to kill each other.

Kwakwang! Uleuleung…!

Judging by the amount of echoes generated, it seems that they are not all normal.

They were fighting so desperately, as if they believed that only the last one standing could escape this indestructible space.

Beyond that, there are various other cages with unreadable inscriptions on them.

Vikir’s current cell was just one of them.

‘So what is this room for?’

Vikir lifted his head and looked up.

Sure enough, there was a sign above the cage.

Vikir stammered over the vague words.

“…Mating Room?”

Mating (交尾). The sexual act of a male and female for the purpose of reproduction.

‘I see. A laboratory where monsters captured from the world outside the tower were mated and bred to produce various subspecies, subraces, and variant second generations.’

Humans run these kinds of facilities for their domesticated animals, too.

But it was still a thrill to be dropped into it.

In the other mating room next to his, a few creatures were wandering around nervously.

But there was one difference between the mating room with the other creatures and the one with Vikir.

‘Why am I here alone?’

Vikir thought for a moment.

Of course, he couldn’t mate alone. There must be a female individual here to mate with.

But Vikir is the only human in this aviary.

‘Surely there must be a passenger who was trapped here before me….’

If there is a woman who came here before Vikir, he may be able to get information from her.

About what they need to get out of here.

‘But that’s a best-case scenario.’

‘Worst case scenario, the woman here is already insane or full of malice.’

Who knows what horrible experiences she may have had on her way here.

‘It is highly likely that his normal personality and values ??have already collapsed.’

It would be impossible to stay sane in this tower without a heroic mindset.

So Vikir kept a close eye on his surroundings.

You never know when a sword might come out of hiding.

But.

Vikir soon realized that he was wrong.

Zeeeeeee-ing.

A gate suddenly opened down the hill from where Vikir stood.

And a person jumps out of it, rolling on the ground.

“Ouch- where am I?”

Rubbing her head, the person getting up was clearly a cloaked female student from Colosseo Academy.

Vikir couldn’t help but sigh a little as he saw that familiar face looking around with an anxious expression.

‘…Was I the passenger?’

Chapter 332

The Mating Room (2)

◆

-Ding!

[9th underground floor, ‘Dragon Majin’s Laboratory’ -Mating place/Object code 12B-S73062190/Human/Classification: 1 pair]

[Conditions for 2 people have been met]

[Creating a mating environment]

[1st time limit 10:00:00]

.

.

Unidentified notification sounds rang out loudly.

However, the girl in the center of the warren didn’t seem to understand the situation.

“Humans? Mating? What does this mean? There are no fairies here….”

She brushes the sawdust out of her white hair with her hands.

Eyes as big as a deer, face as gentle as a puppy. The cloak she wears, symbolizing the first year of Colosseo Academy, is torn and stained with blood.

Sinclaire, Bourgeois J Sinclaire.

She stood on the sawdust of the warrens here.

“….”

Vikir hunkered down on the hill and thought for a moment.

But there was no way to hide all the way in the barely spacious warren.

What’s more, Sinclaire would soon realize that there was a two-person limit to the warren.

‘We’ll have to hold hands.’

After assessing the situation, Vikir turned to Sinclaire.

“Hey. Here.”

“…!?”

Hearing Vikir’s voice, Sinclaire instantly crouched down and assumed an alert stance.

Her face was as rigid as ever, a sign of the trouble she’d been through in the tower.

But Sinclaire’s expression quickly softened when she realized it was Vikir’s voice calling her.

She broke into a wide smile and started to run.

“Brother, My brother, fell here too! Ah, ah … Isn’t this something you’ll like… I guess I was so excited for a moment because I saw a familiar face.”

“Did you also go through hellhounds and blood daylily?”

“…Yes. You too?”

Sinclaire was happy to see Vikir, but regardless of her expression, signs of hardship were evident all over her body.

Her clothes were stained with blood, and she had lost a lot of weight.

She seemed to have suffered more in her mind than in her body.

Vikir wondered how many levels Sinclaire had warped from.

“Did you meet with the Shadowless King of the Black Sea?”

“No? What level of mission is that? I came over from the 5th floor.”

Apparently, Sinclaire had done a different mission on the same floor as Vikir.

“What was the mission on the fifth floor?”

Vikir asks, and Sinclaire suddenly pauses.

She hesitated, and then looked at Vikir.

“It was….”

Just as she was about to open her mouth.

A loud bang!

Suddenly, the cage shook once.

“…!?”

Vikir quickly jumped up and ran down the hill.

He looked around to find the source of this sudden earthquake.

…Thump! … rumbling, rumbling, rumbling!

The loud noises and vibrations were definitely coming from the mating room next door.

“…What is that?”

Sinclaire came to stand beside Vikir, his expression a mixture of wariness and wonder.

They peered over the translucent wall into the other kennel.

There, two enormous mantises stood in sharp confrontation.

<Giant Mantis>.

Danger Rating: A

Size: 8 to 16 meters

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 4

-Nicknamed ‘Giant Mantis’ or ‘Life Harvester’

Using its giant scythe-like forelimbs, the Mantis is capable of slashing at anything larger than itself.

At full-grown size, the Mantis’ scythe is a formidable weapon against even a Graduator-class swordsman, and the female’s is more than twice as large and sturdy as the male’s.

After mating, the female will eat the male.

A huge female mantis and a small male mantis.

As if they had just been dragged into the enclosure, these two creatures brandish the scythes of their forelegs to keep each other in check.

Sinclaire cocked her head.

“What is that, and why are two mantises fighting over there?”

“….”

Vikir thought about telling Sinclaire the purpose of the warren, but decided against it.

In the meantime, the two mantis were still spewing flesh at each other.

Neither the female nor the male seemed to like the other.

But then.

…Poof!

Something happened.

-Ding!

[Creating a mating environment]

[2nd Time Limit 00:00:00]

A warning sound indicates that the time limit has expired, and a blue mist emanates from every corner of the warren.

Swiiiiig-

The blue mist swirled around the bodies of the two mantis, who were locked in a tense struggle.

And then something amazing happened.

Shhhhhh.

The smaller male was rapidly approaching the larger female.

The odds of them mating were close to zero, based on their previous hostility.

It was clear that the male would soon be torn to shreds by the flesh-spewing scythe of the female.

But.

For some reason, she didn’t block his approach.

In fact, she even turned her body halfway around so that her back and buttocks would be more comfortable for him to ride behind her.

‘Is that blue mist an aphrodisiac?’

Vikir set his chin in thought.

Apparently, the mist was meant to spray when the time limit was up.

-Ding!

[Underground Level 9, Dragon Majin’s Laboratory -Mating Site/Object Code 010M-M9902/Giant Mantis/Classification: 1 Pair]

[Biorhythm: Unbalanced]

[Physical condition: active]

[Mating status: possible].

.

.

Another flurry of beeps.

The two mantis began to breathe harsh, unsteady breaths, and soon they were tangled in each other’s arms violently.

Two giant worms indulging each other with bloodshot eyes.

But.

[…Shhhh!?]

The smaller male was more susceptible to the effects of the aphrodisiac mist, but the larger female seemed to resist it fairly well.

Pudeudeudeug!

The female shook her head to clear it, and then slapped the male on her back with her wings, knocking him off.

The male sprawled on the ground and tried to get back up, but she was having none of it and stabbed him with her scythe.

Koo-koo-koo-koo…

Giant Mantis are enemies in their own right and top predators in the Black Mountains.

Their physical prowess rivals that of a Graduator-class knight, and they are comparable to Masters in terms of strength and the sharpness of their scythes.

Their mental prowess is so great that countless mages of the mental realm have attempted to tame them and failed.

Is that why? Fully grown, the massive female spreads her wings, clearing away all the blue mist, and lunges at the male.

She would not mate with such an inferior individual, not even in death.

Just then.

-Ding!

[Entering mating environment]

[Begins third attempt]

.

.

Another external intervention has begun.

…Swoosh!

The ceiling, which was filled with darkness, opened, and two giant hands shot out.

The backs of the hands covered in blue scales, fingers with sharp nails at the ends.

They grabbed the two struggling mantis, one each, and began to squeeze them down.

They grabbed the hips of the female mantis as she struggled, swinging her scythe, and then grabbed the hips of the male mantis as he struggled to escape.

Like a violent trainer forcing a dog to mate, the female is held down and the male is squeezed in front of a huge, irresistible force.

And with that, the mating of the two mantis is over.

The blue hand slipped back through the darkness of the ceiling as if it had no regrets.

The overwhelmed male fell to the floor and began to shiver, while the female, who had been stressed to the breaking point, slit his throat with her scythe.

..Ujeog-ujeog-ujeog!

The female mantis then proceeded to chew on the severed head of the male mantis.

And then the severed neck, chest, stomach, intestines, and toes.

Shhhhhhhh.

The blue mist was completely gone.

When the female mantis had finished eating the male mantis, she wandered around the enclosure on her own, until she was picked up by the blue hand that reappeared and carried to the other side of the room.

It was a room that had been labeled “spawning room” on a sign earlier.

Next to the spawning room where the forcibly impregnated female mantis had been transferred, another spawning room was already piled high with monster eggs that had undergone a similar process.

A truly horrifying sight.

“…This is a scary place.”

Vikir muttered in a low voice.

Now he understood. Why the fairies had sent him down here.

A place to fight to the death, to mate to the death, to give birth to the death, to be bled to the death, to be caged to the death.

It was a terrifying place where all animals and plants, including humans, were reduced to experimental livestock.

Vikir recalled what he had known about this floor before his regression.

‘…Doesn’t look easy at all. All or nothing, this one.’

Turning his head to look up, he sees the same kind of status window floating above the warrens on this side of the room.

[Enters creating mating environment]

[1st Timeout 09:54:59]

Even as this happens, that euphemism “timeout” is getting shorter and shorter.

Apparently, the time limit is only 10 hours.

If something is not done within that time, there is a high possibility that forced intervention will occur from outside.

You know, like the “blue hand” that was forcibly snapping the mantis earlier.

“Whoa… what was that? Is this some kind of cage match where monsters kill each other?”

Meanwhile, at the clear voice of Sinclaire, who seemed to not yet fully understand the situation, Vikir had no choice but to place his hand on his head for a moment.

‘…How do I explain this?’

Chapter 337

Trap (1)

◆

When you look into ‘it’, ‘it’ looks into you.

Those who hunt ‘it’ must be careful not to become ‘it’ themselves.

Beyond the veil of good and evil, on the fringes, far beyond the bounds of human thought, the “It”‘s are sprouting up toward this side.

-『Notes of an Old Nameless Demon Hunter』 (This is the last record found in his corpse’s arms) –

◆

‘…!’

Vikir opened his eyes in the darkness.

There was no body. Only the severed head remains, floating in the air.

Vikir smiled bitterly.

‘So it is. Was I dreaming?’

A brief dream, the moment his head was cut off.

Everything was just a momentary dream.

In the dream, Vikir had accomplished so much.

Vikir had gained all the things that had been taken from him since his infancy.

He uncovered the dark side of death, took revenge on his family’s brothers, and entered the academy, where he became friends with future great heroes.

He also hunted down and killed countless large-scale demons.

…But all of this was a dream. It was nothing more than an illusion.

Now Vikir was facing reality again.

A burning land. A mountain river of corpses and blood. A flock of crows swarming in the sky.

An age of destruction. The battle between the human and demon worlds had ended in victory for the humans.

But it was a hollow victory.

99% of humanity was wiped out, and the bloodlines of countless great heroes were cut off.

Once opened, the Gate of Destruction would never be closed, and there was no telling when a second or third wave of demons would arrive from within.

For this reason, Vikir could not close his eyes even in death.

His bloodshot eyes remained open despite the fact that his throat had been cut by the thoughts of his comrades who had died and those who were still alive.

Then.

‘Vikir.’

A voice called out.

Vikir tried to turn his head, but with only his neck remaining on the pole, he couldn’t see behind him.

‘Vikir.’

But the voice was coming toward him first.

Then, a warm hand on his cheek.

He turned his head to see a soldier looking down at him.

A woman with a long scar on her cheek. She had vague, blurry features.

But Vikir recognized her at a glance.

‘Sergeant Janet, 1st Platoon, 4th Company, 207th Regiment, you’re alive!’

But she wasn’t the only one.

Many more faces followed.

Vikir knew each and every one of them.

‘Captain Kirke, Ensign White, Sergeant Kuberin, Corporal Saladin, Private Miryamu… all, all alive! I thought you were dead! I thought…. you were dead!’

What could be more joyful than the return of a comrade you thought was dead?

Vikir cried out at the top of his lungs.

…?

The sight of his comrades in arms before him was a little strange.

Had blood dried on their corneas? The red and blurred appearance of his comrades was quite different from the last time he remembered them.

‘Sergeant Janet. Come to think of it, the stab wounds and burn marks that covered your entire face have completely disappeared? Your face is so fine, you looks like a well-groomed beast.’

‘Captain Kirke. Didn’t you lose your left leg in the last battle? I believe I even made you a prosthetic…’

‘Ensign White. You’ve got your… ear back, haven’t you?’

‘Sergeant Kuberin. You lost my sight in one eye….’

That wasn’t all.

There were junior officers, junior non-commissioned officers, and soldiers who had spent their entire lives in poverty and hardship, only to be dragged into the war.

Every single one of them looked healthy and happy.

Those who were missing limbs, eyes, ears, and other parts of their bodies were fully functional, and those who had suffered from poverty, hunger, and disease were dressed in rich, lavish clothes.

A moment.

Something flashed through Vikir’s mind.

In his dream, Vikir had met a woman named Cindywendy.

She had sponsored many of his future comrades-in-arms early on.

Is that why?

Every single comrade-in-arms he met again was alive, not dead.

They were doing what they wanted to do, living their lives, and enjoying themselves.

And now they were together.

Each holding Vikir’s arms, fingers, legs, toes, ears, nose, mouth, and eyes.

‘Vikir!’

They cried out in unison.

Suddenly, the body parts carried by his comrades-in-arms rushed toward Vikir.

A whirlwind of emotions spiraled through his mind.

Sorry.

I’m ashamed.

I’m burdening you with everything.

I’m rooting for you.

Be strong.

Move forward.

So many words make his vision spin.

And then.

Vikir heard one word from everyone that echoed deep in his head.

‘Thank you.’

◆

-Ting!

[Exits the underground 9th floor ‘Demonic Dradon’s Laboratory’]

[Entering the 10th underground floor, ‘Lost Paradise’]

A series of loud beeps hit his ears.

“…!”

Vikir opens his eyes.

The ceiling is unfamiliar.

“…I see. This is the reality.”

For the first time in a long time, Vikir had a dream that wasn’t a nightmare. Somehow, he felt like he had regained some of his strength.

‘To think that my comrades-in-arms in my dream gave me strength… is too sentimental.’

Vikir looked up, remembering the details of his dream.

The color white. A vast expanse of nothing but white.

‘This is just one more level down from the Demonic Dragon’s Laboratory.’

The moment he was crushed by the Ryumajin’s fist on the 9th floor, Vikir turned into a dog once again and was barely able to escape.

He would have been pinned down if Sinclaire hadn’t used his magic to save him at the last second.

When Vikir opened his eyes, the first thing he saw was his reward.

-<Strange Candy>/ Level / Golden

A candy that raises your level by 1.

Tastes sweet.

-Level +1

50 golden candies.

This was a huge reward, worth five thousand ordinary candies.

It was probably a combination of the reward for escaping from the Demonic Dragon’s Laboratory and the reward for escaping the Demonic Dragon’s pursuit.

‘Surprisingly, no items.’

Could it be because Vikir had told the fairy several times that he didn’t want an item reward? Strangely, only candy was being offered as a reward.

‘As a normal challenger, it’s hard to complete missions without items. The fairies’ trick to make it harder for me was actually helpful.’

Vikir checked the rewards and stood up.

He wasn’t wearing any clothes, so something soft touched his naked skin.

‘By the way, this is…’

He looks around and sees a cozy soft couch next to him.

Vikir was now lying on a large, fluffy soft bed.

Beside him is a desk and a chair, and on top of them is a silver candlestick and an assortment of delicious fruits and bread.

<Floor 10: Lost Paradise>

Vikir already knew the information about this floor.

In fact, there’s not much information.

Most of the settings on this floor are open, except for a few hidden ones, and they’re written on the walls in nice detail.

<This is a shelter for challengers who are tired of the trials of the tower!>

<This is the largest candy store in the tower>.

<Challengers can trade their items for candy here>.

<Challengers can exchange their candy for items here>.

.

.

And next to it was a catalog with the prices of the items sold in the shop.

<Small, hard wooden bed- [1 red candy]>.

<Large, fluffy duck bed- [2 red candies]>.

<Small cloth couch- [1 blue candy]>.

<Large Leather Sofa – [2 blue candies].

<10 cans of cold beer – [1 blue candy]>.

<10 pieces of crispy fried chicken legs – [1 red candy]>.

<5 slices of sweet hole cake – [1 green candy]>.

<1 newest game console – [2 green candies]>.

<Letter to the person outside the tower – [1 golden candy]>.

.

.

At the bottom of the catalog, there was a list of ways to enjoy shopping.

<You can exchange items you have for candy!>

<Originally, when exchanging an item for candy, you only get 50% of the price back, but on this floor, you will receive a special exchange of 100%!>

<Candy that has already been eaten and become stats can also be vomited out and turned into candy, but only if you are a resident of this floor!>

<If you vomit out candy that was consumed before entering this floor, you will receive an additional 1 candy for every 10 candies!>

<The color of the extra candy will be randomized between red, green, and blue!>

<Now you can decorate this empty space by purchasing your own items from the catalog!>

.

.

Vikir looked at the bottom of the disclaimer.

<※ A small perk for all the trouble you’ve taken to get here – send a message to a figure outside the tower who will be anxiously waiting for you!>.

<※ A ‘letter item’, originally worth one golden candy, will be given away for free once a month to the residents of this floor!>

<※ The probability of entering this room is less than 0.0001%, you are the lucky one who has been chosen!>

<※ From the very next floor onwards, the difficulty will increase by at least ten times compared to the floors you’ve been through so far!>

<※ Please rest here to refresh your mind and body before attempting the tower again!>

That was the end of the notice.

The large empty space can be filled with things from the store.

Necessities and luxuries that are reasonably priced.

No threats to survival, and plenty of ways to relax and entertain yourself.

Above all, you could send a message to your family or friends who might be worried about you outside the tower.

All of these things were not dreams, fantasies, or mirages; it is a stark reality.

…And Vikir thought to himself.

‘This is the worst.’

Before the Regression, the most dangerous floor, where all the great heroes who said they were going to fly were holding their tongues.

A trap set by demons to hunt down challengers.

The vilest, most despicable, and most blatant trap in the entire tower was here.

Chapter 338

Trap (2)

◆

<10th Floor Lost Paradise>

A translucent screen floats on the wall.

The first thing that catches his eye is a catalog that lists numerous items and their prices.

<Hot Water Faucet- [3 red candies]>

<Cypress Sauna- [1 red candy]>

<Marble Bathtub- [2 red candies]>

<Luxury Bath Salts+Luxury Sampoo+Luxury Conditioner+Luxury Body Wash- [1 blue candy]>

<Oak Barrel of Aged Wine- [1 blue candy]>

<Assorted Fresh Fruits- [1 blue candy]>

<Braised Pork Hind Leg – [1 Red Candy].>

<Modern Card Game- [1 blue candy]>

<Letter to the person outside the tower- [1 golden candy]>

.

.

A rest area where you can buy anything with candy.

Comfortable and cozy things are everywhere.

The items aren’t too expensive, so even people with low levels and stats can relax here.

Delicious food, fluffy furniture, interesting entertainment… You can even send a message to someone outside the tower!

The downside is that you only get one reply and it costs an additional golden candy to read it, but you can still communicate.

Plus, it’s free to send once a month, so that’s an added perk.

With less than 0.0001% of challengers making it to this level, and the next level being 10x harder, you’ll be lucky to even make it to this level.

So for all the comforts and conveniences, Vikir had this to say.

‘…That’s one hell of a trap.’

This is the first time he’s seen a trap laid out so blatantly.

But it’s the traps on this floor that are so effective nonetheless.

Even Vikir, who has seen it all, would have fallen to it if he hadn’t had the knowledge he had before the regression.

‘Even the great and powerful Camus had a hard time on this floor,’

Vikir didn’t relax, recalling an incident from long ago.

The face of Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of the Baskerville family, flashed in his mind.

‘Do you know how to catch the big beast?’

One day, Hugo gathered the young hounds of the Baskervilles around him and said that.

One of the hounds raised his hand and said, “It’s called a pack,” and Hugo shook his head.

‘I’m talking about a very large beast, a beast that can’t be defeated by many. What would you do if such a thing ruled an entire mountain and reigned like a king?’

A large beast that reigns supreme over a region.

A single entity whose combat power and danger is so high that even an army can’t handle it.

Indeed, the western fringes of the Baskervilles’ territory were home to quite a few such beasts.

Did all the seeds dry up after Hugo moved his family to the lower reaches of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain?

Hugo told him of his methods of extermination.

‘I didn’t use much force. Anyone with the time could have done it. Even if you’re just a criminal.’

Hugo said he left chunks of meat all over the mountain.

He didn’t use poison or traps. The smell of poison or iron would only make the enemy more wary.

The chunks of meat scattered throughout the beast’s territory were seasoned.

The fatty, cholesterol-rich meat was selected from the fatty parts, stir-fried and deep-fried, and scattered throughout the beast’s hunting grounds.

Even the beasts that were initially wary of the meat chunks would eventually eat them if they saw them laid out all over the hunting trail.

The amazingly delicious chunks of meat keep coming. They’re everywhere.

You don’t have to go hunting, you just have to set foot on a trail and you’ll always have access to those fatty, delicious chunks of meat.

It’s a life of lying down and sleeping, then waking up when you’re hungry, following the scent, and picking up chunks of meat.

This goes on for a while.

In the meantime, the beast gains weight. It develops a belly and wrinkles.

Its claws, always sharpened as it runs across the land, and its teeth, sharpened by breaking prey’s bones and soaking in blood, become dull.

His ears and eyes, which allowed him to sense the signs of his prey from miles away, have grown fat and dull.

A fleshy underbelly and fatty intestines weigh it down.

‘Now is the time to hunt.’

When the beast has completely lost its wildness, the hardened hounds of the Baskervilles break their leashes and run.

And from that day forward, the territory changes hands.

In this way, Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman, would eliminate his enemies and the beasts of the Black Mountain, one by one.

‘…The principle of this floor is the same.’

Vikir closed the catalog.

‘The reason this floor is dangerous is not because of the presence of life-threatening demons or traps.

Rather, it is the certainty that there is none.

It’s so peaceful and relaxing that everything you’ve been through seems like a nightmare.

Conveniences that are only a small price to pay for the stats you’ve worked so hard to accumulate.

Once you leave, not only will you never return, but you’ll face missions that are ten times harder than anything you’ve ever faced before.

And the ability to send letters to people outside the tower is another reason to stay.

The chance to let your family, friends, and loved ones know you’re okay, even if they’re probably crying right now.

Even better, you can write back to them!

This is what keeps challengers on this floor.

As you stay, you’ll spend more and more candy in your stats.

Little by little, like clothes soaked in a drizzle.

Once they’re gone, they’ll never come back.

Your strength, agility, and stamina… will decrease by a further level.

Outside of this floor, you can spit out candies of the stats you’ve already eaten, and they’ll give you back more candies, so there’s no reason not to exchange them.

The longer you stay here, the faster and more rapidly the challenger will weaken.

Weakened in body and mind, the challenger will eventually be unable to descend to the next level and will remain here for life.

A prison without bars.

The challengers of the tower, whose bodies were locked up but not their minds, will eventually find their minds locked up here as well.

Of their own volition!

‘Here I will grow fat, old, and weak. Content to exchange letters with people outside the tower for the rest of my life.’

If someone else clears the tower, even if it’s not you, you’ll automatically leave this floor and go outside.

‘It doesn’t have to be me…’

As a result of this psychology, challengers become even more unable to escape this floor.

‘Besides… there must be hidden traps here.’

Vikir turned his head in silence and looked at the screen in the corner of his eye.

<※ A small perk for all the trouble you’ve taken to get here: send a message to a figure outside the tower who will be anxiously awaiting my return!>

<※ A ‘letter item’, originally worth the price of a single golden candy, will be given away for free once a month to residents of this floor!>

It was equipped with the ability to send letters outside the tower.

Vikir boldly pressed the send button.

Suddenly, words appeared out of thin air.

[To. Sergeant Janet, 1st Platoon, 4th Company, 207th Regiment].

[I miss you, comrade. Are you getting along well there?]

.

.

Vikir sent the letter.

Within seconds, he received a reply.

<Do you want to see the reply right away?>

<One golden candy will be deducted>

<You can check it for free in 30 days>

.

.

Vikir spent the one golden candy he had and opened the reply.

[From. Sergeant Janet, 1st Platoon, 4th Company, 207th Regiment].

[Company Commander, is that you Company Commander Vikir, are you alive, where are you, everyone is waiting for you, we thought you were alive after all, everyone at the front says you can’t be dead…]

.

.

Vikir slammed the letter shut without another look.

‘It’s a trap after all.’

The seasoned Vikir saw through all the oddities in the letter.

For one thing, Sergeant Janet is a person from a time before the regression, a time in which she had already been executed.

And at this point in time, Sergeant Janet would be living as a normal, wealthy family figure with the support of Cindywendy.

This is because the future has changed.

In other words, the Sergeant Janet that Vikir remembers no longer exists in either world.

Nevertheless, the immediacy of the reply means that….

‘A trick.’

The ability to lure people into a false sense of security, to make them feel safe and secure in the knowledge that they are in touch with someone they care about.

…But all of this is false.

The letters are replies written by a demon who has read the letter, picked through the memories and emotions of the writer, and cherry-picked what they wanted to hear as much as possible.

‘With the restriction of once a month, I can only write down the words I need to send to the people who really need them, and all the emotions of longing and longing are read by the demon fairy.’

And now, a letter ghostwritten by a demon will make the challengers in the tower complacent.

Once they reach the next floor, even this small exchange of communication will be impossible.

‘Being petty and cowardly is exactly the strategy of the demons.’

Vikir grunted and pushed himself up.

With no one waiting for him outside the tower, no one to miss him, Vikir could leave this floor without any regrets.

‘…But I will only remain here until I regain my strength and magic.’

Even now, the wound was regenerating at a rapid pace.

Madame cub and Decarabia are also sleeping comfortably under the bed, so they will open their eyes soon.

‘…But who moved me to the bed?’

Vikir suddenly realized something was wrong.

“Whoa? You’re awake.”

A voice said from beside him.

Where Vikir turned his head, there stood a female student with a familiar face.

Dolores. The student council president of Colosseo Academy stood across the bed from Vikir, staring at him.

Suddenly, Vikir realized something else he had forgotten.

‘Yes. There’s always a male and female on this floor.’

To ensure that those imprisoned on this floor don’t go mad with loneliness and try to escape, the demons always place another prisoner here.

So that the two can become friends and remain here.

Dolores had apparently entered this floor before Vikir.

She stroked the wound on Vikir’s forehead sympathetically.

“You should lie down a little longer, there are almost no external injuries, but the internal injuries are severe.”

Vikir was momentarily flustered by Dolores’ casual approach.

‘…What?’

Was he now in the state of a Night Hound? Or Vikir, a first-year student at Colosseo Academy?

Judging by her half-speech, she’s talking to Vikir, a first-year student at Colosseo Academy.

However, the affectionate look she’s giving him right now is definitely that of a Night Hound.

‘…No way. Has she found out who I am?’

Vikir scrambles to his feet.

Dolores pulled him into a tight embrace.

“Uh-huh, This guy! You’re not listening to me when I tell you to lie down a little longer!”

At the same time, she slipped her hands under Vikir’s sides and lifted him up.

In an instant, Vikir’s reflection appeared in Dolores’ large, clear eyes.

It was neither Vikir nor Night Hound.

“Listen to your sister, Choco, before I have you neutered.”

Choco, Peanutblack’s hound.

It was Vikir’s third identity.

Chapter 339

Private Life (1)

◆

‘Oh, I see. I see I haven’t finished my transformation yet.’

Just before Vikir was crushed by the Ryumajin’s fist, he had transformed into a dog, making him smaller in size and thus avoiding being crushed.

Of course, this was only possible because Sinclaire’s last-minute magic had bought him some time.

Unaware of this, Dolores was examining every inch of Vikir’s body.

“Wow, your wounds are almost healed already. You’re a good constitution to divine power, my choco.”

She rubbed the ointment she’d bought with the candy all over Vikir’s wounds.

With that, Vikir’s external wounds were almost completely healed.

“Mmm~ But you still have internal injuries, so you’ll need to heal a bit more. I’ll get some medicine for you, just wait a bit.”

Dolores patted Vikir’s head and turned on the shop window.

<Medicines for internal injuries!>[3 blue candies]>

Vikir thought to himself as he watched her pay three candies for a medicine for internal wounds.

‘…You’re still being a brat.’

The internal injuries are severe, but a few days of rest is all it takes to recover.

Besides, who gives three pieces of candy to a stray dog on the street in the first place?

(And if you count the trauma medicine, that’s a whopping six candies!)

Vikir didn’t swallow the pills Dolores gave him, instead sneaking them into the corners of his mouth.

He planned to secretly return it later and exchange it for another candy.

Dolores, meanwhile, had no idea what Vikir was thinking when she opened her mouth.

“Choco, you were there and you got caught up in it, poor thing…. But how did you end up here? It’s quite a coincidence, no matter how random the circumstances you encounter on each floor.”

“….”

“With a 0.0001% chance of ending up here, we’re pretty lucky, aren’t we? Right?”

“….”

Vikir lowered his head for a moment in embarrassment.

‘In order to escape this room, both prisoners must agree to leave. If one of them wishes to remain in the floor, neither of them will be able to leave.’

Vikir would have to somehow convince Dolores to leave the room.

But Dolores had already made up her mind to live in the room for quite some time.

She’d set up a fluffy bed, a couch, plenty of food and water, and even a bath.

“Choco~ While you’re healing from your trauma, why don’t you take a bath with me? The holy water I make is great for internal wounds!”

Vikir sighed softly.

Why does this girl love bathing so much?

◆

Vikir eventually entered the bathhouse.

He didn’t have the strength to resist, and he didn’t really have a good reason.

In fact, the holy water was so effective at healing internal wounds that Vikir had to bow down and ask.

A large wooden bathtub filled with warm water.

The peak.

Dolores hugged Vikir tightly and soaked in the water.

“Wow- we’ve bathed together before, haven’t we? I remember.”

Vikir nodded slightly.

Back when he was a Graduator, after his first encounter with Camus, he had been dragged to the baths by a passing Dolores on her way back to the Academy after fighting tooth and nail and being turned into a pulp.

Even then, Dolores seemed to have said something similar while bathing.

“Taking a bath was my only pleasure in life. I didn’t have time for any hobbies because I had so many things to do, like study, work, volunteer work, and …. The board game club, which was my other hobby, was closed down because the number of members was too small. Nowadays, everyone is busy doing extracurricular activities to keep their grades up, and the job market is so bad.”

Words like romantic, geeky, and surplus are now rarely heard.

While Dolores acknowledges that this is a change, she is also nostalgic for the past.

“Haha – I can’t believe I’m talking about something that’s after been captured by the demon and locked in a tower. It’s not very realistic either. Right?”

Vikir nodded silently.

Then Dolores tapped the tip of Vikir’s nose and snorted.

“Wuu. You act like you understand me, don’t you?”

Vikir turned away silently as Dolores lifted herself out of the water.

Silence descended on the bath for a moment.

Vikir sniffed the thick steam rising from the water and concentrated on healing his wounds.

His internal organs were healing rapidly, thanks to the holy power emanating from Saint Dolores’ body.

‘At this rate, a day or two should be enough.’

Vikir was mentally estimating the time it would take to recover.

“I know, I know. This is not the time to be killing time in a place like this.”

Behind him, he heard Dolores muttering to herself.

Her voice quivered slightly as she continued.

“My classmates, my juniors, they’re dying in front of me, people I’ve lived with and studied with for the last few years, and they’re killing each other, murdering each other, … using each other, betraying each other, …..”

What could she, who was both a student and a religious person, do in the midst of that chaos?

The rules were set by the demon in the first place, a game played out of malice.

There was no place for righteousness or love in it.

Dangerous creatures such as Hellhounds and Daylily of Dlood lurked on every floor.

There was always a fixed number of survivors, and those who didn’t make it were simply culled and left to die a miserable death.

Dolores has tried many times to sacrifice herself in their place, but those around her desperately urged her to protect the Healer.

With a splash-

Dipping her face in and out of the water, Dolores wiped the water from her face.

But she couldn’t wipe the water from her voice.

“I took the hearts of those who tried to protect me by pretending to be invincible. I ignored the sacrifices of the few in favor of saving the many. I betrayed the desires of the weak.”

The weak being offered up as food for the Daylily of the Blood, the strong pushing the weak out on a limb.

It’s an absurd situation for anyone to see, not just religious people.

…But without human sacrifice, everyone dies.

She wanted to sacrifice herself, but it wouldn’t change anything, and she was already the leader of the group, the spiritual center of the survivors, so she couldn’t move.

Throughout the process, Dolores was torn.

What was the right course of action: to sacrifice unconditionally, or to preserve her life for those left behind, or neither…?

In the end, Dolores did not find an answer to this question in time.

The result of the many weak against the few strong was an overflow of Blood Daylily that wiped out all of the surviving students.

In the midst of the carnage, Dolores was forced to tear up the return scroll

For no other reason than to keep herself alive.

“…I was helpless, I could do nothing, I was tested by the demon from beginning to end.”

Dolores bowed her head deeply.

The hot steam from the baths was making her eyes red.

Vikir closed his eyes and thought.

‘The mind trick worked.’

This was Amdusias’ intention.

A strategy to break the faith and will of young sprouts who will grow into heroes in the future from the very beginning, and to instill in their place a sense of inferiority, self-destruction, and helplessness.

Indeed, many aspiring great heroes died here before the regression.

‘…But there were also those who came out of it stronger and more hardened.’

Such was the case with Dolores, who would later become known as the Ironblooded Saint.

She was said to have awakened on the front lines of the battlefield after the Age of Destruction, but it was actually a second awakening, the first a stepping stone before that, here in the Tower of Abyss.

‘It will be a matter of how you shake off this spirit.’

Vikir knows, having been through the grueling process of becoming a Master himself.

A word or two of advice from someone who has traveled this path before you can make all the difference.

Ultimately, Vikir’s path to Master was paved by a few words from Cane Corso, whom he met at the Grave of Swords.

‘…I wonder if any of those words would apply to Dolores at this point.’

Vikir pondered.

‘Something to say to a future hero.’

For now, he had to put aside all thoughts and distractions and focus on the first word.

Even though his body and mind were exhausted after the battle with the Demonic Dragon, he still had to keep his spirits up and focus as much as possible.

‘After all, Dolores, Saint of Steel, it would be best if I told you what you said, right?’

One can only speak as one has been through.

She, too, would understand best.

Vikir recalled what the middle-aged Dolores had said before the regression, as she tended to the wounded.

“The more painful the reality, the more deeply you should think about the meaning of life and religion. Only then will it lead you to a better realm of greater goodness.”

It was not a simple well-wishes.

They were words spoken by Dolores, Saint of Steel, in a makeshift shelter for wounded soldiers, to a young saint who was weeping and berating herself for not saving more lives.

Years later, Dolores, who had overcome more hardships and trials than anyone else, had distilled her life’s experience into a teaching.

It was passed down across the time axis of several decades to the young, fledgling saintess Dolores.

Sure enough, Dolores lifted her head up as if she had come to great realization.

Then, in a voice of disbelief, she said.

“…Choco. Did you just say that?”

Chapter 342

Ballak (2)

◆

Tudor and Bianca.

Vikir looked at the two, who had both grown up by now, with a strange gaze.

“….”

Memories of the time before the regression came flooding back.

The true intentions of the two heroes, who had been bickering for a lifetime, were revealed during the Fifth Battle, when humanity was at its most vulnerable.

At that time, the arch-demon Amdusias, who was leading the Demon Tree Legion, used the roots of countless demons to hinder the human alliance.

Among them, the one that hindered humanity the most was the Blood Daylily.

Growing in any terrain with water, this terrible monster was a great threat to human soldiers in combat, but many times more dangerous to those retreating after losing a battle.

There was a moment when Vikir was retreating with arrows piercing his body, only to find his path blocked by a river swollen by a sudden rain and the blood daylilies that were everywhere, waiting to kill him.

The heroine who stepped forward in the midst of this dire situation was the Usher family’s Usher P Bianca.

She fired an arrow of fire with all her might, exploding all the dense blood daylilies and giving the survivors a last chance to escape.

However, after saving countless soldiers, Bianca herself was trapped by the roots of the many daylilies and was unable to escape.

…And. As she was about to give up her life, her last shield appeared in front of her, and he was Tudor Donquixote.

‘Run, you’re in danger!’

‘…But how can I go when you’ve been captured!’

‘Go! Go and call for backup!

‘No! I can’t go!’

Just like the conversation just now, the two heroes were bickering with each other back then as well.

In the end, Tudor’s efforts to save Bianca and the other survivors cost him his life as he tried to block the explosion with his body.

Bianca clutches Tudor’s charred body in her arms.

Vikir can still see the dazed look on Bianca’s face as she was left alone.

The death of a man she had known her whole life as an adversary, a childhood friend, and a lover.

An eternal goodbye, one she’d never spoken to, one she’d never whispered her love to.

None of the survivors could speak of the rain showers that poured down over the burned earth, or the image of Bianca sitting in the rain with her arms around Tudor.

And Vikir had watched it all from behind.

‘…Then, it was from the point of view of a mere soldier 1, watching the great heroes from afar.’

But now, Tudor and Bianca stand here.

Facing Amdusias, who separated them before the regression, much earlier than expected.

And this time, the reliable veteran Vikir stood before them.

‘Fear not. In this life, Amdusias will die by my hand.’

That way, Tudor and Bianca would not face a tragic future.

Vikir sincerely hoped so.

“Ouch! Why didn’t you run away earlier, when I told you to!”

“I was just pissed off!”

“Then be a good girl, you only grabbed my ankle!”

“That’s ridiculous! You’re the one who got grabbed by the neck by Vikir!”

“You think I got caught because I’m weak! Vikir is stronger! And you would have been caught too!”

“Are you a bowman or a spearman? I can’t take one of those crap!”

“In the future, go when you have to.”

“It’s up to me!”

They’ll continue to bicker like they do now, affirming each other’s preciousness.

Together, perhaps forever.

“….”

Vikir stroked his chin in silence.

It was time to analyze the reality at hand.

Vikir realized that Tudor and Bianca had changed a lot since he had seen them.

They were taller, with more bone and muscle.

In Tudor’s case, his jaw has thickened and his voice has deepened, making him look more mature.

Bianca’s body shape has also changed in many ways.

Most importantly, their auras have increased to a level that is unparalleled.

“…How long have you guys been on this floor?”

Vikir asked, and Tudor shook his head.

“I think we’ve been here for over a week. It feels like it.”

“By the feel of it, yes. If you count the sun rising and setting, it’s exactly 2,555 days today. Seven years.”

Bianca had the right answer.

She had only been on this floor for a little over a week, but in the time of this floor alone, seven years had passed.

The ever-positive Tudor hissed and swung the spear at her back.

“It’s good that a little bit of training here is worth a whole day’s training, seven years’ worth in one go, right?”

“On the other hand, don’t you realize that you’ll grow old just as fast?”

“What the hell, I’m still young.”

“Hey, you burn out, who knew how much longer I would be trapped on this floor….”

“That’s a question for another time. Right now, the answer is to train hard!”

Tudor could only smirk at Bianca’s tangy words.

Vikir nodded.

From what he’d seen earlier, Tudor and Bianca’s skills had improved tremendously.

They’ve adapted to the harsh conditions of the jungle, and they’ve practiced tirelessly in between.

Add to that the passage of time, and their progress must have been swift.

‘This tower is not called the Tower of Opportunity for nothing.’

The trials thrown by the demon were certainly harsh, but humans have the ability to use them to build upon themselves.

That’s why mankind survived that terrifying battle of destruction.

Just then, Tudor tapped Vikir on the shoulder.

“Come on, let’s get to the lair. I have more friends for you to meet.”

“Who else is on this floor?”

“Of course. Don’t freak out! Pigi and Sancho are with us! Hahaha! They’ll be so happy to see you, they might even faint. We’ve saved up a lot of food, let’s have a barbecue party today!”

Tudor patted Vikir on the back and headed into the bushes.

He grinned from ear to ear in anticipation of the tearful reunion to come.

“That’s it. On the previous stage, Sinclaire was also there… Well, the mission didn’t go well, so I only sent Sinclaire down. The remaining four of us fell into this forest due to a penalty or something, but the daylilies outside don’t attack you unless you get close to the water, so we’re okay. Well, the real problem was ‘somewhere else’… hmm!?”

But Tudor didn’t finish his sentence.

The color drained from his face and the smile vanished.

He was right, for all that remained of the wide-open plain beyond the bush were ruins.

A hut, apparently made of stones and logs, was completely destroyed.

In what appeared to be a warehouse, broken sacks were rolling around, and grains and fruits were rolling around.

And in the center of it all, two men sit, looking dejected.

They had grown beards and were taller, but Vikir recognized them at a glance.

Sancho and Pigi. The two men guarding the lair looked up at Tudor and Bianca.

“…Eh!?”

Their helpless gazes suddenly came alive.

“Vikir!”

Sancho, now much taller, and Pigi, now looking quite grown up, ran over.

“Uh, how did Vikir get here!”

“Are we the ship owners this time?”

They grabbed Vikir’s hand and shook it wildly, unable to contain their excitement.

Meanwhile, Tudor and Bianca were looking around with serious expressions on their faces.

“ …Is this what ‘those guys’ did?”

“They stole all our food. While we were away.”

Sancho nodded.

“We tried to fight them off, but we were outnumbered. And their individual strength was superior. We were barely able to hold on for our lives.”

Sancho and Pigi were covered in wounds, as if the battle had been quite intense.

Tudor gritted his teeth.

“Shit. This is the ‘other problem’ I was talking about earlier. This is far more troublesome than the blood daylilies. Here we are, meeting Vikir, and we can’t even have a barbecue.”

Then.

Vikir noticed something strange.

The color of the blood oozing from Pigi’s wound.

“Pigi. Is your blood naturally black?”

“Huh? Aaah, it’s always been like this, huh? I’m not demonized or anything! It’s been like this since I was a kid! The doctors said it’s because there’s a lot of iron in my blood… but it seems like it’s gotten a little darker since I’ve been in the Hell Tree?”

“Hmm.”

Bianca, who had come back from surveying the damage, spoke up just as Vikir was showing interest in something other than food.

“That’s not the point right now, we’ve lost all the food we’ve been saving, and at this rate, we won’t even have enough to eat tomorrow, let alone complete the mission, let alone … the barbecue.”

“What’s the mission?”

Vikir asked, and Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca simultaneously popped up a status window above their heads.

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※Each and every one of the ship’s owners possesses powerful powers! Living is inherently difficult~

※ Recognized only if everyone clears the mission!

Apparently, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were fighting the shipowners who had arrived on this floor first.

“We don’t know who they are either. We’re guessing barbarians, but we’re not sure.”

“It is clear that we are hostile towards each other. We are competing with this side for food.”

“They are incredibly fast and strong, and we’ve lost all the food we’ve gathered.”

“They are skilled with the bow, perhaps rivaling the archery of the Divine Archers….”

Apparently, the force of the ship owners attacking this way was considerable.

The arrowheads embedded in large boulders and thick logs proved it.

Holes that spiraled in circles, as if a tremendous rotational force had been applied.

Shots twisting and turning in every direction, front, back, left, right, and center.

And Vikir knew people who shot arrows this way.

“…I have a hunch.”

Vikir began to walk in one direction, retracing the tracks of the battle.

“Huh? If we go that way, we’ll be in the territory of those shipowners.”

“Head-on combat is dangerous, Vikir.”

“But I feel strangely confident, why?”

“Well, it’s only been the four of us so far, and with Vikir on board, who knows?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca unwittingly followed Vikir’s lead.

Towards the base of seasoned ship owners who have lived on this floor for a very long time.

Chapter 344

Ballak (4)

◆

<Underground Level 11, ‘River of Flow’

This is a strange place indeed.

Time passes faster for creatures that move faster, and slower for creatures that move slower.

This is a law that holds true in the normal world, but in this tower, the phenomenon is especially noticeable.

Vikir moves at breakneck speed, and each time he does, his stats are boosted by the effects of his items.

-Ding!

[‘Agility’ stat increased by ‘1’…]

[Stamina stat increased by 1 to…]

[Your ‘Physical Resistance’ stat increased by 1 to…]

[Magic resistance stat increased by ‘1’ to…]

[Reflexes stat increased by ‘1’ to…]

.

.

Vikir’s stats were rising at an incredible rate as he moved more violently, more violently, and more destructively.

Kkadag-

Vikir dodged a flying arrow with a simple tilt of his head.

An extremely frugal move, an evasion without waste.

Not only has his reflexes blossomed, but he is also growing, so something like this becomes possible.

Natural Gifted.

An extremely rare talent, possessed by only a few individuals throughout human history.

Vikir, an all-rounder, was naturally born without it, but that all changed when he entered the tower.

All the innate and natural things he had been denied simply because he was unlucky, he could now claim them all here.

Jjuuug-

His vision expanded, then contracted, then expanded again.

The passage of time was strangely distorted.

It feels like he’s living on a different time axis than everyone else.

It’s as if everything is moving slowly on purpose.

‘…Even though time is passing several times faster, it seems as if it has stopped. Is this the realm of the gifted?’

Stepping forward to avoid the arrows that almost stopped in front of him was as easy as walking around a boulder or tree that stood still.

And with each passing moment, it was getting easier and easier.

That’s because his reflexes stats kept going up.

‘It was originally an item I got to increase my 6 stats and 3 special stats by 1, but I never thought I’d hit the jackpot in a place like this….’

The levels in the Hell Tree are random and have different locations and characteristics, so I never thought I’d find a place where time warps so quickly.

Even the windfalls were not like this.

Once your stats go up, they never go down.

They stay the same whether you’re in the tower or outside.

Of course, if you leave the tower, you won’t be able to see your stats.

‘If I were to leave the tower, I could… really reach the 8th Form. Even without the help of a saint!’

The Baskerville 8th Form is more powerful than any officially recognized sword form.

Even Hugo, the iron-blooded swordman patriarch of Baskerville, could only reach seventh dan after a lifetime of training.

‘…But that would have been the story when I left.’

In order to escape the tower, you must first focus on reality.

…Teoeog! Bing-geul-

Vikir grabbed the arm of the warrior charging at him with his dagger and twisted it back.

Crunch-

With a crunch of bones, the Ballak warrior fell to the mud.

…Pongdang!

Warriors who fell into the mud often dropped golden candies.

“I guess it’s because they’re ship owners, so their level is high, right? The dropped items are also of a high level.”

Vikir said as he picked up the golden candies that had fallen into the mud.

The warriors cowered in fear at the sight of such force and the fluency of the Ballak’s language.

Meanwhile, Vikir checked the golden candies in his hand.

‘…I wonder if I should have just switched to regular candies instead of collecting golden candies, then my maximum gain would have been much higher, not just 798.’

But that’s too short-sighted.

The golden candy levels you up, and it increases your stats in %.

Therefore, its effect could be maximized only when used at ‘critical moments.’

With achievement rewards and other considerations, it’s best to save the golden candy for later.

Crunch-clunk-clunk!

Vikir craned his neck from side to side.

Vikir’s vision had improved to the point where he could see his reflection in the dewdrops on the tips of the pine needles in the distance.

He seemed to have grown several centimeters taller.

His arms and legs were longer.

His body had put on several years of age as a result of moving so much faster than anyone else.

‘I’ll probably end up back to the age I was before I regressed.’

Not a bad idea. Because I’m more familiar with that side than the image of a young boy.

It seems like the surroundings might be a little less noisy.

Peoeog- udeug! Kwagig!

Vikir continued to swing his sword.

His snake-like aura slices through the flying arrows and targets the archers behind him.

Ballak’s warriors ducked and dodged, but Vikir’s blows tore through rocks, logs, and other obstacles in their path.

“Is he a shipowner, too? That can’t be right!”

“How can a novice have such power! We’re no match for him!”

“Damn it! This is out of standard! What are those fairies doing!”

“Sah, the hunting leader must come, Otherwise…!”

Even the brave and warlike warriors of Ballak eventually lost their will to fight.

…Bang!

Vikir grabbed one of the fleeing warriors by the scruff of the neck and slammed him to the ground.

Whirl-

He twisted his body just before hitting the ground, minimizing the impact.

Still, it was enough to immobilize him for a while, but at least he was spared from being knocked out.

A moment. Vikir was a little surprised.

Not because the fallen warrior was an elderly man with graying hair who looked to be the oldest of the group.

‘This guy uses Baskerville style, doesn’t he?’

Vikir had taught Ballak’s warriors the basics of Baskerville style when he had lived among them.

However, Ballak’s martial arts were far more advanced than the Baskervilles’, and the more experienced warriors hadn’t bothered to learn Vikir’s techniques.

‘…What happened?’

Vikir scratched his head.

But even as he wondered, Vikir’s hands slowly grabbed the enemy’s wrists and elbows and twisted them.

Udeug! Ppudeudeug!

Vikir said as he snapped the arm of the oldest warrior he had just captured.

“This is what you’ll all look like if you try to fight me.”

If the oldest and strongest warrior was like this, there was no way the others could resist.

“….”

“….”

“….”

Ballak’s warriors were speechless.

Helpless. An entity outside the norm that hadn’t been on the floor before had suddenly appeared and was exerting overwhelming force, and they were helpless, even if they were normally warlike and brave.

Then. There were voices interrupting them.

“It’s bad, you barbarians!”

“I understand. You’ve never seen anything like this before. I feel thrilled when I see it, but you must be so appalled.”

“But how did you get so strong, or were you always strong?”

“Oh, yeah, you were the one on the rooftop smelling like rum on entrance day, I recognized you!”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca appeared from behind Vikir.

“Hey, look at the size of their food pouches, Vikir! Don’t stop me! I’m not going to let them take my…!”

“I got everything back. The ones we farmed and hunted to death.”

“Hmph- my tomatoes, radishes, and cabbage! I worked so hard to grow them!”

“Aaah! I even found my salted pork! Ugh, I risked my life to go to a Daylily colony to get salt….”

But Vikir reached out and blocked the path of Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

Vikir’s gaze was on something other than the recovered food.

…Sparkle!

Something shone from the ear of the warrior they had just captured.

It was definitely an earring.

Glass bead earrings with some traces of modernity on them.

And with Vikir’s enhanced vision, he could make out the words etched into the surface of the glass bead, so worn and tattered by the elements that they were now barely more than a faint color.

‘Made in Cindywendy studio’

It was obviously one of the first items Cindywendy had selected for trade with the Ballak, a trinket for the Ballak’s infants.

‘Why is she wearing this?’

Vikir scratched his head.

PING-

An arrow flew from the front.

It flew with a force and speed that not even Vikir dared to ignore.

“…!”

Vikir deflected the arrow with the back of his sword.

A dull thud of pain echoed through his wrist.

Vikir dropped the warrior he had captured and stepped back, and a new warrior appeared in the center of the battlefield.

A woman with long, flowing hair.

She looks to be in her early thirties, but the aura she exudes is decades older, fierce and seasoned.

For a moment, Vikir thought she reminded him of the Ballak chieftain Akwilla.

‘…This woman is going to be a little tough.’

For the first time, he broke out in a cold sweat.

The female warrior in front of him was such a powerful opponent that even Vikir, who had all six of his stats in bloom, couldn’t guarantee a victory.

She wasn’t quite the Ryumajin he’d encountered on the previous floor, but she was certainly a more difficult opponent than Cerberus, Blood Daylily, and the Black Sea King.

Vikir was tensely holding the tip of his sword.

…Teoeog!

Something surprising happened.

A female warrior, the most senior of the group, stepped forward and knelt down on one knee in front of Vikir.

“Greetings from the hunting grounds of Ballak.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and all of Ballak’s warriors, even Vikir, were stunned.

Vikir stared into the face of the woman kneeling before him.

A woman who looked to be about middle-aged, with a strength that reminded him of Akwilla.

When you’ve had a relationship with a warrior of this caliber, it’s hard to forget.

“…?”

Vikir thought hard, hoping there was something he didn’t remember.

And then.

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes widened at the sight of a familiar face.

It is something that can only be seen once the dignity of a seasoned veteran has been removed, a legacy that has been gained through countless experiences and the passage of time.

It’s the face of a child.

‘…I wonder if I can get a glass bead?’

It was an old memory with a little girl who wanted to turn a caterpillar into a glass bead.

Chapter 345

Ballak (5)

◆

A child who ate one-pot meals for two years in the depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

‘The girl you helped today is his sister. Her name is Aheul.’

Vikir thought for a moment and remembered a girl named Aheul.

The young girl who had once lined up outside the barracks at dawn to be Vikir’s wife.

They had grown very close after Vikir rescued her from being mocked and sexually harassed by Bourgeois merchants.

‘Aheul was always weak. I was worried that she was getting weaker and weaker due to an unexplained illness, but now that I think about it, it might have been the glass beads that those merchants brought with them.’

Vikir found the earrings that were causing Aheul’s health to deteriorate and removed all the drugs that were in them, and she was able to regain her health.

But Vikir hadn’t seen the girl since leaving jungle.

“…You’ve grown up a lot.”

Vikir said with a somewhat dazed expression.

On the surface, the girl in front of him looked to be in her early to mid-30s.

However, what he heard was that she was actually closer to sixty.

Aheul gave him a watery gaze and said.

“It’s been a while, big brother.”

◆

“What happened?”

At Vikir’s question, Aheul told him everything.

After Vikir’s departure, trade opened up and Ballak began peace negotiations with the Empire in earnest.

At first, everything seemed to be going well.

It would have been like that if it weren’t for the ‘unusual’ that suddenly appeared one day.

Amdusias. Without Winston’s body, the demon appeared under its own power and attacked Ballak’s warriors.

‘I’ve come to capture the Madame of the Depths, but I can’t find it, so I need to catch you guys instead.’

He seemed to be gathering terrain for the Hell Tree, just simple entertainment.

But the demon’s entertainment demanded the blood of too many.

Ballak’s warriors had the battle of their lives against the unicorn, who had begun to lay waste to the village.

In the process, the chieftainess Akwilla was killed.

She died with a fatal wound on the horns of Amdusias.

She had never fully recovered from the wounds she had sustained in her battle with Adonai, and this proved to be the final straw.

“The other warriors were also scattered. The attacking unicorn was too strong….”

“Why did you end up here?”

“I was hiding in the ruins at the time, protecting the newborns. Then I woke up and realized I was here….”

Listening to Aheul’s story, Vikir nodded.

It made sense now.

It’s been a while since we’ve heard reports of the disappearance of Ballak’s warriors.

It makes sense that Aheul, who was in her early teens when she was swallowed up by the Hell Tree, would have aged so much since arriving on this plane.

It also explained why the middle-aged warriors who followed Aheul hadn’t recognized Vikir, as they would have been infants at the time.

“I see. That’s why your tattoos are so faded. They were done as infants, and the color faded as your skin stretched.”

Vikir turned his head and made eye contact with the female warriors he had captured earlier.

He remembered that when he had once taught the warriors of Ballak the Baskervilles’ fighting styles, the adult warriors had shown no interest in learning such things, but some of the very younger ones had followed him around, eager to learn them.

“You must be Ajin, and you must be Ami.”

“Huh!?”

“Hah!?”

The two middle-aged warriors who had been addressed by the names Vikir had scrounged from his memory each gulped down their huffs.

Meanwhile. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were questioning Vikir’s acquaintance with the so-called barbarians of Ballak.

Vikir kept his explanation short.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were stunned to hear that Vikir and the Ballak warriors were like family.

“You’re from the West, Vikir! Night Hound, Ballak’s hunting grounds, a student at the Colosseo Academy, and… how many identities do you have?”

“Amazing, a Ballak and an Imperial can live together.”

“Well, yes. I heard the Ballak warriors are very closed-minded.”

“That’s why you’re such a good archer, somehow….”

Vikir looked away again.

Aheul was looking apologetically at Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

In fact, the mission that the shipowners, that is, Ballak’s warriors, received was the same.

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※ Don’t let your guard down! Latecomers become increasingly stronger as time goes by! If you don’t want to be caught up, even if you’re a ship owner, you have to work hard, right?

※Recognized only when everyone has cleared the mission!

Aheul and the other warriors must also kill Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

But the good-hearted Aheul doesn’t want to kill them, so instead, she had no choice but to engage in a regular fight because they only took food.

“Didn’t you ever think about joining forces and doing something about it?”

“It’s not that we didn’t, but if we blatantly create a peaceful atmosphere, the fairies show up and ruin everything, like giving us missions where we have to kill each other outright….”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca nodded at Aheul’s words.

They, too, had been parted from Sinclaire in the pursuit of peace.

Aheul sighed deeply.

“I’m worried about what happened to the others, especially my brother and the chief….”

Aheul was worried about her brother, Ahun.

And the other one, the ‘she’ who remained the most intense in Vikir’s memory.

‘…Aiyen.’

Vikir stroked his chin for a moment.

They hadn’t been brought into this tower.

So what had happened to them?

“We’re lucky to be here, to be alive now, but what if… if those who didn’t make it here had suffered a more miserable fate….”

“….”

Vikir put a hand on Aheul’s shoulder.

“Don’t think bad thoughts. You’ll just have to go out and see for yourself.”

“…Can I get out of here?”

“Of course.”

Vikir told Aheul everything he knew about the tower.

The Hell Tree. The Worldview Absorber. Amdusias’s strange hobby.

Aheul’s mouth hung half open as she listened, almost as if it were a runescape.

“So… this place was created by a demon by piecing together parts of entire worlds, and if you clear a level, the world and its inhabitants are freed?”

“Half right, half wrong. There is no liberation. Until you clear the tower.”

Vikir remembered the Insectking he had encountered in the Black Sea not long ago.

The Insectking race who tried to leave the tower were struck by lightning and reduced to ashes.

Perhaps they had failed to make the escape they had hoped for.

‘This tower is especially unforgiving of quitters.’

Vikir had urged Aheul and the other Ballak warriors not to abandon the mission halfway through.

Whether it’s porridge or rice, you have to go to the end.

“My brother is still trustworthy.”

Aheul had been sending envious glances toward Vikir.

Then. Tudor stepped forward.

“…Uh, excuse me. Sorry to interrupt, but what about the mission?”

It was a reasonable question.

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※ Each ship owner has powerful powers! Living is inherently difficult~

※ Recognized only when everyone has cleared the mission!

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※ Don’t let your guard down! Latecomers become increasingly stronger as time goes by! If you don’t want to be caught up, even if you’re a ship owner, you have to work hard, right?

※ Recognized only when everyone has cleared the mission!

Both sides are given the same mission, which means killing the other group.

If you don’t, you can’t complete the mission. You’ll be stuck on this floor forever.

“…In the end, you have to choose.”

Pigi spoke up, his voice trembling with anxiety.

The Colosseo Academy or the Ballak.

Only one of the two groups could leave this floor alive.

So which one should die now?

That matter was entirely in Vikir’s hands.

“….”

“….”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca. Even Aheul and the rest of Ballak’s warriors stared at the tip of Vikir’s sword.

Then.

Vikir’s mouth, closed until now, opens.

“Do you trust me?”

Vikir looked at the Ballak warriors.

Needless to say, they all nodded, including Aheul.

They had all been children when Vikir was at the height of his heroism.

A generation that naturally heard all of Vikir’s deeds as legends and myths.

Everyone, including Aheul, bowed before Vikir.

“We will obey the words of hunting leader’s words.”

With that, Vikir nodded.

Then he turned and looked at Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

“And you guys?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca each spoke up.

“Of course we trust you, you’re our friend.”

“I’ve always felt that way, you’ve always been like a big brother to me, even though we’re the same age.”

“I believe anything Vikir says!”

“Hmm. This mission has been stalling since you arrived, and I can’t believe I don’t trust you. I won’t bet against you, so do whatever you want.”

Everyone agreed with Vikir.

Nodding.

Then Vikir bowed his head with a stern expression.

And then.

…Dengeng!

He swung his sword, beheading Aheul in front of him.

“ …Uh!?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Ballak’s warriors gasped.

Puff-puff-puck!

A barrage of sharp slashes traveled in an infinite orbit, decapitating them all in one fell swoop.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca’s heads rolled across the blood-soaked, reddened grass.

A flowing fountain of blood. Faces frozen in shock.

“….”

Vikir stood still in the center of where the bodies of all his friends lay, looking up at the sky.

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※ Each ship owner has powerful powers! Living is inherently difficult~

※ Recognized only when everyone has cleared the mission!

The mission was still not cleared.

Vikir had killed all those who trusted him and survived alone.

Soon, his dry lips also became heavy.

“…I also believe in you.”

Chapter 348

Key man (3)

◆

-<Return Scroll>/ Scrolls / Rank: ?

A scroll that allows you to return to the Tutorial Zone for one time only.

It contains the answer to the question, ‘Lord, where are you going?’

※Using this scroll will reset your level

A one-time use item received when you first leave the tower’s tutorial area.

The overwhelming majority of challengers to the Tower use this scroll early on.

This is a great item to have when you’re in a life-or-death situation, or when you’re faced with a mission that you just can’t seem to complete.

It’s a last resort, so to speak, to preserve one life.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca all looked surprised.

“You haven’t used this scroll before?”

“Great, I remember using it on the third floor.”

“I used it on the first floor….”

“Ugh! I used it right before I died on the third floor, and I was so pissed that all my hard-earned levels were reset!”

In addition, Ballak’s warriors had also used up all of their scrolls before reaching the Flowing River.

Vikir decided it was time for him to use it, too.

“….”

Before tearing up the scroll, Vikir noted the words at the bottom of the item’s description.

Debuff that resets your level to 1 upon use.

Not that it matters when your life is on the line, but it’s still a pretty significant loss.

‘I knew it, and I’ve been saving up golden candies all this time without leveling up.’

Vikir held up the scroll.

Suddenly, the conversation between Amdusias and Pope Nabokov I that he had overheard before entering the tower flashed through his mind.

‘You, too, will eventually suffer the same fate as me. You will deny God, humanity, and yourself three times.’

‘Holholhol. Horse head. You are right, we Quovadis are descendants of those who ‘denied God three times’. … But there’s a story behind that.’

The First Apostle denied the Prophet Lun three times before the dawn rooster crowed.

One day, he received a call from the resurrected Lun.

After answering all three questions, he was finally forgiven.

Then he turned and shouted at the departing prophet.

“Quo Vadis, Domine ? (Lord, where are you going?)”

The Prophet replied

‘…We go back to the beginning to be persecuted again.’

Vikir mulled over the words on the scroll.

To return to the beginning again.

And so on.

As Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Aheul, and the rest of Ballak’s warriors looked on in concern, Vikir tore the scroll.

Buuk-.

The moment the tough scroll was torn in two, a brilliant ball of light rose up and enveloped Vikir’s entire body.

Then.

“Vikir!”

Pigi called out.

“Can, We can all see each other again, right?”

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca, who were beside him, turned their heads as if he were talking nonsense.

“Of course we will, man!”

“Vikir will never be defeated.”

“He’ll clear the tower for sure!”

But Pigi was still uneasy nonetheless.

Pigi’s pupils, which were trembling slightly, seemed to reflect something different from what was reflected in the pupils of the other friends.

And towards that Pigi.

“…Wait for me.”

With a dry smile, Vikir left only one short word.

◆

Kiiiiing-

A pain like an awl piercing his eardrums shot through his head.

With an unpleasant vibrating sound, Vikir opened his eyes.

<Underground Level 1. Tutorial area>

Dirty bats were flying around in front of him, and the ceiling was slowly descending.

It was the same scene as when Vikir first entered the tower, except the rats had changed to bats.

Then.

[ Hello ? ]

Flesh and internal organs dripping from the distorted features, a lump of meat flapping its ugly, dried wings.

[ I am a ‘fairy’ in charge of the tower’s guide? ]

The fairy appeared. Just like when he first entered the tower.

The creature purses its swollen lips and utters a formal statement.

[ From now on, it’s first-come, first-served…… uh ? ]

However, the fairy never finished the line that was supposed to be uttered.

…Grasp! Bam!

Vikir, who had closed the distance in an instant, grabbed the fairy with a vicious hand and slammed it to the ground.

The grip strength that erupted from a strength stat of 798 was not at a level that even a fairy could ignore.

Moreover.

Ppug!

Vikir plunged the Beelzebub awl, coated in Pigi’s blood, deep into the fairy’s belly button.

[ Eub eub eub eub eub ? ]

The fairy struggled a few times and then died.

With a look of disbelief in its eyes.

“What’s it like to be the victim, is this new to you?”

There was no way the dead fairy could answer, but Vikir asked anyway.

Vikir’s mind flashed back to the faces of the students who had died in the tower, and the faces of the fairies who had watched with giggles.

With that, Vikir kicked the fairy’s body aside as if it were garbage.

Then he drew the sack that hung from his waist.

Walgraak-!

The sack was filled with golden candies.

Vikir scooped them all into his mouth, chewed, and swallowed.

Crunch-clack-clack!

The hard pieces of candy quickly melted in his mouth.

At the same time, a loud notification sounded in his ears.

[Level 1 Warrior Vikir has leveled up!]

[Level 2 Warrior Vikir has leveled up …]

[Level 3 Warrior Vikir…]

[Level 4…]

Levels rising at an incredible rate.

Soon, Vikir’s status window began to show changes accompanied by a large vibration.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 100 (%)

-Title: ‘Gutter Rat Hunter’, ‘Hell’s Dog’, ‘Daylily Lumberjack’, ‘Majin Executioner’, ‘Black Sea King’s Executioner’, ‘Demonic Dragon Great Rival’, ‘The Leading Boatman’

-Stats

Strength: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

?Agility: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

?Stamina: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

?Physical Resistance: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

?Magic resistance: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

?Reflexes: 1,000 (+98,941) = 99,941

Now we don’t need to tie up levels.

Vikir quickly maxed out his level and was back to where he was before entering the tower.

What’s more, the base stats he’d built up at level 1 had exploded with his level increase, including three special stats he wasn’t naturally born with.

“…!”

Strength. Agility. Stamina. I can feel my basic three stats are much stronger than they were before I entered the tower.

But that’s hardly a perk compared to my newfound talents.

Reflexes. Physical resistance. Magic resistance. These three talents are innate, unavailable to anyone but those favored by the gods and the world.

Vikir had succeeded in blossoming them, developing them to the extreme.

The invisible became visible and the inaudible became audible.

This immense sense of exaltation was something he had not felt even when he first stepped on the threshold of the 8th Form.

‘If now… maybe…’

Vikir drew his sword.

Whoosh!

A crimson aura coursed through Beelzebub’s sword.

With that, Vikir took a deep breath and cast the ultimate sword technique he had spent so many years honing in the flowing rivers.

The 8th Form of Baskerville.

It was something that he hadn’t accomplished much with since his first clue in the Tower of Stabbing, and could only master with the blessing of Saint Dolores.

Vikir’s swordsmanship, which was technically only 7.5 Forms, finally shone.

…Flash!

Turning The Sky Upside Down (翻天).

Seven giant teeth. The 8th tooth, which had grown to almost the same size as the others, ferociously tore through the air.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The strikes, swung in eight directions, bit into the ceiling that was slowly descending.

…Kugung!

The ceiling descended and stopped slightly.

Its movement had slowed, but it was still descending.

‘It’s about as strong as the fist of the Demonic Dragon I met before.’

Vikir watched the tutorial ceiling descend.

Next, Pigi’s blood coated the hilt of Beelzebub’s sword from the leather scabbard at his waist.

Crackle!

The newly fiery aura prepared to reveal its eight teeth once more.

Hounds. The Hound of Iron Blood Swordsman. It leaps forward with its fur all over its body standing up sharply and with a fierce look in its eyes.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

Eight sword strikes hit the ceiling again.

But this time, it was different.

“…!”

Vikir felt a strange sensation on his fingertips.

It was a supersensory sensation he would never have felt if it weren’t for his nearly 100,000 reflexes stat.

It was beyond the ceiling.

Something evil and sinister was lurking and sitting on top of the first level of the basement.

‘Common sense tells us that if we want to go up to the ground, we should go further up from the basement level.’

Vikir poured more and more power into Beelzebub.

And then… it started to respond.

Ku-deuddeudeuk!

The ceiling stopped its descent, and then it shook violently.

…Creak, creak, creak!

And then it began to crack with tremendous force.

At the same time, an enormous mana storm began to rage.

A wind that not only crushed the body with its powerful wind pressure, but also contained a strange heat that caused the mana in his body to boil over and run wild.

But Vikir remained standing, unmoving, and withstood the mana storm.

Neither the wind pressure that blew him away nor the magic waves that shook the mana in his body could help him.

This was because Vikir’s physical and magic resistance stats were ridiculously high.

And Vikir was staring sharply through the gusts of wind from this fierce mana storm that was blowing through the cracks in the ceiling.

‘…There is an answer.’

A high Reflexes stat will give you a clear view of what lies beyond, even through the fluctuating wind in real time.

<Amdusias, the ‘5th Corpse’>

Danger Rating : S+

Size: ?

Found in: The Serpent’s Womb, deep within the Gates of Destruction.

-Also known as the 5th corpse.

A natural enemy of mankind, one of the ten plagues known as incomprehensible and unkillable.

“I will take away the lives of the first born that year.”

– The Book of the Ten Commandments 10: Above –

Instead of the holy and sacred energy that is always mentioned in myths, it is a giant unicorn full of only hostility and evil.

[…How could a human even reach this place!?]

The 5th Demon King that had corrupted Winston, the Principal of Colosseo Academy, was hiding right there.

Chapter 350

Outside the Tower (2)

◆

[This is impossible…]

Amdusias stares up into the air in disbelief.

Size in the mental world is the size of a thoughts. It’s how much weight you carry on your shoulders.

However, the size of Vikir’s ego that was visible before his eyes was truly enormous.

Something that could not be explained unless one had experienced the full weight of karma, infinite doom, and the destruction of an entire world.

How could a single human being carry such a large and heavy burden?

How can such a being be here!

[What in the world are you, who are you, where did you come from, where did you grow up, to have such visions in your mind…]

Amdusias asked in a trembling voice.

But Vikir didn’t answer.

He only repeated a single word to himself, like a mantra.

“Demons kill.”

A hound from the Age of Destruction, a world where everything burned and rotted.

Carrying the grudges, the anger, and the mission of the entire world, Vikir’s mind is so deep, so vast, so dark that even Amdusias cannot fathom it.

Ku-gugugugugu!

Vikir raised his fist, each finger like a giant mountain range.

He slammed it down on Amdusias.

Quack!

The entire mental world shook.

An impact that could easily bring about the destruction of a world.

[Kuhugh!?]

Amdusias was slammed down by the giant fist.

At the same time.

…Wajangchang!

The mental world maintained by Amdusias’ mental power began to shatter.

Cracks rippled through the air. Amdusias’s magic field was fluctuating uneasily.

[Oh, no! Hell…!]

But Amdusias hadn’t even finished his sentence.

The owner of this mental world is Vikir, and you cannot leave until the owner lets you go.

Kwakwang! Kwang! Kwakwakwakwang!

The Age of Destruction is shattered by one punch after another.

…Jjeojeojeog!

Amdusias’ magic field is completely shattered.

Ttudug! Ujijijijijig!

The entire Hell Tree began to shake.

◆

“…?”

It was a small start.

A man who had pitched a tent in front of the Hell Tree, thinking of his children who had entered the Hell Tree, raised his head.

The Hell Tree, which hadn’t budged no matter what the heroes had done to it, had just tilted slightly to the side.

‘Did I see it wrong?’

The man scratched his head.

But he wasn’t mistaken.

Kugugugugu…

Hell Tree was definitely leaning to the side.

Slowly, faintly, enough that most of the people gathered didn’t even notice.

“Huh!?”

His eyes, which had been unraveling from sleepiness, snapped open.

He hurriedly opened his mouth, waking his wife who was sleeping next to him.

“Honey, wake up, I think it just moved…”

But he didn’t finish his sentence.

Peoeoeoeong! Kwakwang! Ujijijijig!

This is because the Hell Tree suddenly caused a loud explosion and twisted.

The roots of the Hell Tree, which were spread out in the shape of teeth, dried up, and the main roots snapped like broken bones.

Every time that happens, the concentrated sap inside pops out, and as soon as it hits the atmosphere, it immediately boils and vaporizes.

Pssssshhhhh…

Luckily, the aftermath of the explosion was mostly directed at the sky, so the parents and professors gathered around were not harmed.

However.

“Monsters! Monsters are coming out!”

“Dungeon! Is it a gate!”

“Prepare for battle!”

The problem was that the Hell Tree burst open and a myriad of monsters crawled out of it.

Orcs, hellhounds, ogres, goblins, harpies, and more were leaping out of the Hell Tree with all their might.

Parents and professors scrambled to their feet.

The heroes, led by Cervantes the Spear King and Roderick the Archon.

…But.

“What? What are they doing?”

“They’re running away.”

“They don’t look like they have any intentions of fighting.”

The demons that had emerged from the Hell Tree were still running away with their butts in the air.

Some of them were weeping and kissing the ground.

It was as if they hadn’t come out to fight, but had been imprisoned somewhere and had been lucky enough to be released.

They weren’t the only ones.

Various humanoid race, such as Insectking, Elves, Dwarves, and Beastmen, also come out of the Hell Tree and run away.

Among them were the barbarians of the western jungle.

The warrior tribe of Ballak. Most of those who emerged from the Hell Tree were young, pale-faced boys and girls, but they were all seasoned warriors.

They broke through the parents and professors, who were shocked, and flew over the barrier like the wind and disappeared.

Slowly, the parents and professors realized what was happening.

“Surely the things that were trapped in the Hell Tree have come out!”

“My daughter! Where is my daughter!”

“Oooh, my son, This mom is here!”

Everyone who had been waiting anxiously was soon able to recognize the faces they had missed so much.

“Aaahhhh! Where else is this place?”

“Hmm? The Academy? Have we come to another floor?”

“Huh? I thought I had been eaten by a Daylily?”

“Hmph! Where am I? I must have fallen asleep in the common room of Paradise…”

The challengers were trapped inside the tower. The students of Colosseo Academy have all returned to their families.

The dead, the living, those who gave up, and those who tried, all came back alive equally.

“Oh, my son!”

“Oh, my daughter!”

“Oh, my graduate student!”

Everywhere, there were tearful reunions between parents and children, teachers and students.

“Awww mom, I’ve missed you for the past 10 years!”

“Dad, don’t be so dramatic, I was only locked up for three days!”

“What are you talking about, you kids, it’s been months since you were trapped in the Hell Tree!”

“More than that, father. Did you get the letter I sent you, apparently from a place called Lost Paradise…”

“Yes, I received it. Thanks to that, I was able to feel at ease.”

Talks about recent events continue here and there.

Passssssss…

In the meantime, the Hel Tree bracelets on the students’ wrists have burned black and disappeared.

Meanwhile. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca have also emerged from the Hell Tree.

“Unbelievable! Wow, we really came out! Really!”

“He’s cleared the tower! Wow! Hooray!”

Tudor and Bianca hugged each other as soon as they were outside.

“Ugh! I thought I was going to be stuck in there for the rest of my life!”

“Huh! Don’t cry, you’ll make me cry too!”

But just as they were overwhelmed with joy at being out, they became conscious of the many eyes on them.

“…Huh!?”

Tudor and Bianca, who had fallen into an awkward silence.

“Son!”

“Daughter!”

Cervantes and Roderick came over and pulled them apart.

Sancho and Pigi also burst into tears in the arms of their families.

“Phew.”

Outside, Dolores is also breaking out in a cold sweat.

She could see Mozgus running in the distance, tears streaming down his face, and the face of Pope Nabokov I behind him, but her gaze went elsewhere first.

“…Are you successful?”

Dolores muttered in a small voice, looking down into the abyss below the sinking pit.

Then.

Triplets fell from the side, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

“Huh! What is it? Did we come out?”

“Did we come out?”

“Is it?”

They quickly realized what was going on.

Someone had cleared the tower, and they seemed to know who it was.

Then.

A grim-faced young man stepped in front of the Baskerville triplets.

Osiris Le Baskerville.

After staying here for quite some time, he asked the half-brothers in front of him.

“I’m glad to see you seem unharmed.”

“Thank you.”

Highbro bows his head in representation.

Osiris nodded, then looked around and asked.

“…Where is he?”

He refers to Vikir.

And there were more than one person looking for Vikir.

Dolores, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro, and countless others whose lives had been saved by Vikir all looked up.

“And what about him?”

“Vikir! He’s the reason we’re alive!”

“Yes. He was a true hero.”

“I said I would definitely show my gratitude if I could get out of the tower…”

“Uh, there is no way, except for him!”

“Are you sure he didn’t get out?”

All the students had managed to escape, only Vikir was not there.

“….”

That was when Professor Banshee Morgue, who came running in a huff after hearing the news that all the students had safely returned, had his expression darken.

…Kwakwang!

A pillar of light of enormous size rose up from the very center of the Abyss where the Hell Tree sank..

It was thick and long, like an ascending dragon, and radiated tremendous power.

An aura. A pillar of aura.

It was a divine status that could not even be imitated by anyone other than a being in the Supreme Realm.

“What, what is that?”

“Master, it’s the aura of the master!”

Even The Spear King Donquixote’s Cervantes and The Archon Usher’s Roderick were so shocked that their eyes popped out.

Swordmaster. A solid aura that could only be manifested by a supreme being.

All eyes were focused on this absolute and bizarre phenomenon that had suddenly appeared.

And.

Someone tore the curtain of the abyss and soared above it.

A being whose sword radiates the Sword Master’s aura like a black sun.

Vikir was there.

Chapter 354

Crime and Punishment (1)

◆

Vikir’s line from last night was featured on the front page of every newspaper the next day.

[Breaking News] Night Hound Arrested!

[Breaking News] The identity of the Night Hound has been revealed…, and it’s a first-year student at Colosseo Academy!?

[Exclusive] “I am Night Hound.” The identity of Night Hound, the villain who terrorized the Imperial Capital!

[Update] Night Hound is revealed to be the illegitimate son of an iron-blooded swordsman, causing a ripple of shock …!

Night Hound’s identity is revealed to be Vikir Van Baskerville, the illegitimate son of Ironblood Swordsman Baskerville!

Vikir’s official charges were as follows.

1. Murder and escape from the Baskervilles.

2. Assassination of Cardinal Humbert and Evangelist Quilt of the Quovadis Family.

3. Assassination of Patriarch Bartolomeo of the Bourgeois family.

4. Charged with involvement in the assassination and disappearance of numerous other prominent persons.

.

.

These are just a few of the major charges.

Night Hound, a fearsome villain who has shaken the Empire for years.

The Colosseo Academy has been the most affected by the revelation of his true identity.

Whenever students gathered in groups of three or more, they would talk about it.

“Oh my god… that scary monster was our classmate, I can’t believe it.”

“How did it hide so nonchalantly? That’s really scary.”

“Well, didn’t he help us when we were trapped in the Hell Tree?”

“It must be a coincidence. Or is it the killer’s two faces? You never know.”

“Either way, it’s terrible, really. I understand he was in the newspaper department, so he wrote a column criticizing himself? There is no such thing as deception.”

“Dude, I was in the room next door to him, it was so creepy! I could always hear the sound of a sword being sharpened in the next room….”

“Me too! I ate with him once in group practice! He was so expressionless, it was kind of creepy.”

“Ugh, I used to run into him at the gym all the time~ I almost got killed too!”

By far, public opinion was negative. Which is to be expected.

The image of Night Hound that had been steadily forming in the newspapers was that of a villainous threat to the tranquility of the Empire.

But there were a few who disagreed with the majority.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and others.

“Have you already forgotten what happened in the Hell Tree, all thanks to Vikir… those ungrateful things.”

Sancho nodded as he listened to Tudor’s mutterings.

Sancho, who is always deep in his heart, did not pay attention to what happened with Vikir yesterday.

“Because Vikir first coldly drew the line, he must have shaken off what little burden he had in his heart. He’s a deep thinker to the end.”

“Exactly. Vikir took measures to prevent sparks from flying to us, so he kept his distance.”

Pigi muttered in a grim voice.

Then Bianca, next to him, snorted.

“Ugh. How can you fool anyone with that kind of behavior? You know, me, Vikir, and Sinclaire. It’s really immature of you to hide your true feelings.”

“Are you immature? How could you do that in the midst of the moment, with all those tears and snotty noses calling you a traitor?”

“What! I, when!”

Tudor’s sarcasm sets Bianca off.

But their verbal sparring, which would normally have lasted hours, dies down within seconds.

Neither of them had any energy left to fight.

Even Tudor, usually a cheerful man, sounded as dead as grass.

“What do you think we can do for Vikir?”

“…But one thing’s for sure, we can’t stay like this.”

“That’s right, we have to do something! It’s a trial! Shall we attend as an audience member and shout slogans?”

“Nah, you’ll just get dragged out of there. We need something a little more real and immediate…”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca began to cross their arms.

Just then.

“Let us help too.”

A low voice came from behind them.

They turned to see a group of students standing on their toes.

Gordon. Underdog. Granola. Highbro, Middlebro. Lowbro.

All of them had been involved in some way with Vikir within the Hell Tree.

“I-all of us-are alive because of Vikir, and I owe him a favor.”

“I’m glad I met him, too, so I could atone for my sins. If it weren’t for Vikir, I’d be the demon’s plaything forever.”

“I don’t like Vikir, but… there’s a girl I care about and she seems to be very worried about him.”

“We protect our lord.”

“We protect.”

“Protect.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca weren’t the only ones thinking about Vikir.

And from the very back of the group, one person walked out.

Student Council President Dolores.

She was a longtime supporter of Night Hound. Since the days when everyone, even Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, had criticized Night Hounds.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca’s faces light up when they realize that they’re on the same newspaper staff.

Dolores, meanwhile, spoke in a calm voice.

“This is a very bad situation, guys.”

Her words made everyone tense.

Vikir had severed all ties just before turning himself in, so no one around him was affected.

However, that meant that no one was there to defend or support him, and he had to bear the full weight of his punishment alone.

Dolores continued in a calm voice.

“The Baskervilles claimed that the illegitimate son who murdered the second son and escaped was acting on his own, and that the red horn that summoned the Knights was stolen. The Knights were sent out to retrieve it in the first place.”

Cutting off the tail. The Baskervilles issued an official statement denying any connection to Vikir.

The powers that could have treated Vikir as a nobleman and allowed him to avoid the death penalty have turned their attention.

Dolores bit her lip.

“Vikir-nim will most likely be sentenced to death, so we need to convince the jurors of this trial as far in advance as possible.”

The judge in the trial of Night Hound was the Emperor, or his representative.

The jurors are seven, and each of the Seven Families that support the Empire sends a Patriarch, or Patriarch’s representative, to attend.

Dolores scanned her surroundings.

Fortunately, the social status of the students here is generally high.

Dolores gathered students with the same goals and intentions and divided the work.

“Tudor, I want you to convince the patriarch of the Donquixote family, and Bianca, I want you to convince the patriarch of the Usher family. Sancho will appeal to the mercenary guilds of the north for the truth, and Pigi will work with me to produce a newspaper. I will, of course, appeal to the Pope of Quovadis Family with the whole truth. Gordon and Underdog, you will persuade the Aristocrats, Barons, Commoners, and Student Council officers, respectively. Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, I want you to gather as much information as you can from Baskerville Family, in case there are any possible extenuating circumstances…..”

After speaking, Dolores closed her eyes tightly and bowed her head.

“Please, guys!”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and everyone else nodded, their faces determined.

“You don’t have to ask, it’s something we’d love to do, and we’ll do everything we can.”

The students gathered in a circle around Dolores and spoke in unison.

“…Thank you.”

Dolores looked back at everyone with a moist gaze.

Even though there was nothing she could do about it now, she felt as if a hole had been opened in her chest.

It feels like progress, albeit a little.

…Just then.

“What the. A real kid idea.”

A sarcastic voice came from behind them.

Where everyone’s eyes turn, they see a female student with red-haired hair burning like a flame, grinning.

“Hi, I’m here because Vikir told me to get acquainted with you guys.”

On her chest patch, a name tag reads ‘Camus Morgue’.

“…?”

Dolores squinted and looked at Camus.

As if demanding an explanation for what she had just said.

As if on cue, Camus jumped right to the point.

“Your intention to convince the jurors to reduce Vikir’s sentence is good, but do you really think Vikir wants that?”

“…What do you mean?”

Dolores spoke up, representing everyone’s questions.

Camus shook her head and tapped her fingers against her head.

“Use your head.”

“….”

Everyone’s breath caught in their throats at the sound of Camus’s words. Never in their wildest dreams did they think anyone would say such a thing to Dolores.

But Dolores was unfazed.

“I thought this was the best I could do… You don’t think so?”

“Of course not. Because what you’re about to do isn’t the best, and it’s not what Vikir would want.”

Dolores’ expression hardened at the continued provocation.

She asks in a hard tone.

“What would Vikir want, and what are your plans?”

Then Camus smiled, darker than before.

“I used to be like you. I didn’t know anything. What Vikir wanted.”

“…?”

“But now I think I know. What he’s preparing for, what he’s waiting for, what he’s fighting for. All of it.”

“…!”

For a moment, the smile wiped from Camus’s face.

“Leave Vikir alone. He’s not the kind of man who needs your worries.”

“Yeah, how would you know?”

Tudor asked, and Camus gave him a pathetic look.

“Then don’t you know, he’s got a brain. And that he’s carrying a mission so heavy that normal people don’t even dare to understand it.”

“….”

Everyone knows that.

They’ve seen Vikir’s many accomplishments at the Colosseo Academy and in the Hell Tree.

Camus continued.

“Vikir’s every move is probably calculated, perhaps a lifelong plan, and it’s not something we dare to worry about or interfere with.”

“…I admit that, but does that mean there’s nothing we can do?”

At Dolores’ words, Camus shook her head.

“We must do what we can.”

“And what is that?”

“Simple, we do what Vikir has been doing all this time. Stopping it.”

“…Stop? What Vikir has been doing all this time is stopping what?”

Dolores’s question resonates with everyone.

And under their gazes, Camus pulls something out of her bosom and places it on the table.

Tsk.

Everyone’s faces hardened as they saw what was on the table.

It was a bloodstained mask, a picaresque mask symbolizing Night Hound.

As everyone looked up in bewilderment, Camus spoke.

“The gate that is about to open. … ‘The Gate of Destruction’.”

Chapter 355

Crime and Punishment (2)

◆

Nakajaniye, the Great Judge at the center of the ecliptic.

Standing before the place where the guilty are judged, Night Hound stands still with his characteristic expressionless face.

Despite everyone’s worries, Vikir was quite at peace.

‘…I’ve finished my work at the Academy.’

With a lot of things checked off his to-do list, a weight was lifted from his shoulders.

Everything was going the way he expected, and now it was really just a matter of finishing touches.

That’s why Vikir feels lighthearted. In fact, he’s even looking forward to it a bit.

Meanwhile, there are many eyes on Vikir as he stands there with a nonchalant expression.

First of all, there were the members of the Seven Great Families of the Empire: Baskerville the Iron-Blooded Swordsman, Morgue the Mage, Quovadis the Faithful, Bourgeois the Conglomerate, Leviathan the Poisonous Dread, Donquixote the Spearman, and Usher the Archer Divine Palace.

Representatives of the families were seated separately in the courtroom as jurors, while other family members were seated in the audience.

With the Emperor absent from the trial, the representative of the Imperial Family, dressed in a nun’s robe, a distinctive garb often worn by members of the Imperial Family, sits at the bench and conducts the trial in a mechanical, clerical manner.

“Juror Hugo Le Baskerville, Iron Blood Swordsman Baskerville”

Juror Hugo Le Baskerville, representing the Baskerville family.

He was sitting in a wheelchair with his back to the judge.

The deputy called on Hugo and asked.

“Attempted poisoning of the second son, Seth Le Baskerville, and the patriarch, Hugo himself. You have accused Vikir Van Baskerville of the theft of the Red Whistle, a sacred item that could mobilize the family’s military power; is that correct?”

“….”

Hugo turned away and did not answer.

The poison had left him too weak to move, let alone answer.

Instead, his eldest son, Osiris, stood beside him and nodded.

“….”

With an extremely dry expression.

With that, the deputy ended the Ironblood swordsman’s final interrogation.

Then he abbreviated.

“The allegations against the Baskervilles are as follows. While the crimes of rebellion, premeditated murder, and the poisoning of a patriarch are serious and heinous, the accused is a member of the Baskerville family and therefore deserves to be treated as a nobleman. I therefore request a verdict of mitigating circumstances.”

There was no objection.

The deputy took his eyes off Baskerville and looked at Morgue next to him.

Morgue’s juror, Raspane Morgue.

She stood over the judge, her expression stiff and rigid.

The deputy was still reading from the papers in a bland voice.

“Morgue’s case is as follows. Although the crimes charged are grave and heinous – rebellion, murder with intent to kill, and poisoning of a patriarch – the accused is entitled to the treatment of a nobleman. Therefore, I ask for a verdict of mitigating circumstances.”

Raspane Morgue came to the same conclusion as Baskerville.

No matter how grave the offense, a man of noble blood should be treated as such.

Raspane spoke in a calm voice.

“…The previous precedent for this can be found in the 47 Men’s Riot, 35 years ago.”

Back then, the problem was much more serious.

It could have overthrown an empire.

“There were two heroes who put down the 47: Winston, who is no longer with us, and Orca, who is no longer with us. Their sacrifice ensured that what could have been a dangerous situation was quelled early.”

Everyone in the courtroom swallowed hard at Raspane’s words.

“But what was the verdict in the end? Despite the strong pleas for death from the two heroes, Winston and Orca, who quelled the riot, the Marquis de Sade, the ringleader of the riot, was not sentenced to death in the end. Wasn’t it because of the ‘respect for the Great Nobility’?”

In other words, Vikir, too, has the blood of a great nobleman, so the death penalty is too much.

Raspane concluded with these words.

Following her, Nabokov I, a juror from the Quovadis family, and Damian, a juror from the Bourgeois family, expressed similar opinions.

“Holholhol… that kid is a devout believer in Lun. I realize we have to take into account the circumstances of the dead, but I can’t help but be merciful. I think the death penalty is excessive.”

“I believe the accused has already paid his dues. The astronomical amount of money he’s put on the line shows that he’s remorseful, and I, too, believe that the death penalty is excessive.”

Baskerville, Morgue, Quovadis, and Bourgeois.

Four of the seven major families argued for Vikir’s commutation.

But there were others who disagreed.

“This is nonsense, if we don’t execute a murderer who has killed so many people, who are we going to execute?”

“Exactly, I think we should at least isolate him forever so he can’t crawl back into society, and the death penalty is the best way to do that.”

The attitude of the jurors in Usher and Donquixote was decidedly hostile.

They were representing the patriarchs Cervantes and Roderick, both of whom were in need of nursing care as a result of the Hell Tree incident.

Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte, and Usher P Madeline.

These young men and women were each patriarch siblings and stood before the jurors in the capacity of the family’s representative.

They were also the uncle and aunt of Tudor and Bianca, respectively.

And, finally, Hobbes de Leviathan, the patriarch of the extreme poisonous family of Leviathan, broke the heavy silence and delivered the final verdict.

“…Death, and no other punishment will make him pay the price he deserves.”

Four of the seven families were arguing for mitigating circumstances, and the other three were arguing for the death penalty without mitigating circumstances.

Even the Imperial family’s representative was perplexed, for he had never seen a trial with such a divided jury.

He looked back at Vikir and asked.

“Do you have any last words before the verdict?”

Vikir looked up at that.

“….”

His calm eyes swept over the judge.

Hugo, sitting in his wheelchair, his back turned, his expression unreadable.

Osiris, his brow furrowed.

Raspane’s face is stony as she thinks of her daughter.

Nabokov I and Damian, who look like they’re having a bad day.

The other three jurors have different expressions.

Passamonte, Madeline, and Hobbes.

On the outside, they appear calm, just, and fair, but in reality, they harbor evil intentions that are uglier and more hideous than anything else.

‘…Almost all of the remaining Ten Corpses have come out.’

Vikir kept a sharp eye on the three remaining demons.

Originally, the ‘Gates of Destruction’ could only be opened if ten demons gathered together.

But with only four of them left alive, it was likely that they would have to resort to more extreme measures to accomplish their mission.

And it was clear that they would want to eliminate Vikir first.

‘I’d be happy to play along with your plans.’

Vikir also had a separate goal, and it did not particularly conflict with the three demons’ goals.

So Vikir simply closed his eyes in silence and swallowed all the arguments.

Meanwhile, those listening in on the trial were growing impatient with Vikir’s demeanor.

“Look at him, look at him, look at him, look at his shamelessness!”

“He killed so many people and he doesn’t even show any remorse!”

“ …I thought you were a hero, how disappointing.”

“The death penalty! Evil people like him should be put to death!”

“Let’s show him that justice is alive!”

The uproar barely subsided after the guards left.

The imperial family’s representative descended the stairs, the hem of a nun’s robe fluttering, and asked

“I’ll ask you again, this is the last time. Do you have anything to say before the verdict?”

Only then did Vikir answer.

His eyes were fixed on the imperial representative, but his voice was directed elsewhere.

“Retreating is not running away, and it is not wise to wait when danger outstrips hope. A wise man knows how to save today for tomorrow and does not risk everything in one day.”

From a brave knight of the Donquixote family long ago.

“….”

“….”

“….”

Hearing this, Passamonte, Madeline, and Hobbes exchanged meaningful glances.

Then, the verdict was in.

The Emperor’s representative read the verdict in a reverent voice, with the hem of the nun’s robe hanging down.

“The defendant, Vikir Van Baskerville. He is a devout follower of Lun, son of the Baskervilles Family, evangelist for the Quovadis, prospective son-in-law of Morgue, and godfather of the Bourgeois.”

This means that he is a scion of the Baskervilles, is on good religious terms with the Quovadis, has a marriage contract with the Morgue, and is considered by Damian of the Bourgeois to be the godfather of their deceased daughter.

“But the accused has committed the unpardonable felony of murder on several occasions, and the offense is the more grave and heinous because each of the persons he has murdered has played a vital role in the security and progress of the Empire. Accordingly…!”

The final verdict came.

“The death penalty is denied, with due consideration for the noble lineage of the accused.”

The words brought a sigh of relief from Baskerville, Morgue, Quovadis, and Bourgeois.

“However, given the gravity and viciousness of the accused’s crimes, a mere sentence of imprisonment is deemed unnecessary.”

Another sigh, this time from Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan.

Now, Vikir’s fate was officially sealed.

“I hereby sentence the defendant, Vikir Van Baskerville, to ‘3,021 life terms of imprisonment without parole’ …. Furthermore, the place of confinement shall not be a ‘general prison,’ but a ‘special prison’ intended for the permanent social isolation of felons.”

Life imprisonment without parole. That too over 3,000 times.

This meant that even if he lived and died once, he would not get out of prison until the process was repeated three thousand times and twenty-one more times.

The sentence reflected the court’s determination to never reintegrate Vikir back into society.

…However, what Vikir had in mind before the sentencing was something else.

Not a ‘normal prison’, but a ‘special prison’. This could only mean one thing.

‘…Nouvelle Vague.’

It was a prison that existed at the very edge of the Empire.

A prison so terrifying that once imprisoned, even their souls were trapped there.

Vikir is imprisoned in a prison so harsh and horrific that death is considered preferable.

For a life sentence that will last a whopping 3,021 times!

Baskerville, Morgue, the Quovadis, and Bourgeois audience members are in a somber mood.

On the other hand, the audience of Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan is buoyant.

A swirl of mixed emotions.

In the middle of it all, Vikir was quietly sharpening the sword in his heart.

‘…This is the end game.’

End game.

A few chess pieces left on the board. The battle becomes extremely fierce.

It was the beginning of the final chapter.

Chapter 357

Voluntary Escort (1)

◆

The day of the transfer had finally arrived.

The streets were packed with people wondering about the identity of the Hound of the Night, a felon on his way to Nouvelle Vague, the world’s worst prison.

“Oh my God, I never thought the Night Hound would be caught.”

“I read in the newspaper that he turned himself in.”

“…Why on earth would he turn himself in?”

“I don’t know. I’m more curious about what it looks like.”

“Well, he’s a serial killer who’s killed tons of people, so of course he’s gotta look creepy.”

“I’ve heard rumors that he’s over six feet tall. He’s got horrible tattoos all over his body.”

In the morning, a huge crowd gathered to watch Night Hound being transported.

Then a carriage began to pull up in the distance.

A moving carriage, surrounded by dozens of layers of guards.

On top of it was a cage of blackened grates.

Additionally, there are handcuffs on both wrists of the criminal, shackles on both ankles, and chains wrapped around the body.

All of these were special restraints made of ‘BDISSEM’, a mystical substance that neutralizes mana and forcibly binds all physical forces.

A mark reserved for felons who were to be sentenced to death or imprisoned in the Nouvelle Vague.

Whenever a prisoner is escorted in wearing it, clouds of people gather to watch.

But this time was different.

It wasn’t the BDISSEM restraints that caught the crowd’s attention, nor was it the largest convoy ever.

“…That’s Night Hound?”

“Isn’t that a kid?”

“No. Isn’t that some kind of photo shoot?”

The sight of Vikir’s face, sitting alone and silent in the cage, caused the crowd to quietly put down the rotten food and rocks in their hands.

“….”

“….”

“….”

No one dares to shout or throw garbage in Vikir’s face.

His aura is untouchable. A razor-sharp momentum that makes the air around him tingle, even without mana.

Vikir moves forward, silently, without much fuss.

Then.

“You, you bastard, my father’s enemy!”

A boy ran through the crowd.

He flung the dagger he held in his hand with such skill that it flew through the gap between the many guards.

But of course.

Thwack!

The boy’s dagger was intercepted by a long sword.

Black hair that stood up like pointed ears. Eyes as red as rubies. A uniform of black and brown.

It was Countess Isabella la Baskerville, the leader of the Doberman Knights of the Iron Blood Swordsman Baskerville.

She was one of the Seven Counts of the Baskerville family and the one in charge of Vikir’s convoy today.

“…It’s bittersweet to have to send my nephew to the Nouvelle Vague.”

A somewhat distant blood relative who is equivalent to Vikir’s 7th cousin’s aunt.

Though they had only met in person twice in the past, once at Seth’s execution and once during the Hell Tree incident, she genuinely felt sorry for Vikir.

“I should have been present at that great banquet. If you had joined the Doberman Knights, none of this would have happened…”

But Vikir had something else to say.

“I am having a hard time because my successor, Professor Sadi, is gone.”

Isabella was originally a member of the imperial arrest team, but returned to the family after handing over her position to her successor, Sadi.

However, the Hell Tree incident exposed Professor Sadi as a traitor, and the failure to capture Sadi meant that there was no one left to serve as escort.

Isabella was forced to become Vikir’s escort, even though they were related by blood.

Isabella nodded obediently, knowing that there was no point in paying respect to a prisoner when they were already in a relationship.

“Sadi, she’s a mystery, and I’ve always suggested that we should be wary of her, because she’s very skilled, but we don’t know what she’s capable of….”

Isabella clicked her tongue, as if she’d seen this coming.

“….”

“….”

An awkward silence hung between them for a moment.

It was unlikely that a prisoner and his escort would talk, but since they were related and there were no hard feelings, Isabella had a word of advice for Vikir.

“My nephew.”

“?”

Vikir turned his head, and Isabella spoke in a voice that could not have been more serious.

“You would be better off committing suicide now.”

If he died now, he could be buried in the ground. That might be better.

The Nouvelle Vague, a place so horrific that these words came from the mouth of Isabella, a woman who had been through it all.

That’s where Vikir is headed now. The place where he will spend the next 3,021 life sentences without parole.

◆

A little while later, the convoy began to sail out to sea.

Naturally, Vikir did not commit suicide.

He simply boarded a ship at the tip of the northern continent and sailed out into the “harsh waters” of the ice drift.

Vikir’s cell on the deck of a huge ship. Handcuffed, shackled, and chained, Vikir sat stiffly in the pouring rain and icy waves.

‘…Even the road to Nouvelle Vague is difficult.’

The waves that were tens of meters high and the pouring storm were so violent that it seemed as if they would capsize the ship at any moment and engulf it.

Then.

Vikir was alone, meditating in silence, when a group of people approached him.

“How does it feel to be looking for a place to die?”

“Hmph, I’d rather drown in the sea here.”

“You don’t know what Nouvelle Vague is like, that’s why you’re so nonchalant.”

Three giggling voices.

Vikir turned his head and saw familiar faces.

Pedro Donquixote. Usher P Isolde. Thomas De Leviathan.

They were convoys from the Usher family, the Donquixote family, and the Leviathan family, respectively.

The fact that all seven families present as jurors sent one escort was due to the fact that Isabella, who should have been the sole escort, was related to the guilty party, Vikir.

To balance the equation, six families of varying skill and status were sent to keep the Baskervilles in check, three of whom were Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas.

“The Nouvelle Vague, It’s a very dreadful prison, sunk deep in the ultra-deep zone of the ocean.”

“You will die on the way there.”

“So why don’t you kill yourself now, it’s better that way, because Nouvelle Vague is indeed a living hell.”

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas whispered slyly in Vikir’s ear.

Of course, Vikir wasn’t listening to them.

He was focused on the faint stench that emanated from them.

‘…They are the demon’s minions.’

They smelled similar to the stench of Passamonte, Madeline, and Hobbes in the courtroom.

But even without the scent, Vikir already knew their faces, their names, and their bios.

Like the prey he’d been hunting all this time.

“Pedro Donquixote. Usher P Isolde. Thomas de Leviathan. Each rose to high positions within their families after sacrificing their men, their cousins, and countless people in their fiefdoms to the demon, and gaining demonic powers. Was the taste of easy power sweet?”

The three of them stiffened at Vikir’s words.

They exchanged glances and then spoke.

“Indeed. I see why my master told me to kill you and get rid of you somehow.”

“You are a squire who will not be relieved by imprisonment in the Nouvelle Vague.”

“This ship will be your grave.”

Vikir is an easy prey, as he has no mana due to his BDISSEM restraints.

That’s what Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas thought.

But.

“…, What’s going on?”

A voice interrupted the trio.

Isabella La Baskerville.

The leader of the Doberman Knights stood on the stormy deck, glaring at them.

Her fierce eyes were already filled with hostility.

“What conversation was that just now? Demonic power? Master? Why should this ship become a tomb for sinners on their way to the Nouvelle Vague?”

Isabella’s voice was dripping with life.

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas clicked their tongues.

“Did you hear that? That was careless.”

“What do you think? You were going to kill them all anyway.”

“Better to nip the Baskervilles in the bud, you never know what she knows.”

A 3:1 situation.

Even if Isabella was the First Countess and an expert in combat, she couldn’t take on three of them at once.

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas were also among the most powerful men in Donquixote, Usher, and Leviathan respectively.

But the tables were about to turn again.

“You’ve been planning something fun, I see.”

“Lord Lun. Punish those peculiar servants.”

“What’s going on here, why have those bastards suddenly become demon worshippers?”

Three new shadows stretched out from behind Isabella’s back.

A dark-haired middle-aged man with a stern expression, a hulking cleric, and a gentle, kindly-looking man.

They were convoys sent from Morgue, Quovadis, and Bourgeois, respectively.

Banshee Morgue, Mozgus Quovadis, and Bourgeois Ju Lovebad.

Banshee, the Academy’s next principal, and Mozgus, the Archbishop of the New Testament Sect, were specially selected for this convoy.

Their strong willingness to volunteer was the main reason.

Behind Isabella, the leader of the Doberman Knights, came Professor Banshee, Archbishop Mozgus, and Lovebad, the cousin of Merelini Lovegood, the student body president of Themiscyra Academy for Women.

“I’m afraid I’m not going to be able to overhear what was just said.”

“Since demons were mentioned, I’ll need to check Vikir-kun’s testimony as well.”

“I don’t know, but your side is certainly suspicious. And you revealed your intention to kill Isabella first.”

The battle situation became 3:4. In this case, Isabella’s side clearly seemed to have an advantage.

But.

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas were still frowning.

“Do you think we did this recklessly?”

“Hehehe. Such idiotic things.”

“…Hmm. It’s time for the medicine to take effect.”

Thomas de Leviathan, an ultra-doctor, pulled out his pocket watch.

Isabella’s expression changed first.

“Ma, mana…!?”

At the same time, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad’s faces hardened.

Thomas smirked.

“The tea you drank contained a substance that is the raw material for BDISSEM. It was in powdered form and in very small amounts, so you probably didn’t notice.”

“The amount each of you drank could easily buy this ship. How could it not be effective? It’s worth the price, isn’t it?”

“You’re wearing a pair of BDISSEM. handcuffs right now. The effect lasts only a few minutes, but it’s enough.”

Pedro and Isolde opened their mouths as well.

They exuded life and pressed back against Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad.

Thomas said with a sneer.

“Don’t worry. I will report that the ship was sunk by a rampage of Night Hound and that you were wiped out because of it. You will go down as heroes, martyred in the line of duty.”

Mutiny on board.

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad, faced with the most terrible thing that could happen on a ship, could not hide their panic.

“Damn it. My mana really isn’t boiling.”

“…I feel like I’m wearing BDISSEM handcuffs.”

“I can only last so long in this state.”

“Holy shit! BDISSEM powder! What the hell is that substance?”

A storm of confusion rages on the deck.

“Handcuffs?”

Vikir’s voice came from inside the cage.

“You mean these?”

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas turned to see Vikir with his palms spread wide.

At the same time.

…Poof!

The smiles on the faces of Pedro, Iselde, and Thomas stopped.

The BDISSEM handcuffs shattered before their eyes.

Fragments of the shackles shattered and fell.

Vikir pushed himself to his feet in front of the three men, who were too stunned to show any change in expression.

Ujijik-

BDISSEM The cage bends so easily, as if it were a bunch of sorghum.

“Don’t sink the ship.”

Night Hound stepped out of the cage.

“I must go to Nouvelle Vague.”

He looked so nonchalant.

Chapter 358

Voluntary Escort (2)

◆

…Ttug! Pakang! Kkigigigig-

The BDISSEM restraint was shattered before their eyes.

At the same time, the cage bends like a stick and the whole cage collapses.

Vikir unbuckled all the restraints with a look of nonchalance on his face.

‘So this is the effect of my title in the Hell Tree? That’s fascinating.’

Even Vikir himself hadn’t realized how easy it was to break the bindings of the BDISSEM.

-Title: ‘Daylily Lumberjack’

Deals enormous additional damage to monsters in plant form.

Taunt, Confuse, Blind, Bleed, Burn, Poison, and other status abnormalities last slightly longer.

-New title: ‘Leading Boatman’

? Deal massive additional damage to aquatic creatures.

Taunt, Confuse, Blind, Bleed, Burn, Poison, and other status abnormalities last slightly longer.

The untapped energy simmering within him, this was clearly the power of his title, gained within the Hell Tree.

Although it was impossible to see now that the status window had disappeared, this power had set off a strange chain reaction that had broken Bidis M’s handcuffs.

‘…I don’t know exactly what BDISSEM material is made of, but I have a rough idea that it can be shredded by these two titles.’

After easily resolving the BDISSEM restraint, which was the only obstacle to his future plans, there are signs that things will be easier in the future.

Meanwhile.

“…!?”

Everyone gasped as Vikir broke the handcuffs and stepped out of the cage.

Not only Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas, but also Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad were stunned.

“Oh, my God, you broke the BDISSEM handcuffs!”

“How is that possible?”

“What, I don’t know, wouldn’t Professor Banshee know better?”

“I’ve never seen anyone break a BDISSEM. restraint before. Is that how it works?”

With no mana to spend, the only thing they can do is watch the battle between Pedro, Isolde, Thomas, and Vikir.

It was then that Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas showed their true colors.

“I don’t know how you managed to get out of the BDISSEM. restraints, but there’s no way you could have done it on your own.”

“On the contrary, it’s a good thing. It gives me a chance to tear you apart myself and earn my master’s approval.”

“You’ve only ever dealt with lowly contractors, haven’t you? Today you’ve met a real one.”

The three of them opened up completely to the power the demon had given them.

The black blood they had kept hidden in the depths of their hearts pumped through their muscles.

As the demon blood began to flow in the veins of their bodies, the appearance of their human skins began to change.

…Udeudeug! Ppudeudeudeug!

Vikir had seen this before.

Most recently, perhaps, when he encountered the demonized underdog within the Hell Tree.

[He-aaaahhhhhhhhhhh!]

[Kkikkikkikkikkikkikkikkig!]

[Pooh-pooh… huug!]

Then three giant demons looked down on Vikir.

Whoosh! Kwa-kwa-kwa-kwa-kwa-kwak!

The flames and magical magnetic fields from the demons’ metamorphosis ripped through the deck.

“…!?”

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad quickly scrambled out of the way of the spurred storm.

Even with their mana depleted, they used their extreme physical strength to put distance between them and the demons.

Pakang! Pang!

Isabella swung her sword to slice through the flying debris, while Banshee used his grappling skills to kick through flying ropes and barrels.

Mozgus and Lovebad grabbed Isabella and Banshee by the collar as they flew through the storm, stopping them from falling over the railing.

“I can’t believe they’s got this kind of momentum from just transforming….. What kind of power is that.”

“It’s bad, it’s a demon, it’s a demon!”

“Pedro, Isolde, Thomas, I can’t believe they were demons!”

“I can’t believe it, from earlier. Am I dreaming?”

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad were stunned by this latest development, in which executives from as many as Seven Families were revealed to be demonic minions.

But regardless, Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas were burning black flames all over their bodies to kill Vikir.

Pedro was the first, his gums and teeth protruding from his mouth.

[Retreating is not running away, nor is it wise to wait when danger outstrips hope. The wise man knows to abstain today for tomorrow, and does not risk everything in one day.].

“….”

[Is this what my master told me to listen to?]

A line spoken by Vikir before his final judgment.

At that, Isolde and Thomas also bared their sharp teeth and snarled.

[Upon hearing those words, my master realized that you had not yet given up, and he was alarmed and dispatched us. Something was suspicious from the moment you turned yourself in].

[Your careless tongue got the better of you, and you will die here because of it. Kkilkkilkkilkkil!].

When you become a demon, your entire body is filled with uncontrollable power.

It’s an exhilarating feeling of being unstoppable.

For a moment, they ignored Vikir’s presence.

…And the price was great.

Huug-

Vikir unleashed the mana he’d been unable to tap into due to the BDISSEM bind.

Black Sun.

The aura of the time when Amdusias, the 5th Corpse, was brought to his knees by force, despite the fact that no one could match him 1:1, emerged like a black sun.

[…?]

For a moment, the ease and laughter evaporated from the faces of the minions, and then only a salty sourness set in.

‘Something is wrong.’

It was the last thing Isolde and Thomas could think in their right minds.

…A flash!

There was no time to attack, defend, or flee.

Vikir’s 8 enormous teeth formed into a sphere, like a black sun, and it devastated the area around it.

A feast of countless teeth that rose like a frightening flame. In the swirl of the aura, Isolde and Thomas’ bodies were torn apart in an instant.

Standing before them, limbs severed, neck and torso only, Vikir asked in a voice that still lacked any emotion.

“I assume the fact that the three of you are here means that… your three masters have joined hands as well?”

[Hic!]

[Hic!?]

But there were only two returning whistles.

Puff-puff!

Pedro. He had turned and run as soon as Vikir had sent the black sun overhead.

The demon sped across the surface of the water at breakneck speed.

‘Hey, this isn’t it. I can never handle this..’

He’d trusted his BDISSEM restraints like a rock until now.

His foolish companions were belligerent despite the fact that it was broken, but not Pedro.

…Cheombeong! …cheombeong! …cheombeong! …cheombeong!

It was a blessing in disguise that he was now running on water, stomping his feet like a madman.

Unlike the other two idiots, he thought he was going to make it home alive.

…But it soon became apparent that this was an illusion.

“Too late, you should have turned around and run when you saw the handcuffs break.”

Vikir was now holding Pedro’s back without a sound.

‘Uh, how?’

Pedro felt a chill run down his spine.

He’d been running on the surface of the water, spurred on by his incredible speed.

But how had Vikir gotten here without a sound or a sign of what or where?

Pedro turned his head, and his heart leapt to his throat in surprise.

Pang- paang- pang!

Vikir was following him, kicking through the air, stepping on bubbles and droplets of water that popped up with each stroke.

“It might have been a little awkward if you’d self-destructed and blown up the ship.”

[Hiig!?]

“But it’s too late for that, you should have done that before you jumped into the water.”

Vikir sliced off Pedro’s limbs in a flash, then dug his fingers into the back of his neck.

Like removing a bomb’s detonator, Vikir ripped out the nerve bundles inside Pedro’s neck, sending him sprawling back to the surface.

…Thud!

Vikir landed on the railing with a limbless Pedro in his hand and Isolde and Thomas at his feet.

It had all happened so fast.

“….”

“….”

“….”

“….”

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad could only stand there with their mouths half open, unaware that their powers had returned.

But even though they are convoys, they don’t dare to restrain Vikir again.

The atmosphere doesn’t even call for him to be handcuffed again now.

In the first place, Vikir didn’t care about them at all.

Vikir crouched down on the floor and turned to Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas.

“Your masters will be quite sad when they find out.”

Probably three of the remaining Ten Corpses had sent them. With the plan to blow up the ship by self-destructing in the middle of the ocean.

But now that all that has come to naught, all that remains is the interrogation.

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas snorted as Vikir gave them a look that demanded answers.

[Just kill me].

[We can’t betray our master].

[We’re not blowing anything up].

The demons were determined.

But Vikir only smiled weakly at the sight of it.

For a moment, unease flashes across their faces, the first time they’ve seen Vikir smile since the convoy began.

Then, sure enough, Vikir spoke up, a hint of anticipation in his tone.

“Yes, please don’t blow.”

The stress of the trial process had been building up quite a bit.

He planned to blow it off before going to prison.

Chapter 360

Voluntary Escort (4)

◆

‘Nouvelle Vague? Don’t even talk about it. It’s a living hell. It’s a place I never want to go back to.’

‘We were lucky to get out of there alive.’

‘…I never thought that monstrous old man would free us with his own hands.’

Vikir remembered a time before his regression.

During the war against the demons, Vikir had many comrades in arms who were prisoners.

The Demon War had united all of humanity.

Once categorized as human, criminal records didn’t matter.

Everyone was on the same side, everyone was a comrade-in-arms.

Living and dying with the prisoners of Nouvelle Vague, Vikir had seen and heard many things.

In many ways, he was able to experience firsthand the horrific prison culture.

Just as a man who has been in the army can tell you endless stories about his time in the army, the prisoners at Nouvelle Vague would tell each other detailed, long, and lengthy stories about their time in prison, and Vikir never once found it boring.

‘…So I know it well. What Nouvelle Vague is like.’

Vikir stepped into the coffin.

As the lid closed, the nails in the coffin pierced Vikir’s body without warning.

But his flesh, hardened by the protection of the Styx River, his physical resistance stats from the Hell Tree, and his aura combined.

Thud!

The nails in the coffin were unable to pierce Vikir’s skin and bent.

In the midst of it all, Vikir spoke through the upper layers of the coffin, through the eye and mouth openings of the Iron Maiden.

“Push.”

A firm voice. No wavering.

Eventually, the coffin containing Vikir tilted toward the sea.

All the holes in the coffin were sealed with special wax, and a heavy additional weight was hung at the bottom.

Now the coffin would ride in the middle of the whirlpool and sink at a rapid pace.

Towards the bottom of the deep ocean, the deepest ocean below.

“….”

Isabella slipped her longsword onto the chain at the bow that connected to the coffin.

Her mission was essentially to get Vikir away, even if it meant killing everyone on board.

But what can she do, when the one she’s supposed to get away from wants to go to Nouvelle Vague so badly?

Even Vikir seemed to have something else in mind.

Whatever it is, it’s something in a higher realm that even she, Seven Counts, can’t fathom.

Isabella, meanwhile, was quite surprised by the situation.

In all her years of sending many prisoners to Nouvelle Vague, it had never occurred to her that she would ever see them again.

…But now it was different.

Vikir seemed to realize that one day they would surely meet again.

‘It’s a strange thing. For someone going to the Nouvelle Vague to have such thoughts.’

Isabella let out a light sigh.

And soon, her black sword radiated anticipation.

Fit-

A drop of liquid aura, sticky as honey, descended, cutting cleanly through the coffin and the chains attached to the ship’s bow.

…With a plop!

The coffin sank heavily beneath the water.

The white foam that rose to the surface of the black waters was the last reminder of Vikir’s presence in this world.

Even that was soon swept away by the raging torrent.

The ship reeled in its anchor line and began to gradually move away from Malstr?m’s sphere of influence.

By midnight, the whirlpools had subsided and the currents were rapidly becoming milder.

Whirring.

The sound of sails flapping in the sea breeze is loud.

Each of the four surviving convoy officers maintained a heavy silence.

Finally, Lovebad of the Bourgeois was the first to speak.

“…Ha, I don’t know what to tell my youngest sister. To the kid who was already sick from lovesickness.”

“I agree, our young lady will have an uproar.”

“I can’t imagine how bitterly she’ll feel….”

“I’m going to go back and be devastated by the patriarch.”

Banshee of Morgue, Mozgus of Quovadis, and Isabella of Baskerville also put their hands to their foreheads.

In the end, it was Banshee who faced reality first.

“For now, let’s get back to the ship as soon as we can, and put those minions in the hold on trial, and shed some light on the mutiny on board.”

“We should also demand a retrial for Vikir-kun.”

Isabella nodded at Mozgus’s words.

“That’s not all. We need to investigate the testimony of Donquixote La Mancha Passamonte, Usher Poe Madeline, and Hobbes De Leviathan.”

“They’re all powerful men, and if we get it wrong, we’ll have a huge feud between the Seven Great Families….”

Lovebad’s fears were confirmed.

Vikir was on his way to Nouvelle Vague.

Instead of just leaving, he planted a huge blue seed and left it behind.

It was so ominous and dangerous that it could shake the very foundations of the empire.

◆

Meanwhile.

Vikir was in a coffin, sinking to the center of a long, vertical vortex.

Even though he is innocent and a retrial is nothing to worry about in the first place.

All that mattered now was getting down to Nouvelle Vague safely.

Purrrrr…

The water bubbles and the vision grows darker.

He could feel the water leaking through the narrow toe space, which was getting slightly damp.

The coffin was caught in a swirling wave, bobbing violently, then settling down.

Its weight made it sink faster.

After a while, a strange sound came from the lid of the coffin.

Udeudeug-

The coffin is sinking rapidly, and the water pressure around it is getting higher and higher.

The coffin, made of an orthoharcon alloy, began to crack.

It will eventually crumple until it fits perfectly around Vikir’s entire body.

Most prisoners would not survive this process and would either commit suicide or go insane from the claustrophobia.

“….”

However, Vikir endures this time in silence, keeping his mouth shut.

Crunch-clunk-clack-clack!

The Iron Maiden strongly embraces Vikir.

Aside from the pressure crushing his entire body, the lack of oxygen was a problem.

Then.

Sssssssss…

Oxygen flows from somewhere.

It was bubbling outward through a faint crack in his toes.

‘Is this the power of these cuffs?’

Vikir lowered his gaze to the bindings that wrapped around his wrists, ankles, and the rest of his body.

The mysterious material was emitting a faint puff of oxygen, helping Vikir breathe.

‘Absorbs mana, enforces physical force, and even emits oxygen? It’s a strange substance.’

Vikir recalled stories he’d heard from his former comrades-in-arms before he’d regressed that, while the BDISSEM cuffs inhibited movement, they were an essential survival tool in the deep.

Crack! Puddeuddeuk!

The distortion of the coffin was getting worse and worse.

The depths of the ocean are now so deep that there is not even the slightest bit of light, and the world is pitch black.

An infinite void of nothingness.

A space that is both empty and full.

Being placed in a coffin and thrown into the depths of the ocean was no different than being buried alive in the depths of the earth.

An iron maiden guiding the way to death.

The journey to survive more than three thousand life sentences is a long and arduous one.

But Vikir endured it all.

The giant metal tubes that cling to his body like an uncomfortable garment, the endless sinking into the darkness of the lightless void, the giant, nameless monsters of the deep that prowl around him.

The only thing that helps is Decarabia embedded in his chest.

[Human. Are you okay?]

“It’s worth holding on to.”

[An impossibly large creature just passed in front of us, and it had a lot of legs].

“Is it as good as Shadowless King of the Black Sea?”

[That’s right. Hehehe… You still have a lot of free time, right?]

“You shouldn’t talk about dying like this, you’ve got a lot of work ahead of you.”

Upon hearing Vikir’s words, Decarabia pouted, as if in good faith.

[Very well, human, then let me show you one of my many abilities, perhaps the one you need most at this point].

After speaking, Decarabia emitted a strange light from its only eye.

“…!”

Vikir was a little surprised.

As the Decarabia glowed, a vision of the outside of the coffin began to form in his head.

“Vision sharing. That’s good.”

[Is it worth using? Hmph- maybe it’s because it’s the sea, isn’t it a bit salty for a compliment you receive in return for finding the light?].

Decarabia grumbled in dissatisfaction, but Vikir shrugged it off.

Eventually, Vikir’s vision began to take in the landscape below the sinking coffin.

It looked like a forest.

A jungle. A giant forest.

A vast expanse of seaweed, each stalk as massive as the pillars of a mythical temple.

Expanse

over an enormous area.

Colonies of seaweed.

Standing tall and flowing

The seaweed seems to have been forgotten

Giant soldiers of ancient civilization

Stand upright and stand guard

It seems like it exists.

The coffin containing Vikir

In the center of this seaweed forest,

To the top of the highest cliff

It was sinking.

Kkuleuleuleug…

An awl-sharp cliff rose above the blackened forest of giant aquatic plants, and at the end of it stood a structure that emitted a dim light like a lantern.

An old castle with an old and gloomy atmosphere, built in a very ancient style, made of large bricks piled tightly on top of an extinct volcano in the deep sea.

Nouvelle Vague!

The world’s worst prison

awaited Vikir.

Chapter 363

Ghost Castle of the Ultra-Deep Sea (3)

◆

The entrance ceremony was over.

The bodies of the dead prisoners were tossed off the cliffs into the crater like garbage.

No one cared about the fate of the prisoners, who would still be reported as ‘alive and imprisoned’ in the terrestrial registers because they had not been officially ‘executed’.

They would remain trapped in this prison on paper forever, even after death.

On the other hand, the prisoners who survived the ceremony received their floor and room assignments.

Vikir, who had not only come here with more than three thousand life sentences, but had also shown a nonchalant attitude during the inspection of his belongings, medical examination, and bath, was naturally assigned to Level Nine, the ninth floor.

…Clang!

Vikir was locked in a cramped room. Level Nine was basically a solitary confinement system.

The atmosphere in the room was surprisingly plain.

A large black brick stone chamber. The entire stone chamber was lined with bars made of BDISSEM, a substance that absorbs mana and physical power.

“This is why you can’t even dig through the bricks with a spoon.”

Not only were the bars closely spaced, but they covered the ceiling, walls, and floor, making escape impossible.

There was no point in digging a hole to get out through the walls or the floor, as they were 10,000 meters below the ocean floor.

Tsk, tsk, tsk.

Cold droplets of water dripped from the bricks.

The water was extremely salty and concentrated.

Indeed, an enormous amount of moisture sticks to the entire body.

A dark, cold, dank aura filled not only the cell, but the entire hallway.

The interior of the stone chamber was bare.

Not even the usual bedding or bowls, just an empty cube of space.

But Vikir’s assessment was pretty harsh.

“Not a bad place to live.”

After rolling across so many bloody battlefields against demons, it’s a nice change of pace.

Vikir muttered to himself.

…Kung!

The heavy iron gate beyond rang loudly once.

Kkigigigigigig-

A door so heavy that it took over a hundred guards to open it.

It opened and the prisoners who had originally been held here were seen entering.

Presumably on their way back from forced labor outside.

“Heoeog! Keuheoeog! Kkeuleuleug-”

“Ughhh….”

“Kkeueug- kkeueueueug-”

The condition of the prisoners returning from their forced labor in the workshops was terrible.

Vikir recalled the information he already knew.

All of Nouvelle Vague’s prisoners, from level one to level nine, were required to go to the workshop every day at dawn to perform labor.

The labor is to dig down into the interior of the volcano where Nouvelle Vague is located.

It’s an expansion project to increase the interior space of Nouvelle Vague.

It’s an extinct volcano, but it’s still a volcano, and the enormous amount of geothermal heat inside doesn’t dissipate over time.

So the prisoners dig and dig and keep digging, boiling, burning, drying up, day after day.

“The new prisoners are put to work tomorrow, too.”

A voice came from the side of the cage where Vikir was standing.

The guard he had seen earlier, Lieutenant Garam, was now standing beside him.

He walked up beside a procession of prisoners groaning from burns and exhaustion.

“You will wake up at 4 a.m. and work nonstop until 1 p.m. You will have 10 minutes for lunch, after which you will work again until midnight. After that, you will return to your room and have an hour of prayer and repentance before going to bed at 1am.”

That’s three hours of sleep a night, one meal a day, and that meal had to be consumed in less than 10 minutes, and it had to be something crappy like black bread or a piece of jerky.

Not to mention the grueling, high-intensity slave labor that continued day after day.

Garam’s voice echoed upward due to the Nouvelle Vague’s vertical panopticon structure.

Vikir could hear the sound of Garam’s voice and the wavelengths it created, and he could sense the overall structure of the Nouvelle Vague.

‘…A large cylindrical structure. Prisoners’ cells are arranged in a circle around the walls, with a workshop in the center of the bottom nine levels.’

The stronger prisoners, closer to level 9, seemed to be working in the central depths of the bottom nine levels, breaking rocks and digging down into the ground, while the weaker prisoners, closer to level 1, were working in the distance, blowing mounds of dirt and rocks and dumping them outside.

The prisoners in the middle were divided into work areas according to the level of the floor they were imprisoned on, and worked to move piles of rocks and dirt.

This means that if you’re closer to level 9, you’re working in the deepest, hottest, and most dangerous part of the worksite, and if you’re closer to level 1, you’re working in the shallower, less hot, and safer part.

This may sound complicated, but it was very easy and simple to illustrate.

Lieutenant Garam said.

“You are currently engaged in the glorious labor of expanding the great Nouvelle Vague. Do it with pride, and do it well.”

Expanding the Nouvelle Vague.

To be more specific, they were currently creating an area deeper than the 9th floor underground called ‘Level 9’.

Aka “Level 10,” a massive undertaking to create a 10th underground floor.

Since they’re digging down to the 10th floor, it makes sense that the workshop is on the 9th floor.

“The new section, Level 10, will house criminals who cannot be housed on Level 9. It would be wise for you, the prisoners, to cooperate if you care about your own safety.”

Garam had a point.

Every once in a while, Nouvelle Vague would have a rampage of criminals it couldn’t handle, and it was always the prisoners who were the first and most likely to die.

So from the prisoners’ point of view, the weaker they were, the harder they worked on the construction, and the sooner the more dangerous ones were sent down below, the better off they would be in the long run.

Vikir nodded in agreement.

‘Indeed. Nouvelle Vague has a lot of out-of-order monsters.’

Vikir could think of quite a few criminals he knew who were currently imprisoned in Level 9.

‘Cystus Ent Megidio, Lord Griffin, Aurora of Sleeping Beauty, Snowwhite of the Assassin, Cinderella of the Glass Heel, Marquis de Sade,’ ….

Each of these monsters was powerful enough to wipe out an entire nation with a single blow.

Imprisoned here after being sentenced to life imprisonment more than 5,000 times during their time on earth, even the Nouvelle Vague’s Level Nine floor could not contain them.

“For your information, if you refuse to serve or resist the guards’ control, you will be sent to solitary confinement. Don’t think there’s a floor worse than Level 9.”

Garam opened his mouth as if aiming his words at Vikir.

Vikir heard the words and nodded slowly.

The cell the guard was referring to was probably nothing like the one Vikir was in now.

‘Solitary. A terrible place. I’ve heard it’s a hard place to get out of alive once you’re locked up in it… and that there’s only one prisoner in all of Nouvelle Vague who can survive it.’

Vikir was recalling all the information he’d heard before his regression.

“…Huh!?”

“Oh, they’re coming, they’re coming!”

“Get out of the way or you’ll get eaten!”

The low-level prisoners, returning from their labor, backed away to the left and right, terrified.

The guards, too, stood tense, their weapons crossed, staring at the other side of the gate.

Black shadows stretched across the fiery horizon.

Shadows that are big, small, or incredibly large.

“….”

“….”

“….”

They are the prisoners of Level 9, returning from their work in the center of the labor fields.

All eyes were on the returning prisoners of Level 9.

Vikir turned his head away as if he didn’t care, and spoke in a deep tone.

“Hey, guard, do you happen to have a newspaper or something?”

Lieutenant Garam, who was breaking out in a cold sweat, turned his head.

Then, incredulously, he replied.

“Newspapers? Why would you look for such a precious thing in a prisoner?”

“Newspapers are precious? I didn’t know that.”

“Anything from the outside world is valuable, especially something as informative as a newspaper. Even among the guards, newspapers are rarely seen, and only the warden and a few other privileged people can read them.”

The connection to the outside world is both precious and dangerous.

At least that’s how it worked in Nouvelle Vague.

Vikir clicked his tongue ruefully.

“We’re as good as prisoners and guards who are imprisoned here.”

At that, Garam put his hands on his hips in disbelief.

But he did not bother to pull out the three-stage baton attached to his waist.

‘…Tomorrow, that leisure will disappear.’

Even if you are a demon trapped in Level Nine, once you taste the labor of the Nouvelle Vague, you will be stunned.

This prison is named after the volcano Nouvelle Vague, which was once hotter than any other.

It is now an extinct volcano, but the geothermal heat still trapped inside and unable to escape is as hot as hell.

Garam expressed his condolences to Vikir, who had to dig down there starting tomorrow, especially the deepest and hottest part of it.

It’s where even the demons of Level Nine die casually.

Chapter 364

The Underground Extension Construction (1)

◆

4 a.m. the next day.

Vikir was taken to the workshop as soon as he awoke.

Even the strongest and most ferocious prisoners have no business having the BDISSEM chains around their necks forcibly pulled by a giant pulley in their sleep.

Countless prisoners were dragged out and lined up in the corridors like rotting zombies.

Then the guards on duty at dawn would come out and count the prisoners from a distance, out of their reach.

That’s the morning count.

The prisoners were generally well behaved.

They might be chronically sleep deprived and malnourished, but that didn’t stop them from being irritable and sensitive.

There was a risk of being killed by a fellow prisoner, but mostly because they didn’t have the energy to be angry in the first place.

Standing in front of the massive iron gates to the workshop, Vikir waited to be given his tools.

As he waited, he could see the prisoners on the next lower level lined up to get their tools.

“Hey, give me more nails. I can’t work with these today.”

“Guard. The pickaxe is too dull to dig the tunnel.”

“The sledgehammer is loose, do you have anything else?”

The prisoners were jockeying for every bit of good equipment they could get.

They knew that the quota was always set, and if they didn’t meet it, horrible corporal punishment awaited them.

The guards were also relatively cooperative with the prisoners’ demands, as they were punished in terms of wages and vacation time if the prisoners in their group did not complete their assigned areas on time.

Some guards even fought with other guards to ensure that the prisoners in their group received good tools.

Vikir tried to estimate the number of guards in the Nouvelle Vague based on the number of roaming guards and their chain of command.

‘The number of combat-capable guards is roughly 3,000, and the number of non-combatants is at least 4,000.’

Due to information prior to the return, he also knows that there are five ‘chief guards’ in charge of these guards.

The numbers are higher than expected, and he needs to be careful what he does.

Then.

A sack of tools was placed in front of Vikir.

The familiar face of the guard, Lieutenant Garam, was calling out the tools to Vikir.

‘Strange how often we meet.’

Without thinking, Vikir took the tools from him.

Lieutenant Garam gave him instructions in a businesslike tone.

“Work tools are strictly controlled to prevent prisoners from getting carried away. You must return your work tools intact at the end of your working hours, and if you lose them, you will be sent to solitary confinement until they are found. If your tools are broken or lost, you must have a note from the guards to prove it, otherwise, of course, you will be sent to solitary until they are found.”

If you lose your tools, you’re dead.

So prisoners guard the tools they were given at the beginning of their work like their lives.

Sneaking them away to escape or fight is unthinkable.

And, of course, the prisoners had to fill out and sign an inventory form before going to work, stating what tools they had been issued.

Every strand of rope and every nail had to be meticulously written down and inspected by a guard before the prisoner could leave for the workshop.

“Come on, don’t waste time, let’s get moving!”

“If we miss the construction deadline, we’ll be sent to solitary confinement again!”

“Hurry up and write the status board and get the hell out of here, you slug!”

The prisoners were anxious to get out of the workshop.

Not because they liked the work, but because they were afraid of the harsh corporal punishment they would receive if the project was delayed.

Vikir was also silently gathering his tools.

“You’re early.”

A sledgehammer, a bundle of chains, and a handful of nails were all he had.

Prisoners at Level Nine aren’t given much in the way of tools.

The conditions in which they work are so harsh that wood burns and iron quickly turns to molten metal.

So they have to break rocks and scoop up dirt with their bare fists.

They must endure the heat with their bare skin, and they must climb barefoot, no matter how high or deep.

Anything sharp and pointy, anything hard and tough, anything rough and heavy, they had to deal with.

This, of course, was something Vikir had been preparing for since he was imprisoned in Level Nine.

Then.

“What’s with this kid, are you a level nine too? Kuru-kuru!”

A sarcastic laugh came from the back of the next row.

Vikir turned his head to see a man with a huge frame, fearsome eyes, and a nasty birthmark.

Sakkuth De Leviathan.

The prisoner who had been labeled a “Level 8” at yesterday’s intake was openly arguing with Vikir.

Every time he bursts into laughter, a foul odor spreads.

The prisoners around him were too afraid to go near him for fear of catching a plague.

“Did you hear? That lunatic wasn’t even disinfected by the sulfur shower when he came in.”

“They say you can’t go near him without catching the plague. The guards don’t know what to do.”

“Damn, I’m afraid of shit. I avoid it because it’s dirty.”

“…That shit was scary.”

Hearing the chatter around him, Sakkuth became even more agitated and began to giggle.

A foul stench of poison and fetid odor emanated from his teeth, which had fallen out due to the vile poison.

“Kid, what did you do to get in here? You must have messed with somebody’s delicacy, I’ve heard of people being imprisoned like that sometimes. Yesterday, after the entrance ceremony, I went to the room and there was a guy who looked like a gisaeng old lady. I think his name was Casanova or something. Well, it doesn’t matter now, because I ate him yesterday. I chewed him alive. Kuru-kuru.”

There was no interruption from the other prisoners.

The other prisoners cringe, fearing they might spread the plague.

The guards, in their masks and hazmat suits, stood at a distance, frowning arrogantly.

But.

“….”

Only Vikir stood there, unmoving.

He was simply scribbling a list of the missing tools on the status board.

Then, as if on cue, the prisoners around him shuffled to his side.

“Hey, kid. Can’t you hear me?”

“….”

“Ohora, I saw you yesterday at the entrance ceremony, and you seemed to have a lot of nerve. Are you a level 9?”

“….”

“Hey. Just because I’m on the 8th floor and you’re on the 9th floor doesn’t mean you think you’re stronger and more dangerous than me, does it?”

Sakkuth said, running his fingers through Vikir’s hair.

“I came here to the Nouvelle Vague on purpose to have ‘him’ by my side.”

“….”

“But what’s this? He’s at Level Nine, why should I be at Level Eight? Isn’t there something wrong with this? Someone like me should be at Level Nine, why is a weakling like you at Level Nine and I’m not? Send me to Level Nine, too, so I can be by ‘His’ side!”

As he shouted in excitement, a dark aura began to emanate from his entire body.

It was a poisonous aura that could not be blocked by the BDISSEM restraints, and the poisonous energy he had accumulated in his body naturally rose up regardless of his mana.

“Why am I a level 8? Is it because I turned myself in? Isn’t that enough to send me to level 9? If so, why don’t I just turn this place upside down? Let’s see if I can sprinkle some plague on it! Let me give you a taste of my ‘Red Death’!”

While roaring maniacally into the air.

“…I think I know why.”

A brief voice caught Sakkuth’s attention.

It was Vikir speaking, gathering up his tools after he’d finished cleaning up.

Sakkuth sounded a little confused.

“Kid, did you just say that?”

“Yes.”

“Kurururu! Kururu!”

Sakkuth spat out a laugh that sounded like a thousand fires boiling deep in his throat.

And with a terrifying expression, he thrust his face in front of Vikir.

“I see. Why do you think I haven’t reached level nine?”

“Because you don’t have the basics.”

“Basic? What’s that…?”

He opened his mouth to ask.

Shhhh.

Vikir’s hand moved.

Vikir shoves a handful of nails into Sakkuth’s gaping mouth.

Then he raised his fist and punched him in the jaw.

Ppeo-eog!

Sakkuth’s head turned.

At the same time, the nails in his mouth clattered together, piercing his cheeks, nose, chin, and neck, and sticking out in all directions.

“Puhak!? Keueeeeekh!”

Vikir smirked as he stepped over the blood-spattered, struggling Sakkuth.

“You should at least learn to recognize whether you’re the predator or the prey.”

At the same time, the sound of numerous military boots clattered up the stairs above the door to the workshop.

Guards ranging in rank from major to lieutenant colonel and above were running frantically.

“What’s the commotion, ‘Night Hounds’!”

The blood drained from the faces of all the prisoners as they heard the shout from the work commander, Lieutenant Colonel Bastille.

The Night Hound. Sentenced to life imprisonment 3,021 times. Prison level 9.

Who would have guessed that the scary resident who had only been rumored so far would actually be such a handsome boy?

Chapter 365

The Underground Extension Construction (2)

◆

Construction on the new Level Ten has begun.

Digging down into the interior of the great volcano was hard work indeed.

Even Vikir, who had crossed countless lines of fire, thought that it was probably the hardest labor in human history.

…Udeudeudeug!

Vikir rolled the huge boulder with his bare hands.

Pushing the boulder up the steep slope.

The boulder was not only heavy, but hot. As if it had just been pulled out of a fire.

But it wasn’t just the boulder he was pushing up.

Digging up soil, gushing groundwater, sulfurous gas, melting rock, billowing oil vapor, and blazing flames.

Everything about the construction site in the crater was extremely hot.

Prisoners were forced to walk barefoot and carry heavy objects over the insanely hot bedrock.

Inside this extreme heat, the flesh dries out and becomes crispy.

Blood, sweat, and the moisture of the flesh would drain away, leaving only the tiny bones and nerve bundles underneath.

Compared to this heavy labor, the entrance ceremony seems like a child’s play in the cradle.

…If Vikir, a superhuman, felt this way, what about the other prisoners?

All around the workshop, people were collapsing, and the crack of the guards’ whips echoed through the air.

Higher-level prisoners, level 6 or 7 and above, also collapse one by one from the constant hard labor and poor food.

Each time, the lower-level prisoners upstairs would fall to the ground.

“Did you hear? There was a death in Level 6 this time.”

“What? Level 6 is where the inmates are trapped, right?”

“There are deaths there, too. I thought it was just pure monsters.”

“Even among those monsters, there’s a division of power.”

“Damn, that guy who died there would have reigned like a king if he were on our floor, right?”

Seeing monsters that were much stronger and more vicious than them fall like that, how harsh must the depths of the workshop be?

That’s why the prisoners upstairs are so careful to never be transferred downstairs.

Naturally, the vague fear of the prisoners downstairs who survived in such a harsh environment cannot help but grow.

Meanwhile, the prisoners downstairs had fun laughing at and belittling their dying colleagues or the prisoners upstairs.

“Tsk, tsk, tsk. Hey, I hear there’s a death upstairs, must’ve been working.”

“On level six? You’re doing all the embarrassing work yourself. They should’ve transferred that weakling upstairs.”

“So, who ate it? The corpse, My mouth is watering….”

“The guys around here ripped it apart and there wasn’t much left, just bones and skin, nothing to eat.”

It is a strangely distorted boast about the class to which one belongs.

It was a sense of pride and superiority over who was enduring the most severe suffering.

In this atmosphere, a prisoner’s body, dried up like a mummy, receives no sympathy or remembrance.

“That monster bastard, he’s finally gone. There will be no need to worry anymore.”

“Haha – I can’t believe you’re like that even though you worked comfortably in a cooler place than me. Pathetic.”

The dead are greeted with fear, scorn, sneers, and sighs of relief.

Even the corpse is reduced to a piece of meat to be chewed and swallowed in a few bites.

The ‘Level 10’ construction site was such a place.

At that time.

Ttuu-

The sound of a horn echoed throughout the area, announcing lunch time.

A honeyed ten-minute break. Ten minutes that melt faster than ice cream thrown into lava.

This mealtime was my only hope and oasis to make it through the day.

…Tug! …tug! …tug! …tug!

The guards circled among the prisoners, distributing food from their baskets.

Vikir, too, was given lunch, the only meal rationed once a day.

…Tug!

A chunk of bread so charred it could have been coal fell in front of them.

The bread was already coarse and hard, but something had gone wrong in the cooking process, making it even blacker and harder.

The bread was served with salted sardines that hadn’t been gutted, and they reeked of a disgusting smell from the heat of transportation.

But the prisoners ate it gratefully.

Vikir chewed the bread and salted sardines and thought idly.

‘…I wonder if the message got through?’

Before being escorted to Nouvelle Vague, he’d sent a message to those who remained via Cindywendy.

He’d even left one more message through Isabella before entering the Iron Maiden, just in case.

There’s no telling what the demons might do on Earth without him.

With their companions gone, the remaining demons must be quite nervous.

But Vikir had a job to do here in Nouvelle Vague, and he couldn’t stay on the surface any longer.

So Vikir had shared his plan with a few trusted people.

‘For now, I’ll do what I can.’

Vikir shook off his thoughts and looked up.

Before him lay a vast crater, a shaft of sulfurous gas and bubbling lava.

It’s hard to believe this is the inside of an extinct volcano.

‘There’s something down here I’m looking for.’

Vikir stared at the bottom of the pit, not knowing how much further he would have to dig.

It was then that Decarabia, who had been silent in Vikir’s chest, spoke.

[It’s not long now, ‘it’ is surely near].

“So it is. I thought so, too.”

Vikir nodded, remembering the time before the regression.

The Level Ten work here in Nouvelle Vague is aimed at digging deeper into the volcano and expanding its interior space.

And it was serving some of Vikir’s purposes.

Even if it wasn’t for the Level Ten, Vikir had something else he was looking for, and he needed to dig down into this volcano.

To do so, he turned himself in and traveled all the way down to Nouvelle Vague.

It was as if the power of many prisoners was helping him.

Then.

“…!”

Vikir’s thoughts were interrupted.

He heard a group of prisoners giggling and shouting from the workshop above him.

“Hey, ‘Stupid Garam’!”

“Not enough bread, damn it, what if we screw this up!”

“What the fuck! Are you asking us to starve to death!”

“Give me your share of bread, you asshole!”

It was an amazing scene.

The prisoners were shouting accusations and profanity at the guard.

And he could see that the guard was rather shaken.

Vikir recognized the guard’s face at once.

‘You’re looking strangely familiar.’

The guard was Lieutenant Garam, who had given Vikir some guidance in the past.

His bushy hair, his cap pressed down so deeply that it obscured his face, and the burn marks that covered his face made it easy to recognize him, but they made it hard to tell what he looked like.

“I-I’m sorry. Inmates. There’s a problem with the bread ration, and there aren’t enough of them.”

“Who cares if there’s a problem, you probably stole our bread from the other guards!”

The prisoners’ accusations were fierce. No wonder, they were deprived of their once-a-day bread.

The work system at Nouvelle Vague was a bit unusual, with one guard in charge of dozens of prisoners, each working in their own section.

The guard in charge and the prisoners in charge change every month, and it’s all recorded as a monthly performance, which benefits and penalizes both the prisoners and the guards.

As a result, the guards do their best to improve the performance of the prisoners they are in charge of this month, often using whipping or solitary confinement as a weapon.

But just begging doesn’t work, so the guards try to encourage their prisoners by giving them better tools or extra bread.

And naturally, there were rivalries and nervousness among the guards, who would put well-behaved prisoners in their groups, or sneak extra tools or bread for the prisoners.

Of course, here in the Nouvelle Vague, all goods are limited and scarce, and if someone gets one more bite, someone else has to go hungry.

So the prisoners in Lieutenant Garam’s group resented his timidity in bringing them extra bread or work tools, only to have them taken away by other guards or prisoners.

“Damn it, Why should I be assigned to the ‘Stupid Garam’ group!”

“I thought you said he was the lowest performer among the new lieutenants?”

“Pathetic, I mean, ignored by his fellow guards and even the prisoners.”

“Did you hear, those burn marks on his face were inflicted by a prisoner?”

“Pfft- that’s not all, the asshole says he gets his meals taken away by prisoners too.”

“Do you want to know something more surprising? I heard that the higher-level prisoners even make him keep watch over them at night.”

As Vikir listened to the prisoners’ descriptions, he suddenly realized why the guard’s face looked so familiar.

‘It was a lot of hard and difficult work.’

Going to the prisoners of Level Nine to show them around would be something even most guards would be reluctant to do.

You never know when you’re going to get into trouble.

Meanwhile, ten minutes into the meal period, the prisoners in Garam’s group were still stretching out their legs.

“Damn it, we haven’t had any bread anyway, we’re not working, just beat us, beat us!”

“I’m not working either~”

“Well, since I’m in the stupid Garam group anyway, I’m not going to get any work done this month.”

“I’ll just get corporal punishment.”

“Hey, take out that triple baton on your waist. And kill me.”

Lieutenant Garam was at a loss as the group of prisoners was in a state of despair.

Clearly, there was something a little off about him.

Meanwhile, Vikir thought to himself.

‘Now that I think about it, other prisoners are also sabotaging work.’

It’s no wonder that the stronger and more violent prisoners are less likely to cooperate with construction.

Prisoners held at higher levels and in deeper cells tended to neglect their work, and the guards couldn’t easily intervene with them.

They are dangerous people who are lucky if they don’t go on a rampage.

‘It would also look weird if I worked too hard on my own.’

Vikir, is a prisoner at Level Nine. Most of the floors here at Level Nine are empty.

Most of the inmates are in and out of solitary confinement on a regular basis, either because they’ve been labeled as rebellious, a traitor, or a candidate for transfer to Level Ten.

But for personal reasons, Vikir had to work hard on the construction of the Level Ten, and if he did anything wrong, he could be suspected of being too diligent in his labor for a prisoner of Level Nine.

‘I’ll need to have some sort of ‘excuse’ for that. … And there’s something else I’d like to try out.’

After making his calculations, Vikir dropped the rock he was holding.

Kurrrrrrr!

The boulder rolled down the slope at a tremendous speed.

“What? What the hell is that!”

“Boulder rolling!”

“Stop, stop, no, dodge!”

The guards scrambled out of the way.

Quack! Pow!

With a loud bang, the boulder crashed into the lava pit, sending rocks and lava droplets flying in all directions.

Soon, all eyes turned upward.

The area where the inmates of Level Nine labor.

There stood Vikir, the culprit behind the boulder, looking nonchalant.

“I didn’t do it.”

The idea was to see how the guards came out.

Chapter 366

The Underground Extension Construction (3)

◆

…Boom!

Waves of rock fragments and lava spread in all directions, creating an earthquake and tsunami.

All the prisoners and guards lifted their heads and looked at Vikir.

“I will not.”

Vikir expressed his unwillingness to speak in brief words, and it was a revolutionary statement that shook the very foundations of Nouvelle Vague.

Prisoners work and guards supervise. This is because this was the system that kept the Nouvelle Vague alive.

….

For a moment, silence filled the whole place.

Vikir thought to himself.

‘It’s almost time for the guards to start whipping.’

According to the Nouvelle Vague manual, if a prisoner refused to work, the guards could use whips, batons, or knives to punish them.

…But?

Things turned out a little differently than Vikir expected.

“Huh! A riot on level Nine!”

“This, this, this, this, this is beyond our ability to handle!”

“Backup! Call for backup!”

“Kyaaahhhh! Blow the horn!”

The guards screamed like girls, their faces drained of color and turned to A4 paper.

Soon, the red horn, the most serious warning sound, echoed heavily throughout the workshop.

Ttuuuuuu! Ttuuuuuu! Ttuuuuuu! Ttuuuuuu!

As soon as they heard it, even the most distant prisoners dropped to the floor with their hands covering their eyes and ears, their mouths open, and their waists raised.

They braced themselves for a possible massive shockwave, a move that was apparently practiced often.

“….”

Vikir closed his mouth, suddenly feeling sick.

‘Now that I think about it, I heard that all of my comrades who escaped before regression were imprisoned at around level 3 or 4.’

A Level 3 or Level 4 prisoner rioting would certainly be treated differently than a Level 9 prisoner rioting.

But I didn’t realize it would be this different.

Vikir, who had simply refused to work, was being treated like a terrorist who had come to blow up Nouvelle Vague.

…Jeobeog! …jeobeog! …jeobeog! …jeobeog!

The clatter of military boots broke the cheaply frozen atmosphere of the workshop.

Guards of the highest rank.

Fierce-looking men, each with a sword or two emblazoned on their shoulder epaulettes, gathered in scrums of dozens.

Beside them were a circle of captain-ranked guards, each wearing a three-diamond insignia.

At the head of the line, a Bastille lieutenant colonel spoke.

“Night Hound. Resume your labor at once, or there will be only punishment.”

He was in charge of various events, such as entrance ceremonies and execution ceremonies, and management of labor camps, and was a high-ranking prison guard ranked just below the fifth warden in the Nouvelle Vague.

Upon hearing the stern warning, Vikir raised his right hand and slipped it into the pocket of his prison uniform.

The moment he pulled his hand out of the pocket, all the guards tensed up.

Seug-

But what emerged from Vikir’s pocket was a fist with only his middle finger extended straight out.

…Ppadeug!

A line of blood stood on Bastille’s forehead.

“Suppress him! Even if you kill him, I won’t hold you guilty!”

At those words, the guards in front of him raised their weapons and rushed forward.

Huge unyielding swords, massive maces, murderously sharpened longswords, heavy axe blades, and long, gaunt daggers fell upon Vikir without warning.

Vikir stroked his chin and pondered.

‘I don’t see the face I’m looking for, so why don’t I just run around a bit until it comes out?’

At the moment, Vikir’s eyes saw the guards flying at him with mana, and their attacks were extremely slow.

Although he couldn’t use his mana due to the BDISSEM handcuffs, it wasn’t difficult for him to dodge their attacks thanks to the Physical Resistance, Magic Resistance, and Reflexes stats he gained in the Hell Tree.

Vikir’s psychic nerves, which had blossomed to the extreme, were complemented by his experienced combat senses.

Puff-puff-puff!

With a few swipes of his head from side to side, Vikir dodged all of the attacks and soon slipped around the back of the scrum organized by the consular guards.

Then, the high-ranking guards who were building a siege network behind them were startled and surprised.

“Hiig, we can’t get through!”

“Don’t be silly! He can’t use mana anyway!”

“Kill him!”

Each of the guards drew a baton or sword and swung it at Vikir.

But.

“Bad judgment.”

Vikir swung the BDISSEM chains around his wrists and ankles in the air, knocking them all away.

Clang-woosh!

The BDISSEM chains, meant to restrain the prisoner, became a weapon.

The snake-like chains snapped the guards’ noses, cracking their bones.

Vikir continued to pummel the three guards with his fists, feet, and elbows, then broke through the encirclement of the higher-ranking guards.

“Ugh! Kkeug!”

“Keuhag!?”

“Whack-”

One by one, the lower-ranking guards were knocked out by Vikir’s blows.

“Ugh! What’s wrong with him, he can’t use mana!”

But it was only natural for the guards to react this way.

Woosh!

Vikir thought to himself as he stomped on the face of a Major-level guard who followed him the rest of the way.

‘They say the guards at Nouvelle Vague are mostly evil, and they’re right.’

No sane prison guard would come to work in such a dreadful place.

Most of the guards here at Nouvelle Vague have been demoted for excessive harshness or corruption.

Most of them are human beings who are no different from the prisoners except for the clothes they wear.

Vikir knew this because he had seen and heard many testimonies of how the guards took out their perverse desires and stress on the prisoners.

Then.

“…!”

Other figures entered Vikir’s vision.

Older faces with less grime than the high-ranking guards.

Guards of the so-called rank, the lowest class in the Nouvelle Vague, were gathered in groups of twos and threes, pointing their swords at Vikir.

Every single one of them was trembling.

“Stand, the seniors are down, now it’s our turn!”

“As a prison guard of the Great Nouvelle Vague, I will never back down!”

“Yo, be brave! Let’s fight!”

But no one stepped forward.

They were still too young and weak to jump into something that would surely kill them.

‘They must be about the same age as the students at the Colosseo Academy.’

Vikir thought as he looked at the new recruits in front of him.

Then.

Fit-

Vikir felt a streak of lightning pass across his cheek.

Bam-bam-bam.

A few strands of hair fell off his head from the sharp blow.

“…!”

Vikir turned his head in disbelief.

A determined-looking female guard stood there, a knife tucked into her waistband.

She looked to be in her late teens.

She had a pretty face, but her stern expression made her look much more seasoned than her years.

A diamond was pinned to her breastplate, along with a nameplate that read ‘Kirko Grimm’, a ranking badge indicating her so-called rank.

Vikir stared in pure admiration.

He could tell by the way she’d wielded the sword and the lead sword earlier that this girl’s talents were not ordinary.

‘A rare quality. Comparable to Tudor or Bianca or Sinclaire… or perhaps even Camus or Dolores.’

A girl with the potential to rival even the young heroes of the Colosseo Academy.

Why would someone with such wasted talent be in a place like this?

‘Kirko. Didn’t any hero have a name like that before the regression?’

Even the guards of Nouvelle Vague, who had declared themselves uninvolved in worldly affairs during the first half of the Demon War, had come to the surface to fight demons during the second half of the Demon War.

The situation was as bad as it was.

However, none of the female heroes who rose to prominence during that time were named Kirko.

‘…With all her talent and skill, why wasn’t she known?’

Vikir looked at Kirko with a bit of a question in his eyes.

“Hot!”

With no one else moving, Kirko alone bravely drew his sword.

Another lightning-like slash, this one touching the peak of Sword Expert.

‘Such a waste.’

Vikir dodged Kirko’s sword with a paper-thin gap.

…Kwang!

He stretched out his snake-like grip, grabbed Kirko by the throat, and slammed him to the ground.

“Keoheog!?”

Kirko hit the floor, vomiting.

Vikir had just lifted his foot to pass by Kirko’s side.

“Oh, no!”

There was another guard blocking his path.

Garam. Lieutenant Garam Nord.

A guard who was known as the ‘asshole’ among the prisoners as well as the guards.

This reckless junior guard stood in Kirko’s way and started a confrontation with Vikir.

“….”

Vikir lowered his gaze in a strange way.

Kirko slumped to the floor, moaning, and Garam standing in front of him in desperation.

Whatever the relationship between the two crybabies was, it wasn’t a pleasant one for Vikir.

“Get out of the way.”

“Oh, no, Kirkoman…!”

But Garam couldn’t finish his sentence.

Pfft!

Vikir raised his hand in annoyance and slapped Garam across the cheek.

…Kwakwakwak!

Garam was sent flying backwards in an instant, knocked out cold.

“Keueug!?”

The gathered guards stamped their feet, helpless to do anything about Vikir.

Vikir, meanwhile, could not outrun all these guards without expending mana, so he could only look for gaps in the encirclement.

Just then.

“What’s the commotion?”

A gravelly voice came from the top of a cliff far up the slope.

A voice as heavy as boiling water.

All the guards’ faces lit up as if they’d seen a savior.

A man stood on a cliff, looking down at them.

He had jet-black skin and eyes that burned yellow.

His short hair, the scars that covered his face and body, his log-like biceps, his waist, and the muscles that packed his body so tightly that his uniform was about to burst.

D’Ordume D D’Orcdile.

One of the five pillars that support the Nouvelle Vague.

One of the Five Warden, the most powerful of the Five.

Chapter 368

The Servant (2)

◆

…Udeudeug!

Vikir was crushed under a huge palm that pressed down on his entire torso.

“…It’s not human power, that’s for sure.”

Vikir was right, the palm of D’Ordume that was now crushing his entire body was not human.

A palm as big as a bed, the back of the hand covered in rough, thick scales, and nails like sharp claws.

And what was visible beyond the thin webs spread between the five thick fingers were black scales and burning yellow pupils.

Saltwater Crocodile.

D’Ordume was revealing a grotesque creature, half human, half crocodile.

“I don’t like this look because my uniform is torn.”

D’Ordume muttered, baring his fearsome teeth.

Meanwhile, Vikir looked at D’Ordume’s beast form and thought.

‘…I wonder if the rumor was true that all five wardens of Nouvelle Vague are not human.’

Beastman. Humans with a mix of genes from various beasts.

They are considered to be similar to orcs, dwarves, and elves, and are capable of coexisting with humans due to their high intelligence and general appearance.

However, when their emotions get the best of them, they transform into grotesque forms that look like a mix of animals, and because of this, they have been discriminated against, and their numbers have decreased to the point where they are almost non-existent.

“Being a member of the saltwater crocodile family… this is rare.”

Vikir burrowed into the soft dirt of the floor, slipping out of D’Ordume’s palm in an instant.

D’Ordume bared his teeth and chased after Vikir.

A long, thick tail protruded from its black uniform and swung like a whip.

Quack!

The stone mountain behind him crumbled to pieces.

Vikir darted inward, following the hollow where the tail had passed, and swung his BDISSEM chain at D’Ordume’s side.

However.

…Taaang!

The inside of D’Ordume’s uniform was already filled with black, thick scales and barbs.

That’s why Vikir’s punch earlier hadn’t done any damage.

“You don’t stand a chance.”

D’Ordume said, the aura of spirals still spinning from his forearms slamming into the ground.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

A pulsating storm of blows began to erupt from beneath the ground, threatening to tear the world apart.

Rocks, dirt, sand, and lava all turned to fine-grained dust in this whirlwind.

What’s more, the surrounding atmosphere is boiling madly as sulfurous gases are being sucked into the center of the storm and ignited.

Kuleuleuleuleuleug- kwakwakwang!

Explosions and crushing. Prisoners and guards alike shuddered in the distance at the sight, as if the god of destruction had descended.

And Vikir also made his decision.

“Ah, this won’t work.”

As long as he’s wearing the BDISSEM restraints, he can’t win, even if he comes back from the dead.

If it weren’t for the stats he’d built up in the Hell Tree, he would have been torn apart long ago.

“Then how about this?”

Vikir ducked out of the way of a flying blow.

The destination was the slope where Vikir had been laboriously pushing boulders up just moments before.

D’Ordume had just reached the top of the slope when Vikir followed him.

Tig-

Vikir kicked out all the loose rocks he had been working on.

And then a huge shower of boulders ignited and began to tumble down.

Kwakwang!

The flaming boulders rolled down the slope at breakneck speed, crashing into D’Ordume.

“Familiarizing yourself with the terrain is fundamental to combat.”

Vikir was always in the habit of studying the terrain around him in preparation for battle.

It was true in the jungle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, it was true in the orphanage, and it was true here on Level 9 in Nouvelle Vague.

But.

“You underestimate the Warden of Nouvelle Vague, kid.”

D’Ordume was unfazed by the house-sized boulder that rolled right up to his nose.

“Heub!”

Taking a deep breath, D’Ordume raised his bulging forearms high in the air.

And then.

Kwah-bang!

The blow shattered the rock.

The powerful fist and the swirl of blades that followed didn’t just shatter the rocks, they ground and crushed them into dust.

U-ooooo!

The guards, watching from afar, cheered at D’Ordume’s incredible feat.

However.

“It’s nice to have some strength. Please try more.”

Vikir stomped his foot over a few more trunks on the slope.

Kuleuleuleuleuleung-

Boulders, even larger than before, began to roll down the slope.

“….”

A bead of cold sweat formed on D’Ordume’s forehead.

“Eh!”

It would be disgraceful for him to back down while his men were watching.

As Vikir had planned, D’Ordume was forced to use his strength to break every falling rock.

Kwang! Kwakwang! Kwajijijig!

D’Ordume smashed three of the boulders in quick succession.

However, the fourth boulder proved to be a little too much for him….

Ppeoeog-

He was only able to break it in half.

The remaining piece of rock sent D’Ordume flying backwards, and he landed upside down on a lava pool at the bottom of the slope.

…Pungdeong! Pusiiiig-

The lava pool, which was boiling at a temperature far beyond common sense, swallowed D’Ordume whole.

….

The guards who were cheering just a moment ago froze in place.

A strange silence settled over the entire labor camp.

Then.

Pur-pur-pur!

The surface of the lava pool was shattered, and something large and dark soared upward.

D’Ordume. He leaped up, his face a mess of anger.

The uniforms issued to wardens are supposed to be fireproof, but judging by the fact that they were so ragged, the burns he had sustained were serious.

“Kaaaagh, you bastard, I’ll kill you!”

D’Ordume seemed to be blinded by his extreme rage.

One only had to look at his muscles, which were more than twice as bulging as before he fell into the lava.

Then.

“Enough.”

Vikir held up his hand.

While D’Ordume paused, wondering what was going on, Vikir quickly explained.

“I have no intention of resisting any longer. Let me live.”

“…?”

D’Ordume doubted his ears for a moment.

Criminals vicious enough to be locked up in Level 9 usually had huge egos.

So once they start a riot, the only way to quell it is by execution.

…But?

“I can’t beat you. Unless I use mana, but I don’t want to be killed anyway, so I’m done. I’ll accept any punishment if you let me live. From now on, I’ll be a good servant.”

All the guards, including D’Ordume, understood what Vikir was saying.

Oh, my God, a prisoner of Level 9 is surrendering himself! If he was going to do this, why did he start a riot in the first place?

“You, you ridiculous…!”

D’Ordume was about to shout when Vikir nudged him to the side.

“Just so you know, I’ve been working on loosening up all the joints a little while now.”

“…!”

“If you don’t let me live, I’ll zero out all the work you’ve done so far.”

Vikir has been working on a lot of nails, not just the ones he just removed.

If all the boulders on the shaft up there were to roll off, the entirety of level nine would be wiped out.

Grrtt.

D’Ordume gritted his teeth hard enough to break them.

If the little bastard has his way, he’ll be caught someday, but the damage is too great.

With so many of his men watching, and the other workshops’ laborers stopped, he couldn’t afford to keep the commotion going any longer.

“Very well. If you surrender, I’ll spare you execution.”

“Very well then.”

Vikir descended the slope only after receiving D’Ordume’s public promise.

As Vikir descended, a number of guards who had been flanking D’Ordume rushed to his side and placed double and triple BDISSEM cuffs on him.

Thud, thud, thud.

D’Ordume walked over to the kneeling Vikir.

And then

Bam!

With all his might, he slammed his fist into Vikir’s face.

Ttug- ttuug-

D’Ordume snorted as he looked down at Vikir’s bloodied body.

“Take him to solitary confinement. Three months, no, a hundred days.”

“Yes! A hundred days in solitary is a de facto ‘execution’.”

Beside him, Lieutenant Colonel Bastille nodded.

Next, a number of guards rushed over and pulled at BDISSEM’s chains.

Vikir fell to the ground, dragged, and disappeared into a deep pool of blood.

“…The commotion is over! Resume your labor!”

D’Ordume turned and shouted.

Then.

“….”

Neither the guards nor the prisoners stirred, but no one moved from their seats.

Then D’Ordume shouted again.

“What are you doing, resume your labor immediately!”

Just then, Lieutenant Kirko, next to him, spoke up in a low voice.

“Excuse me, Colonel…. I’m sorry to have to tell you this, but… don’t have anything to do with labor.”

“What?”

D’Ordume frowned as if he didn’t know what she was talking about.

Then Kirko cautiously raised a finger and pointed behind him.

“…?”

D’Ordume turned his head to see what was behind him.

A collapsed mountain. Shattered rocks. Deeply dug up dirt.

The construction was so far advanced that there was nothing for the prisoners to do but labor.

The destruction was going on so fast and so much that it was overwhelming while D’Ordume ran around sweating.

“…! …! …! …! …!”

The veins on D’Ordume’s forehead, who had single-handedly fulfilled the prisoners’ work quota for the day, seemed as if they were about to burst.

Chapter 369

Solitary Confinement (1)

◆

Solitary confinement. Corporal punishment for sharing a room alone.

Solitary confinement is a common form of corporal punishment in prisons.

One might wonder why solitary confinement is a form of corporal punishment, but it makes sense if the room is small enough to defy common sense.

The popular concept of solitary confinement is that of a small space that’s less than half a meter square, a complete claustrophobic space with nothing to see and nobody to talk to.

However, this is the definition of solitary confinement in most prisons, and Nouvelle Vague is far more severe.

‘…, I was told.’

Three months in solitary confinement for refusing to do labor and fighting the guards.

Now Vikir will experience firsthand what it means to be sent to solitary confinement, the second harshest punishment in Nouvelle Vague after execution.

Creak- Creak- Creak- Creak-

One of the guards carried Vikir, who was stretched out and covered in blood from D’Ordume’s blows.

As he dragged the cart, he spoke in a low voice.

“As of this hour, you will be held in solitary confinement. You will be released after 100 days.”

Vikir raised his head, removed the blood scabs, and opened his eyes.

He saw the familiar face of the guard.

<Garam Nord>

The name on his nametag was a familiar one.

“Did you get caught again?”

Vikir asked, and Garam smiled bitterly.

“No. This time, I volunteered.”

“…Why?”

“To get you to your cell in relative safety.”

Garam said that there are vicious guards who often kill prisoners who have been found dead for fun.

That was why he had volunteered to make sure that Vikir would not suffer any further penalties beyond those prescribed by law.

Vikir shook his head.

“What does it matter to you if I die or not?”

“I just wanted to thank you ….”

“Thank you?”

“Yes. Because you didn’t kill me.”

Vikir was silent for a moment at Garam’s words.

This was a calculated rampage in many ways, and there was no need to escalate things any further than necessary.

So Vikir had been deliberately careful not to cause any deaths, and Garam seemed to have misunderstood something from that.

Vikir was about to tell him the truth when Garam spoke up.

“And… most of all, thank you for bringing Kirko back safely.”

Kirko? Vikir paused for a moment.

Then he remembered the face of the imposing girl guard he’d fought so briefly before the fight with D’Ordume.

‘She was quite a character, too good to be rotting in a place like this.’

After his brief reminiscence, Vikir glanced away again.

Garam’s ears were slightly red from pulling the cart in front of him.

“All the other guards had their noses crushed, their teeth knocked out, and their limbs broken, but… Kirko was unharmed, so I’m grateful for that.”

“Why are you thanking her for being uninjured?”

“Well, that’s because….”

Garam faltered and started to say something, but then clamped his mouth shut.

Seeing that, Vikir understood why Garam was despised by his fellow guards and prisoners.

‘He’s too normal, the kind of personality that can only be considered shallow in this bottom of hell.’

Garam was an ordinary boy in his late teens.

So, it was inevitable that people would be at a disadvantage in places that were out of the ordinary.

As a result, he was bullied by his fellow guards in the dormitory and looked down upon by the prisoners in the workshop.

He was even despised by a female coworker he had a crush on.

‘In many ways, he doesn’t fit in at Nouvelle Vague.’

That was Vikir’s assessment of Garam.

‘He seems to have a good nature, but that is of no use in Nouvelle Vague.’

Then.

Garam spoke up.

“…You’re going to be in solitary confinement from now on.”

“….”

“I recommend that you bite your tongue before that, because solitary confinement is… really terrible.”

Such was the advice of the good-natured Garam, and he meant it.

Naturally, Vikir ignored the advice.

“That’s the kind of advice I was given when I was being escorted to Nouvelle Vague.”

“Ha, but solitary confinement is something else! It’s nothing like a convoy or an entrance ceremony, it’s horrible…!”

But. Garam could not finish his sentence.

Suddenly, a long shadow had begun casting in front of the cart.

“Hohoho- Oh my? Who is this? It’s been a while since we had a guest?”

A woman’s voice echoed through the black cave.

The moment he heard it, Garam’s body began to stiffen.

“Well, that’s it for me then. Good luck.”

Garam gave Vikir one last pat on the back.

He turned to face the other side and gave a powerful salute before turning and running away.

“….”

Vikir looked up.

He saw a mountain peak jutting up like an awl. It was reminiscent of the Red Awl Castle in Morgue’s territory.

A woman walked toward him, leaving the harsh background behind.

She’s tall, slender, and sexy voluminous body, and even more colorful mustache.

Beneath her sunglasses, the woman with the bushy mustache looked down at Vikir.

Vikir knew who she was at a glance.

‘…Colonel Souaré.’

A half-dwarf, half-elf, she was one of the five leading wardens of Nouvelle Vague and, along with Colonel D’Ordume, the most likely next in line for the position.

With dwarf blood in her veins, she grew a beard despite being a woman and had a natural talent for working with minerals.

“Hmmm~ Let’s see. You must be the new prisoner who fought D’Ordume, lively one.”

Souaré looked down at Vikir and chuckled.

Kwagik-

Souaré stomped on the cart with the heel of her high heel, crushing it, and lifted Vikir by the throat with her hand.

“Let’s see~ which cell do you want me to put you in?”

Souaré said in a seductive voice as she shook Vikir.

Vikir frowned.

There wasn’t anything around that looked like a room, so what the hell was she going to do?

…But Vikir’s doubts were quickly dispelled.

“Oh, yeah. Let’s mix asphalt, concrete, and some BDISSEM powder and sculpt it.”

Souaré then rolled the floor with her foot.

And then something amazing happened.

Kkulleong-

The ground beneath Souaré’s foot melted away, then boiled over with a lava-like red glow.

It soon turned into a liquid as thick as molten metal and began to change its appearance at Souaré’s will.

“I’ll make you a solitary cell, just the right size for your body.”

Souaré grinned, set Vikir on the floor, and popped a large pipe into his mouth.

“This is your breathing hole. Don’t lose it.”

Frighteningly, Souaré’s words were barely out of her mouth when the concrete and asphalt from above began to cover Vikir’s body.

Soon, Vikir’s body was swallowed by the concrete and asphalt and turned into a cocoon.

Hot lava flows over him.

Chirrrrrrrrrrrrrr.

The mold was solidifying.

Vikir had to squeeze his eyes shut against the high internal temperature rose to the point where it was unbearable and the feeling of emptiness rose.

‘…So this is the Nouvelle Vague’s solitary confinement.’

Even for the mighty Vikir, solitary confinement was grim.

No wonder prisoners feared solitary almost as much as the death penalty.

Usually lasting a day or two, sometimes even a week, Vikir was sentenced to 100 days in solitary confinement.

-‘Put him in solitary confinement. Three months, no, 100 days.’

-‘Yes! One hundred days in solitary is a de facto ‘execution’.’

He could see now why Lieutenant-Colonel Bastille had treated Vikir as if he were on death row after hearing D’Ordume’s order.

‘Still, I’m glad I got a pipe in my mouth.’

Water and food will come in through this, and he’ll be able to breathe anyway.

But without being able to do anything, it was a waste of time for the hardworking Vikir.

‘…I’ll take this opportunity to let my body rest a bit and organize myself a bit.’

It’s important to stop and take a look back after all the running you’ve been doing.

However, he couldn’t help but notice that the place was unpleasant.

Whatever happened next, Vikir realized, the last thing he needed was solitary confinement.

Three months and ten days.

Vikir would train his mind through meditation, and at the same time, he would try to piece together the information from before the regression and plan his next move.

….

He would have done just that if it weren’t for a voice that came out of nowhere.

“Pushishishishi… A young fellow has joined this time, right?”

The voice of a man who looked quite old.

“It’s good to have a solitary companion in my later years, young man, I hope you live long. That way, you will be my companion as well.”

The voice was quite unpleasant to listen to, like a nail scraping against a glass plate.

“Who are you?”

Vikir said briefly, pushing the hardening concrete with his lower jaw.

He had to be careful not to let the pipe in his mouth fall.

Then.

“….”

There was no answer for a while.

As the silence slowly hardened like concrete.

“Pushishishishi….”

The eerie laughter continued for a long time.

And soon, the person locked in the cell next to him revealed his identity.

“Just call me ‘Angajumang’.”

Chapter 371

Sucker Shark (1)

◆

Three months later.

“Hohoho-what’s this, you’re alive?”

The concrete of the cell shattered with Souaré’s exclamation.

Ppageujag- ppadeudeug! Ujijijig!

The hardened concrete shattered and V ikir opened his eyes.

His body had been reduced to nothing but bone and skin, but his eyes were still bright with life.

Souaré stroked her mustache and said.

“Well, if I’d known you were going to be like this, I should have taken you out a month or two ago. You’re better off in my room than in solitary confinement, aren’t you? I’ve been having some lonely nights lately.”

“No thanks.”

“Hohoho – you’re a cheeky little thing, really. I like you, and I’ll be nice to you next time you’re in solitary confinement ~ see ya!”

Vikir walked out unsteadily, being waved goodbye by Souaré.

A quick glance behind him revealed a pile of concrete and asphalt, covered in countless piles.

It must be the solitary confinement cell of the old man Angajumang.

‘It was a terrible time.’

Next to him, old man Angajumang kept asking him to play nonsword bimu.

Vikir was returned to the stone chamber of Level 9, where he was originally imprisoned.

BANG!

The door slams shut, and darkness immediately descends.

He would be taken to the labor camp at dawn in a few hours.

Vikir decided to save some stamina for that time.

Jiiing- twes!

The Ring of Andromalius was spat out from Decarabia’s unknown mouth.

He had stockpiled quite a bit of food in it, so Vikir took it out little by little and consumed it.

“I guess I’ll live a little longer.”

Vikir looked down at Andromalius’ ring.

In the past, after creating a large barrier at the Academy, the power has not been gathered well, so he could only use it to take out food like this.

It was a shame.

[Human, what will you do from now on?]

“I have to do labor, now I have an excuse to work hard.”

[Human. The other humans must think you work hard because you’re afraid of solitary confinement].

“Right. I need to get to work on Level 10 as soon as possible. So I can find what I’m looking for.”

When Decarabia asked, Vikir responded indifferently

But today, Decarabia had a lot of questions.

[What on earth are you looking for at such a deep seabed, anyway? Is there some kind of treasure hidden beneath a dead extinct volcano?]

“….”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

What Vikir is looking for.

It’s a very important thing, especially now that there are only four of the Ten Corpses left.

‘If the three survivors of the ten corpses join hands, something will happen.’

They would most likely try to hasten the age of destruction by force.

If that happens, no matter how hard Vikir try to get out of the way, he’ll only have one body.

A terrible war that would kill countless human beings. There will be a war of destruction.

Now, the battle against the Ten Corpses has entered its final phase. Vikir, too, had something to lose and something to gain.

‘Maybe I can end the fight once and for all.’

And so Vikir traveled to Nouvelle Vague to find a weapon that could counter the final weapon of the Ten Corpses.

[The final weapon of the Ten Corpses, which presumably means the Rainy Season of Fear?]

“You know very well.”

[I know, for I was once their ally].

Decarabia narrows its eyes in agreement, then continues asking questions.

[…, Did the human side have any weapons to counter the ‘The Rainy Season of Fear’, as far as I know, no].

“The demons would know that.”

Vikir said, his eyes shining.

But there is. Deep within the Nouvelle Vague volcano, beyond the reach of even the eyes of the demons….

An ancient weapon, ‘one that shakes the earth with a roar’, that no mortal knows even exists.

“‘Poseidon’ definitely exists.”

The Rainy Season of Fear is the final weapon of the demons, and only Poseidon, the final weapon of humanity, can quell it.

Vikir had traveled all the way down to Nouvelle Vague to find it.

Even if it meant tearing up all the relationships he’d built with his friends.

‘They’re just schoolmates, people I knew for a year or so when I was a teenager. They’ll quickly forget about me.’

Vikir briefly flashed back to the faces of Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, but quickly dismissed them.

What matters now is life in Nouvelle Vague. He must push forward with the construction as quickly as possible, so as not to be outdone by the demons.

‘The ones who joined hands must have been Cimeries the 4th, Andrealphus the 3rd, and Flauros the 4th, right?’

The speculation came from the mouths of those who had tortured him before he entered the Nouvelle Vague.

Cimeries, who was apparently a Donquixote, Andrealphus, who was apparently an Usher, and Flauros, who was apparently a Leviathan.

‘Is the last one still in the imperial family?’

It is suspicious that the Emperor did not even show his nose until this division was born from the of the Seven Great Families.

So Vikir planned to infiltrate the imperial family the day he escaped from Nouvelle Vague.

‘If I have to, I’ll slit the throats of the entire imperial family….’

Then.

A voice interrupted Vikir’s thoughts of casual treason.

“Everyone wake up! It’s time to go to work!”

It was the wake-up call of Lieutenant Colonel Bastille.

◆

All prisoners in the Nouvelle Vague are required to perform labor at 4 a.m.

There were no exceptions, even for prisoners returning from solitary confinement.

…Kkang! …peoeog! …kwasag!

Vikir was pickaxing while wearing several layers of BDISSEM handcuffs and shackles.

The guards chattered as Vikir continued to dig without pause.

“I’ve never seen a Level 9 prisoner work so hard.”

“Don’t you think there’s something fishy about this? Is there an ulterior motive?”

“No ulterior motive. He’s the one who refused to do his labor the other day and was subdued by Warden D’Ordume and sent to solitary confinement.”

“Oh, right. He was in solitary confinement for three months or so, and he made it out alive? That’s a badass.”

“He made it back alive, but… After that, he keep his mouths shut and do nothing but labor.”

“Indeed, solitary confinement is scary, isn’t it? Even the monsters of Level 9 have a human side.”

“It’s frightening. I’ve seen a man come out of solitary confinement after only half a day, his head white as a sheet, and another after a full day, dead of a heart attack.”

No one, not the prisoners, not the guards, thought anything strange about Vikir’s hard work.

From then on, Vikir became known as the hardest-working prisoner in Level 9.

“Okay, it’s meal time! Ten minute break!”

The next thing he knew, it was lunchtime and the guards were calling for a break.

Vikir sat down and ate his half-steamed sardines and stone-hard black bread.

Waddeuk-

The black bread, which was hard enough to break a tooth, did not crumble even when it was hit hard against a rock.

The sardines, despite being heavily salted, gave off a sour stench.

But the prisoners ate this trashy meal without a second thought.

The work of completing the Level 10 was hard labor.

Someone called it an extinct volcano, and the slightest digging into the cooled strata unleashed a fearsome burst of heat.

A scorching sun that dried everything to a crisp, and lava cascades that flowed everywhere.

Being here is like being turned into jerky.

A normal person wouldn’t last more than a few seconds.

Turning his head, he saw some of the prisoners staring down into the lava-filled pit.

Presumably, they’ve gotten tired of the stale pickled sardines and rock-hard black bread and are looking for something else to eat.

“ …Are there any?”

“Yes. I just saw a shadow.”

“Let’s go fishing.”

“Pull the line and needle before it burns!”

With that, the prisoners reeled in something with a chain fishing line and hook and line needle made from work tools (which are a death penalty if lost).

Chwaak-.

It was a lava shark, a monster that lived in the lava, eight meters long and over a ton in weight.

“Gotcha!”

A prisoner shouted, and the surrounding prisoners rushed towards him.

The lava shark, which had nothing to eat but bones and skin, was quickly torn to shreds by the hands and teeth of the countless prisoners.

The prisoners searched for other food.

But Nouvelle Vague is not a hospitable environment for hunting creatures in the first place, and the prisoners’ hunger forced them to look elsewhere.

“…Heoeog, heoeog.”

Vikir looked at a prisoner sitting in the distance, gasping for air.

His skin was pale and soft, and he was plump and overweight, making him unsuited to the harsh work environment.

He could see the other prisoners making sure he didn’t have to work.

“You don’t have to work. We’ll do all the work for you.”

“Don’t even move. Just lie down.”

“Uh-huh, don’t move, you’ll lose weight.”

Next thing he knows, the most powerful prisoner in the room walks up to the fat one with his mouth watering.

Wajag-

The prisoner tears off a piece of flesh and eats it.

The prisoner screams in pain as his flesh is ripped off, but he can only swallow his tears in frustration.

“Hehehe… Get this bastard treated. He’s going to be chewed up for a long time.”

“I’m glad you put the ointment in in check.”

“Tomorrow it’s me.”

“This asshole’s flesh needs to heal fast.”

The expression “Rip Off” is often used to describe the exploitation of another person, and here in Nouvelle Vague, it was happening in a very literal way.

Of course, Vikir had no reason to engage in such a disastrous food war, as he had plenty of food stockpiled within Andromalius’ ring.

“…They live so hard.”

Vikir marveled.

At this point, it was impossible to tell who was human and who was demon.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir’s eye caught a third way the prisoners were getting food.

It was neither hunting nor eating. Surprisingly, it was the most normal and common-sense way.

Chapter 372

Sucker Shark (2)

◆

A third way for prisoners to get food.

It was called begging.

Several guards were sitting on a rock eating lunch.

While the prisoners were eating pickled sardines and black bread, the guards were eating better things.

Guards receive a hunk of salted pork, a large hard-boiled fish roe, fresh seaweed, a bottle of manatee’s milk, and, on rare occasions, carrots, spinach, or potatoes as a special treat.

More senior guards at the rank of major and above were sometimes given fruit, such as apples and oranges.

It was nothing compared to the food on the ground, but at least in the eyes of the prisoners, the guards’ meals were the most delicious food in the world.

The guards would sometimes use this food as bait to lure the prisoners.

“Hey, sucker shark~”

One of the guards waved his hand playfully, and a prisoner who had been waiting in the distance ran over, his feet sweating.

“Get down.”

The prisoner immediately dropped to the ground and exposed his stomach.

“Stand up.”

“Sit down.”

“Raise your legs.”

“Open your mouth.”

“Hands.”

The prisoner did as he was told, performing all the actions a pet dog would do.

The guard finally chuckled and tossed the prisoner a piece of leftover pork.

“Keep up the good work, boy, and don’t get in trouble.”

“Yes! Guard! My honor!”

The prisoner waits with his head on the ground, drooling.

Like a “sucker shark” picking up what the big fish has left to eat.

Finally, the guard gives him permission to eat.

“That’s enough, eat.”

With trembling hands, the prisoner picked up the piece of pork and sniffed it for a long time.

Then he licked his tongue excitedly across the fat that had hardened on the outside of the pork.

He savored the salty, savory flavor for a long time, his eyes filled with tears.

Little by little, he tasted the flavor on the tip of his tongue, gnawing at it with the tips of his teeth like he was sharpening his nails.

As he did so, the piece of pork melted in his mouth, almost like candy.

The other prisoners watching could only gulp down their saliva.

“Now, you guys, if you finish your quota of work this month, we’ll let you eat the leftovers!”

“Work like hell, and I’ll let you have my fixed sucker shark!”

“Work hard! I’ll take care of the guy with the highest workload on the floor this month and let him eat ice cream!”

The guards said as they tossed leftover fish roes, scraps of meat, and manatee milk onto the floor.

No wonder the prisoners’ eyes rolled when they saw the rotten sardines and stony bread they couldn’t eat.

“Oooooooh, let’s get to work!”

“Did you hear? It’s ice cream!”

“It’s mine! I’ll work the most!”

The prisoners’ morale soared. They were now confused as to whether they were human or not.

Hunger is a terrifying thing, male or female.

They had been so deeply tamed down to their bones.

…But.

Not all prisoners dreamed of sucker sharks like this.

“Hey.”

In some cases, the hierarchy between guards and prisoners was completely reversed.

A prisoner at Level 8. Aka ‘Plague Leper’.

He was currently sitting on a rock, picking at his pimples.

The other prisoners dare not go near him for fear of catching the plague.

“Hey- can’t you hear me, is your liver so swollen it’s sticking out of your stomach?”

And it was the guards, not the prisoners, who were calling out now.

“….”

It was a lowly guard with bushy hair and a large burn scar on his face.

It was Lieutenant Garam Nord.

Sakkuth stretched out his palm toward him as if it were a matter of course.

“Give me your meal.”

“….”

Garam glanced at the guards around him.

Unfortunately or fortunately, his fellow guards had no idea that he was being insulted.

This was not because Sakkuth’s actions were covert, but because Garam was in a position to be unnoticed by his coworkers in the first place.

Sakkuth smirked and snatched the meal from Garam’s hand.

“I knew you weren’t looking at all the other guards, man. Thanks?”

“….”

“Be grateful that I’m letting you get away with offering this much food. Do you understand?”

The voice was low and threatening.

“If I set my mind to it, you know, that Kirko or whatever the hell she is, she’ll get the plague, and she’ll die a very miserable death.”

“….”

“You’re in love with that bitch, aren’t you, and you don’t want to see the girl you’re in love with shit all over you and then dry up like jerky, do you?”

“….”

“Then, take care of it and bring me lunch like this every day. Kurukuru….”

He muttered in a sullen voice and tried to shove bits of pork and fish roe into his mouth.

Just then.

“Hey!”

A sharp shout echoed throughout the workshop.

It was a shout so loud that it made him hiccup in surprise as he tried to swallow his food.

Where Garam turned his wide-eyed gaze, a lone female guard stood.

Ensign Kirko Grimm, an elite junior guard, soon to be promoted to lieutenant.

Her eyes narrowed, and she glared back and forth between Sakkuth and Garam.

“A guard gives food to a prisoner, are you crazy?”

Garam doesn’t dare to meet Kirko’s demanding gaze.

The prisoners clicked their tongues.

“That annoying couple again?”

“A stupid woman and a stupid man.”

“What a waste of a woman.”

“Kigkigkig- it’s hard when you have the wrong motives.”

Judging by the prisoners’ reactions, this was a fairly common occurrence.

Kirko stalked over and snatched the food from Sakkuth’s hand.

Then, with a sharp glare, she said

“If you are a prisoner and covet food one more time, you will be beheaded on the spot. I will report you to my superiors immediately.”

“Kurukuru- why is our pretty female guard so cranky today… eug!?”

Sakkuth tried to deflect the situation with a sneer, but it was impossible due to Kirko’s footsteps behind him.

Cha-kang!

Kirko quickly drew his sword and cut off the tip of Sakkuth’s beard.

As Sakkuth’s eyes widened in disbelief, Kirko snorted once and looked at Garam next to him.

“Don’t embarrass your mate… No, don’t embarrass the guard, you idiot.”

“I’m sorry.”

“Don’t even say sorry. Are you really an asshole?”

There was a faint contempt in Kirko’s gaze as she glared at Garam.

“…If you can’t do your job, you’re an asshole.”

And with that, she walked away, her hair whipping in the cold wind.

Garam hung his head, unable to argue further, and the prisoners laughed at him.

“‘Stupid Garam’ is just as stupid today.”

“He’s really pathetic, how can a guy like that be a guard?”

“You said that if you join that bastard’s group, you can steal that bastard’s meals?”

“He’s a piece of shit. He doesn’t make me work, but he gives me meals.”

“I want to work under him next month, because I don’t have to work and I get to eat delicious food.”

The nicknames that followed him were varied.

“Stupid Garam,” “stupid dog,” “walking bread,” “idiot,” “hogwash,” etc…. All of them were negative.

And to my surprise, the nicknames came not from the prisoners, but from their fellow guards.

“Hey, did you lose your meal to the prisoner again? This guy is really stupid.”

“It’s good to prevent problems by giving a meal as a bribe… If you do that, the other prisoners will also have bad habits. So don’t do it to your coworkers.”

“Eh, are you okay, Kirko? Don’t worry about him, he’ll just stress you out and ruin your pretty face.”

“Asshole. I’ll see you later, after dinner.”

His coworkers scowl at him.

The more they talked, the deeper Garam’s burn-scarred face sunk.

Kirko glanced at it, and with a light sigh, turned completely around and left with her comrades.

“Kurukuru… I’m letting you off today because of that damned bitch, but not tomorrow, don’t forget. Bring your entire lunch. Otherwise, like I said, I’ll turn that Kirko bitch into a second plague leper.”

He whispered in Garam’s ear again, this time in a low voice, and walked away.

Even humming a song.

“….”

Alone, Garam soaked up the scornful glances and sneers from the prisoners and guards around him.

All the while, his gaze remained fixed on Kirko, who stood in the center of their circle.

….

And there are eyes that watch this whole sequence of events wordlessly.

“…Hmm.”

It was Vikir.

After much thought, he formulated a plan.

‘Maybe I could use this to my advantage?’

Garam. And Kirko.

Perhaps the relationship between these two young men could help.

‘In the upcoming moment of escape.’

Vikir was now plotting his escape from Nouvelle Vague.

A plan that would be put into action as soon as he found Poseidon, the hope of mankind.

…And.

‘That moment’ came much sooner than Vikir had expected.

Chapter 373

Poseidon (1)

◆

Buuuuk-.

A sound like tough leather being torn.

Suddenly, the sky tore open.

A rim of searing fire burned around the crack, and giant snakes of fire lurched toward the ground.

Patter-patter-patter-patter-

Searing raindrops fell from the sky above.

The showers of fire left no place untouched.

The grass and trees of the mountains burned, and the forests became a desert of ashes.

The oceans and lakes boiled over and turned into wastelands, and all living and breathing things were burned or dried up.

Skeletons cried out even in death, and those who hadn’t yet died were afraid to take a single breath.

A time had come when nothing could be promised and nothing could be assured.

Protecting and preserving has become a crude joke, and the concept of yesterday and tomorrow has been lost.

Showers of fire became floods of flame, flooding across the continent for 150 days.

After five months of non-stop torrential rain, the world was set ablaze.

Burned and dried corpses formed mountains, and flames leaped across the horizon, searing like a tongue licking the sky.

‘Rainy Season of Evil Fire.’

Endless, endless rains of fire, winds of fire, thunderbolts of fire, floods of fire.

It was the long rainy season that marked the end of humanity.

It was the final weapon of the demons that inflicted the greatest and most devastating damage on the human alliance by wiping out 98% of all living humans.

◆

It’s 3:30 in the morning.

‘Aaaah!’

‘It’s hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!’

‘Help me!’

Screams come out of nowhere in the quiet stone chamber.

Burning people screaming at the top of their lungs.

“…! …! …! …!”

Vikir opened his eyes in a cold sweat.

He’d had a nightmare. A dream about ‘those days’ for the first time in a long time.

“…A shower of fire. Is this a nightmare I haven’t had in a long time?”

Who said that the trauma caused by fire cannot be washed away even after a lifetime?

The burn-in marks on the old hound’s retina were still clearly visible.

It had been several minutes since he’d awakened from his dream, but his hair still stood on end.

The goosebumps on his forearms were still there.

Cheolpeog- cheolpeog- chwaag!

Vikir washed his face in the salt water that dripped down from the ceiling.

The icy cold water dug into his hair and soaked it, shaking him out of his dream.

The Rainy Season of Fear. The terrible season that had cost humanity the most in the Age of Destruction came back like a nightmare.

A time when countless drops of fire fell from the sky, scorching the world.

The day when most of the faces Vikir had met, known, and remembered had burned to blackness.

“…I don’t know if I did a good job of finishing what Cindywendy asked me to do.”

Vikir muttered as he flopped down on the ground.

Anticipating this terrible rainy season, Vikir had warned Cindywendy once before.

‘There will be a great flood soon, so have the ‘Ark’ ready.’

Vikir crouched in the corner of the stone chamber and contemplated what lay ahead.

It had been about two years since he had been imprisoned here in Nouvelle Vague.

‘…It seems like just yesterday I was in solitary confinement for a hundred days.’

A lot has happened in the Nouvelle Vague since then.

First of all, the construction work on the Level Ten has progressed a lot.

The already deep crater had become even deeper and was now called the Great Crater.

Old prisoners were dying and new ones were coming in.

Two years ago, the prisoners who had been in charge had grown weak from the hard labor and poor nutrition and had either died or resigned from power, leaving their places to be filled by younger, less imprisoned prisoners.

A small number of new guards have also been appointed.

Most of them did not last long and died on the job due to the extreme conditions of the prisoners, the territorial nature of the original guards, harsh working conditions, and unknown endemic diseases.

In the meantime, Vikir has been able to get most of what he wants.

The construction of the Level ten sector has progressed, and he has earned the trust of the other prisoners and the guards by staying out of trouble and serving them faithfully.

…But only one. There was one thing that even Vikir didn’t have, and that was a newspaper.

‘Or, more accurately, news from the ground.’

What had happened on the ground during Vikir’s nearly two years inside Nouvelle Vague?

Vikir tried hard to find out, but it ended up being fruitless.

Neither the other guards nor the prisoners knew what was going on outside, and in the first place, only a few guards at the top knew.

But once, Vikir managed to catch a glimpse of news from above, and it wasn’t all that reliable.

‘…Damn. Why was this magazine shut down? It was good.’

A third-rate pornographic magazine that Lieutenant Colonel Bastille grumbled and threw away.

The magazine, which was popular among the guards due to its extreme sexuality and other sexual controversies, had stopped coming in at some point.

A pornographic magazine that had always been a bestseller was suddenly discontinued. It could have been, but there was something suspicious about it.

‘Maybe there’s a problem with the supply of magazines. Maybe the trees to make the paper are gone, or maybe the building where the magazine is housed has collapsed, or maybe there’s no one on the planet who can afford to subscribe anymore?’

Vikir set his chin in thought.

They may be making excessive assumptions based on the fact that a third-rate pornographic magazine unilaterally canceled its subscription.

But as with everything, it never hurts to be prepared.

Vikir thought.

With no way to get news from the ground, he couldn’t be sure, but it was likely that the demons were preparing for the final war by now.

No, they would have started the day he was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague.

‘…It’s time for me to start producing some tangible results.’

Vikir was feeling a rare feeling of impatience.

Ttuuuuuu-

At 4 a.m., the wake-up call cut through the air like a sword.

Vikir, who is always up and ready half an hour before the wake-up call, was the first to hit the grate today.

The BDISSEM grate becomes as mushy as a blade of grass, and when he laid it on its side, an opening was created for him to exit the room.

What a mysterious material.

“The labor begins, scum!”

The prisoners crawl out of their cells to the workhouse today under the command of Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, who oversees the labor camp.

The miserable meals, the poor rest, the prisoners growing increasingly angry.

In the two years that Vikir has spent here, countless faces have come and gone.

Almost all of the overwhelming majority of the prisoners were assembled in the labor yard, waiting on the floor, looking as if they might collapse and die at any moment.

Every day was the same as yesterday. And tomorrow would be the same as today.

Hot air, bursting steam, foul sulfurous fumes, roaring flames, scorched earth, heavy loads, little sleep, sweat, and hungry bodies.

In this daily race to the death, the prisoners were living the same life as the dead, with no past, present, or future.

Their thoughts in the labor camp were always the same.

Before entering labor, they thought, ‘I want to die like this,’ after going into labor, ‘Please just live my life,’ and after the labor was over, ‘I want to be safe today too.’

It was always the same pattern.

…But not Vikir.

‘Not today!’

Every day was a new challenge, every moment a first exploration, every race a certain destination.

Unlike the other prisoners, Vikir had come down here of his own free will, and he knew what he wanted.

So for the past two years, without a single day off, he has been chipping away at stone, scraping dirt, and digging deep into the crater.

…And today. This very moment!

Vikir is faced with a day that is completely different from the 700 or so days he has spent in Nouvelle Vague so far.

BANG!

The sound of a mysterious explosion echoed through the center of the labor camp on Level 9.

Explosions were as common here in Nouvelle Vague as death and starvation, but something was different this time.

A heavy, loud boom, and an unusually long-lasting earthquake.

“Uaahhhh! Run! Here comes the tsunami of lava!”

“Huh! Something’s not right with this explosion!”

“Everyone out of the area!”

Guards and prisoners alike scramble backward.

The falling rocks and churning waves of lava were signs that something was about to happen, and rightly so.

But there’s one man who doesn’t back down, and instead steps forward.

Vikir.

While everyone else was running around in panic, Vikir was staring at a glowing blue light between the waves of lava and the collapsing bedrock.

He sees the lava, extremely hot and glowing blue.

It was shaped like a rounded sphere.

A being that shakes the earth with a roar, Vikir muttered in a low voice towards this blue lava sphere.

“…I found it. Poseidon.”

The hope of humanity, the Allied forces’ counterattack.

It was a wonderful discovery after about two years of being trapped in Nouvelle Vague.

Chapter 378

The Hound of the Nouvelle Vague (4)

◆

Sakkuth froze in the presence of the killing intent, a killing intent that could not even begin to compare to the killing intent that Garam had exuded just moments before.

It was so thick that it was almost visualized in the target’s eyes.

It was the shape of a black dog, with bulging eyes, gaping maw, and razor-sharp teeth. It was like a blazing fire, ready to bite and tear the world apart.

And then, slowly, the one who exudes such deep killing intent revealed himself.

The dog that emerged from behind the gutted dog was no ordinary dog. It was a hound, It was also a hellish dog that specializes in biting and killing demons.

Vikir’s red pupils reflected the shrinking of the dog.

“Stop right there.”

The words were spoken in a calm tone, but there was a frighteningly understated violence in his voice.

Sakkuth recognized it and took a step back.

Two years earlier, Sakkuth had been beaten to a pulp once while arguing with Vikir.

‘You should know whether you’re the predator or the prey.’

He still gritted his teeth when he remembered the days he spent trying to get the nails out of his mouth.

However, he couldn’t just bend over and take it, because if he were to be imprisoned in Level 9, he would have to face it.

Sakkuth opened his mouth to growl.

“What if I don’t want to? I’m already in trouble. It can’t get any worse.”

“There’s a basement under the floor. If anything, I can show it to you now.”

“….”

Vikir spoke so nonchalantly.

But knowing how much raw madness and violence lurked beneath that calm expression and soft-spoken tone, Sakkuth couldn’t say more.

Vikir does not bluff.

If he says he’s going to show you the floor, he’s going to show you the floor, and if he says he’s going to show you the basement, he’s going to show you the basement.

Sakkuth had seen Vikir for the past two years, and he knew it well.

‘Crazy asshole. What kind of child’s eyes are those….’

Vikir’s face is a typical nobleman’s handsome face, but his eyes are filled with hatred and the killing intent that has been brewing for centuries.

How many fierce and deadly firing lines does one have to cross to have eyes like that?

Even Sakkuth, who had been conducting illegal human experiments and genocide on countless human beings, could not have dared to imagine.

Ugh.

Sakkuth glared at Vikir with bloodshot eyes.

Then, through clenched teeth, he spoke.

“I will not forget what happened today. I will retaliate.”

“If you can, do it. But you’ll have to do it fast.”

Vikir brought up a topic of interest.

“I’m getting out of here today.”

“…What?”

Sakkuth’s mouth opened halfway in disbelief.

Then he started giggling.

“Now I know you’re crazy. You’re going to break out of Nouvelle Vague?”

“….”

“What ‘He’ could not do in the end is escape from prison. What kind of guy are you….”

At this point, Vikir was getting impatient.

“What makes you think jailbreaking is impossible?”

“…What?”

“Is that all you can think about?”

He frowned at Vikir’s blunt question, not quite sure what he meant.

Then Vikir smirked at him.

“You think you’ve been abandoned, but you haven’t.”

“…?”

“That’s because I think well of you.”

Vikir’s piercing gaze swept over Sakkuth’s entire body.

“I’ve been watching you for the past two years. You’re weak, and you don’t have much muscle, but I like your brashness and your ability to take action. Your loyalty is strong.”

“What the hell are you talking about?”

“You’ll find out soon enough. After I break you out of here.”

He clicked his tongue in disbelief, then turned away.

“It’s a move that’s not worth dealing with. Don’t talk nonsense like jailbreak. Because one day I will definitely kill you with my own hands.”

But even as he spoke, there was a glint of agitation in Sakkuth’s eyes.

Vikir caught the slightest shaking of his pupils with the unique sense of an experienced hound.

Tatag!

Sakkuth quickly jumped out of the rocky canyon and ran beyond the wasteland.

He spewed out a blood mist filled with plague aura.

“…You have the perfect personality to take advantage of.”

That was Vikir’s assessment of the vanishing figure.

With that, Vikir turned his head to look at the two guards on the ground.

Lieutenant Kirko.

She was unconscious with a large wound on her forehead.

Large eyes, a sharp nose, a stubborn-looking mouth, a face so pale it hadn’t seen the sun because of the depths of the ocean, and long hair down to her waist.

This is a typical imperial beauty.

If it weren’t for the uniform and the sword, she could have been mistaken for a courtesan.

“Is she dead?”

Vikir cupped the back of Kirko’s head and traced the veins in her neck.

“…Ugh.”

Kirko’s brow furrowed and an involuntary groan escaped her.

The blood had stopped, at least, though she was still breaking out in a cold sweat and her body temperature was dropping.

A faint heartbeat told him that she was alive and well.

‘She’s a lucky woman.’

With proper hemostasis and prolonged rest, she should be able to recover without too much trouble.

…The problem was Garam.

‘It’s bad.’

At first glance, Garam’s condition was disastrous.

His body had already been damaged beyond repair by his continuous clinging to Sakkuth.

His bones had been crushed to powder, and the fragments had pierced through his intestines and burrowed deeply into them.

Apart from that, the pressure inside his body had exploded, rupturing all of his vital organs that controlled his metabolism, and his body temperature was rising to an abnormal level, which seemed to be the result of being contaminated by the poisonous aura.

Of course, if he were taken to the temple immediately and given intensive treatment by the high priests, he might be able to survive, but that was unlikely to happen here in Nouvelle Vague.

Death. Inevitable.

It seemed clear that if left like this, Garam would be dead within minutes.

In excruciating pain, like every nerve in his body was on fire.

Then.

“I… Ki….”

Garam opened his mouth to say to Vikir.

“Are… you… there…?”

Both of his eyeballs exploded, and he couldn’t see.

He spoke bravely through his broken teeth and severed tongue.

Vikir stood by his side and listened to his last words.

His hand flailed weakly, grasping at thin air.

It was like holding the hand of a loved one.

“I wanted … to show that… girl… the outside world… and… but….”

The last words didn’t flow into a nice, complete sentence like they do in comics and novels.

Instead, his voice broke off mid-sentence, haltingly and hollowly, and his body sagged completely.

“….”

Vikir stood for a moment beside Garam’s limp body.

Then he knelt down on one knee and closed his empty eyes.

“That’s too bad, I didn’t mean for it to turn out this way.”

Vikir had only been aiming for the épaulettes, insignia, rank, and military boots pinned to Garam’s clothing.

But things took a turn for the worse, and this is what he ended up with.

It wasn’t of his own making, but he couldn’t help but feel a bitter taste in his mouth.

“Still, she’s alive because of your efforts. Rest in peace and go to a good place.”

Vikir activated the power of ‘Starvation Drought’ on Garam’s body.

The Blood Daylily’s inherent power drained the blood and moisture from Garam’s body.

The blood dries up and turns to dust.

The flesh, bones, and organs shriveled up and slowly collapsed.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

Soon, Garam’s body, crumbled to a fine powder, was blown away by the wind.

The dreams and soul of a young man from a faraway land, the earth, came to wander here in the distant deep sea.

It was the similar fate of prisoners and guards, unable to leave this prison even in death.

Jjalgeulang-

Badges, épaulettes, and rank insignia clattered to the floor.

One by one, Vikir gathered up the uniform, boots, and insignia that Garam had left behind.

Then.

“…!”

Vikir looked up.

The sound of military footsteps was coming from beyond the steaming canyon.

Thud, thud, thud, thud, thud, thud, thud, thud, thud.

Perhaps reinforcements were on their way.

Vikir glanced up.

Garam’s body warmth, which he thought had been blown away by the wind, was hovering around the fallen Kirko.

After circling for a while, the wind swept through Kirko’s hair, wiping the sweat from her brow, and then disappeared beyond the flames.

“….”

Vikir made a short bow to where the wind had come from.

Then he slipped out the other side of the canyon with Garam’s clothes at his side.

Now that he had the materials he needed, there was no need to delay.

Jailbreak. The hounds are out today.

It was going to be done tonight.

Chapter 379

The Hounds of Nouvelle Vague (5)

◆

The night had been noisy all day due to a prisoner riot on Level 8.

Numerous guards were injured and taken to the infirmary, while others were stranded in the rugged terrain of the labor camp and had to be searched.

Even uninjured guards were hospitalized in large numbers, complaining of itching and fever after inhaling a thick mist of blood.

The night shift was also put on emergency alert. The guards continued to be on watch duty, skipping the evening and early morning rounds of the day.

There were too many vacancies.

“What a shame that this happened just as we were reassigning the guards.”

“I think Colonel D’Ordume has shown poor judgment. He shouldn’t have pushed the construction so hard.”

“I’m sure it has something to do with the blue lava that was found in the Level 10 sector.”

“By the way, is Nouvelle Vague really an extinct volcano? What if it turns out to be active?”

“Well, it could blow up the whole of Nouvelle Vague, but that’s probably not going to happen.”

The two guards yawned and switched shifts.

Neither of them was normally in charge of this section, but they had been forced to fill in when there was an opening in the schedule.

…And Vikir took advantage of the gap.

He dipped the green vodka he’d stolen from the guards into a puddle of seawater on the floor of the stone chamber.

The dark ink smeared into the water, turning the entire pool green.

Vikir dipped his prisoner uniform in it.

Cheolpeog- cheolpeog- cheolpeog-

After several dyes, the prisoner’s uniform was completely green.

The black stripes that characterized the prisoner’s uniform were faintly visible, but it was hard to tell in the dim light of the Nouvelle Vague.

Vikir glanced over the bars and saw that the guards were preoccupied with something else, so he clapped his hands together.

Zeng-

The BDISSEM’s handcuffs broke very easily.

Vikir felt his mana return to his body and nodded.

‘But what are these restraints made of to break so easily?’

The exact material that makes up the BDISSEM is unknown.

However, it was clear that it was influenced by Vikir’s title of Daylily Lumberjack from the Hell Tree.

Eventually, Vikir completely destroyed the BDISSEM restraints attached to his body, broke the iron bars, and came out.

He began to walk slowly down the hallway.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

At that moment, one of the guards on duty in front of him noticed Vikir and his eyes widened.

“ …? Why is a doctor here?”

He must have seen Vikir’s green top and bottom and mistakenly assumed he was a doctor.

After all, at this hour of the night, no one would think of a man wearing green and walking around outside without cuffs or chains on his body as a prisoner.

Vikir replied nonchalantly.

“I’m the doctor in charge of quarantine for the Level 9 area, and I was just doing a final check because a Level 8 ‘plague leper’ sprayed blood and saliva everywhere.”

“Oh, really?”

The guard gave him a slightly suspicious glance, but he couldn’t imagine that the other man was a prisoner.

“Well, I looked at your last shift sheet and there’s no record of you coming in or out….”

“Is that so, it’s been a while since I’ve been in, I guess I lost track of time with all the quarantine, did everyone else leave first?”

“Haha – you have a sense of duty. I checked the previous shift log, and there was a quarantine, but it says you all left then… I’ve been busy lately, so I must have missed one.”

The guard smiled, surprisingly pleased with what Vikir had said.

Apparently, he was relieved to hear that the area where he was on duty had been thoroughly sanitized.

“Yes, you may go. Please take care not to spread the plague to us”

“Would it be possible?”

Vikir gave the guard a curt nod and headed down the hall.

‘…Good, I’ve made it through phase one without incident.’

Poseidon found at the blast point, Colonel D’Ordume’s reassignment of the guards, and a loud commotion.

It was an exquisite combination of these three results.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Walking through the corridors of the Nouvelle Vague at night was refreshing.

The sense of freedom and liberation seemed to add a few centimeters to his height and limbs.

But it was short-lived, as Vikir quietly made his way to a corner of the hallway.

It was the supply room.

It was an armory where the guards’ uniforms, epaulets, boots, and weapons were stored.

‘The prisoners’ supplies are managed like a knife, but the guards’ supplies are surprisingly poor.’

Items such as sardines, bread, and work tools issued to prisoners are meticulously inventoried and counted.

But the supplies for the guards were surprisingly neglected.

The military officer on guard duty in front of the warehouse sits lazily, reading a novel whose pages are tattered from hundreds of readings.

“‘The Worn and Torn Newbie’ … I must have read this one 200 times already. I can’t wait to see the movie.”

Just then, someone caught the military officer’s eye.

His bushy hair and burn marks covered his face.

It was Vikir, dressed in a guard’s uniform, torn and bloody in places.

[What a vile creature, scarring his face with burn marks. Well, with the basilisk’s super regenerative powers, it can always heal].

Vikir could hear Decarabia whimpering in his chest.

Vikir slammed his fist down on the chest plate in frustration, silencing Decarabia.

Then he pressed the brim of his hat against his mouth.

“Greetings, sir. I was wondering if you had any spare uniforms.”

“Uh-huh-what, did you get ripped off in the riots too? I’m seeing a lot of ripped uniforms today.”

“Yeah. I was just getting back from being stranded under a crevasse in the canyon. I tried to repair the uniform, but it seemed like there was no way I could sew it….”

“Yeah, well, in that case, you might as well just get issued a new one. Hold on. I’ll find one in a minute.”

The military officer closed the book he was reading and went into the storage room, rummaging around.

He emerged with a guard’s uniform that fit Vikir perfectly, along with a full set of accessories: boots, épaulettes, rank, and badges.

“What do you want me to write your name?”

Vikir asked, and the military officer answered immediately.

“Second Lieutenant ‘Garam Nord’.”

◆

<Garam Nord>/ ◆

A name tag and a single diamond.

Vikir pinned his rank on his chest and shoulders.

He had watched the guards so closely that he could mimic their actions and words.

Except.

“It’s not time to wear it yet.”

Vikir stuck the name tag labeled “Garam Nord” into his mouth.A lowly guard with no name and no affiliation to the Nouvelle Vague.

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Once he put on his uniform and ranking badge, it was all one and the same.

He was able to walk through doors and corridors that would have been off-limits to anyone but a guard without raising suspicion.

Then. A guard called out to Vikir as he walked down the hallway late at night.

“Hey. Second Lieutenant over there.”

A guard with the rank of captain stopped Vikir.

Vikir paused for a moment. Had he aroused suspicion by not wearing a name tag?

…But no.

“Don’t you see the trash on the ground there? Pick it up.”

The Captain made Vikir pick up the trash that was closer to him and went on his way.

‘Good thing we’re a society that looks at rank before name.’

Humans are like that everywhere.

We decide whether to be interested in someone or not, whether to remember their name or not, based on their title or rank.

In that sense, the second lieutenant was the perfect disguise to avoid suspicion.

No one was interested in the name of the low-level guard, Nouvelle Vague, so there was no question about whether he wore a name tag or not, what his face looked like, whether he was tall or short, or what he was wearing.

Vikir walked smoothly up the central staircase on the 9th floor and made his way to the 8th, 7th, and 6th floors.

His final destination was the 5th floor.

Vikir had just left the 6th floor and was about to open the door to the 5th floor.

“…?”

Vikir heard a voice behind him, stopping him in his tracks.

For the first time, someone recognized Vikir’s face and body type, not his rank.

Vikir slowly turned to see a familiar face standing there.

A female prison guard standing on crutches with her legs and arms bandaged.

Lieutenant Kirko Grimm stood there, cocking her head in question.

“You’re Garam, right? Why are you here at this time of night? I didn’t see you when we were on watch earlier, and where have you been all this time….”

Suddenly, Vikir was met with undue attention.

Vikir thought for a moment.

‘Should I remove it?’

But he didn’t want to.

Normally, he would have been relentless, but after lending his name and identity to …, and considering Garam’s last wishes, he felt he could let it slide.

‘It’s nothing compared to what’s going to happen on the 5th floor anyway.’

Vikir’s long-planned escape is perfect.

And if she didn’t know it now, she was definitely someone who would be helpful in the future.

“….”

Vikir didn’t respond to Kirko’s call, simply stepping through the door.

“Huh? Hey- Garam!”

Kirko’s eyes widened in surprise at the unexpected turn of events.

This was uncharacteristic of Garam, who usually smiled like an idiot whenever he saw her.

“What, are you going to be on guard in another area?”

Kirko didn’t have time to stand there for long, as she’d just gotten off duty.

She shook her head and turned to go.

“…What the hell, I just wanted to say thank you for the Level 8 riot incident.”

But the other side is different. That ‘stupid Garam’.

Kirko soon lost her attention to Garam.

The timid little guy isn’t going to get into trouble, so wherever he goes at this ambitious hour will be no big deal.

‘Maybe I’ll thank him the next time I see him and we can talk properly.’

Jeobeog- jeobeog- jeobeog-

Like Vikir, Kirko melted into the dark hallway.

Vikir going up, and Kirko going down.

They went in opposite directions.

Chapter 384

The Rotten Dog of Nouvelle Vague (2)

◆

Name ‘Garam Nord’. Rank Second Lieutenant. A junior officer in the suppression squad in Nouvelle Vague.

A 21-year-old man characterized by a timid stance, a dark expression, bushy uncut hair, and large burn marks on his face.

This was the “new identity” Vikir had been observing for the past two years.

Vikir did not escape.

Or, more accurately, he made a pretense of escaping and then returned to Nouvelle Vague when BDISSEM was unconscious.

After all, stealing a gulper eel wasn’t going to get him away, and he still had work to do in prison.

‘I need to activate Poseidon.’

There was nothing else to do.

Once he fulfilled certain conditions and activated the Poseidon, his work here in Nouvelle Vague would be done.

‘…Honestly, I wouldn’t mind dying here if I could get this done.’

Simply stopping the Rainy Season of Fear will save more than half of humanity.

The rest was up to the survivors.

But Vikir wanted to do the job perfectly.

It would be a good business if he could do it with his own life.

Then.

TOOOOOOOO-!

The sound of a horn announced the guards’ wake-up call.

3.30am.

The guards wake up half an hour before the prisoners, who wake up at four.

Garam, or rather Vikir, pushed himself up from his room, which was just over 3 square meters.

The shower room is a stone cubicle, barely big enough for two people.

Vikir turned on the rusty tap and washed his face and body under the dripping cold water.

Unsurprisingly, the water is seawater, so even when he scrubbed soap into it, almost no foam came out.

When he got out, his skin still felt sticky.

When he looked in the mirror, he could see nasty burn marks under his wet hair.

With the strength of the basilisk, Vikir could erase the scars, reshape them, and so on.

His voice, too, could be modified by swallowing hot charcoal and burning his vocal cords.

Decarabia on Vikir’s chest spoke wearily.

[Human. Doesn’t it even hurt, how awful!]

“That’s what it takes to enter the Iron Maiden and be thrown ten thousand meters under the sea, walk across bladed bridges, fight leeches, endure sulfurous showers, and mine under a volcano so hot that it burns the flesh.”

In any case, the initial jailbreak was a success.

The Night Hound was declared dead, and he was turned into a guard.

This was a good thing, as it would be much easier to keep an eye on Poseidon’s movements as a guard.

Vikir glanced away as he prepared for roll call.

His desk and bed were piled high with palm-sized notes.

They were the journals that Garam had kept every day of his life.

Hundreds of these journals piled up in a room that was already cramped.

But Vikir didn’t throw them away.

Instead, he treated them like treasures, reading and memorising every word on the damp, smudged pages.

‘It’s good to know the daily routine of the lower guards.’

Garam’s diary reveals the lives and struggles of the lowly guards, living in a single, flat room.

Vikir finished reading the diaries, as there was still some time before the horns sounded and the morning watch began.

He had spent the entirety of last night’s dawn reading, and there was still quite a bit left.

Vikir decided to cut through the nonsense to get to the essentials: the structure and systems of the Nouvelle Vague, information about the people in Garam’s life, and other things to keep in mind. ….

Other than that, the overwhelming majority of the information was personal, revealing the thoughts, beliefs, and humanity of Garam.

Vikir had decided that he didn’t need to see the personal records of Garam, but he couldn’t help but read through the voluminous pages and read every single line.

And in the process, he came to understand his humanity to some extent.

“…It’s a good thing he doesn’t have many close people around him.”

Garam had an extremely narrow circle of friends.

However, he was able to observe others neutrally and objectively, and these views are reflected in his diary.

Nouvelle Vague seen through the eyes of a prisoner and Nouvelle Vague seen through the eyes of a guard are surprisingly similar.

For example, in most of Garam’s diaries, the last sentence was ‘I want to get out of here’.

It was like reading a prisoner’s diary.

“…Now that I think about it, the places where guards and prisoners live are similar.”

Vikir looked inside the cramped stone room.

There were no windows, and it was practically a coffin.

It wasn’t much different from a prisoner’s cell, except for the handcuffs and bars.

…No, the guards had handcuffs and bars too.

“Morning call! Everybody out!”

It was an insanely dense rotation and shift schedule.

It was like an invisible bar that trapped and manipulated the guards.

The guards, who control and manipulate the prisoners, were controlled and manipulated by the system.

Vikir stood up and closed Garam’s diary.

…No, he tried to cover it.

“Hmm?”

Vikir turned to the next page.

From there, the diary began to reveal things it hadn’t before.

Until then, Garam had been writing in his diary in a calm and dry handwriting, even including himself.

But now, bordering this page and every page thereafter, there is something different.

It was about Kirko.

About how spirited, how strong, how determined, how great, how admirable, and how pretty the girl across the room named ‘Kirko Grimm’ was.

From one page to the next, Garam’s diary was full of talk about Kirko.

There was even a pretty good sketch of her.

The story of how she came in first in the end-of-month evaluation.

How she briefly quelled a prisoner riot.

How she was promoted first among her colleagues.

How she won first place in a swordsmanship competition.

.

.

And the last entry in the diary, which had always been the same, was slightly altered.

After the line “I want to get out of here,” the line “with her” began to appear.

-I want to show her the outside world.

-If only I could show her the blue skies, salt-free lakes, and wild animals running through the fields where I was born…

Vikir closed his diary at this point.

Suddenly, Vikir remembered something that came to him out loud.

-‘About twenty years ago, I think, there was an incident where a prisoner forcibly insulted a guard, which is why the guards at Nouvelle Vague are so sensitive to the lower levels.’

-‘Kurururu- I heard that a child was born as a by-product of that unpleasant process.’

-‘You’re a frog, born and raised in a well, and you’ve never seen the outside world, have you? After all, what right does a bitch born of rape have to walk this earth? You’re worthless, and you’re stuck in these deep seas!’

Garam’s records said so.

Kirko was born and raised in Nouvelle Vague. A girl who knew nothing of the earth.

“Hmmm. Unrequited love? Or longing? I’m not sure about the emotions of kids this age.”

Vikir muttered quietly to himself.

Even though he had spent quite a bit of time at the Colosseo Academy, he still found it difficult to understand the teenage emotions of young people.

However, he did know this.

Both Garam, who wrote this diary, and the girl in it, Kirko, were blossoming 21 years old.

What if they had attended the Colosseo Academy on earth instead of here in Nouvelle Vague?

Kirko is a very talented girl, so maybe she would have been the head of the Cold Weapon Department. No, she might have gone beyond that and become student council president.

Because from the glimpses Vikir had seen of her, her talent, her potential, her will to improve, was more than Tudor or Bianca or Sinclaire or Dolores.

“…But reality is harsh.”

Not everyone can be a flower and live beautifully.

Where there is a top, there is a bottom.

You didn’t have to come through the Age of Destruction to know that.

Vikir closed the diary and turned away.

He left the cramped stone chamber and closed the soundproof door behind him.

Kikigeek- Tung!

A narrow, smelly corridor opened up.

Everywhere he looked, there was damp, slimy moss.

The musty smell of sea moss, the salty dampness that clings to the skin.

Cheap cigarette smoke hung from the salty, dripping ceiling.

A constant smell of decay emanated from the crumbling plaster in the corner of the corridor.

Through a side door that was slightly open, he could see his fellow guard lying on his bunk, looking at a tattered pornographic magazine.

(The magazine was over 60 years old, so the models in its pages were probably already dead.)

Soon, it was time for roll call.

The junior guards all came out with wide eyes and lined up in two rows facing each other in the corridor.

There was no distinction between men and women as they shared a room.

Due to the Nouvelle Vague’s directive that there are three genders: men, women, and guards, everyone here is considered to be of the same sex.

Then.

“…!”

Vikir took note of the one person in the group of junior guards with rotten fish eyes.

She was Kirko.

Kirko lived in a cell diagonally across the room from Garam’s.

‘It’s strange to see her in person after having seen her on paper.’

Vikir was looking at Kirko in awe.

…Snap!

Someone slapped Vikir hard on the back of the head.

“…?”

Vikir turns his head to look at something and sees the next room, and the guards across from him, giggling.

“Hey, stupid Garam, spying on Kirko again today, you sullen pervert. You should know your place.”

“Tidy up your clothes, straighten up your angles, and don’t show off your shitty uniform. Don’t you want to be seen as a jerk by the prisoners?”

“In the meantime, why did you put an old name tag on it? Who took it off?”

“As expected, he is like a ‘Rotten Dog’ from morning.”

Aka ‘Stupid Garam’, or ‘Rotten Dog’. That was the nickname that always followed him.

Vikir, who had read his diary, was of course well aware of this.

‘Humans are like that everywhere.’

In the army before the regression, in the Colosseo Academy afterwards.

Humans will always bully those weaker than themselves, and when that bullying becomes a systemic phenomenon within an organization, it actually serves to solidify it.

So when Garam was bullied by his colleagues, his seniors and superiors turned a blind eye.

If the other guards could build solidarity at the expense of Garam, it was a win-win situation.

This was because it was a profitable business if one guard could be sacrificed to increase solidarity among the other guards.

“You must be a bit lazy today after your crazy shift yesterday.”

“Since you’re free, why don’t you go out and bully stupid Garam?”

“Hey, you stupid bastard, why didn’t you show up for the night watch last night? You weren’t even on duty. Were you really in distress?”

“You do understand that failing to show up for inspection is a military offense, and you could end up with a ‘black tongue’, you know?”

Then. Kirko’s eyes met those of one of the bullies who had been harassing Vikir.

Seeing the mixture of pity and patheticness in her eyes, the bully chuckled and called out.

“Hey, Kirko, why don’t you come to your boyfriend’s rescue, you two are in a relationship!”

All eyes then turned to Kirko and Garam.

Kirko’s frown widens.

“…Crazy assholes.”

Kirko jerked her head away.

Only the snickering mockery echoed behind her.

Just then.

TOOOOOOO-

The horn sounded once more.

Everyone wiped the smiles off their faces at this sudden alarm, which sounded completely unrelated to the roll call.

Suddenly, from the other side of the corridor, an off-duty guard burst into the room, shouting.

“Riot, there’s a riot! There’s a riot! There’s a riot in the Level One area! Emergency deployment of suppression squad!”

Chapter 387

The Rotten Dog of Nouvelle Vague (5)

◆

Another page has been torn from the Nouvelle Vague calendar.

At the end of each month, the guards are evaluated at the end of the month.

The Nouvelle Vague labor system is somewhat unusual, with one guard leading 12 prisoners to work.

At this point, the guard is like a god to the 12 prisoners in charge.

Whether he uses corporal punishment, how much there is to do, how much he makes them work, and how much he lets them rest are all at his discretion.

This group is changed once a month.

At the end of the month, both the prisoners and the guards are divided.

So the guards have a month to work with the prisoners in their group, and they can decide whether to punish them, reward them, make the work harder, or make it easier.

However, this did not mean that the guards were always able to accommodate the prisoners.

The guards at Nouvelle Vague were also subject to evaluations at the end of the month, as mentioned above.

They receive a score based on how much work they complete with the 12 prisoners they are responsible for during the month, which is then factored into their performance review for promotion.

The guards had to get the maximum amount of labor out of the prisoners for their own score.

It was up to the guards to use any method to achieve this.

Some guards would beat the prisoners with knives or whips, restrict their food, sleep, rest, or solitary confinement, while others would appease them by giving them a little more bread or work tools.

Prisoners also had to work hard to ensure that the guards in charge of them did not receive poor scores.

Otherwise, the guards, who had the power of life and death over them, could do anything to them.

…Well, whatever.

At the end of the month, an announcement was made in Nouvelle Vague.

It was a ranked list of the best performing guards.

It’s a competition between the guards to get a good ranking on the list.

There was a constant battle of nerves, with guards cheating in the ratings to get a good, well behaved prisoner into their group, bribing them with riches to get them transferred, or sneaking bread or tools for the other group.

Of course, goods in the Nouvelle Vague are limited, and if someone gets an extra meal, someone else has to go without.

One of the more talkative members of the group was the junior guard, Second Lieutenant Garam Nord.

Garam’s life was always miserable.

No motivation, no grades, no future.

Living up to his name, ‘Stupid Garam’ or ‘Rotten Dog’, Garam was always given only the rudest prisoners to work with.

Bread and work tools were always stolen by other guards, and Garam had to give up his own meals to encourage the prisoners to work.

Of course, the prisoners in Garam’s group were not at all eager to do their labor.

Once they were in Garam’s group, they had no intention to perform well, and Garam’s timid nature meant that he rarely used corporal punishment.

As a result, he was always ignored, even by his fellow guards.

Needless to say, he was bullied by his own colleagues.

In terms of grades calculated by adding up the progress of construction in the area in charge, the number of prisoners sent to solitary confinement, and the number of riots suppressed, Garam has never been outside of last place.

However, an unusual and unprecedented turn of events has occurred.

<List of Report Cards>

※ Name/Rank/Task Completion Rate

Garam Nord / ◆ / 108%.

Kirko Grimm / ◆◆ / 96%.

…/ … / 89%

…

.

.

Garam has always been in last place.

This time, he scored first in the monthly evaluation.

He even exceeded the workload guidelines set by his superiors.

Instead of achieving 100%, he exceeded it by 108%. This was unusual among junior guards.

So whenever the junior guards got together these days, they always talked about the report card.

“Wow – did you see the report card this time? It was crazy.”

“I found out for the first time today that the task completion rate can exceed 100%.”

“You know, they always set the achievement rate a little too high, just to make sure you don’t hit it.”

“Exactly. That’s why even Kirko only gets around 95% to 96% every time.”

“That’s huge. Did you see the gap with third place? 7%.”

“But the gap between first and second is 12%. How is that possible?”

“Did Garam ever do that well in the first place?”

“Of course not, it’s ‘Stupid Garam’, he was always in the bottom 40%.”

“What, he’s been hiding his power and acting like a nerd all this time? That’s a pretty damning development….”

Then. The atmosphere in the dining hall, where the junior guards were gathered, suddenly became quiet.

It was because Kirko, who had always been in charge of the first place, and who was ranked second in the monthly evaluation, appeared.

…Tag!

Kirko set her plate down on the table and sat down to eat.

Grilled waterfowl, fermented sea catfish, boiled peas, and a cup of sea cow’s milk were on the menu.

As Kirko ate in silence, she heard the chatter of the other junior guards.

“Kirko, does she look like she’s in a bad mood today?”

“Of course she is. She just lost first place to that Stupid Garam.”

“ …If this continues, isn’t Garam going to get promoted first?”

Kirko stopped chewing her peas.

Then she turned her head in displeasure.

Then.

“…!”

Both Kirko and the junior guards who were talking behind her back stopped in unison.

Garam. The subject of the conversation had entered the dining hall.

◆

Garam. No Vikir was chewing on a boiled pea, thinking over his plan.

‘To activate Poseidon, I need to apply as much mana, or physical impact, as possible to the detonation point.’

To do that, it was much easier to act as a guard than a prisoner.

He could keep an eye on Poseidon’s behavior at all times.

However, access to Poseidon in the depths of Level 9’s labor camps was not possible with a lower ranking guard.

‘It would be beneficial for me to be promoted at least to the rank of Captain, and safely to Major.’

A captain wears the insignia of three diamonds.

A Major wears a single leaf.

This should be enough so that there is no hindrance to activities.

‘…Mid-level guards of the rank of captain and above are allowed to roam the labor camp without reporting. It will be possible to activate Poseidon secretly at night.’

To do so, he had to earn his merits diligently.

Luckily, unlike the regular army, where promotion could take months or even years, in the Nouvelle Vague the rewards for performance were quick and certain.

This was especially true since so many guards were killed or crippled during their service.

Vikir was thinking about this and that.

…Thud!

Something was placed on the table in front of him.

It was a powder in a paper bag.

“Garam Nord. You have a birthday today, right? Congratulations~”

The cook tapped Vikir on the shoulder.

Only then did Vikir realize that Garam’s birthday was today.

“…?”

The paper bag was filled with a white powder.

He dipped his finger in and tasted it, and it tasted sweet.

“Is that sugar?”

It was the same one in Garam’s diary.

At Nouvelle Vague, a bag of sugar is given to each guard on their birthday as a gift.

However, the sugar in the bag had a somewhat unpleasant taste.

It was the same white powder, so it was hard to see, but there seemed to be a significant amount of salt mixed in.

“What is it?”

Vikir shook the envelope and scratched his head.

Then.

“Are you a real idiot or what?”

A sarcastic voice came from beside him.

Vikir turned to see Kirko standing there, arms crossed.

“Same reaction every year on your birthday. That’s why the others call you ‘Stupid Garam’.”

Kirko peered into the bag of sugar in Vikir’s hand and shook her head.

“Colonel D’Ordume must have done it, from what I’ve heard he has a sneaky sweet tooth. I’m sure he’s embarrassed for himself, so he filled it with common salt.”

“I see. Blindfolded.”

“Don’t you know why Colonel D’Ordume was demoted to Nouvelle Vague in the first place? He was caught mixing sand and rice bran into the rice he gave his subordinates when he was serving on the ground. He claims he was discriminated against because he’s a Beastman, but in fact, it was because of embezzlement of military supplies.”

Kirko grumbled, saying, ‘I can’t spoil a dog.’

She must not have a normal personality because she was swearing at her boss as well.

“…Anyway. Well, happy birthday.”

Kirko hesitated for a moment before continuing.

“And thank you for helping me last time.”

The words that followed were so muffled that even Vikir, whose hearing reached a superhuman level, had a hard time understanding them.

‘Birthday.’

Vikir thought about the day he was born.

A date he didn’t remember or attach much significance to.

It was a common thread in all of his lives, the three lives he had lived before his regression, the years of old age he had spent in the Hell Tree, and now this one.

In the Nouvelle Vague, a birthday was merely a low point in the gloomy, languid passage of time.

It was always the same in the Age of Destruction, in the Abyss Tower, and in Baskerville.

The sugar quickly became sticky due to the sticky moisture.

The tangy fishy smell of the peas was stifling.

…Tag!

Vikir picked up his empty plate and headed for the exit.

Kirko looked back at Vikir with a slightly embarrassed expression on her face.

“…Is weird, too.”

Muttering quietly to herself.

◆

For the next few days, Kirko kept a close eye on Vikir.

‘Garam, is he always like that?’

She had watched him occasionally since they were children.

The Garam she’d seen had always been pathetic and stupid, but not to the point of disrespect, unlike the others.

Just someone who didn’t fit in here in Nouvelle Vague, that’s all.

Kirko hated Garam for some reason, though she wondered if it was because he had lived on the surface as a child.

For her, born in Nouvelle Vague and never having seen the surface, the surface was represented by Garam’s image.

Idle, wimpy, not very fast, and somewhat timid. A boy who had never shown any signs of struggle or competition.

…But recently, his behavior has changed.

He’s been leading prisoners to achieve workloads that were thought impossible, and he’s been scoring big on physical fitness tests and written papers.

Gradually, the way his fellow guards looked at him began to change.

The usual indifference, or even disrespect, gradually gave way to a friendly, friendly attitude.

But for some reason, Kirko didn’t want to admit it.

…Inferiority complex.

Maybe it was because she didn’t want to acknowledge the surface world represented by Garam.

Maybe it was a manifestation of the complex of being a frog in a well, no matter how good she was here.

Could it be that? Kirko was stirring up an emotion in Garam that she had never felt before, or with anyone, for that matter: competition.

‘How the hell do they make you work? What do I have to do to achieve that amount of work?’

Kirko had secretly followed Garam and the 12 prisoners in his group as they went down to do their labor.

Kirko wondered how the hell he could get the prisoners to achieve the ridiculous feat of 108%.

Then.

Kirko watched as Garam led the prisoners to the labor area.

Kirko was stunned.

“…!?”

Something she could never have imagined was happening.

Chapter 389

The Worst Torture (2)

◆

…Boom!

The rocks shattered, sending aftershocks through the area.

At the center of the encirclement of guards, a large man roared.

Sakkuth De Leviathan. He was the one who started the riot on level 8 this day.

The guards shouted.

“Hey! Come on, asshole, for how long have you been out of solitary confinement?”

“Shit, this is the second time, you want to go to solitary confinement again!”

“If you don’t behave yourself, I can really make your life suck!”

But even in the face of a siege of swords, axes, and maces, Sakkuth’s insane roar did not subside at all.

“The Queen has abandoned me! I failed to fulfill her orders to come out after ‘Him’, and that’s why she’s abandoned me! The fact that she hasn’t given me a single word about my escape in all this time means she’s abandoned me! It’s as plain as day! Aaaaah! Let me out of here, or kill me!”

He was insane, even at first glance.

Sticky saliva dripped from the corners of his mouth.

The blood vessels in his extremely bloodshot eyes wriggled like intestinal worms, threatening to burst through the surface of his eyeballs.

Sakkuth struggled, flailing at the BDISSEM chains on his wrists, and each time he did, droplets of black blood splattered from the wounds across his body.

Hududug- hududug- hududug- hududug-

The guards were extremely vigilant to keep the spit and blood from touching them.

“Ughh, it’s the blood of the plague leper!”

“Careful, if you touch that, you’ll get the plague right away. ‘Red Death’ or something….”

“I heard it was the worst plague that almost wiped out the natives of Jungle Red&Black Mountain?”

“An unidentified plague that hasn’t been sanitized by the sulfur shower at entrance. Avoid it at all costs.”

“Well, then why do we keep confronting me like this?”

“Then why don’t you come over and get him? I hear he’s from an extremely poisonnous family.”

“I’ll tell you what. The Leviathan family threw him out of the family because they couldn’t control him.”

As if that wasn’t enough, Sakkuth bit his tongue and spat out a fountain of blood from his mouth.

Puhhhhhhh-!

The fog of blood spewed from his mouth rose in a frenzy, causing the guards to scramble like sliced squid.

A pandemic. An infectious disease of the highest order. In a limited and closed space like Nouvelle Vague, it is a phenomenon to be most wary of.

This wasn’t just a matter of losing strength or mana.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, standing at the head of the siege, wrinkled his brow in frustration.

“Damn. He’s nothing in terms of strength, but his plague poison is the problem.”

The adjutant next to him spoke up.

“Shall we bring in the five wardens?”

“How am I supposed to get them if they’re not here? Colonels D’Ordume and Souaré are on ground duty with the convoy.”

“I’ll try sending someone to Brigadier General Flubber one more time.”

“Arthur. We’ve already sent men twice, and the fact that they’re still not back must mean they’ve been ‘eaten’. Don’t waste any more lives against a creature that doesn’t even have intelligence.”

“So even Brigadier General BDISSEM…?”

“She’s the heart of Nouvelle Vague security, and she shouldn’t be allowed to come to a scene like this. If Warden Orca knew, he’d be furious.”

Four of the 5 wardens were a definite no-go.

That left only one man left.

The adjutant spoke the last name with the most cautious demeanor he had ever displayed.

“…What about Colonel Black Tongue?”

Bastille’s face stiffened at the question.

He answered without the slightest hesitation.

“Not that asshole.”

“Ha, but aside from Brigadier Flubber, isn’t he the only one who can subdue that monster right now?”

“Bringing in a psychotic lunatic like Colonel Black Tongue to capture a mere Level 8 prisoner is ridiculous, it would make his navel bigger than his stomach.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille was a well-balanced man in all areas of his career, with moderate strength, moderate personality, and moderate work ethic.

It’s been a long time since he’s looked this frustrated.

“Damn it. We have a record number of residents this time. This is the first time Colonel D’Ordume and Colonel Souaré have been on the ground at the same time. What the hell has been happening on the ground lately….”

Colonel D’Ordume and Colonel Souaré, as well as Warden Orca.

The simultaneous absence of these three, the core power of the Nouvelle Vague, had been causing a lot of commotion lately.

Just then.

Hwaak-!

Sakkuth quickly broke through the siege and rushed forward.

Spraying blood everywhere, he quickly grabbed a lowly guard by the scruff of the neck who hadn’t managed to dodge.

…Sizzle!

The unfortunate junior guard was Kirko Grimm.

“Don’t interfere with me, or I’ll snap this bitch’s head right off.”

Sakkuth growled, one hand clutching at Kirko’s throat.

Kirko shuddered twice, once from the unimaginable strength of Sakkuth’s grip, and again from the sickening stench of blood that emanated from his body.

If she made a mistake, she would die with her neck snapped, or she would die covered in blood mixed with a terrible plague poison.

“A hostage situation?”

“What are you going to do?”

“What do you want, you madman!”

The guards laughed harshly.

“What do I want? Nothing, I just want to enjoy my ruined life and watch you guys mess around. Oh, and you’re going to have to stop working on Level 10 for a few months, because I’m going to spill a lot of blood.”

After he finished speaking, Sakkuth spat on the floor of the labor camp.

Pusisisisisig-

The dirt near where Sakkuth’s spit had fallen was dissolving with an unpleasant sound and smell.

Lt. Colonel Bastille narrowed his eyes on Sakkuth hostage, Kirko.

“A hostage situation, and now you’re doing all kinds of things.”

“Kurururu! In an atmosphere like this, there should be at least one hostage.”

“If you inflict even the slightest harm on that friend, you will not die well.”

“Go ahead. Kurururu! I was abandoned anyway.”

When the confrontation between Lieutenant Colonel Bastille and Sakkuth continues.

“Lt. Colonel, I’m fine!”

Kirko struggled to speak.

“There can be no negotiations with a prisoner, I don’t care about me, so please proceed with the suppression… kuck!”

Kirko couldn’t finish her sentence.

Because Sakkuth slammed her to the ground and then lifted her back up.

“Ugh! You bastard!?”

Kirko spat out blood from her nose and mouth and looked up.

Sakkuth then stomped on Kirko’s face with his foot, crushing it.

“Kurururu… I guess you’re mistaken, but the reason they can’t attack me is because they’re afraid of my plague. Not because they’re protecting some low-level guards.”

“…Ughhh!”

Kirko tried to reach for the longsword at her waist, but there was no way he would just leave it behind.

Sakkuth used the chains on his wrists to wrap around Kirko’s sword and brought it down against her throat.

Udeudeudeug!

Kirko raised her mana, but even so, she couldn’t completely shake off Sakkuth’s strength.

Furthermore.

“Oooh, keep quiet or I’ll spit blood all over your bitch’s face.”

“….”

It was impossible to resist Sakkuth, who was threatening with a plague as a weapon.

As Kirko bit her lip in frustration, Sakkuth chuckled.

“For a scumbag born from a guard who was raped by a prisoner, you’re quick on the subject. Kurururu!”

“….”

Kirko gritted her teeth, even as her stomach turned.

There’s not much she can do about it, however, due to Sakkuth’s strength and the plague factor he possesses.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille muttered bitterly when he saw that his subordinate, though a junior, was being thoroughly manipulated.

“…In the end, there is nothing we can do”

The sacrifice of the little ones for the greater cause is inevitable. It is necessary for the survival of the group.

The situation had to be contained as quickly as possible before the damage was done.

The sacrifice of a lowly guard is a cheap one.

Lt. Colonel Bastille took advantage of the moment when Sakkuth’s attention was focused on Kirko to send a hand signal.

He ordered all the senior guards to raise their weapons.

“Prepare to attack, everyone! We need to behead him as quickly as possible… huh?”

But Lt. Colonel Bastille’s order to charge was cut off in mid-sentence.

Jeobeog-jeobeoh-jeobeog.

A single footstep stepped out from among the guards and headed towards Sakkuth’s direction.

A look of utter calm. A look of nonchalance. As if he were taking a stroll.

It was Garam, or rather, Vikir.

Vikir spoke in his usual bland voice.

“Construction must not be stopped because of your contaminated blood.”

“…?”

Vikir’s words caused a collective gasp and a shake of the heads of the assembled guards.

‘Oh, wait, that’s not it.’

Vikir realized he’d been a little too honest at the moment, so he softened his tone.

“Release my precious motivation. Let’s resolve it through dialogue.”

Name Garam Nord. Age 21. Rank Second Lieutenant.

It was the appearance of a low-ranking guard whose liver was so swollen that it was sticking out of his stomach.

Chapter 390

The Worst Torture (3)

◆

“Let’s resolve it through dialogue.”

Vikir said. Everyone’s mouths dropped open at those words.

Even the guards who were building the siege, and even Sakkuth, who was leading the hostage situation, and Kirko, who was being held hostage.

….

Silence. Silence settled over the labour camp where the hostage situation had just taken place.

Sakkuth was the first to speak.

“What the hell. You’re that idiot, right? Are you insane?”

Vikir was an old warrior who had lived through the Age of Destruction, and he knew better than to hide his mana and presence.

Even Hugo, patriarch of Baskerville Family, hadn’t noticed.

Not surprisingly, Sakkuth did not recognise Garam’s identity.

Vikir shrugged at Garam appearance.

“I have a clean&sober mind.”

“No, you weren’t dead to me in the first place….”

“I almost was, once.”

When a person comes out of a near-death experience, there is often a great deal of internal growth.

Sakkuth narrowed his eyes at Garam atsmophere, who had changed into a different person.

“You still look the same, but it’s like you’ve become a different person. Your eyes have become a little more useful.”

“If you do, then release my motivation so we can continue working on the construction.”

“Kurururu… Fuck you, kid. I’m glad you’ve changed, and you’re trying to make up for it with some words.”

Sakkuth snorted, as if he didn’t need to talk to him.

But Garam didn’t back down and continued to stand there.

Behind him, he heard some guards shouting.

“Hey, lowly guard, where do you think you’re going!”

“Can you get back now! You’re only increasing the number of hostages!”

“Tsk, tsk, you’re going to die. You should know the subject.”

As they said. Sakkuth cleared his throat and and pulled phlegm into his mouth.

…Twees!

A foul-smelling spit of phlegm flew like a quack to Garam’s face.

It was an attack that was sure to infect him with plague.

What?

Shhh.

With a simple flick of his head to the side, Garam dodged the attack.

Even though it was not possible for a low-ranking guard to react quickly.

“…!?”

Sakkuth’s expression changed.

Seizing the opportunity, Garam spoke in a voice barely audible to the other guards.

“I’ve got something to talk about, don’t you think?”

“Kurururu, how ridiculous.”

Sakkuth laughed in disbelief.

“What the hell are you trying to talk about, you and me?”

It worked.

The words spoken by high-ranking guards are not to be trusted in the first place.

That was a fact that the hostage-taker knew best.

However, in the midst of all these high-ranking guards, a low-level guard who walked out alone with guts.

What kind of dialogue would he try to have with him?

Sakkuth was mildly curious about that.

However, the spontaneous curiosity disappeared as easily as it had arisen.

“Oh, forget it. There’s no way this body is on the same level as yours, so how can we have a dialogue….”

“Queen.”

“…!”

“It’s about the one who sent you here.”

But Sakkuth’s expression quickly hardened.

The keyword had just scratched his sensitivities to the bone.

The reason for his rampage was that he had been abandoned by the Queen.

At this point, a terrifying malice radiated from his entire body.

It was the kind of killing intent that made you feel suffocated just by being next to it, and your whole body was weighed down.

“…You’ve got some balls, kid, you’ve suddenly got my attention.”

Sakkuth was starting to show some enthusiasm for the conversation.

His eagerness was so intense that all the guards who were forming a siege line in the distance took half a step back.

But Garam remained nonchalant. The old Garam would never have dared to think such a thing.

Sakkuth held Kirko’s neck tightly and spoke as if chewing it and spitting it out.

“So, you had a crush on this bitch, right? Okay, let’s have a conversation that catches my interest. If it were fishing, I would break this bitch’s neck, kill her, and eat all her internal organs….”

“Wait a minute. There’s something I need to do before we can talk.”

Far from being intimidated by Sakkuth’s killing intent, Garam even raised his palm to cut off his words.

“This conversation contains a lot of important information. It is classified.”

“What kind of top secret is this from you, who is only a low-ranking guard?”

“You’ll see when you listen. My class is not the problem.”

“Kurururu- You were so confident earlier. So what do you have to do before we talk?”

The initiative in the conversation had shifted ever so slightly.

Garam spoke nonchalantly.

“Give Kirko over here.”

“Are you insane? You come to the guy who’s taking hostages, giving up the hostage, and talk to him?”

“I’ll let you keep the hostage.”

“What the fuck are you talking about? Who’s going to be the hostage instead of this bitch?”

“Me.”

Garam was trying to get Sakkuth to let Kirko go instead of taking himself hostage.

“Either this or we can’t talk.”

“…Do you even realise what you’re getting yourself into?”

“I do. I’m a weak, lowly guard. I’m making unreasonable demands on you, who’s holding a hostage.”

“I could take you hostage as well.”

“Then we won’t be able to talk. Too bad. I’m sure you’d love to hear it.”

Sakkuth was becoming increasingly confused by Garam’s nonchalant demeanour as he spoke without changing his face.

“Seriously, what the hell kind of balls do you have?”

“You see, I’ve never been the gutsy type. I don’t even have the guts to bluff with my life.”

“….”

“For someone like me to speak so confidently, it makes you wonder what I believe in, doesn’t it?”

Garam continued.

And Sakkuth seemed to agree with him on some level.

But then.

“Very well. Then show me proof that you are worthy of being my hostage before we exchange.”

“Does being a hostage require proof?”

“Of course.”

He grabbed the shivering Kirko by the throat and lifted her up.

“This woman is not begging for her life, even though she is about to be cut to pieces. She has courage, and she has balls.”

“….”

“But you’re a rotten dog, a piece of shit, and the moment you’re taken hostage by me, you’re going to shit yourself and have a heart attack, and that makes you worthless as a hostage.”

“You’re being unreasonable.”

“Neither are you.”

“Then how do you expect me to prove it?”

Garam asked, and Sakkuth tilted his head to the side.

He turned to the nearest guard, a Major, and extended his hand.

“Hey, you. Give me a cigarette.”

“…?”

The Major happened to have a cigarette in his mouth.

He pulled it out of his pocket and tossed it to Sakkuth.

Huug-

Sakkuth took the cigarette in his mouth and took a long drag.

At the same time, the red blood from his torn mouth and lips soaked into the cigarette.

Blood that smelled disgusting and fishy, and a cigarette soaked in it.

Sakkuth took the cigarette from his mouth and held it out to Garam.

“Smoke this, and I will recognise your guts.”

At that, all the guards fell silent.

Even Kirko narrowed her eyes in thought.

‘…There’s no way he’s putting that in his mouth.’

The blood was a Class 1 hazardous material.

A single drop on the ground is a terrible poison that requires a radius of tens of metres to be disinfected with alcohol, fire, and gunpowder.

Who in their right mind would touch a cigarette that could infect someone with a terrible plague?

Let alone put it in his mouth.

Lt. Colonel Bastille, at the head of the siege, gritted his teeth.

‘For a lowly guard, he was good at taking time, but…Is this where it ends?’

He had planned to advance his men in the rear, little by little, extremely slowly, and attack Sakkuth from behind.

But there wasn’t enough time for that.

Sakkuth hadn’t let his guard down in the slightest.

…Then.

Something happened that shocked everyone.

Shhh.

Garam casually accepted the cigarette offered to him.

Without warning, he popped the cigarette into his mouth.

“Fire.”

And even calmly asking for a fire.

Sakkuth stood still, somewhat dazed.

He didn’t think he’d actually light it.

But Garam shook his head nonchalantly.

“You’ll have to provide fire.”

At that, he turned his head toward the guards with a blank expression on his face.

And then.

Cheog-

A guard of the rank of Major hurriedly rummaged through his chest and threw a match into Sakkuth hands.

Crickss- Swoosh!

Unable to hide his disbelief, Sakkuth struck the match and lit the cigarette in Garam’s mouth.

The sight of a giant poisonous snake, imprisoned on the Level 8, bending down to light a cigarette for a junior guard less than half his height was a strange one.

Huuuw.

Taking a deep drag on the cigarette, Garam immediately blew out a long stream of smoke.

“….”

While everyone watching was with their mouths open with blank expressions.

“How did you know?”

Sakkuth asked with a straight face.

“That I don’t actually have plague poison in my blood.”

It was a shocking revelation.

All the guards watching realised that they had been deceived for the past two years.

In fact, there was no plague in Sakkuth body.

He had mimicked the plague by creating a skin disease that was only apparently serious, using powders of several types of fungi and mushrooms readily available in the Nouvelle Vague, as well as the antidotes and antiseptics injected and applied by doctors, and he had used that to his advantage.

Being a native of Leviathan, an extremely poisonous place, and the founder of the plague, the “Red Death,” supported his bluff.

But it was all just a bluff with a twist.

The question then becomes how Garam, a lowly guard, could have known this beforehand.

“That guy also had something to believe in!”

“But how did he know it was a bluff? The doctors couldn’t figure it out.”

“Really? Is there any way to tell?”

Sakkuth, who holding Kirko by the throat, and all the other guards took note of how Garam had seen through Sakkuth’s bluff.

…And.

Garam opened his mouth and answered everyone’s question in a slow and dry tone.

“I didn’t know?”

Chapter 391

The Worst Torture (4)

◆

…He didn’t know?

Everyone in the hostage situation was stunned.

Even the hostage, Kirko, and the hostage-taker himself, Sakkuth, couldn’t hide their disbelief.

Level 8 prisoner Sakkuth De Leviathan.

It’s also a bastard from poisonous Leviathan.

A vicious criminal who nearly caused a terrible pandemic across the Empire.

He was a mastermind whose viciousness was completely uncontrollable, even when he wore the BDISSEM cuffs that bound his mana and physical power.

It’s the plague and poison he spreads through sweat, saliva, blood, and even breath.

He was assessed to be as a level 9 prisoner, comparable to other high risk prisoners such as Megidio, Lord Griffin, Aurora, Snow White, and Cinderella.

So much so that some senior guards have even recently suggested that he should have been placed in Level 9.

As a result, he is a burden to the guards, an unwanted and at times, a prisoner who is even avoided to the point of fear.

But to accept a cigarette offered by such a monster and smoke it without question, Is that just a low-level prison guard?

This is exactly what the guards are surprised about.

This is something that would never be possible with ordinary guts.

He has already passed the point of no return. Unless you’re desperate to die.

Sakkuth also asked in disbelief.

“…Didn’t you know about it?”

“No, I didn’t.”

Vikir replied, puffing on his cigarette.

It was true that he didn’t know, but it certainly wasn’t a gamble with his life.

After all, Vikir’s body is infused with the poison of Madam Eight-Legs, which is capable of consuming all poisons and plagues.

‘Madame devours many poisons, and then concentrates them in her poison pouches.’

It doesn’t matter what plague you have in your possession.

No matter how vile, no matter how poisonous, no matter how terrifying, the moment it enters Vikir’s body, it becomes mere prey for the Madame.

Knowing this, Vikir nonchalantly puts the cigarette in his mouth.

But to the unknowing Sakkuth, he could not fathom the intentions of the lowly guard in front of him.

“I don’t know what I’m looking at.”

Sakkuth shrugged his shoulders in disbelief.

Then he threw Kirko, who was clutching her throat, into the distance.

…Thud!

Kirko spewed blood and sprawled on the floor.

“Kuughh!”

But the moment she hit the ground, she immediately got up, straightened up, and drew her sword.

Any other junior guard would have been stretched out.

‘…It’s a talent that will serve her well in the future, if she doesn’t die in some nameless battle.’

Vikir glanced at Kirko behind her and realised once more that his judgement had been correct.

Then.

“You. You like her that much?”

A voice broke Vikir’s from his thoughts.

Vikir turned his head to see what was going on, and Sakkuth was looking down at him in disbelief.

“A man risks his life for a mere slut. Don’t you know what it means to be held hostage by me?”

He seemed to understand that Vikir (or, more accurately, the character he was playing) was gambling with his life because of his love for Kirko.

The other guards seem to take a similar view.

“Did Garam like Kirko?”

“You couldn’t tell, he was always staring at Kirko whenever he was on duty.”

“But even so, isn’t that a little reckless?”

“He’s a real man. Risking his life for the girl he’s in love with.”

“What a jerk. He’s an idiot. He’s just an idiot.”

“Look, the look on the high-ranking guards’ faces has already changed. It looks like they will push ahead with the suppression.”

Hearing the guards’ chatter, Sakkuth snorted in response.

“You’re a sacrificial lamb, a pawn, a throwaway card. Do you really think those bastards that surround me care about the life of one of the low-ranking guards?”

“….”

“Hmm. Sure. He’s probably smoking a cigarette with my blood on it because he’s too obsessed with that bitch. Crazy bastard.”

Vikir thought for a moment.

‘I suppose. If it was Garam, maybe it really was.’

The words in Garam’s diary, the love he had for Kirko, the way he’d written about her, would have been enough for him to give his life for Kirko.

But not Vikir.

The reason he came forward was to pursue thorough practical purposes.

“Now, then, let us begin our conversation, and keep your voice down.”

“…Was there really something to talk about? Not just put on a show for your girl?”

“Shut up and listen.”

Vikir was just about to open his mouth.

“Garam!”

Came a voice from behind.

Vikir and Sakkuth turned around, startled, to see Kirko with her sword half drawn.

“Get down!”

At the same time, a slashing blow.

…Flash!

Surprisingly, the aura became denser and more concentrated, almost to the point of being liquid.

Was it an enlightenment in a life-or-death situation?

At the same time, Kirko, whose level had risen to the next level, performed a sword aura.

“Ugh! You stupid bitch!”

Sakkuth was stunned.

Vikir was also quite taken aback by the unexpected turn.

Fortunately, Kirko’s surprise attack was stopped by his fellow guards.

The female guards, with whom Kirko had always been friendly, rushed over and grabbed her by the arms and legs.

“Kirko! Are you crazy!?”

“There will only be two hostages!”

“Let’s not make Garam’s sacrifice in vain!”

The guards, rushing from behind, grabbed the struggling Kirko and dragged her backwards.

It was quite a contrast to when Garam stepped forward and there was no one to stop him.

“Hey, let go of me!”

Kirko looked at Garam, her hands flailing.

His colleague, the man who had stumbled into the limb that should have been her, the man who had risked his life to save hers.

There was nothing but confusion, agitation, and urgency in Kirko’s gaze as she looked at Garam.

Then.

“Don’t come.”

Vikir’s words were short.

“…!”

Kirko stopped struggling for a moment and stared blankly.

Vikir drove the wedge in again.

“It’s only in the way.”

“Ha, but…!”

“Go away. On the contrary, it helps.”

A hard line. But the cold attitude had the opposite effect.

Even those who had just condemned Garam’s actions as reckless could only admire his determination.

What a dazzling display of sacrifice and determination.

By now, Kirko had grown sullen and quiet, and tension was beginning to return to the siege of the guards.

Even the senior guards began to talk.

“That junior guard, he’s got some nerve. Is he risking his life for his motivation?”

“The look in his eyes. It’s like I’m seeing the days when I was a junior guard, and even then, it was motivation and love of country.”

“It is a great loss to lose a man like that.”

“They said his name was Garam. He’s been topping the monthly evaluations among the junior guards for few months.”

“Let’s get to work on saving the hostages as best as possible. First, let’s start by secretly approaching the personnel at the rear.”

“We’ve already sent a squadron through the ceiling.”

…However.

Vikir himself, who was actually the target of the rescue, didn’t seem to pay any attention to his surroundings.

Instead, Vikir simply walked over and stood next to Sakkuth.

He was being held hostage instead, but the atmosphere was somehow different from that of Kirko.

Either way, they were finally alone.

Sakkuth asked Vikir quietly.

“Heh… I’m a little excited to see what kind of conversation we’ll have at this point.”

“I’m glad we’re alone, now let’s get to the point.”

Vikir said in a voice so low that only Sakkuth could hear it.

“The construction of Level 10 must proceed. When you interfere like this, it slows it down.”

“…Is that your point?”

“Yes, indeed. The construction of Level 10 must proceed as scheduled. Your riot has delayed it by a day.”

“What do you want me to do, you madman? That’s your business, what do I care?”

Sakkuth could not hide his disbelief and anger.

But Vikir remained nonchalant.

Putting a finger to his lips to silence him, Vikir spoke in a smaller, lower voice.

“If construction is delayed, it will be a loss for you as well. The moment the blue sphere in the centre of the Level 10 construction zone explodes is the moment of timing, and the longer the construction is delayed, the longer you have to wait here.”

“…Wait? For what? What’s timing?”

“What would it be, you stupid?”

When Sakkuth asked in a curious tone, Vikir scolded him briefly as if he was pathetic.

Sakkuth’s eyes turned red for a moment.

It was bad enough that he was being psychologically manipulated by a lowly guard, but now he was being called stupid.

That’s right, by a ‘Stupit Garam’.

Sakkuth was about to explode when he was told off for talking back.

Unbelievable words came out of Vikir’s mouth.

“Just in time for the Queen to save you.”

It was enough to send a chill down Sakkuth’s spine.

Chapter 392

The Worst Torture (5)

◆

“…?”

Sakkuth was just rolling his eyes as if he didn’t understand what was going on.

Vikir spoke once more.

“Just in time for the Queen to save you. Did I nail it in your ear?”

“I, I’m listening. I hear you.”

Sakkuth responded in a rush.

Vikir clicked his tongue at the sight of it.

“I’m glad you heard. Stupid.”

“You bastard… I’m sure I’m not making a fool of myself when I’m always looking for my Queen….”

“Shut up, asshole. The Queen is still out there trying to get you out of here, which is why I’m here.”

Vikir scolded Sakkuth and went out at his own pace

“The timing was the moment when the blue sphere in the deep center of the Level 10 construction area exploded. The original plan was to activate it and get you out of here. If it weren’t for your foolishness, it would have proceeded as planned.”

“Well, you want me to believe that? You might have listened to what I usually say and made it up…”

“Don’t you want to leave? You’ve been uncooperative since the beginning.”

“…It’s not that.”

“Then stop talking. Just close your mouth and open your ears.”

“….”

Sakkuth shut his mouth with a look of frustration on his face.

In front of him, Vikir loosened his collar a little.

“I won’t tell you to blindly believe what I say.”

At the same time, Vikir showed Sakkuth an object he had retrieved from Andromalius’s barrier.

A word sculpture with an impressive whitish lower part of the blade, a blackish middle part, and a reddish upper part, as well as a spiral embossed pattern.

Shaped like the horns of a Unicorn, it was a fragment of Orwell’s The Sword of Winter.

It was once owned by Winston, the principal of Colosseo Academy, and is said to be a legendary sword that only those who have attained the highest level of mastery are allowed to wield it.

Sakkuth’s eyes widened at the sight of it.

“That, that’s the key to Nouvelle Vague’s main gate…! No way!”

Vikir nodded silently.

The ‘Queen’ who had sent Sakkuth here.

And the object she had been searching for, ‘Orwell’.

Imprisoned deep within the Nouvelle Vague by Orca and Winston during the 47 Man Riot, a long time ago.

Vikir opened his mouth, combining keywords in his head.

“Ms. Ouroboros sent me here. To help you.”

“Oh oh…Ooohhh! Queen! You haven’t abandoned me! You remembered me…!”

“Shut up, fool, the guards will hear you.”

Vikir pushed his hat down deeply and lifted the brim.

Then, on his bare face, Vikir’s face was visible.

“Huh!”

After swallowing the empty air, Vikir continued speaking.

“I told you, I thought you were pretty good.”

When Vikir said that, Sakkuth’s jaw dropped open.

It reminded him of a conversation they had before.

‘You’re going to break out of Nouvelle Vague? What ‘He’ could not do in the end is escape from prison. What kind of guy are you….’

‘Why do you think it’s impossible to jailbreak?’

‘…What?’

‘Is that all you can think about? You think you’ve been abandoned, but that’s not true. That’s because I think well of you.’

‘…?’

‘I’ve been watching you for the past two years. You might have no strength and lacks tenacity, but I like your brashness and action. Your loyalty is strong.’

‘What the hell are you talking about?’

‘You’ll find out soon enough. After I break out of this place.’

After finishing his reminiscence, Sakkuth opened his mouth in disbelief.

“So, you’ve been here since the beginning…?”

“That’s right. The Queen sent me to test you. And you were loyal enough not to reveal any information about her, which is why I gave you a passing grade.”

It was a lie, of course.

It was only because of Decarabia’s testimony that Vikir discovered the connection between Sakkuth and Sadi.

[I wondered where I’d smelled that before, but now I know. His blood smells like Sadi’s. They must be related somehow].

Vikir was convinced after taking a drag from a cigarette stained with Sakkuth blood.

These were enough clues to guess who the Queen was and who had sent her minions down here to Nouvelle Vague to rescue ‘him’.

Vikir snarled.

“I’m trying to get you out of here at the right time, and you pull a stupid stunt like this. What’s more, you sell me to the guards?”

“Pah, I don’t mean sell you, that’s ridiculous!”

“I already know that you reported me to Souaré. If you lie to me again, I will make you rot here forever.”

“Huh! My apologies, well. I, I was completely unaware of Night Hound-sama’s identity, so please stop….”

Sakkuth thought back to his past before he was trapped in this place.

Come to think of it, his Queen had talked about wanting to meet Night Hound quite often.

“At the time, I thought it was just a way of saying she was looking for a minion or partner, but… I, I was short-sighted.”

Sakkuth was completely overwhelmed by the look in Vikir’s eyes.

At the same time, his eyes sparkled with infinite trust and relief.

“So I’m going to live, then? I’m going to get out of here?”

“There’s still a chance.”

“Uh, what should I do?”

“I told you. We need to activate Level 10’s blue orb, get ‘him’, and get out.”

“Teach me!”

“Then from now on, you will do exactly as I say. Considering how you almost screwed up my plan, I’d like to take you out of the Great Escape, but….”

He flinched as Vikir showed his discomfort.

Then Vikir noticed the parade of guards sneaking up behind Sakkuth.

“If you can handle what happens between now and then, I’ll let it slide. Until the next ‘event’, you will live like a mouse and be a model prisoner. Is that clear?”

“Yes, of course. I’ll cover for you with my life.”

“I’ll try to trust you just this once more, and if you make another fuss, you’ll get what you deserve.”

“Yes!”

“Very well, then you will be arrested by the guards approaching from the rear. Just make sure you’re acting reasonably aggressive.”

“Yes! But if I get caught, I’ll be taken to solitary confinement, and possibly executed….”

“You can take solitary confinement, I can’t protect you from that. But don’t worry, if you are sentenced to death, I’ll speed up your escape.”

After hearing Vikir’s words, Sakkuth nodded with bright eyes.

At that very moment.

“Now! Pounce!”

Bastille’s commanding voice came from behind.

At the same time, a group of guards, including Lt. Colonel Bastille, rushed toward Sakkuth’s back.

“Whoa! What the hell, when did it come to this, I never thought it would happen, ouch!”

Sakkuth collapsed to the ground, making a fuss that made even Vikir, who was watching, fret.

Luckily, the atmosphere was so tense that no one was suspicious.

…Peog! …peoeog! Ttudug! Udeudeug! …cheolkeong! …cheolkeodeog!

Sakkuth’s limbs were restrained with heavy bindings.

At that time, the suppressed Sakkuth and Vikir’s eyes met.

Frown.

Sakkuth winked at Vikir and grinned.

Vikir nodded once, his expression impassive.

Before he knew it, his face had returned to Garam’s.

Soon, the junior guards were swarming around Garam.

“Garam, are you okay?”

“Wow, that was a cool smoke, you!”

“What? Why is your face so bloody again? When did you get hit?”

By now, Vikir had recreated the burn marks on his face with the hot dirt he had picked up from the ground.

The slightly changed positions of the scars were not noticeable due to the dust, sulfur powder, and blood stains.

The junior guards crowded around Garam and chattered for a while longer.

Then.

“…!”

The junior guards who had been chattering around Vikir opened a path to the side in unison.

Vikir turned his head to see what was going on, and out of the corner of his eye, he saw a figure.

It was Kirko.

“…I.”

Kirko approached with slow steps and stood in front of Vikir.

In a low voice, Kirko asked

“Are you okay?”

“….”

“Your face… looks like you’re hurt a lot….”

She hesitated, unable to take her eyes off Vikir’s face.

“It’s okay. It’ll heal if I leave it alone.”

It was true. With Basilisk’s power, a burn like this would take less than a second to regenerate.

But Kirko, unaware of that fact, hadn’t left Vikir’s side.

“Wait.”

“…?”

Before Vikir had a chance to respond, Kirko pulled something out of her front pocket.

It was an ointment for burns.

“…That must have hurt.”

Kirko let the word slip out unconsciously.

She kept her mouth shut from then on and began to apply the burn ointment to Vikir’s face.

The junior guards around her were stunned. This was quite unexpected given her cold, detached image.

Meanwhile, Vikir tried to tell her that he didn’t need it, but eventually left it alone.

Because there was something more important than that right now.

When Vikir turned to look, he saw that Sakkuth had been noisily grabbed by the senior guards and dragged off into the distance.

“Listen to me, you’re in solitary confinement for three months!”

“It won’t end with solitary confinement, after that I’ll make you work like a madman!”

“And after that, I’ll execute you! Do you understand?”

“I swear by my name! I will definitely put you on the execution platform!”

All of the senior guards were furious that they have been fooled by Sakkuth’s bluff all this time.

Things must be done right. It was a natural result.

’ …I won’t last long.’

Vikir clicked his tongue.

Ever since Vikir learnt that he was responsible for the Red Death among the natives of Jungle long ago, he had no intention of going easy on him.

If he survived the torture and solitary confinement, it wouldn’t matter, because he’d already thought of the next step.

He could hear Decarabia chuckling in his chest.

[Kkilkkilkkil- lulling a ruined prisoner into a false hope of escape. Your lying is top notch. Walking step by step to certain death without knowing he is being deceived, isn’t that the cruelest form of torture, I don’t know who is the demon and who is the demon hunter].

“Be quiet.”

Vikir pounded his fist against his chest in frustration.

‘Whatever. Is this the end of the situation?’

A riot of Level 8 prisoners.

The disturbance, which could have been catastrophic in the wrong hands, had been put down surprisingly quickly thanks to the efforts of a junior guard.

And then.

“Hey. Guard.”

Behind him, Lt. Colonel Bastille, the chief officer in charge of the suppression, called out to Vikir.

“Well done. You did really well. I can’t believe I have such a good man under me. How did I not recognize this talent before now?”

Vikir knew what was coming next as Lt. Colonel Bastille patted him on the shoulder and showered him with praise.

It was time for a reward based on merit.

Chapter 395

Dead Man Walking (2)

◆

Vikir remembered what Garam had said when he first entered Nouvelle Vague.

‘What the hell, what’s the big deal, this is just a dog’s death, a de facto execution!’

‘No, it’s not. There’s a Nouvelle Vague execution, and it’s not even close to this.’

Garam was responding to a prisoner who was freaking out at the news.

Vikir suddenly realized why Garam had said that.

Jjeoeoeoeoeog-

A mouth appeared in the center of the abyss.

Its enormous jaws twisted the empty space, revealing other spaces nested within it.

Squares, triangles, circles… jagged misshapen features sprouted without order or balance.

Two bulging eyeballs, cloudy as the eyes of a drowning man, were obviously reacting to the ‘prey’ falling from above.

Vikir thought.

‘The most mysterious of the five wardens was Brigadier General Flubber.’

His identity, he was told, was supposed to be ‘a Beastman member of the Snail family’.

However, that was just a classification, and nothing was known about which group, order, or class this strange creature belonged to.

‘I don’t even know why it’s called a Beastman creature in the first place. It doesn’t look human at all.’

Age: unknown. Gender: unknown. Race: unknown. Where it came from: unknown, where it was going: unknown.

Even the rank of Brigadier General was merely a social title that humans have given to this creature.

An ancient, prehistoric creature that was already there when humans first discovered Nouvelle Vague.

No one knew what it was or how it came to live here.

No matter how hard he searched the oldest written records of Nouvelle Vague, all they could find was that Brigadier General Flubber had been there since the beginning.

‘…Whatever. He’s the main force responsible for Nouvelle Vague’s security, along with BDISSEM.’

Vikir thought as he looked at the giant, grotesque creature with its mouth open at the bottom of the abyss.

The BDISSEM, binding the mana and power of the prisoners.

Flubber, who coats the entire castle in slime to keep it from being flooded.

These are the two key substances that keep Nouvelle Vague alive.

Woooooooo…

It was then that Brigadier General Flubber began to make a strange noise.

A long, thick tongue protruded from a crack in the abyss.

A sticky slime called Flubber oozed from the base of the tongue.

That was the source of the foamy windows that covered the doors and windows of the Nouvelle Vague.

And then it dripped down into its gaping maw.

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!”

The sound was obvious.

Nouvelle Vague’s first round of inductions, where the fallen from the Blade Bridge had gone.

The fate of those who, on paper, were still alive.

Sakkuth fell into the abyss.

…With a plop!

The word ‘plunged’ could not have been more appropriate.

Brigadier General Flubber’s body was composed of dark matter mixed with dark green.

It was not hot, but sticky and heavy, as if it had been boiled and then melted.

This sticky conglomerate of mucus had spread endlessly, and there was no hasty limit to its bottom.

It’s like the phlegm in the throat of a giant, the kind of phlegm that appears in ancient legends of World Trees and Giants.

And as he plunged into the abyss of this horrible slime, this dark swamp, he let out a terrifying scream.

“Kkiyaaaaaaaaaaghhh!!”

It was a creepy scream that instantly filled the empty hollow with terror.

It was enough to make even the mid-level guards of Nouvelle Vague, who had seen it all before, cover their ears and bite their lips.

But.

“….”

Only one person.

Vikir was standing motionless, still towering over the edge of the cliff.

Staring down with an air of nonchalance.

Suddenly.

As Sakkuth entire body melted away, he looked up.

His eyes locked with Vikir’s, who stood above the abyss, peering down from the cliff edge.

“…You! …you!”

He realized he had been tricked.

Everything had been a lie.

There had been no rescue, no escape.

There was no such thing as a messenger in the depths of the sea.

It was wrong to look for such a thing 10,000 meters below the surface of the ocean, in the depths of this hopeless sea.

This is Nouvelle Vague. No dreams, no hope, no future, no nothing.

“Geuuk! Beeroooooghh!”

Before he knew it, Sakkuth, his mouth was filled with Flubber mouth, cursed the object in front of him with all his heart.

A terrifying malice swirled through him, energizing his entire body with a new kind of vitality that even he didn’t recognize.

…But it was too late.

Malice, murder, and revenge all have meaning only in the living.

Already, the taste in Brigadier General Flubber’s mouth was nothing more than a squirming mass of meat, just a little fresher than usual.

Teoeob-

The gaping folds sucked in more and more of Sakkuth’s huge body.

Sakkuth De Leviathan, dragged beneath a pitch-black, bottomless abyss.

The last time he saw the light of this world, there before him was Vikir’s expressionless face.

…Suddenly, his lips moved.

And with the superhuman observation and concentration of a man on the verge of death, Sakkuth could read the faint trace of Vikir’s lips.

‘Know your subject, whether you’re the predator or the prey.’

Those were the words he’d heard on their first meeting.

“…! …! …! …! …!”

Sakkuth tried to scream at the top of his lungs.

With all his might, and with a sincerity and earnestness that even he had never shown in his life.

It might have been a man’s anger or malice, or a curse of unspeakable cruelty and viciousness, or an atonement or penance so sincere and pure that it touched the hearts of all who saw it.

…But it never reached the world.

Kurururung!

He disappeared beneath the black swamp with a boat horn sound similar to the laughter he usually made.

It is unknown if he was granted the “rest in peace” so often heard from the dead.

But what is certain is that he will never escape the abyss again.

…For all eternity.

◆

There was an eerie silence among the guards.

Even the bold, fearless Kirko was breaking out in a cold sweat.

“…Brigadier General Flubber’s execution is always dreadful.”

Vikir, who had just returned from pushing Sakkuth off the cliff, nodded quietly to answer her.

‘Brigadier General Flubber. He doesn’t appear to be intelligent, but I don’t know what variables that will be in the event of an escape.’

A monstrous creature who stretches its body throughout Nouvelle Vague’s castle, responsible for its upkeep and maintenance.

Unofficially, it is considered the most powerful creature in Nouvelle Vague.

In fact, the most mysterious of the Five Wardens, there was one who used his time to meet this monster whose identity was the most unknown.

Vikir began to worry about how much he should be wary of this monster and how much he should ignore it.

For the first time since entering Nouvelle Vague, he had encountered an incalculable variable.

…Then.

“Captain Garam.”

A voice called to Vikir.

Turning his head, he saw Lt. Colonel Bastille standing there, a stern expression on his face.

Behind him were his adjutants in full uniform.

“You asked for me, Lt. Colonel.”

Vikir replied with a salute, and Bastille’s lips curled into a smile.

“Okay. Finally, one less troublesome prisoner.”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, who was busy with promotions and advancement, and line work for this, was always on the lookout for prisoner riots.

This is because it has a devastating adverse effect on performance.

So Sakkuth, the most frequent rioter and the most emotionally unstable, has been his biggest thorn in the side lately.

“…Honestly, executing a prisoner is not an easy task. Once the decision to execute has been made, the prisoner may continue to resist, riot, escape, or plan a terrorist attack, and the trauma to the guards who carry out the execution cannot be ignored.”

“I’m glad this one ended safely.”

“It is. A Level 8 prisoner quietly accepted his execution without incident, and there doesn’t seem to be any after-effects for the guards who executed him. … Is that right?”

“Yes, Sir.”

At Vikir’s answer, Lt. Colonel Bastille smiled even more broadly.

“The charisma and resourcefulness to keep a Level 8 prisoner quiet until the very moment of execution, and the guts and boldness to single-handedly carry out a gruesome execution ceremony and not falter an inch.”

“….”

“It’s no exaggeration to say that all of this is to your credit. The more I look at you, the more I covet you, you remind me of my own youth.”

Vikir couldn’t bear to listen, so he gave him the lip service he didn’t usually give to end things quickly.

“I will follow you for the rest of my life, Lt. Colonel.”

The words made the smile on Lt. Colonel Bastille’s face grow even brighter.

Lt. Colonel Bastille, a man whose specialty was forming lines and building factions, seemed to recognize Vikir as one of his own.

“Good. I’m not like those incompetent rulers and generals who have left a stain on history. Loyal and capable subordinates are rewarded as they deserve.”

Vikir looked puzzled.

Then Lt. Colonel Bastille held out a black box to Vikir.

“I hope you like what you see.”

“It would be a great honor for me to receive anything from you, Lt. Colonel.”

“Hahaha, you can open it right here.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille grinned, as if the gift was an opportunity to boast to the world of his weights, measures, and distribution.

Now, in the center of the room, under the watchful eyes of all the guards, including Kirko next to him.

Dakkak-

Vikir opened the box.

And then.

“…!”

What was revealed inside was enough to make everyone’s eyes widen.

Chapter 396

Dead Man Walking (3)

◆

The box opened, and a pillar of silver light rose from within.

It was a badge of rank, a badge with a silver Rose of Sharon embroidered on it.

It was the symbol for the rank of Major.

“…This?”

Vikir looked up, and Lt. Colonel Bastille opened his mouth with a friendly smile.

“I see your construction progress has been over 100% every time, and last month you finally hit 200%?”

“Thanks to the good work of my colleagues.”

“Hahahaha – how humble, I love that kind of comradeship. Anyway, how can I keep a competent subordinate who outperforms everyone else by double or triple every month as a lowly guard?”

The ability to organize and lead prisoners is how a guard is judged.

Vikir was recognized for both his resourcefulness and his integrity.

Lt. Colonel Bastille is also an adjutant in Colonel D’Ordume’s line, and Colonel D’Ordume is currently devoting all of his attention to Nouvelle Vague’s grand project, the new Level 10.

Lt. Colonel Bastille, therefore, has everything at stake in this massive expansion.

Vikir, who has been able to safely eliminate any distractions and whose workload is far greater than anyone else’s, has earned the favor of Lt. Colonel Bastille.

“You’re not the kind of person to work with just a dozen low-level prisoners. Even the great masters who united half the world during the Warring States Period began their careers guarding warehouses loaded with military munitions.”

“….”

“I can’t wait to see what you’ll do with the countless guards you’ll have, and the countless prisoners under you. Do you know if my unusual choice will dramatically accelerate the construction of Level 10?”

Lt. Colonel Bastille was a seasoned politician.

He saw through Vikir’s extraordinary plan at a glance and recognized it as the key to getting the Level 10 completed ahead of schedule.

And that was good news for Vikir.

“I’m going to put everything on the line and make a difference in Nouvelle Vague.”

Vikir is honest about the plan he’s had since he arrived.

And this brought a smile of satisfaction to Lt. Colonel Bastille’s face.

…Chuck!

The rank insignia inside the box hung on Vikir’s chest.

Thus, Vikir was promoted from Captain Garam Nord to Major Garam Nord.

It had happened in less than a year, if you don’t count the time Garam had been a lowly rank.

“Hahaha. I didn’t get promoted this fast when I was a junior guard, either. The only people who ever did it in the first place were Colonel D’Ordume and Colonel Souaré… and aside from those two earlier examples, you’re probably the first in decades.”

“I will work harder.”

“Okay then. You have to work hard, now that I’m counting on you and watching over you. How sad and frustrated have you been because you haven’t had a chance to show off your abilities? If you think about it that way, that guy named Sakkuth, who is no longer around, must have been lucky for you.”

“No, I didn’t think of it that way.”

“Hahaha! That’s what I think. I think so. He was lucky for me, because he allowed me to find such a capable subordinate as you.”

Vikir looked down at the silver and black Rose of Sharon on his chest.

This insignia of rank, which is made by covering BDISSEM pieces with silver, is quite valuable as a sculpture.

But it was the symbolism of the rank that was important: the various privileges guaranteed by the rank of Major.

For starters, a Major is recognized as the end of the junior guards and the beginning of the senior guards.

After being promoted to Major, a person accumulates a small amount of seniority and is treated as a senior guard, with the following privileges

1. Recruit and impose discretionary labor on up to 108 prisoners within the limits of Level 3.

2. Summarily execute one prisoner for grave inferior offenses, such as refusing to serve or injuring a guard, within the limits of Level 7.

3. Freely move in and out of the entirety of the Labor Camp at any time of the day or night, without needing to report to a superior.

4. Access to the ‘Breeding Grounds’, ‘Execution Grounds’, and ‘Punishment Rooms’ if authorized by the higher-ups.

.

.

Vikir’s attention was drawn to numbers one and three of these.

He could conscript prisoners at his discretion and make them serve at his discretion.

He could even inspect the labor camp whenever he wanted, regardless of the time of day.

‘…These are the optimal conditions to operate Poseidon.’

I didn’t even need to be promoted beyond Lt. Colonel.

Major was the ideal rank for Vikir, as he had all the key authorizations he needed for the jailbreak, as well as the relative lack of attention and ease of maneuverability.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille gave Vikir a stern look.

“Just as you have the privileges of being a Major, you also have the responsibilities of being a Major.”

With privilege comes responsibility.

A certain amount of construction progress, the number of times prisoners rioted, the time it took to quell them, the evaluations from superiors and subordinates, etc…..

But Vikir didn’t care about any of this.

‘It’s not long now, anyway.’

The countdown. The moment of escape is fast approaching.

Vikir was already slowly putting his second plan into action following his transformation into a guard.

Then.

“By the way, now that you’ve been promoted to Major, I think it’s time for a new adjutant. What do you think? You can have up to three adjutants.”

Said Lt. Colonel Bastille.

The eyes of the lower-ranking guards around him changed color in unison.

Now none of the men who had looked down on him as an idiot remained.

But Vikir shook his head as if he didn’t care.

“One Lieutenant Kirko Grimm will be enough.”

For a moment, there was a slight hush around them.

“…?”

Vikir turned his head, puzzled by the sudden change in the atmosphere, but all he could see was Kirko, her head bowed low and her ears red.

Then Lt. Colonel Bastille chuckled.

“Hahahaha – an internal love affair, not a bad thing, as long as you watch out for a few factors.”

As he finished speaking, Lt. Colonel Bastille looked at Kirko, who was standing next to Vikir, with a strange gaze.

“…An internal love affair, hmmm. Strange fate, indeed. Children are like their parents after all.”

For some reason, the voice exudes a bit of pity.

He shook his head, wondering when he had muttered such a thing.

“Lieutenant Kirko Grimm. A lieutenant is an adjutant, a rank somewhat insufficient to assist a Major.”

“I’ll work hard to make up for it!”

“You’re already working hard. You’ve consistently performed well on your monthly evaluations, you sacrificed yourself for your comrades during the last Level 8 prisoner riot, and you did an excellent job assisting Major Garam during this execution.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille patted Kirko on the shoulder and said.

“I have prepared a reward for you as well.”

With that, he handed Kirko a box.

Inside were three diamonds and a badge symbolizing the rank of Captain.

“You must have gained quite a bit of experience in this riot and learned a lot. I’m pleased to see that you’ve paired up with a great officer and a great subordinate, and I wish you both the best. Always remember that your promotion is extremely unusual.”

“YES!”

Both Vikir and Kirko echoed at the words of Lt. Col.

Major Garam. Captain Kirko.

They were promoted one rank at a time, to the admiration, respect, and envy of all their junior guards.

It was then.

“…Lt. Colonel Bastille.”

A guard with the rank of Major next to him spoke up in a concerned voice.

Lt. Colonel Bastille turned his head with a puzzled expression.

“What?”

“Well, sir. An order has come down from above.”

“From above? From who? Colonel D’Ordume or Colonel Souaré?”

“…Neither of them.”

For a moment, Lt. Colonel Bastille’s expression hardened as he listened to his adjutant’s report.

“Is this, by any chance, an audit of the specialist?”

“That’s right, Lt. Colonel ‘Black Tongue’ is taking an interest.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille covered his face with his hands.

“…What kind of whim did that crazy person suddenly have?”

“They say good things always come with a price, don’t they?”

“Okay. There is nothing wrong with military law. Where gratitude is expected for unusual promotions.”

The conversation between Lt. Colonel Bastille and the adjutant was becoming increasingly serious.

Meanwhile, watching from the sidelines, Vikir thought to himself.

‘…Black Tongue.’

Lt. Colonel ‘Black Tongue’. A man with no name and an unpleasant nickname: Black Tongue.

He’s one of the top five wardens in Nouvelle Vague and a member of the ‘audit team’.

However, the Audit Team is a team and an organization, and is actually made up of only one person, Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

Another nickname for the Black Tongue is “the jailer who catches jailers”.

The Nouvelle Vague has its own system of laws and punishments because the laws of the land don’t apply to it, and that goes for the guards as well as the prisoners.

Unusually for a guard, Lt. Colonel Black Tongue doesn’t punish prisoners, he punishes guards.

He is the only one of the guards at Nouvelle Vague who is feared, as he investigates internal irregularities, breaches of military discipline, and other misdeeds, and punishes them at his discretion.

But he was also the least known of the five wardens, even more so than Brigadier General Flubber, whose identity was a mystery to the lowly guards, who were never likely to do anything wrong in the first place.

Vikir thought for a moment.

‘…Lt. Colonel Black Tongue. Good, because he’s someone I’d like to meet personally.’

Unlike BDISSEM. and Flubber, who were essential to meet before jailbreak, Black Tongue had no direct business with Vikir.

However, Vikir had a very personal reason for wanting to see Lt. Colonel Black Tongue.

At that time.

Ppudeug-

There was a faint, dull noise.

It was the sound of grinding teeth.

Vikir heard it and turned his head.

There stood Kirko, her face impassive.

“….”

But judging by the faint veins of blood on her neck and chin, it was Kirko who had just been grinding her teeth.

Vikir was just about to call out to Kirko to find out what was going on.

“Major Garam, Captain Kirko. I need to go to the audit room right now.”

Lt. Colonel Bastille spoke up again.

“Apparently, your promotion was too quick, and the audit team has raised questions. You have a clean background, a clean past, and a clean record, so there shouldn’t be much of a problem, but….”

He trailed off, his voice a little underwater.

“Lt. Colonel Black Tongue. Judging by ‘personally’, he’s a man to be very wary of. Just keep that in mind and go.”

An ominous tone that could turn a good mood upside down in an instant.

All the guards, who only moments ago had been looking at them with envy, now look at Vikir and Kirko with sympathy and anxiety.

But. The hound’s eyes, facing this overwhelming ominousness, were calm as always.

“I’ll be going, then.”

No, rather, it glowed with a ‘personal’ interest.